Hotch: Previously
on "Criminal Minds"...
Do you think
he knows about us?
As far as I can tell
he doesn't.
Well, guess I'll talk
to you next Sunday.
Bye. Love you.
I need to tell you something.
Maeve is missing.
I think her stalker has her.
Please help me.
Help me find her.
See, it's not about
the message.
It's about the medium.
What he used to draw on her face.
Reid; The stalker's a woman.
It's black eyeliner.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Reid: I think I know
who the unsub is.
Where did you get
Maeve's clothes?
From her closet.
Right after I bashed
her head in.
Get on the ledge.
If you're gonna kill me,
you kill me,
but I am not jumping.
Spencer has a different idea.
Diane: Take your gun
and vest off and come in alone.
Let me take her place.
You would kill yourself
for her?
Yes.
[Gunshot]
Wait!
Danielle, it's Kelly--again.
Where are you? When I said
let's go out dancing tonight,
I didn't expect it to involve
you leaving me alone
while you scam on some frat guy.
Call me. You've got 10 minutes,
then I'm out of here.
Hey!
Hello?
[Indistinct]
How was work?
It sucked.
Tips were horrible.
[Screaming]
[Footsteps]
Hey.
Thought I'd check on Spence
on my way into work.
Yeah. Me, too.
Are these all from you?
Maybe.
What's in that one?
Mixed nuts and seeds.
I'm trying to think of something
that will help him feel better.
So I went Reid-like
and I did a bunch of research
and it turns out
that nuts and seeds
have naturally occurring
magnesium,
and magnesium influences
the production of serotonin,
which is a happy happy joy joy
chemical in the brain. I don't know.
[Doorbell rings]
Spence, listen,
if you're in there,
we just want to know
that you're all right.
Knock twice
if you're conscious.
[Knock knock]
Is he ever gonna be okay?
Eventually.
And he knows
we're all here for him,
no matter what.
Yeah. What she said.
Come on.
Okay.
Hello. This is Spencer Reid.
Please leave a message.
[Beep]
Hey, Reid, it's me. Again.
Hey, we're gathering.
All right, I'm coming.
Now, listen, kid, uh,
give me a call
when you can.
Was that him?
Voicemail.
It's been two weeks.
You okay?
Yeah.
Well, no.
Sometimes I wonder
if I hadn't pushed him
so hard to meet Maeve...
Blake, you can't blame
yourself for encouraging him.
I know. I know.
It was bound to happen
no matter what.
I miss Reid.
Did he tell you how long?
No. I told him to take
as much time as he needed.
At least I got a chance
to say good-bye to Carolyn.
I can't imagine--
yeah.
Ladies and gents,
the Golden State awaits.
Meet who was formerly
Gary Porter.
He was found dead outside a
San Francisco night club last night.
And Pamela Hurd--
she was found near a cable car stop
in San Francisco's
Mission District.
They were both found
wrapped in clear plastic.
It says here they were dead
only a few hours before they were found.
That's not long enough for the
elements to have made them that pale.
'Cause that's where we enter
the town of weirdville
on the corner
of eew and icky-icky.
Both victims were almost
completely drained of their blood.
Less than a pint left.
He's exsanguinating them.
While they were still alive.
It might be utilitarian.
He needs them alive
so they can pump out
the blood themselves.
Draining a body
like that
is extremely hard to do.
Once the heart
stops pumping,
it's difficult to continue
to extract the blood.
So the question is,
how is he doing it?
Oh, I wish you wouldn't
have asked that
'cause now I gotta
show this picture.
There are large bore holes
in the femoral artery of each victim.
Our unsub could have
medical knowledge.
It's possible. We'll know
more when we get there.
Wheels up in 30.
♪ Criminal Minds 8x13 ♪
Magnum Opus
Original Air Date on January 23, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
JJ: "My blood alone remains.
Take it.
But do not make me
suffer long."
Marie Antoinette.
Why these two victims?
He's crossed socioeconomic,
race, and gender lines.
One white males in his 40s,
a wealthy
hedge fund manager.
And an African American
female, just started college
at San Francisco State, worked
several jobs just to get by.
Yeah, but why drain the blood?
Is he doing it
to torture the victims?
Or is it about the blood?
Might be a form
of psychological torture.
While not necessarily
painful,
exsanguination
does take time.
It could be a fetish for
the blood and the bloodletting.
What about...
drinking it?
Fritz Haarmann,
the vampire of Hanover,
killed many of his victims
by biting through their throats.
This unsub used
some sort of tubing device
to drain the blood
from the femoral arteries.
There isn't any saliva
on the wound.
Just because
there's no bite marks
doesn't mean we should
rule out vampirism.
[Beep]
Bad news, crime-fighters.
Police just found
another body
wrapped in plastic
on a park bench,
drained of blood.
I'm gonna assume there's not
two creeps in the area
doing the same thing?
Garcia, will you tell
San Francisco P.D.
We'll meet them
at the crime scene?
Consider them told.
Dave, you and Blake meet
the detectives at the crime scene.
Morgan, go see
the medical examiner,
and JJ and I will set up
at the police station.
We'll talk to the families,
see if we can find a connection.
Detective.
SSA Rossi.
This is SSA Blake.
Detective Lenny Miles.
It's great to have you guys here.
So the victim's name
is Lynn Stevens.
She's drained,
just like the last two,
but there's something new.
New?
He's removed
her eyelids.
I don't even want to take a guess
as to why someone would do that.
There's excessive blood
around the eyes.
He did this antemortem.
His sadism is evolving.
And his torture
is definitely
more than psychological
at this point.
I just don't understand
why someone would do this.
It's all still
so hard to believe.
I just need to ask you a few
questions about your husband.
Pammy was a great girl.
You know?
Really friendly.
She loved everyone,
and everyone loved her.
And you two had worked
together
the night
that she was abducted?
He called me.
He said he was on his
way home from work.
He just needed to stop off
and close up a deal.
He didn't have anything
in his schedule for that night.
Do you have any idea
what that deal was?
After work, she said she always
liked to go on long walks.
She was always
going on about the architecture,
how it's nothing
like Oregon.
She had just moved
to San Francisco?
Are there any other friends
of hers that you know
who we should talk to?
She was paying her way
through school.
When she wasn't there,
she was always at another job.
Just trying
to stay afloat.
You know?
If you think of anything else,
please, don't hesitate to call.
If these victims are
connected, I can't see it.
It's got to be
about the blood.
Yeah, but even that's
different.
Gary was A-positive,
Pam was O-neg.
We just got the lab report back
on the latest victim, Lynn Stevens.
She was AB-negative.
Maybe these are just
victims of opportunity.
Well, it's possible the
unsub abducted Pamela on
one of her routine walks.
He could have lured Gary with
the promise of a lucrative money deal.
Hi. I'm Aimee.
Nice place.
Okay, so it's going to be
75 for the hour.
Anything more than that
we can discuss.
All right?
Someplace where
I can get changed?
There.
I don't know which positions
you want me in,
but I'm very flexible.
What's up, baby girl?
I'm worried about Reid.
I am, too.
What do you think
he's doing?
I think he's taking the time
that Hotch gave him.
I get it. He's sad.
He should be sad.
But I'm so worried.
And when someone I love
is hurting,
it's like I hurt, too, which I know
is super codependent,
but it's just how I roll, and I feel
like I should be doing something,
and I don't know
what it is, but--
All right, slow down,
all right? Just slow down.
Could you call him?
I have. He's just not ready
to talk to anybody right now.
I need to hear his voice.
It's impairing my ability to work.
Let me try something,
all right?
Thanks.
Hello. This is Spencer Reid.
Please leave a message.
[Beep]
Hey, Reid, it's Derek. Listen,
I got a work question for you.
The unsub's exsanguinating victims
and removing their eyelids antemortem.
Does that mean anything
to you? Hit me back.
[Door opens]
Here's the information
you called about.
Thank you.
[Cell phone rings]
Excuse me for a second.
What's up, Reid?
Have the cornea or pupils
been harmed in any way?
No, no. Blake said it looked like a very
sharp instrument was used.
If he's taking care
not to damage the eyes,
then line of sight is probably
what's important to him.
So this guy wants them
to see what he's doing.
Hey, Reid. How are you?
I gotta go.
Sorry about that.
Not a problem.
Cause of death would
definitely be exsanguination.
But the tox screen
showed high levels of--
say this 5 times fast--
ethylene diamine tetra acetic.
EDTA. It's an anti-coagulant.
Used mostly to treat
heart conditions.
So the unsub probably
used it to thin the blood.
The ketamine we found
may have helped as well.
In humans, it tends
to elevate blood pressure.
Which is how
he's sedating them.
If he knew that he was giving
these drugs to these victims
and he ingested the blood?
He'd be dosing himself
as well.
Well, that rules out vampirism.
Is there any chance this guy works
in the medical field?
I doubt it. There are a few
hesitation marks near the wound,
and the hole in the artery
shows a lot of bruising around it.
I'd say
it's amateur at best.
All right,
so we got an unsub
who's picking his victims
at random,
sedates them,
then bleeds them dry.
If he's not drinking the blood,
what the hell is he doing with it?
Wait...
[Breathing hard]
Shh, shh, shh. Be still.
What's--what--
what are you doing?
Wait--wait--aah!
Well, we got a hit
off the prints.
The victim's name
is Aimee Fortner.
It's only been a day
since his last kill.
Well, this guy doesn't
have a cool-down period.
Rigor hasn't set in yet.
I'd say she was put here
maybe an hour ago,
just after sunrise.
He's getting brazen.
It's his first daytime
disposal.
Well, this part of the park's
not very well traveled.
The city's been trying
to renovate every couple of years,
but you know--politics.
So the unsub is familiar
enough with the area
to know nobody would
disturb him.
Office of omnipotence.
How may I dazzle you?
Garcia, I need information
on the latest victim, Aimee Fortner.
Information is my favorite
way to dazzle, sir.
So sparkly.
Here we go
Aimee Crystal Fortner.
Originally from Santa Clara.
She was super pretty.
When she wasn't bartending,
she supplemented her income
by modeling.
A model?
Yes. And she's
got a website
full of very artistic
pictures of herself.
Girl was not afraid to flaunt
what God gave her at all.
Uh-huh.
Thanks, Garcia.
What are you thinking?
Reid told Morgan
line of sight
was important to the unsub.
We should take a look
at the other crime scenes.
I might know what he's
doing with the blood.
We believe that this unsub
is a white male in his 20s or 30s,
and he thinks of himself
as a painter or an artist.
The placement of the
victims tells us a lot about who he is.
Pamela Hurd was found
near a painting done by
little known San Francisco artist
Henry Floyd.
Gary Porter was posed near
a piece of graffiti art
by a street artist named Cypher, who is
currently wanted by the police.
Hotch: And the third victim, Lynn Stevens,
was found near a mural
painted by inner city youths.
Finally, Aimee Fortner was placed
near the statue of Saint Luke,
patron Saint of the artist.
JJ: This is a compulsion.
It's not accidental.
He is obsessed with art.
Rossi: All of the works
of art are neglected,
ignored, cast aside.
It's how he feels
about himself.
Hotch: We believe it's also
the reason that he's evolved
to removing the victims eyelids.
He's forcing them to see
what he sees.
There's no sexual component
with these murders,
but that's because the blood
and the use of the blood
is his sexual release.
So, wait.
What--what is he doing
with the blood?
Because he's so obsessed
with art,
we believe
he's painting with it.
Rossi: He has a quick
kill pace.
More blood means more paint.
The more paintings he does,
the greater the chance
someone will recognize his work.
We think that because
of his need for acceptance,
he may be trying
to sell the paintings.
So focus your canvassing
on places
that might sell
this kind of fringe art.
[Cell phone rings]
What's up, kid?
If it is about the art,
then it's clear the disposal
sites are scattered
around the Mission
District area.
Wait a minute.
How did you know--
I had Anderson bring over
some of the files.
All right. All right, hold on a second.
Let me patch in Garcia.
[Dialing]
What have you heard?
Is he okay?
Slow down. Slow down.
Reid.
Garcia, you should pull a list
of all the art galleries
in San Francisco.
Reid, I was just--
how are you?
Better.
Thanks for asking.
And thanks for the baskets.
You know, nuts have magnesium,
which helps produce--
Serotonin. Yeah.
I know.
Okay, galleries.
I got a lot.
Focus on the Mission District.
I guess that's better
than nothing.
It is. I will take it.
Okay, there's still a few galleries,
but it's more manageable.
I am sending the addresses
to your mobile.
I got it. Thanks, Garcia.
Yeah.
It's an original Hellman.
He painted it while
literally on his deathbed.
10,000.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah?
Madison.
He's back.
The museum is ready
to make me an offer.
Perfect.
If you want,
I can tell him to leave.
No, it's okay.
Mrs. Riley.
I think you'll be much more
pleased with my piece this time.
Yeah, um, like I told you
the last time,
I'm not interested.
Why not?
Well, because
this type of art
is just not what
we're looking for.
Well, what is it
you are looking for?
Uh...
Look, I can see that
you're getting better.
All I can tell you
is it's a little simplistic.
Look, every good artist leaves
a piece of himself on the canvas.
You have to find
that one thing
that's going to set you apart from
the rest of the crowd.
I used blood.
An unusual medium is not
what I'm talking about.
The world today
doesn't make sense.
Why should I paint
pictures that do?
Picasso.
I'm impressed.
If I find my signature, you'll
consider me for the gallery?
Anything's possible.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Can I help you?
We're from the FBI.
You the owner?
Yeah. Name's Tre.
Do you have any art on display
where blood is used as a medium?
No.
No, but there was a guy
in here a couple days ago
who tried to sell me
a piece like that.
It wasn't exactly my taste,
but a customer of mine
happened to be in here,
saw it, fell in love with it,
bought it on sight.
You think that
could that be your guy?
You wouldn't happen to have any
security cameras in here, would you?
No.
We need the customer's
name if you've got it.
Yeah.
I never quite understood
these things.
It all looks like the guy had
a seizure while painting it.
It's Emile Hartford.
It's early 20th century.
His daughter died
when she was 8.
He said every time he painted,
he'd be able to see her.
Don't know how you see
anything in there.
I guess that's why they say
art is in the eye of the beholder.
Yeah.
You know what else
is in the eye of the beholder?
'57 Chevy I told you
about last week?
This morning, bam,
it won't start.
Now it's in the eye
of my mechanic.
Come on, man, are you
gonna make me ask
or are you gonna be a friend
and offer me a ride home?
We're friends.
Worked together for two years
now. I'd hope so.
You need a ride, Paul?
Thought you'd never ask.
The unsub sold his
painting to this place?
It reminds me
of the eighties.
What?
Do I even want to know?
Probably.
Welcome. My name is Andre.
Before we start, I'll need you
to fill out a small waiver.
No, no, no.
We're not a couple.
That's okay. We cater
to all kinds of relationships.
Well, uh, our relationship
is with the FBI.
Oh.
I run a clean
establishment here.
Clean, legal, adult fun.
Calm down. We're just looking
for a painting you bought recently.
You're gonna have to be
a bit more specific.
I'm a connoisseur
of the dark and depraved arts.
I purchase a lot of paintings.
Well, you bought this one
a couple of days ago.
It's made with blood.
Human blood.
Like I said, I buy
a lot of paintings.
I don't remember them all.
Oh, really? Because
last I checked,
withholding evidence
would make you an accomplice.
We just want to see
the painting.
Just want to see if it's from
the guy we're looking for.
Remembering now?
Possibly.
For that piece, you'll have to
follow me to the spanking room.
I may have bought it,
but I didn't realize
it was evidence
of any sort.
Is that that
you're looking for?
The tortured look in her eyes
is what first drew me to it.
The guy was asking 1,500 for it.
I got him to take 250, cash.
That's our first victim,
Pamela Hurd.
It's definitely from our guy.
Yeah, we're gonna need
to take this.
[Muttering]
What are you doing?
What...
What's going on?
It...
Wawa.
What--
no, please don't.
Why?
It's the only way.
Sorry.
You're insane.
I guess every artist
is a little crazy.
No, come on man,
we're friends.
Exactly.
It's what I've been missing.
Something personal.
I need you to hold still.
Hold still.
Hold still..
Hold still!
Help!
[Grunting]
No! Aah!
No!
No...No!
Well, we now have
a piece of his art,
but we still don't have
anything to identify the unsub.
The lab's got a sample, but it's
probably Pamela Hurd's blood.
Master Andre said he was
an average white guy
in his late 20s
to early 30s.
Same thing the gallery owner said.
He signed it.
Yeah, it looks like
a "B" something or something "B".
I'm going to have Garcia
compile a list of artists
with the letter "B"
somewhere in their name.
It's not much,
but it's something.
We got the report back
from the lab.
They couldn't extract
any DNA from the painting.
They said something about there
only being red blood cells.
Hmm. He removed
the white blood cells.
Plasma.
Why would he take
the plasma?
It would make it thicker.
Easier to use as a paint.
What type of equipment
would it take to do that?
You can easily buy
a centrifuge online these days
for a couple hundred
bucks.
What other reasons would
he have for separating
the plasma from the blood?
It's a habit.
- Reid.
- Spence.
I didn't expect you back this soon.
You sure you're ready?
No, but I think
I figured something out.
Where's Mrs. Riley?
You need to leave.
It's okay, Alan,
I'll handle it.
I did what you said.
This is my friend, Paul.
I even used
some of my own blood.
That's not what I meant.
But you said if I made it
more personal,
you'd use me
in your gallery.
Look, I've been trying to be nice
and give you some encouragement,
but I can see now that that's
really not gonna help you.
So I think I just
have to be blunt.
It's not good.
But...
This is--
this is abstract.
I understand the concept,
but splashing something
onto a canvas,
that doesn't make it art.
Some people have it,
some people don't.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Maybe not, but that still doesn't mean
that I'm gonna buy this.
But you said--
Look, I don't know how
to explain this to you any better.
There is a difference
between a dream and a talent.
Look, I'm sorry.
If there's someone
that you--
He's a hemophiliac.
That would explain
his obsession with blood.
He can't bleed without
a fear of dying.
It's also why he would
separate the plasma from the blood
before painting with it.
It's an antiquated treatment,
but some hemophiliacs
can inject plasma
into their wounds,
kick-starting the clotting process
that's ineffective in their own systems.
Talk about it.
Hey, girlie, I need a list of
hemophiliacs in San Francisco.
Vague. So vague. Okay.
Garcia, for his obsession
to be this profound,
he most likely has the more
severe version of the disease.
It's type B Christmas disease.
Reid, happy to hear
you made it safe and sound.
Thank you, Garcia.
Okay, Christmas disease.
It does not sound very jolly.
It was named after the first known case,
Stephen Christmas.
All right, I got 15 people
who have trouble clotting.
He wouldn't stray too
far from the art world.
Most likely works in and
around the art community,
but not as an artist.
And he's a loner.
So look for people with jobs
where they don't interact
with the public.
Yeah. Yeah. I got 3.
Stock boy at a local
supermarket, an art blogger,
and a custodian.
The victims have
different blood types.
If he's taking the plasma
out of the blood,
he must be
a universal recipient.
Any of them
with AB-positive blood?
Specificity. I dig it.
Okay, if I factor in those "B" names
I was working on...
And bingo is his name-o.
Actually, his name
is Bryan Hughes.
He is an AB-positive
hemophiliac
who works as a janitor
at the Bay Area Museum of Art,
and before you ask, yes, his
address has been sent to your phones.
You're the best,
baby girl.
Dave, you and Blake
take the museum.
The rest of us
will take the residence.
I'm okay.
Yeah. But it's good
to see you.
You really don't need to be here
if you're not ready.
This is going to
take time.
How much time?
It's hard to say.
But we're all here
for you.
Thank you.
[sirens]
Hey, what you got, mama?
A compelling piece of information
about this Bryan Hughes.
3 weeks before
the first murder,
he was involved
in a car accident.
Hotch:
Was he injured?
Uh, no. And if you were
looking at the pictures I am
you would say
that is a miracle.
It may have given him
the impression he couldn't be hurt.
The other driver was hurt.
She bled to death.
Hughes called 911, failed to mention there
was another driver involved.
By the time emergency
crews got there,
thanks, Garcia.
She had already died.
Watching the other woman bleed
to death must have been the trigger.
[Cell phone rings]
Hey, what you got, pretty boy?
I think Hughes may have
his next victim.
An Alan archer just came in
and reported his boss missing.
Madison Riley owns
an art gallery in the Mission District.
Said there was blood,
signs of a struggle.
Hughes even left a painting
of his on the wall this time.
It's the same signature
and it's definitely made of blood,
which got me thinking
about Maeve's stalker.
If this guy's a tortured artist
searching for approval,
in his mind there may be
only one way to get it.
Suicide.
Thanks, Reid.
I put my heart and my soul
into those paintings.
You're going to get
a first-hand look
at what I'm capable
of creating.
Bryan Hughes, FBI.
No! I have to make her see.
Hotch:
Put down the knife.
Bryan, I understand.
No, you don't.
How could you possibly
understand?
Because I've seen
your work.
And I know you may not
be appreciated now,
but I promise you,
if you put down the knife,
I will make sure that
people see your art,
and no one will be
able to ignore it.
It's all I want.
I deserve that.
Then put down the knife,
and let's figure this out.
You know how many paintings
van Gogh sold before he died?
Bryan, don't do it.
Two.
He sold two.
Don't make us do this.
I gotta make you see me.
Get the EMTs upstairs.
We've got another body
over here.
[Gasping]
Well, I counted 5 baskets.
7, but I think
Ms. Cavanaugh next door
may have taken a couple.
I'm really sorry
if I've been kind of...
Spence. You don't...
Kid.
I didn't mean for you
to come all the way out there.
I know.
Listen, if you need
anything at all,
you just have to ask.
Actually, if you guys
don't mind,
I could use some help
with something.
Name it.
Reid: "Sometimes the hardest
part isn't letting go,
but rather, learning
to start over."
Nicole Sobon.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==