♪
How'd I let you talk me
into another round, huh?
Come on.
We need to
decompress.
Yeah, decompression is for the
day after the special election,
especially when your guy
only has a two-point lead.
When are you gonna take
it out of fifth gear?
People are still getting
used to the idea
that Senator Chang
died in office.
They'll warm up to our guy,
once the shock
wears off.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe you're right.
Mm. What's the plan
for tomorrow?
Debate prep,
campaign rally downtown,
fund-raiser, and
then in the evening
there's a cocktail party
for some big-money supporters.
Whoa, this thing is
really moving at warp speed.
Yeah, you know it.
Well, the
saving grace
is that it will all be over...
in two weeks.
Yeah, and then
we'll either be looking
for apartments in DC
or job hunting.
Cheers.
Okay, okay, okay,
you convinced me.
I'm gonna go back to the office,
crunch some more numbers.
Being around all these beautiful
people having a good time,
that's just...
not the greatest motivator.
And I'm saying
good night.
Oh, sorry. Good night.
What, are you sticking around?
Yeah. Yeah, I think I'm gonna,
uh, decompress a little more.
Decompress. Sweet.
I will, uh, see you
bright and early.
Bright and early.
Bright.
And early.
♪
Belvedere dirty martini.
From the gentleman at
the end of the bar.
♪
Hey, handsome.
Please...
please don't do this.
Don't do this.
I swear to you I told you
everything I knew.
Please...
I believe you.
(Hawaii Five-O
theme song plays)
♪ Hawaii Five-O 3x14 ♪
Hana I Wa'Ia (Scandal)
Original Air Date on January 21, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
Hey.
Wow.
You, uh,
you look,
uh, very nice--
suit and tie; that's good.
It's for you. Wore it for you.
Thank you.
All right.
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
Is that a clip-on?
It's not a clip-on.
Are you...
What'd I just say to you?
Your tie's all jacked up--
can I fix it, please?
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
Thought nobody wore
a tie in Hawaii.
No, they don't, but, you know,
it's a special day,
so I thought I'd wear one.
'Course, I'm wearing
my dress blues.
They'd make me
walk the plank
if I don't wear a tie
with the dress blues.
How come the
blues are black?
I know they're black;
I don't know why...
Thank you very much for
being here-- it means a lot.
Okay?
You're welcome.
You'd do the same for me.
All right, you ready?
Yeah, I'm good.
I got, uh...
the speech
all prepared, everything's...
good.
Good.
Tell you something,
they take her away from me,
I'm jumping off a cliff today.
Hey, hey, hey.
That's not gonna happen, okay?
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Danny.
Okay.
All right?
That's not gonna happen.
That's not gonna
happen all right?
♪
In the matter
of Williams v. Edwards,
where are we?
Your Honor, my client
has prepared a statement
he'd like to read
into the record.
Go ahead.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
"Your Honor, uh...
I, uh, I come
before you today..."
Okay, I'm sorry.
Can I start over?
Thank you.
"Uh, Your Honor...
I come..."
That sucks.
Detective Williams,
why are you littering
my courtroom?
I apologize.
I really apologize, Your Honor.
But... um, I was prepared
to give my speech
to Rachel, my ex,
but she's...
she's not here.
Weren't you told
that your statement
should be addressed
to this court?
Yes, I was, I was, but...
I know how busy
a family court judge can be,
right, presiding
over cases much bigger,
more serious than mine.
So I thought that I would appeal
directly to Rachel.
Go on.
Okay. Um...
Okay, look, I, um...
I had a pretty good life
in New Jersey, uh, and then...
I came here.
And it wasn't exactly a fit.
Uh, the sun... sand--
I mean, I can't even get
a decent slice of pizza.
Get to your point,
Detective Williams.
Okay, I hate this place.
Uh...
I apologize,
but I do.
But I was willing
to put up with it,
because this is
where my daughter is.
And now her mother
wants to move again,
and I-I can't
go through with that.
Not to Vegas, not anywhere,
because this... is my home.
This is our...
home.
Your Honor, that little girl
is-is my everything.
She is my life,
she is my breath.
And it may just be
the two of us,
but we... are a family.
And separating us
by two thousand seven hundred
and fifty-four miles of water
is not... something
this court should allow.
Detective, weren't
you recently shot
in the presence
of your daughter?
I can... I can explain
that, Your Honor.
Commander McGarrett,
this is not your forum.
Yes, I know that,
Your Honor,
and I'm sorry, but...
Detective Williams doesn't just
work for me-- he's my friend,
he's my close friend--
and, uh...
I've seen him with his daughter.
He's a great father.
He's actually the kind
of father we all
wish we had.
I'm so sorry.
I have to take
this call.
Yes, Governor?
She was found like that
in a mansion in Kahala.
We got an I.D.?
HPD is still working on it.
But here are the preliminaries.
All right.
We'll do everything
we can to help, sir.
I don't want you to help,
Commander-- I want you
and your Five-O task force
to take over the case.
And I need it cleared quickly.
Well, uh, HPD Homicide
is very good...
And I need it done quietly.
Yes, sir.
Uh...
if I may ask, what brought
this case to your attention?
The people who
own the house
are friends of mine,
close friends.
Very dear friends.
I'd like the matter
to remain private.
Okay, well,
I'll need to talk to them.
You can't.
Why not?
They're trekking in Nepal;
completely unreachable.
I'll need to confirm that, sir.
I'm confirming it for you right now.
Keep me in the
loop, Commander.
I want constant updates.
And don't go through the office.
Call my cell directly.
Understood, sir.
All right,
send him in.
Hold on,
let me get this straight.
Is this official business,
or is this a favor?
What difference does it make?
Well, it makes a very big difference,
you see, because official
business is, uh, official.
A favor is like a quid pro quo
kind of deal, right?
You... solve this
murder case for me,
and I will give you, uh, oh,
five days' paid vacation.
Right? Or tickets to Monster
Truck Jam, or whatever.
Monster Truck Jam's
not in town.
Okay, so then it is, indeed,
official business.
Exactly.
Exac...? Wh-What...
None of this seems
strange to you?
Hold on. None of this seems, uh, in
the slightest bit off?
I mean, what are
these homeowners?
They, uh, big contributors
to the governor's
campaign, or what?
I have no idea.
And we can't talk to them?
Danny, is there a point
coming anytime soon? - Absolutely.
It seems to me like
we're taking a case
just to protect the
governor's friends.
With the governor's task force.
Then why
does it feel like we are performing
janitorial services, blindfolded,
I might add.
We've been given a directive, Danny.
Oh, right, I understand.
When McGarrett gets an order,
he takes the order.
You know what you're like?
You're like one
of those windup
toy soldiers.
Let me get you a drum
for Christmas to beat.
The last time we butted heads
with Denning, he sent Lori home.
I don't want to see what he's got
planned for an encore, do you?
Okay, here are some basics.
The homeowners' names
are Wendy and Patrick Duggan.
I checked into
their passport records.
They landed in Katmandu
last week.
According to their itinerary,
they're halfway into their hike.
Well, confirms what
Governor Denning told us.
How do you think
the cell service is on Everest?
I can't imagine it's too good.
We got any signs of forced entry?
No.
Other than the Duggans,
the caretaker's the only one
who claims to have
a set of keys.
HPD checked
his alibi.
It's airtight.
Max give us a COD?
He hasn't posted the
vic yet, but based
on the bruising around her neck,
he's thinking she was strangled.
Maybe it was a crime
of passion, right?
Killer's having sex
with the vic,
then he gets a little rough,
things spin
out of control.
You got anything else?
Yeah. Max found traces
of a powdery substance
around her left clavicle.
He sent it over
to Fong for processing.
I got an I.D.
on our vic.
Her name is
Serena Andrews.
HPD had her
in their database.
What was she cited for?
Solicitation.
Houston, we've got a problem.
So we have a working girl killed
in a Kahala mansion belonging
to good friends of the governor.
Two questions:
did the governor know her,
and did he know
that she was a prostitute?
And if he did,
is he involved?
You like the way
this is going?
No, I don't.
Serena didn't make it
home last night.
Not exactly a big deal.
So she often stays out
all night?
Look, I'm
her roommate,
not her mother.
But she is a
friend of yours?
Yeah.
How long you guys been here?
Six months.
Mollie, do you know that Serena
was cited for solicitation?
That was over a year ago.
What about you--
you ever been busted?
I'm a student.
Pretty pricey place.
Student loans cover this?
I don't like
what you're insinuating.
I'm not insinuating; I'm asking.
What's an all-night trick go for
these days-- two, three grand?
What I do with my body
is my business.
And when a body
shows up dead,
it's ours.
Oh, my God.
She was found dead at 3500
Hunukai Street in Kahala.
Do you know that address?
No.
Truth.
Look, Serena didn't usually work
with locals, okay?
Just high-end tourists
or conventioneers.
How did she hook up
with the johns?
There's this thing
called the Internet.
Maybe you've heard of it.
Where's your laptop?
So, if we can find
the last john Serena booked,
it could lead back
to our killer.
Her clientele
wouldn't use their real names,
though, would they?
Probably not.
Then again, the guys
we're dealing with
usually aren't thinking
with their heads.
Not the big one anyway.
Okay,
okay, copy that.
Let's just get Serena's laptop
over to Fong
and see if he can trace
the last IP address.
That could
be a while.
Why?
What's wrong?
Black SUV
two cars back--
you see it?
Oh, hello.
Yeah,
it's been tailing us
for the last two miles.
Yeah, okay, thanks, Max.
Hey.
TOD on Serena Andrews
was between 11:00
and 12:00 last night.
Max just confirmed that
she had sexual intercourse
just prior to
the murder.
So there's DNA.
Max just put a
rush order on it.
Lab should have some
answers any time soon.
I just got
off the phone
with the lab.
Did we get a hit?
I don't know.
You just said you got off
the phone with the lab.
I did, yeah, and they told me
they are on strict orders
not to rush the testing.
Orders from whom?
Governor Denning's office.
SUV's still on us.
That's three straight lefts.
Doubt they're looking
for a parking spot.
How do you want to play it?
Hold on.
Five-O!
Get out of the car now!
Hey, hey!
What the hell was
all that about?
I don't know,
but did you catch the plates?
"G" ride, yeah,
government issue.
Commander, Commander,
you cannot
go in there.
Am I running
this investigation or not?
Give us a
minute, please.
Don't ever do that again.
Why'd you ask me
to take over this case
if you're going to interfere?
There is a chain
of command here,
and you're not anywhere
near the top.
There is a state vehicle
surveilling my team.
Sir, the lab
can't process the DNA
on your orders.
Why are you blocking
every move I make?
My orders are not subject
to your scrutiny, Commander.
What the hell
are you hiding, Governor?
Just what the hell
are you implying?
The dead girl-- you knew
she was a prostitute.
The DNA we found
on the body--
is it yours?
No.
Is it yours, Governor?
No!
No, I did not know the
victim was a prostitute,
and no, it is not my DNA.
I don't know what
to believe here, sir.
When I run
that DNA... who is it going
to trace back to?
Chris Freed.
Congressman Christopher Freed?
Yes, our soon-
to-be senator.
I don't understand.
Politics, Commander,
plain and simple.
Protect your flank at all costs.
Protect your ass
is what you mean.
Chris Freed and I go
a long way back.
I told him I'd help out
any way I can.
He needed a place
in town to stay,
I knew these party donors
who were away,
so I arranged it for him
to stay at their house--
the same house Serena Andrews'
body was found in.
Okay, why didn't
you tell me the truth
when you handed me the case?
Because
a scandal like this could
ruin a good man's life
and his chances
of being elected.
You didn't think
I was gonna find out?
I was hoping to contain your
findings as they came in,
determine if they
were credible.
If they were,
act accordingly.
You have to
understand,
Chris Freed is
a Medal of Honor recipient,
chairman of the Veteran Affairs
Committee.
And now he's a suspect
in a homicide investigation.
He is also my friend, Commander.
We served together.
Of all people,
you know what that means.
And, may I add,
he is also
a devoted single father,
so I wanted to
be damn sure
that the facts were straight
before we rip his life apart.
With all due respect...
...we just found
a dead prostitute in his bed.
So I have to ask you--
as his friend,
I have got to ask you...
do you think it's possible
Congressman Freed
could have killed this woman?
I don't know.
Okay, you know
what we call this
in police work?
What?
A complete and total
waste of time.
Just listen to me.
Anybody knows where
the congressman is,
it's going to be
his press secretary.
He's not gonna
tell us anything.
These people lie for a
living-- you know that, right?
- This guy.
- All right, we got anything over there?
Excuse me,
Josh Lowry?
I'll have to call you back.
Uh, yeah, who are you?
Steve McGarrett.
This is
Detective Danny Williams.
We're with Five-O.
Hi. Oh.
Hey, we're looking
for Congressman Freed.
Yeah, Five-O,
thank you guys for coming down,
and you know the congressman
is a huge supporter
of the law enforcement
community.
Uh, can we get you guys
anything-- coffee or water?
No, we're good,
we just want
a minute with
the congressman.
Yeah, you know what?
I-I wish you guys had called.
I could have saved you
the trouble.
Due to the accelerated
campaign schedule,
the congressman-- he's,
he's wall-to-wall today,
guys, he's very busy.
Very busy.
Yeah, slammed actually,
but I'm sure I can answer
any questions
you guys might have
on the issues.
I-I have a question, actually.
Yeah, maybe you could tell us,
what's the
congressman's position
on dead hookers
found in his bed?
Strangled dead hookers.
Um, you know,
why don't we, uh,
why don't we speak
in private?
Sure.
No, there's no way.
There's got to be
some kind of mistake.
The congressman would never get
involved with a prostitute.
His stand on the exploitation
of sex workers is very clear,
and as far as murder goes...
Let me guess,
he's completely against it.
Do you even know
the congressman?
Uh, about as much as
you can know somebody
in a 15-second sound bite.
Okay.
All I'm saying is,
spend ten minutes with the man.
You'd be absolutely convinced
at how outrageous
your accusations are.
Now, if this country had more
men like Congressman Freed...
There'd be a chicken
in every pot
and a dead ho
in every bed, right?
Look, uh, I've been with him
since his days
in the State House.
Okay?
I'm not saying he's perfect
but pretty damn close,
and the mere
suggestion
that he could be possibly
involved in something like this
is incredibly insulting to him,
to his family,
and to his legacy.
Okay, that is a,
a beautiful speech.
Okay, where is he?
Mr. Lowry,
if the congressman is as big
on law enforcement as you say,
then you understand,
we have to do our job.
Now, where is he?
We're not going
to ask you again.
Geez. Ah, boy.
We've been spinning all morning
to cover for him.
Oh, you don't even know
where he is?
No, we don't.
You didn't think
to tell anybody?
Look, the political reality
is this:
the special election
is a nail-biter.
We haven't had any time
to campaign.
Now, any little thing
could tip the scales.
Now, if news got out
that Freed was off the grid,
yeah, let's just say
that'd be bad.
No, no, I'll tell you
what'd be bad.
Bad would be
"Breaking News Story:
Congressman Freed,
Suspect in a Homicide."
Whoa...
Josh,
level with us.
All right,
where do you think he is?
All I can think is that he and
Amy are somewhere, holed up,
prepping
for the debate.
Who's Amy?
Amy Davidson-- she's
Freed's chief of staff,
one of his closest confidants.
She runs
the campaign.
Well, where is she, Josh?
I don't know, I don't,
I really don't.
I'm assuming with him.
So, if I'm Congressman Freed
in the middle
of a special election,
and something goes wrong...
Who's the first
person you call?
My chief of staff Amy Davidson.
Right, so you can get together
and plan an alibi.
Any luck pinging the
congressman's phone?
No, no signal.
Okay, well, try Amy's.
Chances are,
we find one, we
find the other.
Hey, Steve, hold on,
Kono's got something.
You guys aren't gonna
believe this. The lab finally
processed the DNA
from the dead girl.
They got a hit.
Congressman Freed?
No.
Then who is it?
The match came back
from the National Database
to a Ryan Webb.
He's an associate professor
of English from Ohio.
He's in town for
a mystery writers convention.
What's a teacher doing
in the system?
He's employed at a state school.
They require
DNA for background checks. Uh,
the IP address from the hotel
matched Serena's
last appointment.
According to the hotel,
he's scheduled
to check out this morning.
I got it.
Here, here, let me help you
with those bags.
What is this?
Who are you?
Five-O. We're
extending your stay.
Hope you had a nice visit.
Please, this is all
a colossal mistake.
I honestly have no idea
what you're talking about.
A mistake? Well, why don't you
help me understand?
Where's the congressman?
Congressman who?
Congressman Freed of the
great state of Hawaii.
Is that supposed
to mean something to me?
I...
Party last night, remember?
Mansion in Kahala?
Last night?
Last night, I-I was
on an Elmore Leonard panel,
and a bunch of us went
to the room to watch Get Shorty.
Yeah, you left the part out
about the dead prostitute.
What? No.
No, no, no.
Obviously, fiction isn't
your strong suit, Professor,
'cause we have your DNA,
and it puts you in bed
with the hooker
at the congressman's house.
Look, look, come on.
I'm just an English teacher,
okay?
I don't know anything
about a congressman,
and I didn't kill anybody!
Nice wedding ring, by the way.
How long you been married?
Wait a minute.
Maybe your wife
in Ohio knows
where you were last night.
Let's give her a call, see
what she got to say then.
Wait, wait, wait.
Serena was alive
when I left her.
Well, how did you
wind up with the congressman?
I didn't.
Okay, the girl and I--
we never left the bar.
Bar? What bar?
Have you ever been
to Lima, Ohio?
I mean, come on.
This is Hawaii.
I-I just wanted to have fun.
So, I-I found this Web site,
and Serena--
she agreed to meet me
at the Liki Tiki Lounge.
Wait a minute. You're telling me
you had sex with her
at the bar,
is that what you're saying?
When-when she showed up, well...
...we-we did it in the bathroom.
I've always wanted to do that.
Back in Lima...
Then what?
Then-then she left.
What time was that?
About-about 10:00.
What did you do after that?
I stayed and had a few more drinks.
Same bar?
Yeah. No.
If you don't believe me,
you can check
my credit card, okay?
I ran a tab,
and I cashed out at last call.
Bartender confirms
seeing Serena Andrews
leaving the Liki Tiki Lounge
around 10:00.
Well, what about Webb?
Credit card checks out.
He closed the place.
Okay, so, 10:00 was the last
time anybody saw Serena alive.
Mm-hmm, and with TOD set
between 11:00 and 12:00...
There's no way Webb
could have killed her.
We're back
to square one.
Not exactly. Just got a call
from our friend Josh Lowry.
Looks like Freed's Chief
of Staff, Amy Davidson,
just walked into
campaign headquarters.
Josh, where's Amy Davidson?
She's inside with Powers.
Brad Powers. That's, uh, Freed's
opponent. What's he doing here?
Well, he came by to discuss
the ground rules of the debate
with the congressman, I
was handling the situation.
Then all of a sudden,
Amy shows up.
Picks up right where
she left off,
like nothing
even happened.
Did she say where she was?
No, she didn't.
She went behind closed doors
with Powers,
they've been in there
ever since.
Josh, you disappoint me.
I don't know what kind of
campaign you're running here,
but I don't buy Amy's
spin for a minute.
We're not spinning anything,
Mr. Powers.
Really? Then what's
Five-O doing here?
That's between us
and the congressman, sir.
Yeah, well, when you
see him, please ask him
why he blew me off last night
without so much as a phone call.
What time were you supposed to meet him?
11:00.
I've know Chris
Freed for 15 years.
He's never pulled
a stunt like that.
I'm sure it's just
a misunderstanding, sir.
He said he wanted
to run a civil campaign,
one with mutual respect
and all of that.
This is a hell of
a way to show it.
I don't know what you
people are hiding,
but I'm gonna find out, and
when I do, so will the press.
Okay.
We need to speak
to Amy now.
Amy?
I got Five-O here.
They need to talk to you.
Miss Davis,
where's Congressman Freed?
I don't know,
but I think he might have done
something terrible.
Don't you think
I'd help you guys if I could?
I just don't know
where he is right now.
Okay, so, you--
where have you been?
I was out...
looking for him.
Look, you don't get it.
This is complicated.
Then speak slowly, all right?
Because I need to understand
why a man like Congressman Freed
would risk everything
to get serviced
by a prostitute.
To tell you the truth, I brought
her to meet the congressman.
That's a smart move.
Why'd you do that?
Doesn't happen all the time,
but he's under a lot of stress,
and he's a single father,
so he's on his own.
I mean, besides his daughter,
there's...
there's really no one else
in his life.
So sometimes he just needs
a little companionship
for the evening.
So you're chief of staff
and part-time madam for him?
Come on, the guy's human.
All right, Amy,
I have to ask you.
To the best of your knowledge,
has the congressman ever hurt
any of the women he's been with?
Rough stuff doesn't seem
to be his thing,
but you know, who knows what
goes on behind closed doors?
Okay, well, something happened
last night.
Where did you find
Serena Andrews?
Picked her up at a place called
the Liki Tiki Lounge,
and I dropped her off
at the mansion in Kahala.
No, you delivered her
to the congressman,
like a pizza.
Yes.
What about the
congressman's
11:00 with Powers?
Why did he blow that off?
I don't know.
That's why I went
back to the mansion.
But when I got there,
he was gone,
and I found the girl in the bed.
And being the pragmatic
political operative
that you are, you decided to go
to the governor
instead of the police?
Because I knew
they were friends,
and I needed time to think.
To plan a cover-up.
No!
No. Look, something like this
has national repercussions.
Okay, you need
to have a viable strategy.
What time did you pick up
Serena Andrews?
9:00, 9:15?
She was right on time.
Am I under arrest?
Amy might be a
good chief of staff,
but she's a
terrible liar.
All right, the professor
was shot and now Serena
in a bathroom
stall at 9:15.
She didn't leave
the bar till 10:00.
You're right.
If I'm right, then why
isn't she under arrest?
'Cause we still have
to find the congressman,
and if he's on the run, chances
are he's gonna reach out to her.
So let's sit
on her phone,
post a surveillance
team at her door.
Exactly, and let Freed
come to us.
The thing I want to know is,
why is Amy lying?
What do you got?
That powdery substance
Max found on the body?
IR Spectroscopy identified it
as cornstarch.
Cornstarch?
Specifically, the type
used in surgical gloves.
It makes them easier
to pull on and off.
That explains...
Why we didn't find any prints
belonging to our killer.
That does not sound
like a crime of passion.
That definitely sounds like
the killing was premeditated.
So, why would
the congressman plan
on killing a prostitute
he just met?
Unless he knew her previously.
Or there's something
we're not seeing here.
Or unless he didn't do it.
So, I traced Amy Davidson's
timeline. Guess what?
Doesn't add up.
Ah, she was lying.
Very shocking.
Mm-hmm.
She said she picked up
Serena Andrews
from the Liki Tiki Lounge
at 9:15.
But when I ran her credit cards,
it turned out,
she was having drinks
at another place
called the Ocean Lounge.
By herself?
She bought two rounds.
Two drinks each time.
Who she was with?
Josh Lowry,
congressman's press secretary.
He confirmed it.
Said they were having
a strategy session.
He also confirmed
that they didn't leave
the place together.
According to a
bartender I spoke to,
she left with an
unknown male companion.
We need a positive ID
on that companion.
It's gonna be tough.
No security footage
from the bar.
I found an ATM camera
across the street.
Nice.
Only thing is,
I don't think there's
a clear shot of the exit.
Not so nice.
Okay, easy. What it
did give us was a shot
of a police cruiser
pulling someone
over near the
club entrance.
Huh. We got a dashboard cam?
Yeah, we have a dashboard cam,
and I have
footage coming through
right now.
That's Amy. Freeze,
Kono. Freeze that.
Can you push in?
Looks like she's with someone.
Wow.
It's Wo Fat. He's
still on the island.
What the hell is he doing
with Amy?
He's using Amy Davidson
to set up Congressman Freed.
Set up for what?
Think about it.
Who stands
to gain if Congressman Freed
takes a hard fall?
His opponent, Brad Powers.
Wo Fat
sees this special election
as an opening.
He's on the run,
he's got no resources.
What better way
to rebuilt your empire
than to buy a politician?
Right, by discrediting Freed,
Powers definitely gets
the Senate seat.
And Wo Fat gets a friend
in Washington.
Quid pro quo.
Not on our watch.
You need to
start writing.
Go to hell.
I expected a more
dignified response
from a congressman.
Cut me loose, and I'll show you
how dignified I can can be
when I pound the crap
out of you.
You're not
thinking this through.
Why should I sign the equivalent
of a suicide note?
That'd be the end of my career,
my life.
Even if I sign it,
you're going to kill me anyway.
A homegrown treasure like you?
A bona fide war hero?
No.
I have too much respect
for your accomplishments.
However...
my affections
don't extend to your daughter.
Where is he?
Excuse me?
Wo Fat. Where is he? We know
you left the bar with him.
Okay, you need to leave.
I don't think you understand
who you're dealing with.
No, I said, you need to leave.
Everything you've said
up to this point is a lie.
All right, the congressman
with prostitutes,
you bringing 'em
to him, all of it.
Okay, I can't talk to you guys
about this right now.
Get this through
your head, okay?
If Freed's not dead already,
Wo Fat will kill him.
You understand
what I'm saying?
You can stop this.
You can stop all of this, but
you have to start talking to us.
Where is Congressman Freed?
Where is he, Amy?
Huh?
What are you doing?
Don't shush me.
I'm sorry.
I did it because he said
he was gonna kill me.
Listen to me,
where is he keeping
the congressman hostage?
I don't know!
- Amy...
- I really don't know.
Get down. Amy, get down!
I don't see him, Steve.
Everybody, get down!
Get down! Get down! Get down!
There goes our lead
to the congressman.
What is that?
Wo Fat?
Hey, Chin,
we need a trace right away.
I'm sorry, Congressman.
Looks like there's been
a change in plans.
Geez, brah.
You scared me.
I thought you was a pig.
Think of how much easier
this could've been
if you had just
signed that letter.
Get lower to the ground!
Come on, come on.
Go closer!
Grab his leg!
Come on!
He's hit! Let's go! Come on!
How bad is it?
Bad! We need a hospital
right now! Go!
Wo Fat, Danny!
Forget it, let's go!
Forget it!
Let's go!
Come on!
♪
So, how's
the congressman?
No major organs were hit,
just soft tissue damage.
He's gonna be all right.
All right.
What about Wo Fat?
The entire department
is searching the jungle.
Got a perimeter set up,
helicopter in the air,
everything.
You find anything
in the abandoned house?
Yeah, a cell phone.
Wo Fat left it--
must've been in a rush
to chase down the congressman.
And judging
by the call log,
looks like we were right.
He was trying to buy himself
a powerful ally.
Hey!
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank
you so mu...
Nice to see you again,
Mr. Powers.
Relax.
What the hell
are you doing?
Bad taste in friends, buddy.
Bradley Powers,
you're under arrest
for conspiracy to commit murder.
♪
Would you please stop?
Please? We didn't
have a choice.
We had to let Wo Fat go.
And we are going
to find him. I promise.
Okay?
You mind if I join you guys?
Hey.
Of course, Governor.
Sit, sit.
We're not on the clock.
Oh, uh, I got to take this.
Sit down, please.
Your brand?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
What's the occasion?
Powers cracked
under questioning.
Huh.
He admitted he was in bed
with Wo Fat.
Really?
Yeah.
He almost
pulled that one off, huh?
I owe you.
No, sir.
Just doing the job.
No.
You went above and
beyond, Commander.
And...
I'm sorry.
Sir?
I should've been straight
with you from the start.
Trust-   it, um...
Well, it's a mighty big word.
Yeah, it is.
And if I may...
Of course. I'm
sitting in shorts,
drinking beer with you.
All right, fire away
and don't hold back.
I got a lot of respect
for you, sir.
Got a lot of respect
for the office.
But if this thing
between us
is gonna work out then...
honesty is the best policy.
Your predecessor, she didn't
believe in that and, uh...
well, it got her killed.
Well...
that was her.
This is me.
To Five-O.
All right.
Hey.
Uh...
You all good?
she's not moving.
Grace?
The judge
ruled in my favor--
shared custody.
She cannot leave
the island.
the island. Huh?
Huh?
Congratulations.
Thank you, buddy.
Thank you.
Hey.
Uh, the judge said
that your courtroom behavior
was completely unacceptable
Oh, come on. and despicable,
but she also said that you were
a fantastic character witness,
so thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I'll remind you of that later.
I'm sure you will.
Well done, gentlemen.
I can't believe I'm actually
happy to be staying here.
Neither can I.
To Hawaii.
To, uh...
To Hawaii. Okay. Okay.
To Hawaii.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==