(tires screech)
Five-O!
Hands up.
Hands, hands!
(people screaming)
Hands up.
On your knees.
Down on your
knees now.
Put your hands
behind your head.
Put your hands behind
your head.
Hey, look at me,
look at me.
Where's Chin Ho Kelly?
Huh? Where is he?
Did you see that, Officer?
That's assault.
I'd like to press charges.
Yeah?
What is this?
Who are you?
She was so beautiful.
What do you want?
Guy like you has nine lives.
You lost your badge.
You got it back.
Then you break the law
multiple times
and you get away with it.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
(grunts)
(yells)
(Hawaii Five-O
theme song plays)
♪ Hawaii Five-O 3x13 ♪
Olelo Ho'Opa'I Make (Death Sentence)
Original Air Date on January 20, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
Man, it feels like
I haven't seen you in ages.
Just five days.
Not that I've
been counting.
You know, I'm sorry.
It's just, uh, you know,
getting Michael
(laughing):
What?
You... you just
keep apologizing
for something that I don't
have a problem with.
I think it's great that
Michael's back in your life.
Don't you?
Yeah, of course.
But it's...
it's complicated.
Before Michael
went to prison,
I was away at
law school, and...
you know, he was going to run
our father's business.
Now that we're taking things
in a new direction...
Michael's a little out
of his comfort zone.
I think he's really lucky
to have you as
his big brother.
(exhales) It's the best influence
he could have right now.
♪
(phone ringing)
Ah, come on...
That is the third
call in a row.
Yeah, I should
probably get that.
(ringing continues)
Listen...
Really? Hmm?
Don't go anywhere.
(ringing continues)
You better hurry.
(laughs)
ADAM: Hey, I told you not to call me
at this number.
♪
I won't do such a thing.
(thunder rumbles, rain falling)
We didn't agree to this.
Where are you?
I'll meet you in 20.
Everything all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's just...
business.
Listen, uh...
I'm sorry.
What?
Rain check?
(inhales)
(long exhale)
Sure.
(laughs)
(whispers): Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Okay? I'll make
it up to you.
I promise, okay?
♪
KAMEKONA: Trust me, bruddahs, this is
gonna take your taste buds
to a whole new level.
All right.
I think this
is the next big thing.
DANNY:
Wow!
A burrito.
You know, I'm pretty sure
that's already a big thing.
Not like this one--
I'm calling it
Kamekona's Sunrise
Fusion Shrimp Breakfast Burrito.
It's got
eggs, it's got cheddar...
pineapple salsa,
shrimp,
and a very secret
special ingredient.
Spam.
Oh, oh, no, no, no, no. No, no.
How did I sign up for this?
What happened?
Why do you got to be
such a baby?
Try something new.
Expand your horizons.
My horizons are
expanded plenty.
I just do not do
the Hawaiian mystery meat--
you know this.
Yeah, first of all,
it doesn't come from Hawaii.
Oh, no?
No. That's right, it doesn't.
G.I.'s brought it over
in World War II
because it was cheap, portable
and did not require
refrigeration.
And it goes down smooth,
thanks to the glaze.
(muffled grunt)
What you think?
That's interesting.
Okay, I will
have a nice,
uh, old-fashioned
breakfast burrito
with eggs and bacon.
Oh, no, no, no.
No substitutions, no changes.
A true chef
never, never
compromises
his culinary vision.
Ah.
Hey, guys.
DANNY: Wow!
Look at that.
Bringing back the '80s
with the Rollerblades.
You got those Duran Duran
cassette tapes
you can lend her?
Got 'em.
Yeah, you know, good for
a workout, keeping in shape.
But I am "Hungry Like a Wolf."
Wow.
That was good.
That was funny.
Um, you missed
the tasting, luckily.
Oh, that bad?
DANNY: That's one way
to describe it.
Glad I'm late.
Hey, where's Chin?
Oh, he texted me
late last night.
He, uh, said he
was gonna take
a few days off,
go up to North Shore.
DANNY:
Since when does Chin
go on vacation?
I don't know.
He's, uh...
he's not on vacation.
I can't believe
I didn't remember this.
What? Remember what?
He and Malia's first date
was eight years ago
up on the North Shore.
And today's the anniversary.
(sighs)
All right.
Look, if Chin wants some space,
we'll give him some space.
Yep.
(distant voices,
objects clattering)
♪
(indistinct voices)
(MAN over P.A.): Attention on cell block,
watch the gates.
Gates are opening.
MAN:  Time for chow!
Line up and shut up!
♪
(indistinct chatter)
MAN: Step out, inmates.
It's chow time.
Let's go.
Hands by your side.
Everybody step out.
(grunts)
Look who's in lockup.
Same cop who threw me in here.
(grunting)
Inmate, slow down!
On the ground now!
I need your help.
My name is Chin Ho Kelly.
I'm with Five-O.
I said on the ground.
I'm trying to tell you,
I'm a cop. Something's wrong.
Somebody put me
in here last night.
I am not a prisoner.
Come with me.
Hey, Charlie.
You have any luck
tracing that number
I called you about?
Can't say I did.
I traced it,
but the call came from a burner.
Okay. I was afraid of that.
You didn't have me run
that number for a case, did you?
Look... I came to you
because we're friends,
'cause I trust you.
I'm gonna need your help
cloning that phone.
It's a mobile data extractor.
It has a built-in
SIM card reader
and creates a cloned phone.
Sure you want to do this?
Look, I know you weren't in
this cell block last night,
but how the hell did
someone sneak you in?
I don't know.
Two guys drugged me.
Next thing I know,
I wake up in here.
Food service truck
makes night deliveries.
That's the only way you
could've gotten in here.
Tell me about the
two guys. Who are they?
I don't know.
Just get me to Warden Grier,
and I'll prove I'm a cop.
Well, if you are, Halawa's
the last place you want to be.
Cops that serve time in here
don't do too well.
It's okay. It's a shortcut.
It's empty.
Inmates are at first meal.
Come on.
What are you doing?!
Open the door!
(man whistles)
Lieutenant Kelly.
Kaleo.
Warrick told me
an old friend was
sending me a surprise.
Didn't expect it to be one of
the dirty cops who locked me up.
You're the dirty cop.
Good men died because of you.
You belong here.
I don't.
Well, you're here now.
Who put me in here?
Somebody who wants you
to suffer before you die.
(grunting)
(screams)
(screaming)
(groaning)
You must have been
a bad boy to end up
in here, Lieutenant.
I didn't...
I didn't do anything.
Yeah, that's what we all say.
I heard what
you told Kaleo.
Sounds like whoever
locked you up
is looking
to even the score.
Probably somebody
you put away.
I've been a cop a long time.
I put a lot of people away.
But I'm betting... Warrick
knows who's behind this.
Hey.
Lieutenant, whoever put you
in here doesn't matter.
All that matters is,
we got to get you out.
And why should I trust you?
How about 'cause I just saved
your sorry ass from Kaleo?
Also, Five-O
brought me
to this island and put me up
in this classy joint
so I could be
closer to my kid.
I owe you.
Oh, and there's,
uh, one more thing.
Why the hell
did you do that?
The first time we met,
you hit me across the
face with an ashtray.
Now that we're even,
you can trust me.
We good?
We're good.
Warrick runs
Max Security.
His keys only
work in A-Block.
Yeah?
I got to get word to a guard
outside this cell block,
let him know I'm a cop.
Seriously? 'Cause that worked
out so well for you last time.
Look, you don't know
which guards were paid off--
not a good plan.
We keep moving this way.
All right,
what's your plan?
Take the guards
out of the equation.
How you gonna do that?
Bring help
from the outside in.
Look, what we got to do
is find a phone and get
a call out to McGarrett.
There's cons, guards
and cameras everywhere.
You won't reach a phone.
Besides,
you're running out of time.
They'll be back
from chow any minute.
Starting a fire
is not going to work.
That's the problem
with cops-- too analytical.
You got to think
outside the box.
Halawa is not equipped
to deal with fires
if they're big enough.
They'll have to call HFD
to fight the blaze,
and when the first
responders come in,
you tell them you're Five-O.
Look, Lieutenant, you have
a better idea, speak up,
but the way I see it,
right now, this is
the only choice
you got.
So bust a move, huh?
♪
So, what, after I'm gone,
you're just
going to go back
to sitting in a cell?
Come on, brah.
I know you work
the angle.
Why you really helping me?
Okay, truth.
Five-O's got the governor's ear.
I figure, I help you,
maybe I'm out in six months
instead of six years.
Snitches don't last long in Max.
You know that.
I got to get out of here.
Time to send up
a smoke signal, huh?
Ah!
That's smooth, baby.
(alarm blaring)
Hear that?
That's the sound
of freedom.
Hey.
What's going on?
Uh, Steve, this is
Dr. Harriet Palmer.
She's the HPD
grief counselor.
She's here about Chin.
Hi.
Commander McGarrett,
I feel terrible coming here.
I have never betrayed
my patient's confidence before,
but I'm worried about Chin Ho.
Um, Chin's your patient?
For the past few months.
I had no idea
he was seeing
a therapist.
He didn't want you to see his
grief as a sign of weakness.
(sighs)
What can we do to help?
That's the thing--
she's, uh...
she's concerned 'cause Chin had
an appointment today
and he didn't show up.
Well, Chin's on
the North Shore.
But he called me last night
to confirm his session.
I've been trying to reach him,
but he hasn't answered
or returned
my calls.
Hey, Chin's not
on the North Shore.
I just called the hotel
that he usually stays at,
and he never checked in,
so I PING'd
his cell,
and it's at his house.
Hey, Chin, buddy, you here?
KONO:
Chin... Chin.
Hey, he didn't go
to the North Shore.
His bike and his car
are both still in the garage.
Bed's unmade.
Chin stayed here
last night.
Steve... Chin
wouldn't leave
anywhere
without his cell.
DANNY:
Hey, over here!
All right, back door was open.
Someone jimmied the lock,
let themselves in.
I'm thinking
Chin was asleep, two
intruders come in.
One of them uses that towel
to muffle the beeping keypad,
other guy comes over here,
disconnects the alarm.
And cuts the phone line
so the alarm company
never gets the call.
These guys were pros.
Okay, they also left
his keys and his wallet.
This wasn't a robbery.
No, it wasn't a robbery.
They didn't want money;
they wanted Chin.
All right, back door
was opened at 10:43.
Chin texted me
at 12:15.
No, Chin didn't
send you anything.
It was the kidnappers who
obviously sent that text.
Okay, I'll call CSU, get 'em
down here, process this place,
and I'll see if Fong can lift
a print off Chin's cell.
STEVE:
All right.
Okay,
who would do this,
and why send a text?
I'll tell you why.
They knew, as soon as Chin
didn't show up for work,
we would go looking for him,
all right?
They're trying to hold us off,
buy some time.
Time for what?
Everyone out. Let's go.
This is not a drill.
Move it, move it, move it.
Go! Let's go!
Move, move, move.
♪
(siren wailing in distance)
That's HFD.
It's working.
Like I said, sometimes you got
to think outside the box.
(siren continues)
KALEO:
Where is he?
MAN: Come on,
let's move it.
Let's go.
Pick it up.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, no inmates allowed back
inside till we get all clear.
Now, back off.
(grunts)
(prisoners shouting)
♪
So much for your
smoke signals.
We got to get out of here.
Only door
out of here
is through them.
Kaleo! Kaleo!
Bring it down!
♪
(prisoners shouting)
Hold back HFD.
Lock Max Security down now!
I repeat, lock it down!
Listen up.
This is Kaleo.
We got a cop in here.
Locked a lot of you up.
Name's Chin Ho Kelly.
Find him.
Bring him to me.
Charlie, what did you find?
Whoever used Chin's
phone knew enough
to wipe their fingerprints,
so I swabbed the
display for trace DNA.
You got something?
Yeah.
It didn't make sense.
According to CODIS,
the DNA found
on Chin's cell phone
belongs to...
Frank Delano?
It's impossible.
He-he's dead.
Chin killed him.
FONG:
I know. That's why
I amplified the sample
and I'm running it
through CODIS again.
My guess is,
there's a familial match.
(computer trills, beeps)
Got a hit.
Paul Delano?
FONG:
DOB makes him
the older brother.
DANNY: Wait a minute.
Kidnapping Chin has got to be
payback for Frank's death.
Charlie, do you mind?
(keyboard keys clicking)
According to the TSA,
Paul arrived on the island
three days ago.
(keyboard keys clicking,
computer trilling)
And there's no record
of him leaving.
Good, good. We'll put him
on the no-fly list,
get HPD on the hunt.
All right.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey,
listen to me.
Chin's a tough guy, all right?
He's gonna be okay.
We do our job, we find
Paul Delano, we find Chin.
Come on.
Okay.
There it is.
(alarm sounds,
distant shouting)
I told you, those keys
won't get us out of A-Block.
Damn! Damn it!
(P.A. system hums)
KALEO:
I know you're out there, Kelly.
You can run,
but you can't hide.
Why don't you do yourself
a favor
and come to me?
I'm gonna find you...
sooner or later.
There's got to be another phone
in this cellblock.
There is-- in the
security office with Kaleo.
(sighs)
Prisoner holding.
There's a public phone.
It's back the way we came.
There's 200 cons
between us and that phone.
You have a price on your head.
They want me, not you.
You got a son
to think about, remember?
I'll go it alone.
(keys jingle)
Look, hey,
there's no cameras in here.
We can lay low.
Those are bad guys out there.
They will kill you.
Bad guys like those
killed my wife.
I'm gonna get
out of here,
or die trying.
(footsteps running)
(alarm blares in distance)
STEVE: Catherine, somebody's
taken Chin.
Oh, my God.
Can you access
Homeland Security's
video surveillance program?
Yeah, whatever you need.
I need you to monitor
closed-circuit video feeds
from all over the island.
And who am I looking for?
Paul Delano.
What? As in...?
STEVE: Yeah.
I'm sending you his photo now.
Run it through Facial Rec,
let me know
when you get eyes on him.
Roger that.
There's a staircase
off that corridor.
It takes us to holding.
That's where the phone is.
MAN:
Over here!
There's someone
in there.
No time to be a hero.
(woman screaming)
WOMAN:
You can't be in here!
Let go of me!
MAN: Open it!
You hear me?
I'm not going to ask you again!
(gasps)
Open it.
I... I can't.
(gasps)
I don't have the key.
Where is it?
(gasps)
(yelling)
(grunting)
Are you all right?
It's okay.
I'm a cop.
(panting)
You're the one
they're looking for.
Yeah.
Leilani.
I'm Chin Ho Kelly.
There's a phone in
holding, so, we can...
we can call for
help in there.
That's where we're heading, but
we got to go right away, okay?
Okay.
(prisoners shouting)
Too late, kids.
Holding's not an option.
Kaleo's guys are all over it.
I've got a master key.
(keys jangling)
Get me to C-Block,
and I'll get us out.
Okay.
Let's go.
CATHERINE:
I got a hit. I found Delano.
Are you sure it's him?
It's him.
Facial Rec confirmed it.
He's on his way out
of the Ilikai Hotel right now.
That's two blocks
from here.
(tires squealing)
(siren blaring)
That's him.
Get your hands up.
Five-O.
Look at me.
Where's Chin Ho Kelly?
You see that, Officer?
That's assault.
I'd like to press charges.
You do that.
There's a number here
you've been calling a lot.
Why don't we call 'em, see
if they know where Chin is?
(phone ringing)
Delano, can't talk right now.
We're in lockdown.
But it's done.
Kaleo will take care of Kelly.
Chin's in Halawa Prison.
This way.
(distant shouting)
That's C-Block there.
They're getting closer.
CHIN:
All right.
Go get the door open.
We'll try and
hold 'em off.
Come on.
(gasps)
Good to see you
again, Lieutenant.
Come on, let's go.
(Leilani gasps, groans)
LEILANI:
No!
(whistles)
I found him.
The cop's down here.
(grunts)
What are you doing?
It's about survival.
If Kaleo finds out
I've been helping you,
we're both dead.
I knew I couldn't trust you.
(grunting,
loud, distant shouting)
Back off! Back off!
Bring him to Kaleo alive.
Go! Go!
(engine revving,
tires squealing)
(siren whoops)
Yo.
MAN: Steve.
How bad is it?
The inmates have taken control
of the Maximum Security.
Whole place is still
on lockdown.
Warden's not
letting anyone in.
Did you find Chin yet?
Surveillance tapes
from earlier today
prove he's inside.
We just can't get a lock where.
Warden Grier.
Warden Grier, one of
my men is inside.
I just found out, Commander.
We're doing everything we can,
but I have a riot on my hands,
and I have a protocol.
You have a protocol?
Where was your protocol
when Lieutenant Kelly
was locked in your prison?
Guards under
your supervision
conspired to do this.
This happened on your watch.
What's your plan of action
to get my man out of there?
A dozen of my men
are unaccounted for.
Some injured,
some worse.
I won't risk
any more lives.
Lieutenant Kelly's
on his own.
We're going in now.
(tires squealing)
Got my bird all warmed
up for you, sistah.
Why's SWAT not taking
care of business?
They got a whole flock
of choppers ready to go.
'Cause the warden won't let
anything up in the air
over Halawa
till he gives the go-ahead.
And we're not waiting
for permission.
Hey, I got 62 more
payments on this girl.
Be gentle, please!
You may want to step back.
(prisoners shouting)
You and me-- we've
had our issues.
But bringing you this cop means
we're all good, you feel me?
Sure. I feel you.
Lieutenant.
Glad we'll be able
to finish what we started.
(groans)
(men shouting)
Things are different,
little more painful,
when you can't hide
behind the badge and gun.
(grunts)
You're not better
than us.
You're one of us.
You belong here.
You turned on other cops,
locked me up.
I only survived
because of one man--
Frank Delano.
The man you killed.
Delano...
murdered my wife.
He would've
killed my cousin
and me, too,
if he had the chance.
His brother...
don't see it that way.
He put me in here.
And now you die.
Kaleo!
You're making
a mistake.
Why do you care
what happens to him?
I don't.
I care what happens to me.
You know this guy
ain't just some cop.
He's Five-O.
Sure, you kill him,
you get a few seconds
of satisfaction--
but this man's your leverage.
You keep him alive
a little while longer...
...you just might buy yourself
a ticket out of here.
(indistinct chatter)
(groans)
Call them, Kaleo.
Call Five-O.
Find out what
they're willing
to trade for him.
On second thought...
why would I trust a snitch
who gave me up to Five-O?
(punch strikes)
(grunts)
(excited chatter)
Put him in a cell.
I'll deal with him later.
(men clamoring)
♪
Throw!
(guns firing)
(grunting)
(men clamoring)
(explosions)
(explosion)
There's Chin!
(yells)
(strained grunting)
(grunting)
Chin.
Let's get out of here.
Not yet.
Hey, where you going?
Follow me.
This way.
CHIN HO:
Leilani!
LEILANI:
Chin! Chin!
(panting)
These are my friends.
They're gonna
get us out of here.
Follow me.
All right.
Okay, can we go now, please?
One more.
This way.
These are the guys
who took Sang Min.
Well, where the hell is he?
He's right here.
He's gone.
♪
I need a trauma team on standby.
KONO: I'm bringing Lieutenant Kelly in
by helicopter.
♪
KAMEKONA: I was wasting my time
asking these amateurs.
But I know my bruddah
Chin, he gonna...
he gonna let me
know the truth.
What you think?
(Chin chuckles)
Oh...
(quiet gulp)
Uh...
the breakfast burrito's a...
it's a tough nut to crack, brah.
Um...
maybe you stick
with plate lunches
for a little while, yeah?
You know?
I think that's a...
fantastic
idea.
What do you guys know?
You guys just don't
appreciate culinary genius.
(laughter)
(knocking)
Sorry.
Hope I'm not interrupting.
No. No, of course not.
Come in. Please.
Hi. How you feeling?
Uh... better.
Thanks.
KAMEKONA: Let me ask you
something, sistah.
Do you like spam?
I grew up
on the stuff.
You ever do any
food presentation modeling?
I could use
a pretty spokeswoman.
(laughs)
Uh, no, thank you.
I already have a job.
But, um, thanks
for the kind offer.
Let me know.
Okay, well, I think
we should all get going.
Give our jailbird some rest.
(chuckles)
Okay.
But before you
guys go, uh...
just know that I wouldn't
be here without you guys.
Mahalo.
We're 'ohana, brah.
KONO:
Love you, cuz.
Get some sleep.
Yeah, take care, brah.
Hey, anything you need, brah.
You got my back, right?
That's right.
So, I didn't just come by
to check up on you.
Mmm?
I wanted...
to thank you for saving my life.
Oh. Well, you're welcome.
(chuckles)
Thank you.
A nail file?
Yes, well, I figured, you know,
you didn't have one;
otherwise,
you would have used it.
(laughs)
That's good.
Thank you.
♪
ADAM:
Hey, how's Chin doing?
Doctor said he's tough.
He should be out of the
hospital in a couple of days.
Oh, that's great news.
Yeah.
(sighs)
What about you?
Are you okay?
Hey, I want some wine.
Yeah, that'd be nice.
Okay?
Yeah.
(sighs quietly)
(glasses clink)
ADAM: Hey, you feeling
white or red tonight?
Um...
you know... maybe...
maybe red.
(cork pops)
(quietly):
Come on.
Here you go.
Nice.
(clears throat softly)
To us.
♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==