Previously on Bunheads...
I think I forgot to finish high school.
I'm a dropout. Not even a dropout...
dropping out implies action.
I just... didn't finish.
My dad and Faye Mendelson
set the wedding location.
- Fun.
- It's the same place he married my mom.
No way.
The day I lost my husband
was the worst day of my life.
Of course I lost him to the divorcee
in the jeggings across the street.
- So what's up with Charlie?
- What do you mean?
What did he do to make her dump him?
Nothing. He was totally smitten.
( Gasps )
Here's to being dumb.
I have a masters in oceanography.
So they let high school dropouts get PHDs?
I didn't say I was a high school dropout.
I'm guessing that you and
me tonight, we're not...
No. Not tonight.
What did you say to him?
Maybe you can un-say it.
- In a better outfit.
- Did he say something bad to you?
Saw your moves.
Bartender, the girl.
I think you might dig it.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Stop.
Everyone, just stop.
You just killed Baryshnikov.
( Exhales )
Well, would you mind
showing us the combination
again, Jordan?
Oh, sure.
What have I got but loads of time
and sincere enthusiasm
to show you the same freaking thing
over and over again?
Move.
Do that.
They kill Baryshnikov again?
Yep.
I just need to do something
on the computer here.
I'll be super quick. Quiet as a mouse.
( Computer dings )
From now on, Jordan, sir.
Let's try it again, everyone.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Sharper, Ray-Ray.
Cleaner, Ginny. Cleaner.
Be smaller, Boo.
- Smaller?
- Don't talk back.
Matisse, stop. Stop!
Focus, okay.
Without focus, your life
is gonna be jumping
from alcoholic boyfriend to another.
Is that what you want?
I don't think so.
Hey, Jordan, let's take five here.
They look like they need a break.
When don't they? Take five.
Jordan, your group is wilting here.
And the kids in the corner,
what's up with them?
They wanted to stretch before class.
I mean, come on.
"Be smaller."
What a jerk.
I hate him so much.
Me too.
But I'm also in love with him.
- But not anymore.
- Same here.
He's so insane today.
He hasn't even noticed
- that Melanie isn't here.
- Why isn't she here?
He's looking.
- They're being babied around.
- Absolutely not.
You're not challenging them enough.
You can see it in their dancing,
their barre work, their legs,
- their posture.
- Jordan.
Everything they do, it's not correct.
We're talking a break.
We're not doing anything wrong.
Bastard's gotten into my head.
Sasha's AWOL too, by the way.
Well, I know where she is.
Apartment hunting, and she found one.
- Really?
- In that building her aunt owns.
- She moves in next week.
- Who's she living with?
No one. It's just her.
Her own apartment?
I used to dream about
getting married to Jordan
and living in our own apartment.
Kissing him on the cheek
when he comes home,
and making dinner for him every night.
- But not anymore.
- Same here.
He's been a jerk forever, Matisse.
Are you just catching up?
( Phone ringing )
Boo, that's your phone.
- Michelle: Let's not get into my background.
- Jordan: None of them are me.
They don't want to be you.
Who wouldn't want to be me?
Mom, hey, I'm at class so make it quick.
The TV fell over?
Did it fall on anyone?
How can you not be sure?
Better not let him see you.
I know you can do that.
I know you can do it.
Please stop doing that!
So just Lonnie is missing?
Well, do you see any parts of Lonnie
sticking out from under the TV?
Yeah, I'll wait.
Uh, Boo?
So he's there. Good.
Good. This is good.
( Mouths words )
Boo.
Were you talking on your phone?
No.
( Yelling, thumping )
Wait, what is that? Is that screaming?
It's Grant and Dominik.
They're locked in the dressing room.
- Why?
- They know why.
( Sighs )
I'll be right back.
Gather around. Next step.
Do that.
( Sighs )
( Theme music playing )
Bunheads 1x14 - The Astronaut and the Ballerina
Original air date January 28, 2013
Sync and corrections by atrn97g
for www.addic7ed.com
( Whistle blows )
Go!
Pick up your feet. Go go go go.
Bend those knees.
It's not ballet class, come on! Let's go.
Keep the line in the middle.
I don't want us straggling in the front.
Keep it going.
Go go go!
All right, pick up your feet.
Come on, low. Derby stance.
Nice feet, Lolita.
Come on.
( Whistle blows )
All right.
You've been watching for two days,
you want to give it a shot?
( Grunting )
Sure.
- You're late.
- So is everyone else.
They called. You didn't.
I was at ballet. Michelle kept us over.
Then I'll complain to Michelle.
She didn't do anything wrong,
so don't call her.
Here. Something to entertain
you until they come.
- Dad...
- Don't say it's too early.
I totally is.
I'm barely into my junior year.
We know people who planned
their kids' college
- at kindergarten.
- That's a sickness.
You're supposed to leave your keys.
I parked my own car.
After running it through the valet area.
Is that why all those Chinese guys
were staring at me?
- Hey, Claire.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Ginny.
- Hi, Mr. Segal.
Where's Alice?
She's down for the count.
She's got this awful cold.
Mom has a cold?
Can I get you something to drink, Claire?
I'd love a drink.
Can you do a gay marine?
You just muddle some mint
leaves and some lime
with cane sugar and orange liqueur
and then you add some ice and some rum
and you top it all with apple juice.
It's a Chinese restaurant, mom.
They don't do gay marines.
White wine is okay, I guess.
I'll have whatever you have on tap.
White wine is actually great.
You're in a chipper mood, Claire.
I am.
Because...
I am not gonna let it get me down.
Let what get you down?
Here we go.
Hello, Ginny's father
is marrying Faye Mendelson
in less than a week.
Yeah, we're going.
You are?
If that's okay?
Oh, of course it is.
I want you to go, Dougie,
really I do.
So how's the real-estate business
treating you these days, Claire?
- I hear it's, you know...
- Have you seen...
That insane wedding blog that they have?
- No, not me.
- Yes, I have. Many times.
Faye Mendelson is chronicling
their whole stupid life
on this blog
with photographs and diary entries.
Gil is surfing now
and the man is 45.
He's starting to surf.
He likes it, mom.
And all those photos of Faye
cuddling her dog like that,
it's just bestial. Call the SPCA.
( Chuckles )
What's so funny?
Nothing. I guess.
Mom. You're being busted
by the valet police.
Bring 'em on.
Come on, Claire.
Let's go give them your keys
before this becomes
an international incident.
All right.
You're really going
to the wedding, Dougie?
I mean, I know you knew him first,
but he's changed so much.
- Wow.
- She's on that blog night and day
commenting anonymously.
The website blocks dirty words,
or there would be some saucy things
written about those dogs. Believe me.
Oh, check this out.
What is that? A box?
That's my bridesmaid dress.
- This has got to be a mistake.
- It's not.
It's a giant rectangle, why?
Because every time I go to
my dad and Faye's place,
Faye stares at my boobs.
She told my dad that they remind her
of my mom's boobs and she
doesn't want to be reminded
of my mom's boobs at the wedding.
So she's forcing me to wear a dress
shaped like a shower curtain.
Cruel and unusual.
( Sighs )
I don't want to look at it anymore.
So where have you been?
What do you mean?
I mean where have you been?
I never see you anymore.
I see you every day at school.
You're skipping ballet.
You don't answer my texts.
Dad's got me touring colleges.
- Really?
- We just got back from driving around
U.C. Santa Barbara.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Okay, well at least answer my texts.
Some of them are even important.
I will. I promise.
Here.
While you have a shot.
Good thinking.
( Laughing )
Of all the gin joints in all the towns
in all the world,
she has to walk into mine.
"Casablanca."
I know "Casablanca".
- Okay.
- I've seen "Casablanca."
I can spell Casablanca.
I've been to Casablanca.
I was just trying to be cute.
I thought "hey there" would be boring
so I thought I'd throw in a...
never mind. Starting again.
- Hey there.
- Hey.
- For me?
- Yep.
- Guilt gift?
I like the wrapping paper.
It's my 2004 tax return.
Nice.
"Finding Nemo."
See? It's the perfect thing for us
'cause you're an expert on the ocean,
and I like talking fish.
Very nice. Thank you.
Sorry for what I said.
No worries.
I talk, therefore I am.
Not always a bad thing.
Can I buy you a drink?
Yes, you can.
Something with bourbon and an umbrella.
( Laughing )
What are they celebrating?
Tuesday.
My favorite holiday.
- So guess what I did?
- Safer not to.
I went online and read your thesis.
- You're kidding.
- No.
( Chuckles )
I'm impressed.
Well, don't be. I only understood
about 1/10 of it. Plankton.
I got that. And your name.
And I think you mentioned orca
and I did see that movie.
That's probably less than 1/10, right?
Did I mention I didn't finish high school?
Points for trying.
Guess that alcohol buzz
is starting to wear off.
Yep. Now they all get tired.
And the one on the diet
eats every cold French fry
she can find.
They'll probably leave soon.
And then you'll be all alone.
Might as well just close.
With the whole night ahead of you?
How will you fill the time?
And then I got into this whole thing
with the lady I was understudying
'cause I started dating her husband.
They were separated... well,
he said they were separated,
but I should have known
something was weird
when he never let me
come over to his house.
I had to go to the corner
of Sixth and 53rd
and get in line at this halal cart
and I wasn't supposed to move
till he showed up and
dropped a note in my purse
telling me which hotel to meet him at.
And since I didn't have
a phone number for him,
if he was late, I just ordered,
and if he still didn't show I had to eat
'cause otherwise I'm weird. Whatever.
The point is she finally found out,
got mad and then never missed a show
so I never got to go on.
Plus I smelled like garlic
sauce the entire run.
That is not a true story.
Okay, fine, you're right.
It was a Mr. Softee truck.
( Chuckles )
Scotty?
You have flower pots?
Who gave you flower pots?
What are you doing here?
You kill flower pots.
The flowers and the pots. You walk by
and they fling themselves off windowsills.
I can't believe this.
Are you a lounge singer now?
Long stories to have beer by.
Wow, I just...
Oh, sorry. This is my brother Scotty.
Scotty, this is Godot.
Well, hello, young man.
I'm so glad to see you.
Come in, come in.
Oh boy, I...
It's okay. Another night.
It's good to meet you.
You too.
Seriously? Even Mrs. Robinson's
giving you a weird look right now.
I thought you were in Madison.
Well, a funny thing happened
on the way to Madison.
So... Madison.
Right. So I was on my way to Madison
and I stopped at this diner
and there was a hostess.
Not even a waitress?
A hostess is a step up from a waitress.
No.
You're a waitress first
and then a hostess.
- It's a promotion.
- Not at all.
Well, she was a redhead
so one thing led to another.
Oh no. You got married again?
- Never made it out of Tupelo.
- Scotty! - I know, I know.
How many marriages does this make?
- Four?
- You're asking me?
No, four. This makes four.
Oh my God.
But you know, she was different.
- How?
- She spoke very little English.
Perfect.
But she had these eyes that were epic.
I felt if I could just
stare in this woman's eyes
for the rest of my life,
I would be a very happy man.
So what happened? Ooh, cake.
Well, the first month was great.
And then we started fighting,
and then we got engaged,
then we fought some more,
and then I found out she wore
colored contact lenses.
That's when I realized, big mistake.
What else was there to think?
Next thing I know,
it's the day of the wedding
I'm standing at the altar in my rented tux
and she's hurtling down the aisle
like a giant crinoline comet,
and I'm thinking to myself,
"I have got to get out of this."
- So you bolted.
- Yeah.
- When?
- Right after "YMCA."
Well, you don't want to miss that.
So I wrote her a note,
I grabbed you some cake,
and I exited stage left.
Can I give you a piece of advice?
Sure.
If you keep getting engaged
to perfect strangers
and then bailing on the wedding night,
you have to buy a tux.
I keep marrying the wrong girl.
You keep marrying mom.
Well, that's not too
disturbing of a statement.
Well, if the creepy
psychological profile fits.
You mind if I crash here for a few days?
Couch is all yours.
Thanks.
Well, so, this is the new pad.
It's not what I pictured at all.
No? What'd you picture?
Something less decorated
and without a roof.
You're hilarious.
How long do you plan to be here?
Why, you gonna have your mail forwarded?
Just asking.
How attached are you to your toothbrush?
There's an extra one under the sink.
I don't know what problem
you had with this girl,
but boy, could she pick a cake.
I know. I can't imagine what
that must have felt like.
Hey, I grew up with him.
No one knows how flaky
he is better than me.
Hey, what'd you do to the coffee guy?
He hates your guts.
Yes, absolutely. Send it all C.O.D.
Toss it in a box,
tape it up and ship it off.
Throw some bricks in
'cause they charge by weight.
What are you doing?
Getting your stuff.
Oh good.
Oh, I'd rip that letter up.
I mean, seriously, it's not even
remotely heartfelt or poetic.
And it just makes him seem way
smarter than he is, trust me.
Hey, get my purple sweater back.
Hold on a second, Mandy.
- You have a purple sweater?
- It's a very nice purple.
Does Mandy know you're gay?
- Michelle.
- It might make her feel better.
Just get the sweater.
Mandy, there's a purple sweater?
Oh really?
She says it's hers.
It is not hers.
- I believe her.
- Great.
Oh no no. I'm here. I'm here.
I'm not going anywhere, Mandy.
I'm not my brother.
I'm gonna check out the rest of the town.
What stores have you not alienated yet?
No, how bad was the sex, Mandy?
- Oh, come on.
- She hung up a minute ago.
Oh, thank God.
- A purple sweater?
- It's more like lavender.
So not better.
All right, everyone. Places at the barre.
Port de bras.
One. Open, two.
And demi plie.
And stretch.
I'm here.
Keep moving, boys. Keep moving.
I'm so sorry. So so sorry.
I am just gonna set them up here.
Over here, guys.
Oh, what's this?
Beaver.
Beaver. Beaver.
His name's Beaver?
Beaver.
What did I say about ignoring me?
Beaver: You're not my mom.
Boo: Okay, but right now I am your mom.
Okay? Now come on.
- His name's Beaver?
- Sorry, guys.
Hugely embarrassed. So so sorry.
Where are the Legos?
- They're in the bag.
- This isn't all of them.
- I want to make a castle.
- Well, make a condo. That's fun too.
His name's Beaver?
Yes, the kid's name is Beaver.
- Deal.
- Boo.
I'm sorry.
Carl was supposed to
take them off my hands,
but then he got held up at work
and it was either skip ballet
- or bring them here.
- Okay, this is a one time thing, right?
A one time thing. I promise.
And Carl will be here
any minute to take them.
Alright, everyone. Let's continue.
Demi plie.
And stretch.
And demi plie.
( Laughing )
Chris, nose!
- What? What happened? - I want
that out of your nose right now, young man.
You do not know whose nose that's been in.
I'm sorry.
And demi plie.
And stretch.
And demi plie
Ooh, purple. Beaver
your hand is down your pants again.
Nobody wants to see that.
Sorry.
I am so sorry if you guys saw that.
I am so, so sorry.
And demi plie.
And stretch.
I got them.
( Groaning )
I got them, Michelle.
Okay, guys?
Get in the car.
We're going back to the house.
- Aw, I like it here.
- So do I,
but we're in the way.
So we're going to the car now.
- No!
- Okay, guys.
Listen, if you get in my car,
I'll give you candy.
Stranger danger!
He's not a stranger, Beaver.
He's your uncle Carl.
Now get in the car.
Come on.
( Moans )
Don't touch me.
( Door closes )
Okay, people, let's get this class
moving again. Come on.
You heard the woman.
And demi plie.
And stretch.
And grand plie.
- Eat, mommy.
- But I'm off Vicky.
(Folk music playing)
I wanted Asian food.
Everything's getting cold.
- And sticky.
- Chris, stop playing with your spoon.
I'm still sticky.
What is this and how did
it get all over me?
It's what our lives are now, Carl.
We're sticky and we're tired.
Adjust.
Those two have kids?
There's nothing else to
do in this town. Come on.
Greetings, señorita.
- He's talking to me.
- I guessed as much.
Hi there. Nice T-shirt.
It's my Sunday best.
It's good to see you again, man.
You too. Man.
We'll have... what do you think?
Tequila shots?
It's Christmas morning all over again.
He gets younger every time I see him.
He gets hotter every time I see him.
You disgust me with your carnal ways.
Okay, help me find wife number four.
- Five.
- Whatever.
How about blonde pixie-cut behind me?
- No.
- Why?
- She's my manicurist.
- So?
So if something goes wrong, I'll
have to find another manicurist.
Or a town with more than one manicurist.
Okay, back table,
brunette with the bangs.
- Nyet.
- Why?
- She's with a guy.
- I don't care.
She's the mother of one of my students.
Fine.
Red beret and leggings?
- Bible study teacher.
- Moving on.
Ponytail by the planter?
Bagel chip girl at the farmers' market.
Fat broad by the window?
She works with Truly, and you can't
sleep with Truly either.
- Why not?
- 'Cause she's just weird.
Look, if you're gonna block
all my action tonight,
I say you can't sleep
with Junior over there.
He's the only bartender I know in town.
If something happens, I won't
be able to get a drink.
Well, I'm not sleeping with him now,
- so ha.
- Good.
Why good?
Well, he's not your type.
He seems kind of dumb.
He's not dumb. I'll have you know
he's an oceanographer.
You're kidding. That's a thing?
It's a thing.
Wow, okay.
To oceanography then.
Hear hear.
Both: Ahh.
Mm.
You are now and will always be
my favorite drinking buddy.
It's good to see you too.
Keep them coming, son.
Tonight, we settle all family business.
And we get to get really really drunk.
Hey, did we pay?
- Mmm.
- I don't remember if we paid.
You can pay him tomorrow.
In kisses.
Sweet, gentle, little oceanography kisses.
I hate running out on a check
when I didn't intend to.
What?
( Gasps )
My ukulele.
You found it.
Mm.
Oh.
( Strums )
It sounds the same.
- Terrible.
- Yeah. The same.
Oh man.
This is the only good
gift mom ever got me.
The only one I ever wanted.
Do you remember
that ancient console record player we had
when we were growing up?
The needle was big and sharp
like a nail.
And the speaker grills smelled
like wood and cigarettes.
I remember you playing
Judy Garland's "Life Is
Just A Bowl Of Cherries"
over and over and over...
- I love that song.
- And over and over
and over and over and over and over.
I wonder where that is.
Mom still has it.
She still has everything.
( Sighs )
My ukulele.
Thank you for finding it.
You're welcome.
Now maybe you can help me find my life.
Mm, I'm gonna need a super big
compass for that one.
Ah, what am I gonna do?
Brush your teeth.
You haven't brushed your teeth.
I always thought when I grew up,
I'd be some kind of big shot.
A fat cat with a big cigar.
Yeah. Bossing people around.
Do something where you wear a uniform.
You'd look really good in a uniform.
I would look good in a uniform.
It's not too late to be an astronaut.
Or a fireman.
Or a ballerina.
You were supposed to be a ballerina.
Mmm.
Astronaut, yeah. I'll be an astronaut.
Nice.
And tomorrow we'll figure out
what your life's supposed to be.
Ballerina.
( Rock music playing )
( Shouting )
Watch the pivot.
Stripy helmet girl?
She's like your quarterback.
She calls the plays.
- Are your pads scratchy?
- Very.
They'll loosen up the more you fall.
- If I fall.
- You're gonna fall.
- Right.
- So have fun.
Don't be mean.
No pushing, no elbows...
this is a sport with rules.
- Remember it.
- Got it. Remember the rules.
You're not wearing that necklace are you?
- Why?
- You like your head?
Losing the necklace.
A couple of pointers,
Bam-Bam McGee.
Look at her wrong, you're going down.
I thought we weren't supposed to be mean.
Groan of Arc.
She'll give you some slack for a while,
then she gets rough, aggressive. Be ready.
Oh, a lot of names to remember.
And the twins out there,
Scary Skate and Crashley Olsen,
do not get between them.
They will squeeze you
like a watermelon seed.
This is the time half
the girls who sign up
quit, FYI.
I'm not quitting.
I'm ready.
Good.
Are my skates on right?
( Whistle blows )
Only one way to find out.
Hold her. She's right behind us.
Hold her. Hold her.
Right here.
( Grunts )
You okay, Mel?
I'm fantastic.
Well, get back out there.
Where the hell have you been?
- Just out. Why?
- Why?!
This is not a time to go
John Gotti on me, Melanie.
This is a time of emergency.
- What's this?
- Guess.
The bridesmaid's dress.
It's a tank with wings and a rumpus room.
What's it doing here?
It's the only place it's safe.
If my mother found it,
she might Chablis-up
and take a knife to it.
Then you wouldn't have to wear it.
- Don't joke.
- I wasn't joking.
- I have to wear it.
- I know.
Now listen.
Why aren't you answering your phone?
- Must be off?
- Flake City,
- I won't have it!
- Okay, sorry.
You cannot have your phone off
from now until the wedding.
- It's crisis time, get it?
- Got it.
Faye Mendelson has gone into
a total defensive posture.
She moved the photo shoot up a week
to keep my mother off the scent.
Aren't you supposed to do the photo shoot
the day of the wedding?
When everyone's already there, yes.
But Faye's not taking chances.
Oh, she is going to great expense
to make sure my mother doesn't show up.
And she's bringing a trampoline.
Why?
I don't know.
You'll come with me to the photo shoot?
Help with the dress, the makeup,
maybe suicide assistance?
Absolutely.
Hi, everyone.
Hey.
- Hey.
( Cellphone ringing )
Hello? Mom?
Okay, how do you know
Faye Mendelson is getting a massage
and left her dog in the car?
Are you following her?
What does "kind of following her" mean?
You're either following her or you're not.
No, mom.
Hey.
- Hi, Cozette.
- Oh, we're talking.
- Yeah, sorry.
- No worries.
No, she will know who it is
if something happens to her dog.
She will know.
I get what's going on.
What's going on?
Group dynamics are naturally
resistant to alteration.
What is that, like physics?
Madonna.
So why don't you skate for the team?
I thought that's why
you gave me the flyer.
My brother and I do the music.
When you saw me the other day,
we were getting our
set list together.
The dog is innocent.
He's an innocent party.
Do not touch the dog!
You need a name, you know.
For what?
A skater name. Everyone's got a name.
Oh, yeah.
I haven't really thought about it.
We'll think about it. My brother and me
named half the team. Leave it to us.
So you're walking down the street
away from Faye Mendelson's car
and the dog is fine.
Okay. Go home. Chablis-up.
I'll see you later.
( Phone beeps )
We should get downstairs.
Right behind you.
I don't think you
understand what it's like.
Your parents are normal.
They do normal things and eat normal food.
And even though your
mother counts the peas
on everyone's plate to make sure
everyone has the same amount,
I think that's thoughtful.
More thoughtful than wandering the house
at night like Lady MacBeth.
Oh shoot, I forgot my shoes.
You did not forget your shoes.
I drove you off.
I drove her off just like my mother
drives everyone off.
"We mock the things we are to be."
You know who said that? Mel Brooks.
2,000-year-old man.
He was talking about how
we make fun of our parents
and then we grow up
and turn into our parents.
And that line popped
into my head yesterday
so I started looking through
old photo albums of my mother
trying to figure out
exactly when her crazy set in
so I can be prepared.
I think it started around college.
That's the first time I saw her do that
really wild-eyed thing she does.
So I guess I've got
about three to four years
before I go barking mad
which is good.
Now I'm ready for it. I can plan ahead.
You know, have a lot of
rounded corners in my house.
Wear soft, bouncy clothing.
Stock up on tissue, ice cream,
- voodoo dolls.
- Are you Dutch?
- What?
- Dutch. Are you Dutch?
- I...
- Your face reminds me of a Vermeer.
It does?
"The Milkmaid."
I drink milk.
Michelle: All right, everyone.
Butts to the barre.
Well, I should get this over there.
Hey.
Genius is often touched with madness.
That's what makes it fun.
- Tick, tock.
- I guess so.
Ow.
Come on, let's go. Move move move.
Up up up. Come on.
There's no one in here you can date.
I just thought I'd come watch my sister
shape young lives.
I'm just teaching a class.
You are just teaching a class.
- Stop.
- What?
You're being a little bit douchey.
I'm not being a little bit douchey.
I've never seen you in a position
of authority before. Except that year
you dressed up like Angie
Dickinson for Halloween.
Ha ha. Go away.
I'm not gonna disrupt anything.
- Scotty.
- I'm just gonna sit right here
and watch you teach.
I think it'll be interesting.
And possibly hilarious.
All right, everyone. First position.
( Piano playing )
De mi, straight.
Grand plie.
Nice. Beautiful.
Next group.
All right, four turns are not better
than three if you fall, dude.
Cozette, so good, but I need that hold
before you float through.
I'm sorry?
You have to hit that arabesque strong.
And then square everything off.
Then leading with the chin,
arm up and then float through, okay?
Ahh.
Like this.
Yes. Great.
Perfect. Nice.
Pointe shoes on, everyone.
Wow, that Cozette, she's very...
- Intense?
- And weird.
I mean weird in a good way,
- but who the hell is she?
- Beats me.
And why does she bring
that sketch artist with her
- everywhere she goes?
- That's her brother.
Oh, okay. Yeah, not any less weird.
Who brings their brother
with them everywhere they go?
Oh, hey, Scotty.
This is my brother Scotty.
Nice hoofing.
Making Michelle look good out there.
Thank you from the president
of "I have no coordination"
Incorporated."
So seriously, how is she as a teacher?
- She's good.
- Really?
Accept the answer and go sit down.
I'm sorry, I have to say
it is so weird to see you as a teacher.
I know, right?
Thanks, Matisse.
You guys have to understand,
when Michelle was a kid,
she hated her ballet teacher.
Okay, we're in the middle of a class here.
No, it was like a deep deep hatred.
An obsessive hatred.
And then one night she saw this movie.
And it had... Margaret O'Brien,
- remember?
- No.
So, Margaret O'Brien
was this ballet student
and she idolized this old ballerina.
She wasn't old. She was older
than Margaret O'Brien.
And then one day, this other
ballerina comes to town
and steals the lead in "Swan Lake"
from Margaret O'Brien's ballerina.
So she decides to sabotage
the new ballerina
by turning off the stage lights,
but she opens a trapdoor
in the floor by mistake,
and the ballerina falls into it.
Oh my God, what happened?
Paralyzed, wheelchair.
That's terrible.
To you. To Michelle, it was inspiration.
Okay, Scotty.
So Michelle decides to
cut a hole in the floor
of her ballet class
so that old Lady Vinshtick
would fall in and paralyze herself.
I did not.
She breaks in in the middle of the night
and tries to cut
a hole in the floor with...
with safety scissors
and a grapefruit spoon.
It didn't go very well.
Wow.
Okay, shoes back on? Great.
Back to the center. Go.
- Nice kids.
- They sure are.
So how much longer you got here?
I'm thinking dinner.
Don't know. Class, some bookkeeping.
You might be on your own tonight.
Oh.
Okay.
Echappe, echappe, echappe, pas de chat.
Five, six, seven, eight.
( Piano playing )
Sonic Youth segueing into Little Richard
totally worked last night.
As predicted.
Lil' Wayne segueing
into Brad Paisley did not.
Did you know he was country?
The Paisley thing threw me off.
You blending in?
- Me?
- Yeah you.
Trying to.
The name will help.
Just gotta think of one.
- We already did that.
- You're gonna like it.
But you don't even know me.
Yo! Cleo-smacktra, get in here.
Cleo-smacktra?
Cool.
That Beaver. He's evil.
There's evilness in that kid.
At least I'm not late
to class today. Good.
The hand of Lucifer
has touched that child.
No time for the dressing room though.
He played us against each other.
How did we let him do that?
He caught us at a bad time.
I didn't call you doo-doo head.
I would never call you doo-doo head.
I can't believe that for a second
you thought I would call you doo-doo head.
I didn't know what he was saying, okay?
I didn't know what to think.
He's bad. I mean, he's just a bad one.
And we fell for it.
Why did we fall for it?
- We're tired.
- I'm exhausted.
Class is an hour. You and the
kids stay in the vicinity, okay?
But I thought you were going
to bring them all in with you.
Carl, I can't. I have class.
Well, I've got something too.
Something? What something?
You don't have work today.
I'm going to the gym.
The gym.
Yeah, it's been, like, forever.
You're not going to the gym.
I am going to the gym.
- No.
- Yes.
Okay, fine. But I won't be
here when you get back.
I haven't had time to myself in a week!
You knew that kids were a commitment.
These aren't our kids.
You know what I mean.
Carl, please.
Fine. I'll skip the gym.
But if I lose definition in my glutes,
you're to blame, okay?
Carl, please don't be mad.
Let's start class, losers.
Just need to stretch a little first,
- okay, Jordan?
- Absolutely not.
You three, you're my first group.
We're starting with pirouettes.
And tendu.
Fourth, spot spot spot.
Two?
Two and then you stop.
Margaret, how old are you?
- 10.
- 10?
I thought, with that attitude
of yours, you were six.
You want to know how many
I could do when I was 10?
Like a thousand.
Do not look weak, Margaret.
Baryshnikov never looked weak.
Even in "Sex and the City,"
the man never looked weak!
Jordan!
I have had it with this attitude of yours.
Your rudeness.
And your Baryshnikov this
and Baryshnikov that.
- Hey, this is not your class.
- No! You are getting
a time-out, mister.
- What?
- Shh. Quiet.
No no no. Look at me.
Look at me.
Okay, we are here to learn
and to have a good time.
That's what ballet is all about.
( Cellphone rings )
Now, I'm going to have to answer that.
Okay? Because I've got school.
And a job. And three kids.
And that could be news that one
of them just shoved a dump truck
up his nose, okay?
So I'm going to take five minutes.
We're all going to take five minutes here.
And when I get back, I expect to see
a brand-new Jordan.
( Chuckling )
- Yeah?
- Boo, I'm looking for Melanie. Is she there?
- No.
- No?
Are you kidding? Look again.
She's gotta be there. I need her here.
- She promised.
- Honey, honey,
take off the frowny face
and put on the smiley face.
What? Boo, listen...
do you have a juice box?
- Do you want juice?
- Boo. Listen.
- You've got to lose those kids.
- I know.
Okay, what am I gonna do?
Look, call Charlie.
He probably knows where she is.
I will.
( Phone beeps )
All right, everyone. Let's start.
Big smiles now.
Jordan?
Okay, can everyone come
out to the center, please?
And tendu. Fourth.
Very nice.
All right, let's try it again, please?
And tendu.
( Whistle blowing )
( Indistinct shouts )
( Laughing )
Pick up your feet.
( Grunts )
Damn it, McGee, I'll get you for that.
( Indistinct chatter )
Oh my God.
I forgot to go to the photo shoot.
Yeah?
It went bad, didn't it?
Oh yes, yes. Very bad.
- Very bad indeed.
- What's on the dress?
- Punch.
- Punch? From what?
Punch from when my mother came
- and threw it all over us.
- Oh my God.
Where did your mother get punch?
Oh, there are a variety
of places to get punch, Melanie.
Ralphs has punch,
and Vons, and Albertsons,
your local pharmacy
stocks many punch products
to throw on people.
Punch is very easy to obtain.
Ginny, I am so sorry.
I should have told you
why I haven't been around.
But I got caught up in all this stuff,
and I'm sucking at school
and my dad is putting
college pamphlets on my pillow,
and under my breakfast plate,
and in my sock drawer.
And he keeps going on and on
about the S.A.T.s
and what I'm gonna major in
and what I'm gonna do for a living
and what retirement home
I'm gonna end up in.
And I found this, this...
skating thing,
and it made some kind of stupid sense.
And I'm just so...
so sorry.
Say something.
You should have been there.
Where are we? What is this?
It's Roller Derby.
Roller Derby? You're in Roller Derby?
I'm Cleo-smacktra.
( Stammers )
How did this enter your world?
That night at the Oyster Bar,
when I pulled the chair
out from underneath Godot.
Godot got you into this?
Not Godot.
She gave me a flyer.
She?
You!
Hi?
Should you run?
You stay out of this.
You're ruining everything!
I don't know who you are
or where you're from,
or why you know French, or why
you're so close with Mitch Alvarado,
but Melanie is my friend!
And it's the four of us.
And you need to stay the hell away!
And I'm Norwegian!
Does she skate?
( Whistle blowing )
( Knocking on door )
- Is everyone decent?
- Yep.
I was yelling your name for 20 minutes.
- Didn't you hear me?
- What do you want, Scotty?
I just need a key to get in your place.
What happened to the key
I gave you yesterday?
I don't know. Misplaced it.
Is there like a Paradise
Lost And Found somewhere?
Oh.
Is something wrong?
You're suddenly acting like
every other woman in my life.
Michelle?
You told me the ukulele was lost.
- What?
- When I asked you where it was,
you told me to my face that it was lost.
It wasn't lost. You had it the whole time.
- Who cares?
- I do. I wanted my ukulele.
- That was like 20 years ago.
- Is that your excuse?
Oh jeez, I'm sorry.
You know, if you missed it that much
maybe you should have
just bought a new one.
They're very hot now.
Eddie Vedder just did
a whole ukulele album.
That's how out of ideas he is.
- I'll get it for you for Christmas.
- You're undermining me.
What? How?
Your cracks, your jokes
in front of the girls.
I'm being funny. It's humor.
It's what sets us apart from the apes.
That whole Margaret O'Brien thing.
- That was funny?
- I can't...
you basically told them
to cut a hole in the floor
so I'll fall through and paralyze myself.
I didn't tell them to do it.
I told them that you wanted to do it
to your teacher.
I thought it was a cute story.
- You were planting ideas.
- I told them the plot of a movie.
I did not write the movie.
How the hell am I the bad guy in this?
This is my life now, Scotty.
This is my home. This is my job.
Those are my students.
Oh boy. You have snapped
many many caps, my friend.
I'm an authority figure now.
Authority figure? Come on.
- They look up to me.
- They're isolated kids.
You're this strange exotic creature.
You're a mermaid. You're Tinker Bell.
So that's why you're here?
To crap all over my new life?
I worked hard for this life.
You got drunk and married a guy.
- Hard work.
- Hey!
What? I've done it too. No judgments.
Well, he was a great guy.
And his mother has been
really really good to me.
- You're living in a guest house.
- What does that mean?
It means, it's a one room guest house.
- For a guest.
- Oh, so square footage is the measure of stability now?
What's your square footage, Scotty, huh?
Enjoying your six feet of my couch?
- Matt Johnson.
- What?
Matt Johnson. He was
my best friend in school,
you dated him, and as
soon as you guys broke up
he wouldn't talk to me anymore.
What are you yammering about?
You said you never took anything from me?
You took Matt Johnson.
I have no memory of Matt Johnson.
Oh, come on, Michelle.
Matt Johnson? He was my best friend.
The two amigos?
Do you mean Eric Johnson?
Yes. Eric Johnson.
- Wow.
- Doesn't change what happened.
He was so important to you
you couldn't remember his name.
Perhaps I blacked it out. Too much trauma.
Just own up to it, Scotty.
- Take some responsibility.
- What does that have to do with...
You never take
responsibility for anything.
Oh, says the girl who set
every float on fire
at the Fourth of July parade
with a cigarette
and blamed it on rap music.
Why didn't you make me
graduate high school?
- You did graduate.
- No.
- I was there.
- That was the ceremony.
I didn't have the credits
to get the diploma.
Oh, bummer.
You should have made me graduate.
It was your responsibility to make
sure I was prepared for life.
- Why me?
- You're my big brother.
By a year!
All I was supposed to do
was make sure you had beer.
Why is this funny?
Why are you making this funny?
Because all I wanted was a key.
That's all.
And suddenly you're freaking out
and you said ukulele like 60 times
and I don't even know why
we're having this argument.
Don't do that. That is so mom.
She starts stuff, and then
while you're standing there
yelling and screaming
and pulling your hair out,
she says "I don't even know
why we're having this argument"
when she knows damn well
why you're having the argument.
She's the one who started this
argument in the first place.
How did we suddenly get to mom?
- You brought her up.
- I did not bring her up.
Well, by being like her,
you brought her up.
You don't even deal with mom.
I deal with mom.
Mom needs money, I deal with it.
Mom needs to move, I deal with it.
Mom needs help hiding out
from the Jehovah's Witnesses,
I deal with it!
Why was mom hiding out
from the Jehovah's Witnesses?
It's a long story and they're a very
non-violent organization so it takes a lot
to get them to the point
where they are someone
you have to hide out from.
Well, that's your choice.
I washed my hands
of all that a long time ago.
Yes, I know. How long's it been
- since you talked to mom?
- 12 glorious fun-filled years.
Oh, very mature, by the way.
Not much has changed.
Your address, you go to a job every day,
- but not much else.
- You don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah, it took me way longer to figure
things out than it should have,
but look at the road map I had to follow.
The birds ate all those
breadcrumbs, Hansel.
And boy, do I not want to
hear about all the stuff
you have to put up with
with that crazy woman.
Because I've dealt with more than a
lifetime's worth of crap from her.
Her obsession with her face and her looks,
and my face and my looks.
And her completely fictional take
on what our family was.
And if you choose to continue
having negative influences
in your life, then you
have to prepare yourself
for the consequences.
You know who told me that?
Fanny, my mother-in-law.
She told me that you make your own family.
You make your own destiny.
And there is nothing you cannot change
if you are completely committed to it.
And I am.
I am completely committed to it.
And it doesn't matter
if you believe it or not,
the address has changed
and my life has changed.
- Fine.
- I can do this.
( Tuning ukulele )
( Strumming ukulele )
♪ I know I know you belong ♪
♪ to somebody new ♪
♪ but tonight ♪
♪ you belong to me ♪
♪ although we're apart ♪
♪ you're a part ♪
♪ of my heart ♪
♪ but tonight ♪
♪ you belong ♪
♪ to me ♪
♪ way down ♪
♪ by the stream ♪
♪ how sweet ♪
♪ it will seem ♪
♪ once more ♪
♪ just to dream ♪
♪ in the moonlight ♪
♪ my honey, I know ♪
♪ I know in the dawn ♪
♪ that you ♪
♪ will be gone ♪
♪ but tonight ♪
♪ you belong ♪
♪ to me ♪
♪ just to little old me. ♪
No! Do it again, Jordan!
No. Again.
You're better than this, Jordan.
Come on.
Yes.
I'll be better after a banana.
Sync and corrections by atrn97g
for www.addic7ed.com