sync & correction by f1nc0
~ addic7ed.com ~
Some guys just can't
take "no" for an answer.
The Morrigan wants that photo!
Oh, I can't blame her.
Have you seen it?
Awkward!
Kenzi for the assist!
Yes!
Did you like that part? Where
I pretended to fall on my ass
when actually I was like a stealth
missile lasering in on target.
Smooth. Remind me
to book you on "Dancing With The Fae".
Is that a thing?
Just help me drag tall, dark
and hideous out of sight, okay?
You know, far be it from me
to be a Wendy Whiner...
Totally.
But this is the third
Faebag attack this week.
Your point, Wendy?
Yesterday it was the two-headed
thingie that looked like Regis.
Then before that it
was that hotdog vendor
that turned out to be
a fire- breathing...?
- I wanna say, frog?
- Jellyfish?
Whatever it was, we
kicked its gelatinous ass.
You know, I never thought I'd
say this, but I'm only human, Bo.
And, no offense, but you ain't
lookin' so chipper either.
Hey, whatever the Morrigan
dishes out, I can handle it.
You still got that doozie
from yesterday's slug fest?
Yesterday it was a cut.
Today it is a bruise.
I'm healing.
- Slowly. Very slowly.
- What are you saying?
The doc...
I mean...
you know, isn't it like
trying to charge an iPad
- with a hamster wheel?
- Okay, time out.
What exactly do you have against Lauren?
Moi?
Oh, come on, Kenzi, with the little
digs and the rolling of the eyes...
- I'm not stupid.
- Well...
Here's your chance, while I'm still high
off my wicked moves.
Get it out of your system!
She is bossy, territorial,
and controlling.
She thinks you're immature,
irresponsible and clingy.
She does!?
Oh, you've said those
things about yourself.
Yeah, but when I say it, it is adorable.
Okay, the point is I love Lauren.
She's a huge part of my life.
As are you.
So in the Battle of
BFF versus Main Squeeze,
I think it's time we called a truce.
Got it?
Uh huh.
Now, all those on Team Bo...
drinks are on me.
That's right...
Oh, Bruce... you disappoint me.
- I'm Steve...
- How did this happen?
- It's not my fault, she had an army.
- Don't insult my intelligence!
You're a worse liar
than your brother, Eric.
- Dave.
- I don't care!
If I hadn't just had my nails done,
I'd rip your beating heart out myself.
You're too kind.
I think someone's getting a little
too big for her leather britches.
Soon, my pet... soon.
If Li'l Bo Bleep thinks she
can play in the big leagues...
let the games begin.
Life is hard when you
don't know who you are.
It's harder when you
don't know what you are.
My love carries a death sentence.
I was lost for years,
searching while hiding.
Only to find that I belonged
to a world hidden from humans.
I won't hide anymore.
I will live the life I choose.
3x03 - ConFaegion
EKG, MRI, EMV...
Wake me up when you get to S&M.
See, the truth of it, Vex, is that...
No, don't sugar coat it, Doc.
Just give it to me straight.
Okay... there is nothing
physically wrong with your arm,
or your nervous system, or
your musculoskeletal system...
Then...
why... can't I...
- Get it up?
- Oh, regular riot, you are.
Since there's no physiological
reason for your mesmeric impotence...
Aha! I made you do that!
- No, actually, that was just an itch.
- Damn you!
What I'm trying to say
is that your "condition"
may be psychological in nature.
What, you sayin' I'm whacked?
Like I'm a nutter?
A few ounces short of a pint?
It's not at all
uncommon in Fae your age.
Do you have any idea
who you're talking to?
You shall feel the wrath of Vex!
Why aren't you strangling
yourself by now?!
It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
I actually have the pamphlet...
Oh, save your pathetic bedside manner
for your new, presumably
temporary, girlfriend!
- Excuse me?
- Oh, come on... it can't be easy
keepin' up with the
Energizer SuccuBunny.
Though Dyson could.
Okay... you know what?
I think we're done.
Any chance of a prescription refill?
- Out!
- Really?
Bloody physicians.
I mean, imagine sayin' that
there's nothing wrong with it.
I mean, have you ever
heard anything so...
Hello! Barkeep!
I'm talking to you!
- Still?
- Unbelievable!
Here I am, pouring out
my heart to you and...
Ok Dyson, I'm not here for my health.
You wanna look at
these case files or not?
Uh, absolutely.
Just gimme a sec...
Ah... greetings.
- Don't even start, Vex.
- I beg your pardon?
- I'm not buying you another drink.
- Hey, I'm deeply offended.
- Good, now go away.
- Hey, you don't own me.
Okay, look...
we've been listening to
your same sad story for days.
The Dark doesn't want me.
The Light can't stand me.
My friends...
Oh, wait...
he doesn't have any, does he?
- Sucks to be Vex.
- This is an outrage!
Nine ball... side pocket.
What is it with that chick?
She's just not feeling the love.
- But why?
- Because she thinks you're a murderer?
But more importantly,
what have you been up to?
What? Oh...
- The Morrigan again?
- Oh, piece of cake.
Don't underestimate that woman.
After the Garuda meltdown, the Light
and the Dark have agreed to play nice.
Unaligned means unprotected.
Oh, but you are forgetting...
I have this.
My own little insurance policy.
I still think you
should talk to The Ash.
You look like you could use a break.
And I'm guessing Kenzi could, too.
Ow!
Pardonez moi...
- What's his problem?
- I have no idea.
You brought this on yourself, you know.
Is this how you roll now?
Tough love?
You handcuffed the Morrigan
to her bed for a Kodak moment.
You sure this has nothing to do with
your Fae United Nations experiment?
A Light cop partnered
with a Dark cop? Really?
It's cynicism like
that has kept our sides
from building a genuine peace.
Also, why do you care
who Dyson is paired with?
- I don't.
- Didn't think so.
Know what might help your situation?
Just so happens I had a declaration
to the Light all prepared...
I'm not gonna be pressured into
choosing a side out of fear.
Well, can't blame an Ash for tryin'.
You know what? Forget it.
I can handle the shitstorm,
it's just that Kenzi is
starting to feel the strain.
Now who's dishing out tough love?
Bo, hang on...
Look, since we got all Garuda-fied,
I've been doing some serious
inventory of the archives.
And... ?
Seems someone has grabbed
my Staff of Righteousness.
The Staff is a piece of wood...
a treasured ceremonial relic ...
and very powerful.
Currently believed to
be in the possession
of one Mortimer Fassbinder.
Pawnbroker and sleazebag.
So, if I bring you this Staff...
I could probably post a
security detail near your place.
Keep an eye out for The Morrigan's pets.
- Where do I find this Fassbinder?
- Hold up, Slick...
There's something you
should know about the Staff.
Cheers, Bruce!
Lovely lady, it is your lucky day.
I could have you killed just
for crossing my threshold.
Tut tut, bygones and all that...
A heartfelt expression of my
loyalty to the Dark. And you.
I am beautiful in restraints.
Delete...
- Was there something else?
- Well, I thought you'd be pleased.
If you really wanted to
please me you would have
brought me that bitch's
head on a platter.
But... but, I...
But maybe your recent bout of
impotence has spread to your spine?
Lucky for you, my pity
outweighs my disgust.
I won't have you killed.
At least not today.
Oh... you're too kind.
We all have our cross to bear.
Now drink up and go.
The next time we meet...
...either Bo or you will be dead.
The choice is yours.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
Whatcha doin'?
Oh, you know, just some
Doctor-y stuff.
You know, I am actually
interested in your work.
You can talk to me about
whatever it is you do.
Really? You want to hear
about my latest monograph
regarding the rhizome repellent
gradient of Fae blood compared
with human blood, especially when
suspended in an isotonic solution?
- Or we could go to a movie.
- Okay.
- What is that?
- Oh...
- The Staff of Righteousness.
- The who of what?
Don't ask.
Oh, and don't touch.
Well...
what can I touch?
Haha, very funny.
What's gotten into you?
Well, you know, nothing just yet.
But I was kinda thinking
maybe we could, um...
Oh... wow...
and to think I just came by
to see if I left my phone here.
Hmm... I don't know.
Let's look...
Well, it's not in there.
Gosh, you know,
with any luck maybe you
left it on "vibrate".
I thought you'd be too
tired after last night.
Tired? I am going for the
gold in the Succu-games.
Well...
I don't know what's gotten into you,
but far be it from me to stand in
the way of a young athlete's dream.
- Yo, V-man.
- Whatever.
Sounds like somebody
woke up on the wrong side
of the pull-out couch this morning.
What's up?
- It's my arm.
- Again with the pity parade?
Look, you got a busted
wing, you can't fly.
You gotta walk around like the
rest of us poor miserable humans.
Welcome to Kenzi-ville!
Man!
Now you know what it's
like to be surrounded
by superheroes every day.
Suck it up, Pathetico!
You know, if I were you, I'd
re-consider a career in social work.
Can we just...
...forget about your Fae-self
for like a nanosecond,
and talk about something
that's really important?
Doubtful.
- Mascara.
- You have my attention.
Dude, your lashes are freakin' amazing!
Yeah...
it's all in the brush technique. Wait...
I picked up a few tips from Da Vinci.
- As in The Code?
- Oh, yeah, now there was a queen for ya.
He was all over David's
ass like curry on chips.
- Can you help me with my clumping?
- Oh, please...
Hey, y'all.
Hey... Whazat?
The end of a long story, involving
a greasy pawnbroker and
some hardcore negotiating.
Uh, do you mind?
We're working over here.
Anyone seen my phone?
You say phone?
What, your phone?
Here, shift a cheek so I can
look under the cushions...
Nothing...
- Scootch!
- Where'd you last have it?
That's the thing...
I coulda sworn that I left it...
Yeah, iPads, iPhones electricity...
it's all just a fad, really.
The future's analog and all that.
I'm tellin' ya.
Am I doing it right?
Hmm...
just a little bit up...
O.M.G.
You guys are so cute together.
I wish I had a makeup buddy.
I thought she could be my friend,
and she doesn't even like me.
- Who?
- Tamsin!
She is so mean girl, right?
I mean, buy an actual
personality already.
Did you happen to rifle
through my duffel bag,
and scarf down a couple of
yellow pills with tigers on 'em?
I'm gonna talk to Dyson.
And Bee-Tee-Dubs...
It is "trés" private.
Private?
Lauren's pelt is gonna be steamed!
What's it with you and the Doc?
I mean, besides her
terrible bedside manner
and the fact that she's a
damn sight cleverer than you.
Not to mention sneaky.
She spy-banged Bo.
Dyson's drop-kicked Bo's
heart ten times over,
and you still howl
when he comes 'round.
I...! No!
Listen, are you gonna teach me
the double pump smudge-proof
technique or not?
I'm so proud of you.
Come here...
Alright, you're gonna move
it like this just at the ends.
You can't... like shake it...
I do not like your friend.
She's not my friend.
She is my new partner.
What is she saying about me?
Because whatever it is, it's not true.
- Have you been drinking?
- What? Like, alcohol?
I wish.
- Do you have fake ID?
- What?
Let's do it.
Let's get faced!
Okay, you are cut off.
I'm gonna talk to Trick.
Wow, you're so beautiful.
I'm sorry...
I gotta go...
- I think Dyson likes me.
- Say what?
Don't tell anyone this...
but I think I might kiss him!
There's no pupil dilation...
no concussion...
I'm stumped.
You have little specks in
your eyes that look like stars.
Call me crazy, but based on
your little display at the bar...
I mean, I do know that you and Dyson...
Spill on aisle 3!
Ow, ow...
Come on! Let's go to a movie.
Wow, you're really hot.
Have you ever kissed a girl?
I need you to sit still
to check your EKG, ok?
- Bzzz!
- Bo, stop!
We have now swapped brains.
Hi, I'm Dr. Lauren.
I don't like to have any fun.
Take two frownie brownies
and call me in the morning.
You're really starting to scare me.
Okay Bo... just listen to me...
Bo! Listen to me...
have you come in contact with
any strange Fae lately...?
- This is so lame!
- Bo! Please!
Okay, well...
there was this one gross
guy with a magic stick...
Hey, Tammers.
"T-sin". Officer "Slamsin"!
- Okay...
- Are you playin' with yourself?
Did somebody spike your brewski?
Dude... this one time?
That totally happened.
I got to be Kenzi.
Nailed it.
Right... if you're trying
to throw me off my game
before we get down, it's working.
- Do you think Bo likes me?
- Do I look like I care?
I think I'm gonna ask her on a date.
Okay, well...
knock yourself out.
In the meantime...
you're either in the game...
- or you are in my way...
- You are so badass.
Bo and Dyson sitting in a tree...!
Shhhh!
K-i-s-s-i-n-g!
Oh, that would be so awesome!
But, shhh! People are listening.
- Hey, Gramps, what's this?
- Seventh century.
Please, put it back in my study.
- Ew, she's gross.
- Just put it back.
"Put it back."
Can I have the car keys?
No.
If I don't get the car keys,
I'm gonna count to a hundred.
In French .
- Good grief...
- See what I mean?
Un.
Deux!
Trois...
You think this is being caused by
the job that The Ash sent her on?
Quatre...
You tell me.
Can the Staff of Righteousness
have symptoms like these?
- Quatre...!
- Cinq!
- For the love of Aphrodite, it's cinq!
- Sorry, French Police.
Cinq.
Six...
At first glance, there's
nothing in the lore
that suggest the Staff
is causing her symptoms.
You have to admit, it's a
pretty strange coincidence.
She goes looking for the
Staff and comes back like...
- Pollyanna on mushrooms?
- Exactly.
- Hey...
- What?
Where's "seven"?
Bo, get down!
"Don't you wish you're..."
Hey! Let me finish!
Don't Kanye me.
- You are a cheater!
- Whatever!
You're a cheater.
And you're getting a zit.
Bo is right.
You're mean!
Whatever this is... it's contagious.
...you gotta forget about brown...
black is always the new black.
- You can't ground us.
- Yeah. You're not our Mom.
Yeah, we don't even
have to listen to you.
So... Bo shagged them both daft?
- We have a situation.
- More like a SHITuation.
You guys wanna see my room?
- Uh... yeah!
- Shotgun!
- No! No!
- No, wait! Wait!
Something's made them sick.
And what's worse is the...
- Is that...?
- A pig...?
He's looking for something...
Or someone! Bo...
Kenzi, where is there a knife?
Or your trunk?
- Uh, upstairs!
- Well, what about your sword??
- Up... stairs!
- Okay, well, Kenzi, think of something!
That's usually your thing, Doc!
This little piggy's
about to go to market!
We need a weapon!
We need something!
Whoa!
Bloody hell...
That'll do, pig...
that'll do.
How did you...
I...
Aren't you the dark horse.
He's dead.
Dudes, all I did was grab
this stupid shillelagh
and all of a sudden I'm
Darth Vader.
- Let me see that...
- Yeah, about that...
the shaft is kinda...
Fae-zy Glued to my hand.
Yeah...
That happened to me once.
Painful.
"Grab a weapon," she said.
It seems to be an energy bond.
- So un-bond it.
- I can't.
The wood is melded to your flesh.
Worst hand job ever.
Whoa, Mack! The knife!?
No, I saw it on TV.
It cuts right through wood.
And tomatoes.
Not my bad.
Stick bad.
Plus...
your music sucks!
I bought that one ironically.
All of them, actually...
- Um, what the heck is this?
- Oh! Look at that!
What is with your voice?
It's all Scottish-y.
Oh! Well, do you like it?
It's lame.
- No.
- Yo, peeps! We are under attack!
- Big whoop.
- Fascinating.
They seem to be immune
to any sense of danger.
Ohforgodsakes...
Hey!
We have a dead man-pig
in the living room,
I have a tree stuck to my mitt,
and I did not sign up
for the babysitter's club!
Oh, Dyson touched my boob!
That was an accident!
It was with my elbow!
Doesn't even count!
Come on!
Seriously?
Guys, guys, guys!
Let's order pizza!
Yes.
For some reason, only the
3 of them are infected.
Let's not take any chances.
No physical contact until I
know what we're dealing with.
- Got it.
- Double cheese! Yeah!
Double cheese!
Pizza!
- Pizza!!!
- Pizza!
And you three, stay put.
Get the pizza!
Where did you get these??
- It's fantastic!
- Give it to me...
Totally lame...
Aww... There's another one!
Come here, you!
What I don't understand is that
if this disease only targets Fae...
Why isn't Vex infected?
Well, perhaps my superior genetic makeup
has rendered me immune to
embarrassing afflictions.
- What is that?
- What?
You have a strange
pustule behind your ear
that wasn't there when
I examined you last.
Pustule...
Ew.
Ugh...
Ugh! UGH!
Ewww with a double side of hurl.
- What is it??
- It's what's left of a cocoon.
You've been used as an incubator.
- By what?
- My guess?
- A parasite.
- What? I'm unclean?!
Relax... it isn't in you anymore.
But where could you have picked this up?
Have you been with
any strange Fae lately?
Damn bitch!
- What's that?
Oh, nothing, uh...
I was just saying how devastated
I was about all this, uh...
Listen, I'm gonna get some
help from Trick. Alright?
I'm gonna make things right.
Alright?
- What the hell did you do to me!?
- Used you to spread a parasite.
- What kind of bloody parasite!?
- The parasitic kind.
Zaps its victims
with nymphoid hormones.
Turns them into self-obsessed
brats too young for Fae powers.
So, they're completely
vulnerable to attack?
Precisely.
But what about the "other
white meat"? Relatives of yours?
The infected emit a pungent
pheromone that attracts
a nasty breed of
UnderFae in for the kill.
Yeah, well, luckily Kenzi
pounded little Piggly Wiggly
into UnderFae bacon with
her magic shillelagh.
- And the Succubitch?
- Still alive and singing.
Along with the other Twi-hards.
Dyson and his new partner.
Oh!
Now this is getting interesting.
Three of my favorite people,
trapped in one place...
with no way to defend themselves.
And she's got The Ash's play stick.
You want to prove your
loyalty to the Dark?
Finish off the teen trio, and
bring me the Staff of Righteousness.
And if I do?
I'm sure I could find some...
entry level position...
No! I want all titles restored ...
a million in cash
- and my club. I want it back.
- There's the Vex I remember.
"Grab a weapon", she said...
For the hundredth time,
Kenzi, I didn't know!
Alert the media, there is something
Doctor Flawless doesn't know!
This is hardly the time, Kenzi.
Course it isn't...
'Cause that would be "messy"!
Do you think just once!
Maybe just once, you could try to be...
- What? What??
- Helpful!
- Excuse me?
- Sure!
Because everybody else does!
You just bounce through life,
no job, no plan, from one beer
to the next and still, everybody
dotes on you, don't they?
What do you care where they dote?
- Just forget about it...
- Yeah... what is that?!
Why are you always
rolling your eyes at me,
with your normal upbringing
and your medical degree.
You don't know anything
about my life, Kenzi!
I know you think you're
too good for me...
No, I don't actually!
You think that I'm good enough for Bo!
- She's my best friend.
- And I love her.
I know! I know.
Are you sure we're not infected?
No.
We're just...
...stupid.
Well, I prefer...
..."emotional".
Moving on?
- Killer Pig?
- Yeah...
Yep, okay...
I can't believe I ever
thought you didn't like me.
I don't think I was
supposed to like you.
Why? What do you mean?
I'm a Valkyrie.
- I think.
- Wow...
Really?
- What's a Valkyrie?
- I don't know.
But...
sometimes when I like people,
I have to make them go away.
- What are you talking about?
- Can you keep a secret?
Till I die.
- No, I'm not supposed to.
- No, wait! Wait!
I have an idea! Okay...
Let's write down our
deepest, darkest secrets...
...in poetry.
Cool!
But like real poetry.
The kind that rhymes.
You're really awesome.
No.
Um...
Oh, oh!
See its snout?
It's similar in genetic
makeup to the pig.
It was scenting out its
prey, it knew which of us
was infected with the parasite.
Hurray for the Truffle Pig.
These creatures travel in packs.
When their buddy doesn't return...
They'll all go hog wild?
Not even my wonder whacker
may be enough to save us.
That's why we need Bo and
the others back to normal.
Based on the secretions
that I pulled from the cocoon
from Vex, I think I can
cobble together an anti-toxin
- for the parasite. But I need time.
- And a lab, maybe?
Well, not necessarily.
I've got a few basic supplies in my kit.
But I need you to gather
up some ingredients.
Uh, baking powder, vinegar, turmeric...
Yeah, yeah, okay...
Alright, go...
Also, garlic, hairspray,
and lubricating oil.
Flavoured or bulk?
As for me...
I'm going upstairs to take a swab.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Doc, you goin' in solo?
Without backup?
- I think I can do this.
- You're as stubborn as you are bossy.
Godspeed.
Okay!
- What happened?
- I don't want to talk about it.
But... I got it.
Sure did.
Wow...
- Nice job.
- Yeah, I did something else too...
I set up an early warning
system outside, Home Alone style.
Good. That'll help.
Okay...
You must've gone to some
crazy-ass medical school.
Yale taught me chemistry and physiology.
But this kind of stuff is
just experience and luck
and whatever I figured out in the field.
- "Field" meaning...
- Afghanistan.
Shit, dude...
- How long?
- Long enough.
- Why didn't you ever say so?
- You never asked.
You're listening to Dyson take a whiz.
I am not.
Did you read my poem?
It was stupid, right?
No, I liked it.
A lot.
Yours was really beautiful...
in a way.
But it was...
really, really sad.
I wish there was something
I could do to help you.
You can't help me.
Nobody can.
Our secret?
Cross my heart.
Make mine a Fae-cuccino, please...
I'm just straining any
impurities. God, I hope...
Perimeter breach!
- Uh... we've got company!
- How many?
There's just...
Uh, no, there's another one...
- Ugh, it's not ready!
- Oh, God...
The 3 little piggies are back!
And this time, it's personal.
- Vex!
- Dude, what are you doing?
I'm going home.
- You slimy sonuvabitch!
- Ooooh!
Your words are like tiny
little daggers in my heart!
I trusted you!
Yeah, well, just give us the
rugrats so we can all go home!
Not on your miserable life!
Duran Duran?
♪ "...I'm on the hunt, I'm after you..." ♪
♪ "...I'm lost and I'm found..." ♪
♪ "...and I'm hungry like the wolf..." ♪
Bo! Help!
That sounds like Kenzi!
"...I'm hungry like the wolf!"
Bo?!
- Crank it, Tammy!
- Okay!
The antidote's ready!
- I need to get upstairs...
- Go long and wide, Doc!
I got you covered!
Are you gonna be okay??
Sure! This is kinda fun.
Okay...
Way to not overthink it.
Hey... Twinkle toes...
I'll be havin' that wee Staff of yours.
Come closer.
Let me give it you.
Oh, I'd be delighted.
Look what I found.
This isn't really like...
any Spin The Bottle game
I ever played.
- Oh, it's new rules.
- Are you sure?
Absolutely, I read it...
somewhere. It's your turn.
- I gotta kiss you.
- Okay.
- Man... what are you?
- Dude... that was all you.
Are you playing Spin The Bottle?
That was so dope.
- Let's do that again.
- Okay.
Yeah, let's not...
Ow!!!
- Hey, where's our pizza?
- There's no pizza coming.
Come here, you little...
I believe "wanker" is the
word that you're looking for.
A dirty traitor!
And to think I shared my limited
edition purple-pixie glitter with you!
Aw, you think sharing
makeup makes us friends?
Don't do this...
I thought you were your own man.
I am my own man!
And I happen to have an axe.
But you're not doing this for you.
You're doing it for that
stupid bitch!
Anything is better than this!
I mean, look at me!
I'm sleeping on a couch!
People are laughing at me to my face!
You can't believe that The Morrigan's
just gonna welcome you
back with open arms!
Listen, luv, you've
obviously read the book
on "Hostage Negotiation 101"...
Can we just skip
to the bit where you tell
me I'm better than this?
- You are.
- What if I'm not?
Losing your powers was the best
thing that could have happened to you.
I feel like I've
finally met the real Vex!
He's a true artist.
He's a gentle soul!
And he will not be trifled with.
Not even by her!
He's done with that!
Vex... please!
Oh, Kenzi...
I'm getting soft in my old age.
Good choice...
Good choice!!!
It's all right...
She's coming...
Time for Mama
to bring home the bacon.
I don't think I'd mind
getting my ass kicked
- by someone that hot.
- That had to hurt.
Oh! God!
One to go, one to go,
one one one to go!
And that's two!
No, that's two!
Bo for the gold!
Ahem...
Uh, all's well that ends well, yeah?
No hard feelings?
Ow!
Girl, you got you some
gaaame. True.
Come on, Bo...
The whole thing's... blank.
But fuzzy, like...
...like there's something there,
but why can't I remember?
Because you're not supposed to.
We're probably better off this way.
Yeah, good call, Tammy.
- I mean, Tamsin.
- Okay!
Look, all I know is
that this latest crapfest
just caused a whole
mess of Fae paperwork.
So, thank you for destroying
my weekend, and goodbye.
Well, that girl is just no fun at all.
The one who touches the
Staff of Righteousness
shall take up the noble cause,
accept the sacred mantle
of Ruler of Forest Nymphs
and Wood Sprites,
and fight for truth and justice
throughout the land to the
end of their natural days.
You're kidding me.
This is a huge responsibility
you've taken on.
I just picked up a frikkin' stick!
That's how destiny works.
One day you're you, and the next day...
I'm a superhero.
Pro...
I could be awesome, forever.
- Yup.
- Okay... Con...
I would have to learn
how to do everything
with my left hand and I mean everything.
Well... as a last, desperate
resort there is an escape clause.
Sold.
Show me the eject button.
Very well.
Close your eyes and say
the words... No peeking.
"I decline".
I... decline.
It was that easy?
Why didn't you just say so?
What? A Blood King
can't have a little fun?
I don't think much of
your interior decorator...
It's a work in progress.
Much like yourself.
Don't change the subject.
You're not off the hook yet.
Oh! Look at you.
All grown up. "The Ash."
Did you get the new business cards, yet?
Maybe a little vanity plate?
- Daddy must be so proud.
- You violated Fae law.
Oh, by having a little fun with SuccuBo?
You executed a blatant
attack on the Light.
Oh, come on now.
When did everyone get so uptight?
I remember the good old days.
A little raping, a little pillaging,
the odd "collateral damage"...
and then you'd have yourself a party.
Now it's all rules, rules, rules.
Your actions may have
jeopardized the new peace plan.
A plan, in case you've forgotten,
that was endorsed by the
Fae Elders themselves.
What can I say?
Except, mea culpa.
I was just trying to spice
things up a little bit.
I was a cop for thirty years.
One thing I learned...
bullshit stinks.
And lady, you reek.
You ever pull a stunt like this again,
I will personally rip off your head
and shove it up your lily white ass.
This détente is too important
to be screwed up by some petty feud.
Am I clear?
Crystal.
Hey man, we are just one
Vex short of a real fiesta.
Where you goin'?
I don't know yet.
Why don't I go make some tea.
Vexster... hey!
Come on, all is forgiven.
But it shouldn't be, Kenz.
I can't stay here.
Not after what I've done.
Dude, you saved my life...
Or that pig shifted to the left
at just the right moment.
That is not true.
Is it??
You know...
if you'd looked at my history
you'd know I was a betting man.
I'm going to take some
time to reflect, you know?
Reset the system.
I guess the Doctor was right!
Bloody humans...
- You thinkin' maybe Tibet?
- India, via Vegas.
You know, the whole
Eat, Pray, Mesmer tour.
Yeah... well...
I'll be back.
Fully armed and ready to rock.
How do I know I'll ever see you again?
Not your ebony handled
bison bristle blush brush?
You break that brush and I'll kill ya.
Ow!
Catch you in another lifetime!
Maybe...
I'm gonna miss that a-hole...
I know.
- Ow...
- Here...
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ addic7ed.com ~