Hey, uh, doesn't somebody have
a birthday
coming up
in a couple of days?
That's right, I do.
And I hope you're
not planning on
making a big deal
out of it.
Nope. I'm just
gonna stick with
the step-by-step instruction
manual you gave me.
Well...
Don't think of it
as a manual.
Just, you know,
little hints,
crumbs, to guide you
down the right path.
- Got it.
- You do 'em, you don't do 'em.
Up to you.
I see.
So you're not expecting to be
"woken up at 8:00 a.m.
"with butterfly kisses,
warm croissants
and English breakfast tea"?
If it happens, that
would be lovely.
And if it does,
a little bouquet
of fresh flowers
would make it
extra special.
Flowers.
- Your choice.
- Tulips.
Gerber daisies.
Color is totally
your call.
Gerber daisies.
In yellow.
- I choose yellow.
- Ah! (chuckles)
Shall I continue?
Yes, I'm dying to
hear what's next.
Well, after breakfast,
we're going to the museum
to see the dinosaurs.
Uh...
I-I didn't write
"dinosaurs."
Well, you wrote "museum"
and that's where they keep 'em.
Well, I'm fine
with whatever
as long as I'm strolling
hand in hand with
the man I love.
- Aw.
- At the Rembrandt exhibit.
(chuckles)
Art...
Mm-hmm.
Hand in hand.
Now, for lunch,
I'm thinking falafel.
How far off am I?
You know what?
I should've been
more specific.
I didn't know I was
up against falafel.
Hey, guys.
You remember Tom,
my friend-slash weed
dealer, don't you?
Hey, you remember Mike,
my husband-slash
police officer
who arrests people
who deal drugs?
Not drugs, just weed.
Occasionally, 'shrooms,
but all organically grown
in his own greenhouse.
Hey, you don't have any
Gerber daisies, do you?
Tom's place is being tented
and bombed for termites,
so he's gonna crash here
for a couple of days.
You mean,
in the house?
Hey, listen, not to harsh
your mellow,
but if I had
a police dog here,
would he be barking
at your bag?
Not unless he's
been trained
to sniff out pajamas
and ginkgo biloba.
All right, just checking.
I'm very respectful of your home
and your outdated
marijuana laws.
Great. We'll be like
the sheepdog and the coyote
when they say good morning
at the time clock.
(laughs)
Looney Tunes fan!
We'll get along
just fine.
They're not sleeping
together, are they?
No. She never brings
home a guy with a job.
♪ For the first time
in my life ♪
♪ I see love. ♪
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/.
Good morning.
Might've been, if I'd have
gotten any sleep last night.
Insomnia?
No, you and Mr. Zig-Zag
hitting bongos
and bongs all night long.
Oh, you could hear that?
Did I sound flat on "Iko Iko"?
Victoria, how long
is Tom gonna stay here?
This house is pretty
full as it is.
As long as he wants.
He's one of my best friends.
I've known him since
the ninth grade.
You've been buying weed from
that guy since ninth grade?
Tenth. The first year was free.
Well, your houseguest is
in the shower
bogarting all my hot water.
Tom likes to start his day with
a full-body loofah salt scrub.
Says it's like being reborn
every morning.
Well, he better be crowning,
otherwise, I'm heading up there
with forceps.
Namaste, ladies.
Sure.
I've been cleansed in fire,
now I must be baptized in ice.
What the hell does
that even mean?!
He used up all the hot water,
so now he's gonna roll around
naked in the snow.
Oh, great.
So we're gonna have a seven-foot
nude hippie
making snow angels
in the backyard.
He is not like
me and you.
He is an old soul.
Sees the world through
a third eye.
Yeah, I just hope our neighbors
don't get a good look
at his third eye.
That's gross.
I know it's gross!
I'm tired!
I'm telling you, man,
living alone
is the way to go.
I can't believe
I waited this long
to move out
of my grandma's house.
I can't believe she stacked
all your stuff
in the driveway and pushed it
into the street with her car.
She was helping me move.
My grandma can't carry
all those boxes
with that bad back of hers.
Bad back didn't keep her
from dancing in the street
as you drove away.
Point is, I'm on my own.
I can do whatever I want,
whenever I want.
You know what I did last night?
Is it something I'm gonna want
to hear while I'm eating?
I sat buck naked on my couch...
No, it is not.
...watching an X-rated
lesbian movie,
and nobody said "boo."
Allow me. Boo!
Hey, I sat on a pot holder.
I'm not an animal.
Well, I'm glad you're making
the most of your sweet freedom.
Well, you'll get a taste
of it tonight
when you come over to watch
that fight on pay-per-view.
Oh, I can't.
It's Molly's birthday tomorrow
and her wish list has become
a ransom note.
What are you talking about?
I already paid for the fight.
Plus I've been crockpotting
chili for two days!
Well, you can always
freeze that.
But I made enough for you...
where am I gonna get
that kind of freezer space?
Carl, what can I tell you?
It's my wife's birthday.
Do what you want to do.
It doesn't matter to me
because I like being alone.
In fact, I prefer it.
You know what
I'm gonna do right now?
I'm gonna go sit
in the squad car by myself
and enjoy
a little quality time.
What's the matter
with him?
He has never lived by himself,
and like the rest of us,
he has discovered that
a little bit of Carl
goes a very long way.
You're kidding.
I thought he was having a ball.
Well, last night he called me
four times just to talk.
And now I know he was naked
and sitting on a pot holder.
Thank God I didn't let him
Skype like he wanted to.
(groans)
VINCE:
Oh...
Oh-oh... Ooh!
Oh, oh, there it is.
That's Daddy's spot. Oh!
I thought you didn't like
getting a rubdown
from another man.
I usually don't, but this
doped-out longhair has got
the hands of an angel.
Shh. Find your center.
You already found it,
and I think
your thumb's in it. Oh!
Hey!
(shrieks)
That's not the welcome mat
I wanted to see!
ALL:
Namaste.
Tom's giving us all
shiatsu massages.
He's adjusting my chakras.
Did I say it right, Weird Jesus?
MOLLY:
Mom, kitchen!
All right!
Hey, don't wear out
those thumbs.
I got a couple of chakras
nobody's been able
to find yet.
Hey, I've tried.
Why do you think my neck's
all out of whack?
Okay, how are we gonna handle
getting this guy out of here?
What are you
talking about?
He makes dinner,
gives everybody massages.
Of the men living here,
he's not the one
I'd get rid of.
Mom, are you forgetting
that Shaggy in there also
happens to be a pot dealer?
I haven't forgotten.
But the man's
giving us all massages.
We should wait before we hit him
up for free weed.
VINCE:
There go my toxins.
I'm releasing!
I'm moving. I'm moving!
How you doing on toppings?
'Cause I could chop more onions
and grate some cheese.
I'm good on
fixings, Carl.
Well, anything you want,
just holler.
If I ain't got it,
I'll go get it.
I worry that all
this love is being wasted
on the wrong person.
Shh! The fight's starting.
Oh, this is gonna be
a great bout.
These guys are
perfectly matched.
I'm guessing this is gonna go
the distance.
(bell dings)
(blows landing,
crowd cheering)
(body thuds)
I think the Mexican guy
just got knocked out.
Like hell he did.
I paid $40 for this fight.
He's gonna...
Get up!
Carl, it's over.
His mouthpiece
is in the third row
and his teeth
are still in it.
(bell dings three times,
turns off TV)
Well, that was fun.
What do you want
to do now?
Well, I DVR'd that
lesbian porno movie
and I only watched,
like, four minutes of it.
Let me get this straight.
You're asking me
to sit next to you on a couch
while we watch
an adult movie?
It's that or Yahtzee.
Roll the film.
And don't sit so close.
VICTORIA: ♪ You see I've been through
the desert ♪
♪ On a horse with no name ♪
♪ It felt good to be out
of the rain ♪
♪ In the desert,
you can't remember your name ♪
♪ 'Cause there ain't no one
for to give you no pain ♪
BOTH:
♪ La, la, la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la, la, la ♪
Everybody.
♪ La, la, la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la, la, la ♪
One more time!
♪ You see, I've been
through the desert... ♪
No, no, no more times.
No more times!
The horse is dead!
You really have a
beautiful singing voice.
(laughs)
I told her she
should quit her job
and share her talent
with the world.
Oh, you did, did ya?!
You know, become a
traveling troubadour
like Bob Dylan
or Jimmy Crack Corn.
Wow.
Masseuse, pot dealer
and a career counselor.
Hey, you got
to have faith.
- Just leap and the net will appear.
- Oh, yeah.
A net will appear, Tom,
and it's gonna be two guys
in white jackets
throwing it on you and then
tossing you in the back
of a panel van.
Hey, who wants
homemade gelato?
VICTORIA:
I do.
Molly, what don't you like Tom?
I just think
he's a bad influence.
And I don't want you to end up
living in some compound
washing his feet with your hair.
It would appear that someone
got a head start on the gelato.
Uh, it's cool.
They just need to know
that they're gonna be high
for about five days.
What do you mean high?
Hi.
Do we have
any more gelato?
Not for you we don't.
You happy? My husband,
the police officer,
is now stoned out of his gourd.
If you're worried they're
gonna check his urine,
Tom can get
you clean pee.
Absolutely
and the first jar is free.
I'm gonna hit him.
I'm gonna punch him
in his hippie face!
No, Tom take care of this.
I'm on it. I'll
navigate his flight.
Hey, big buddy,
hows about you and I
go for a nice walk
in the fresh air?
Okay, and I'll
be right here
when you get back.
(laughs)
Are you happy?
You turned my husband, the cop,
into a dope fiend.
Don't worry, Tom is
a total expert
at guiding people down
from a total freak-out.
He got away.
What?
(grunts)
(dog barking)
(roars)
(dog whimpers)
(violin playing nearby)
♪ ♪
(screams)
(Mike yelling)
Oh, my God, do you realize
that Mike could lose
his job over this?
Don't blame me...
he was the one that ate
all the ice cream without
asking what's in it.
That's what he does.
He once drank a whole pan of hot
dog water thinking it was soup.
Okay, then it's my fault
then, just blame me.
You blame me
for everything.
Victoria,
you are 32 years old.
You can't keep living
your life like a teenager.
What is wrong with
having a good time?
I am not hurting anybody.
My husband is stoned
and running amuck.
Well, you never make
mistakes, do you?
Little Miss Perfect.
Molly gets good grades,
Molly only dates single men,
Molly doesn't wake up
under bridges.
Slow down, slow down.
Is that him?
No, big stack of tires.
Keep driving.
Boy, you put a head
on those things,
that could be
his twin brother.
Help me find
my husband!
Don't yell at me!
(grunting)
(car horn beeps, Mike yelps)
Oh...
Hey...
(laughs)
You cold?
(grunts)
How you doing, buddy?
Ah!
Warm?
(laughs)
(yelling)
(car alarm wailing,
Mike yelling)
(grunting)
Booyah, Park Place!
Pay up, bitch...
you uptown now.
(knock on door)
Oh, if only I were.
Oh, good, Mike's here.
We're playing Monopoly...
you're the shoe,
and I'm out of jail.
Come on in, man.
You want some chili?
Chili!
Good, you brought
your appetite.
Relax, make yourself
comfortable.
Thirsty!
Well, let me grab
you a beverage.
I got beer, I got soda pop.
I could make you a milkshake.
Mm, milkshake good.
Coming up.
I DVR'd the fight
so you can watch it
three or four times
while I make your malted.
Mmm, M&M'S.
Melt in your mouth,
not in your hands.
Just don't fill up on those
'cause I got
a tub of chili
with your name on it.
Mike!
That's right.
(sighs)
What are we
gonna do now?
We can't call
the police.
He's not picking
up his phone.
We could put flyers
up with his picture
on it that says he
answers to "Mike."
I know I said there was no bad
ideas, but that's a bad idea.
I'm sorry.
I'm just trying to help.
I think some of this
could be my fault.
Some of it?
How about all of it?
You're right.
I'm just a big,
stupid pothead
with less sense than a squirrel.
I... (sighs)
I didn't say you were stupid.
And I certainly didn't say
"squirrel stupid."
I just... I wish you made
better choices.
Probably should've just stayed
at junior college.
But when a Backstreet Boy lures
you on the tour bus,
you don't worry
that it's finals week.
Well, maybe you do.
That's bong water
under the bridge.
You know, you could
still go back.
You mean go
back to school?
Why not?
You'd be a good student
if you applied yourself.
I'm sure you've saved up
a little bit of money.
$36,000.
What?
Well, I don't pay rent.
And I haven't had to
buy a meal or a drink
since my boobs came in.
(quietly):
Wow.
Can I borrow $8,000?
We should probably keep
looking for Mike.
Okay.
Mmm.
(groans)
All right, that's the
last of the chili.
But don't worry,
I'm whipping up some
of my famous silver
dollar pancakes.
Maple syrup.
(cell phone rings)
Man, your phone's ringing again.
It might be important.
Mike's phone,
Carl speaking.
Oh, hey, Molly.
Yeah, he's right here.
No, he's fine...
we're just hanging out,
enjoying my new apartment.
Stoned?
I don't think so.
Nah, it seems like
the same ol' Mike.
Pancakes!
Yup, same ol',
same ol'.
Well, somebody's already
slept through page one
of his birthday list.
♪ Happy Birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy Birthday
to you ♪
♪ Happy Birthday, dear Molly ♪
♪ Happy Birthday to you. ♪
Aw, you remembered.
Well, you left a great
big note on the fridge.
Well, that was actually
more for Mike.
Thank you.
By the way,
I am going to the college
this morning
to sign up for some classes.
Really? That's great.
I appreciate you
believing in me.
I'll try not to let you down.
You could never let me down...
you're my baby sister.
Well, I'm gonna do it.
I mean, if not now, when?
Besides I'm going to take
a history class and if I wait
much longer, there's gonna be
a lot more to learn.
Very true and very smart.
Love you.
(door closes)
"To the best big sister
in the whole wide world."
Aw...
20 bucks?
No wonder the tightwad's
got 36 grand.
Croissants.
Oh, help yourself.
But right when you get
finished with that,
we are going to
the art museum.
Art museum?
Cool.
Aw, you're still high.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/