What are you doing here?
I just want a chance to make it up
to you and George.
I don't remember you
ever being sober.
Lost a bit of money. My money.
It's a fine thing that Ellen Love
drops into the store.
She encourages people to buy.
Maintain a professional
relationship with her.
Buying up the store on his credit.
People are talking.
He's installed Miss Love in a flat.
I'm Roderick Temple, I'm a painter.
Why don't you paint me?
But I thought we were having lunch.
Not today.
I hope you're wrong, Mr Grove.
Miss Bunting, a moment.
Miss Mardle, your assistance,
please.
Is something wrong, Mr Grove?
Mr Selfridge?
Miss Mardle, the hem of
Miss Bunting's skirts, please.
Please say it isn't true.
Miss Bunting,
this is our best lace and silk.
I'm so sorry, Mr Selfridge.
Consider that sorry and fired.
I-I-I was going to pay for
everything, just as soon as my -
You were one of the first people
that I hired.
You don't steal from your work
family.
It's a betrayal of everything
that we stand for.
Don't you see that? Don't you see
that? Yes.
I...
Increase random checks of all
departments, starting tomorrow.
I hate this. I hate it!
I-I'm all on my own with an invalid
mother, Mr Grove.
How am I to get another position,
without a reference?
Mr Selfridge takes theft very
personally, Miss Bunting.
He also takes staff problems very
personally.
Why on earth didn't you come to us?
I was too ashamed, Mr Grove.
Collect your things.
If you could get back to me...
Yes, that would be kind.
Yes, indeed.
Another hand-delivered card from
Miss Love, sir.
Make some time for Mr Grove to see
me, tomorrow.
We need to see about a replacement
for Miss Bunting.
Miss Bunting's being replaced?
Anyone can be replaced.
Good night, Miss Blenkinsop.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Smells nice. Yeah, it looks nice.
Could you butter me a little bit of
bread? Yeah.
Aggie?
Mrs Payne must have left the front
door open. Agnes, come on, girl.
Well, he can't get in, can he?
The locks have been changed.
Hello?
Agnes, you can't do this. We're a
family.
I'm out on the streets.
I don't have two brass farthings.
Hey, eat it up, George, while it's
hot. Agnes?
I need to talk to you.
Agnes, open the door!
George, are you in there?
George, it's all right.
Agnes, I'm warning you.
Open the door!
This mutton's lovely.
And the dumplings turned out well.
Agnes!
See that the car is waiting for us,
Fraser, thank you.
Pa! Where are we going, anyway?
What's the big secret?
Pavlova so close I could touch her.
Thank you, Harry. A true gift.
Bravo. Bravo. Bravo.
Bravo.
Woo!
Oh, Frank.
Her performance was so beautiful.
She was so enchanting.
I did cry. Did you? Yes.
Beatrice would have loved this.
I wish she could've been here.
How beautiful you look tonight, my
dear.
Thank you, Lady Loxley.
I've never seen Rosalie at such a
loss for words.
Rosalie. Pa!
I like the young - fresh and
untainted,
before the world gets hold of them.
But I suspect Rosalie will be safe
from that corruption,
you'll see to that.
Mr Selfridge, have we won you over
to the charms of the ballet?
The look on my wife's face would've
won me over to anything.
I've never seen you so enchanted.
What struck you so?
I don't know. Well, it was like a
moment of perfect beauty,
where everything
just came together.
I just wish everyone could enjoy
this.
You are an idealist, my dear Mrs
Selfridge.
Only the very select can enjoy such
a gift. No, I disagree.
I think every woman should have
a Pavlova moment, like this.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Madame Pavlova.
There she is.
My dear...
Bravo, Miss Pavlova, you were truly
amazing.
We Americans like to show our
enthusiasm, freely.
Stunning, beyond words. You are too
kind.
Thank you for coming so swiftly,
Frank.
A girl likes to know that she can
still summon a gentleman
at the click of her fingers.
Not even a click, Miss Love, not
even that.
So... do you have plans after the
show? Huh?
I thought, perhaps, you and I...
I want you to find out what's going
on with Harry. Oh.
What do you mean?
He doesn't come near me.
He won't take my telephone calls.
He doesn't respond to my notes.
Is there anything I need to know,
Frank?
Not that I'm aware of, Ellen, dear.
You know Harry, he's his own man.
He's my man.
Look.
Look at the things he's given me.
Anything. 'Anything I want,'
that's what he said.
Well, he's a very generous chap.
Generous? Are you blind?
Have you seen my apartment?
The best of everything.
That's not generosity, that's -
that's a man putting down roots.
Roots?
Ellen, I hope you're not...
Surely you don't think...
Why not?
Lady Loxley was a Gaiety girl.
She nabbed Lord Loxley.
I'm sure that Harry has the same
intentions for me.
He... just needs reminding, that's
all.
That's all.
Just reminding.
Mm.
Look. Oh, my dear girl.
You didn't slide down, you fell
right off the horse.
Actually, it was more of a pony, a
small pony.
You're such a liar, Violette.
It was huge. I didn't fall.
I thrashed you - Gordon, Violette,
enough!
Beatrice, please, poppet. Just a
little more egg.
Rosalie isn't telling enough.
You do know I'm going to be a
ballerina, don't you?
I thought you were going to be in
variety shows, like Ellen Love?
Couldn't I do both? You could do
anything you set your mind to.
Come on, she's a girl. Who beat you
at arm wrestling the last 10 times?
You two!
Can I please eat my breakfast?
Good morning. Mama!
Mama, was she beautiful?
Did you cry? Yes and yes.
Rosalie, didn't you tell
your sister all about Pavlova?
How do you explain female
perfection to an over-eager puppy?
Well, all puppies have to learn, I
suppose.
Best they don't pick up bad habits
from the beginning, though,
hey, Rosalie?
I should die if I could meet Anna
Pavlova.
I might have to cancel a certain
arrangement, then. What a shame.
You don't mean - I could mean
something. I could mean nothing.
Oh, Papa,
40 kisses every day for a week.
20 in the morning,
and 20 before bed.
Impressive arithmetic.
I tell you what, you make it
50 kisses and you've got a deal.
Good morning, everyone.
Morning. Good morning.
She'll be coming to the store
tomorrow
and you'll all get a chance to meet
her.
You, dear Rose, will have afternoon
tea with her.
Oh, my! Who loves me?
Who the heck in this room loves me?
We do.
Neaten the brooches.
I'd like to see your best inset
collars, please.
Finest gauze with a pearl motif,
preferably.
We're not open yet, madam.
I'm not a client, or I wouldn't be
here before doors opening.
White and a silvery grey, if you
please.
What do you want them for, madam?
For the decolletage on the
mannequins, of course.
You have to check with Miss Mardle,
Head of Accessories.
I will, send her to me. Now,
collars, please.
Did you see that, Doris?
Her skirts are around her ankles.
That motor van you're loading...
I don't see the Selfridges livery
on the side.
How often does it come? Mornings,
sometimes.
It'll be back around three, today.
It's always you that loads it?
I do what Alf and Sam tell me.
What are you getting out of it? Eh?
My wage, of course.
What else should I be getting?
Miss Irene Ravillious.
London-trained at
the House of Lucile, no less.
Our new visionary Head of Fashion.
Liberty's loss
is very much our gain.
She'll breathe new life into our
fashion department.
Isn't that right, Miss Ravillious?
Well -
In fact, she's so confident,
that women's fashion might even
surpass accessories one day.
Are you asking me, or telling me,
Mr Selfridge?
A little bit of both, I guess.
That would be acceptable.
So I'd even go so far as to predict
that, within my lifetime certainly,
it won't just be the men who can
purchase ready-made for purpose,
but also the ladies.
What do you mean?
A lady shall enter our store,
see a costume, say, 'I want that,'
and purchase the very day.
No fittings, no seamstress,
no waiting about.
All well and good, Miss Ravillious,
but surely ladies tend to...
..tend to...
Tend to what, Mr Crabb?
Shapes and sizes, Mr Selfridge.
Precisely the point, Mr Crabb.
We shall stock all shapes and sizes.
Fashion will be big one day.
Mark my words, it's just a matter of
time.
Meanwhile, I have a great event
planned.
Anna Pavlova, any of you heard of
her?
Indeed. Yes.
She will be on our shop floor.
Surely not? Yes, Miss Mardle.
The beautiful and unique Pavlova
will be on our store floor,
for all to share -
from a Duchess to a lady's maid.
An experience
they'll always remember.
She'll mingle, Mr Selfridge?
You bet she'll mingle.
I'm gonna pay her handsomely,
I might add.
Every woman should have a Pavlova
moment.
Meeting adjourned. Back to
your posts with vim and vigour.
Thank you all.
I can't help but notice that your
skirt is shorter than the usual.
Is this the coming fashion?
My skirts are shorter because I'm a
champion of the Rational Dress
Movement. The what?
I believe clothes can serve a
purpose other than mere drapery.
I use my bicycle to get about,
consequently my skirts hang an inch
or two above the norm.
And I don't bother with whalebone
corseting - too restricting.
Vigorous exercise is sufficient to
keep my figure intact.
You are entitled to your ways, of
course, Miss Ravillious,
but may I advise you on our way in
the store,
with regard to taking stock from
one department for another -
Thank you, but I use my initiative,
as the staff manual decrees.
Day's not ripe, don't mind if I do.
I'm an upside-down creature, Frank.
Day's my night, night's my day.
You're a delectable, upside-down
creature. Cheers.
I take it you've spoken to Harry?
Is he coming to see me, today?
I shouldn't think today.
He's gonna be very busy.
Oh, no, red stuff's my poison.
Thanks all the same.
Why today in particular, Frank?
Who is she?
Who? Who, Frank? I'm sure it's just
business.
That's why we press...
Anna Pavlova is
visiting Selfridges, today.
THE Anna Pavlova?
I see.
My dear, you know what men like
Selfridge are like.
He's always in hot pursuit of the
next big thing.
Take my advice
and leave well alone.
She'll be gone like a puff of air
and I'm sure he'll be -
I am the Spirit of Selfridges,
Frank. Ellen -
How can I not be there to welcome
Pavlova?
I have to be there. Oh!
Just go, Frank!
How much longer?
I'm about to drop off.
Just hold the pose, just another
while.
I get the message.
I'm being greedy. That's enough for
today.
You know, it's such a rare quality,
a woman so comfortable in her own
skin.
I'm American, maybe that's it.
No.
No, that's not it.
So when I can see - Ah-ah-ah!
When it's ready for showing at the
Chelsea Arts Club.
I was hoping to buy it as a gift
for my husband.
Come with me to the club, Rose.
You'd love it there.
There are some amazing paintings.
Now? No, no, I can't.
Some amazing paintings -
No, really, I can't.
We'll take our entrance from here.
We will have a great deal of press
in this area.
Have as many people gathered here,
just beyond a roped off area,
right here.
- All set for Pavlova's arrival?
- Yes, Mr Selfridge.
Miss Ravillious? Yes, Mr Selfridge?
We must make the most of her
presence. Sales-wise, you mean?
So it's not just about giving women
a moment to remember?
Business is about giving people what
they want.
That's what keeps over 2,000 staff
employed.
The more people purchase, the more
memories. Simple commerce.
I am open to all of
your suggestions.
Please feel free to use your
imaginations
and both departments working
together.
I welcome all of your ideas as soon
as possible.
Thank you very much.
Don't give Miss Ravillious anything
from accessories, unless I say so.
Is that understood? Yes, Miss
Mardle. Sorry, Miss Mardle.
Now, you heard Mr Selfridge,
any ideas, ladies,
before Miss Ravillious gets in
there first and shows us up...
Great idea, Miss Ravillious.
All we have to do is add the white
braiding to our existing capes.
See? How quickly can this be done?
I'll get the seamstresses to do
what they can today
then, if they sell, we can put them
on shifts through the night
to be ready for tomorrow.
Excellent.
Good idea. Have my wife's initials
sewn into the cape.
I cannot wait to see her face.
Come.
I got them, Roger,
those tickets for Drury Lane.
Oh.
Josie, I'm so sorry.
Oh, no. Please don't say you can't
come.
Hettie's nurse asked for the night
off. I completely forgot.
Let me pay for them. Take a friend
instead.
It was my treat.
Another time, perhaps.
Oh, and while I'm here,
Miss Ravillious needs to know she
can't pinch from other departments.
You may find that
she is looking for white braiding
from accessories.
An idea she's putting to Mr
Selfridge as we speak.
From my department? And she didn't
ask me to go and see him with her?
It even goes with that, I think.
Mm-hm.
Victor?
Your George - you might wanna ask
him about the vans he loads.
Well, how do you mean?
Well, just that.
Just check
he knows what he's doing, is all.
What do we think, Miss Towler?
Which ribbon for rose buds? Hm?
White, Mr Leclair. I agree.
Thank you, girls.
You're welcome, Mr Leclair.
Can we make a start?
Yes, Mr Leclair. Good.
Miss Mardle, with your permission,
I'd like to move Miss Towler to the
fashion department for today.
By all means, Mr Leclair. Move all
of accessories, why don't you?
It's the way things are heading,
as far as I can see.
Only Miss Towler. Thank you.
Why not one of us?
She's no better than you or me. Hm.
Sometimes, I think I'll turn into a
boring chicken.
Cluck-cluck.
Wouldn't that be amusing, Mr
Colleano?
Let me add some flavour, Lady
Loxley.
Something original.
Of course, Lady Loxley.
Ah, Lady Mae, always a pleasure to
see you.
Quite a coup you've pulled off, Mr
Selfridge.
Pavlova in a shop.
This shop.
Actually, she's having tea with Rose
at 3:30, if you wanna join them.
I certainly would.
Your wife's company grows on me
with each encounter.
Me too.
How dare you speak about my beloved
Rossetti like that.
His paintings make me swoon.
Because they're overblown,
sentimental tosh. Here, here.
Do I get a kiss every time you
disagree with me?
Come on, Cora, kiss him.
Mrs Buckingham, is your husband a
patron of the arts also?
In a manner of speaking, yes.
Buckingham? Buckingham?
I can't say I know any other
American involved in that circle.
Anyone else?
The Buckinghams, they're relatively
new to London.
I'm so sorry, I really am running
rather late.
Oh!
But thank you so much. I'm sorry,
but I'm so late -
Tell us everything.
Has your husband commissioned
paintings of you before? Tell us.
Victor, what do you think you're
playing at?
Satisfying the lady, Mr Perez.
Gentleman's relish and a typical
Italian touch.
Chopped olives and capers. Mm.
You have an inspired touch, Mr
Colleano.
I look forward to tasting more from
you.
Any time you say, Lady Loxley.
I say in a couple of hours,
Mr Colleano.
Do let me know when Mrs Selfridge
arrives, I'm taking tea with her...
..which sadly means I shall have to
reserve my appetite
for any more of your creative
touches.
Still, the pleasure is in the
anticipation.
Don't you think? I can't rightly
say, Lady Loxley.
I like to eat when I'm hungry.
Welcome.
Beautiful. Good to see you.
Thank you, Mr Selfridge.
Gentlemen...
Such beautiful emeralds.
The finest, madam, from Columbia,
mounted on white gold and fashioned
by our designers in Hatton Garden.
Ooh!
A child in a confectionery store is
what you make of me, Mr Selfridge.
I like to spoil ladies,
Miss Pavlova.
Your presence and pleasure suit the
image we want to convey.
So how shall we transport all these
perfumes, lotions and petticoats?
Do we have enough items of luggage?
Spasibo.
Oh!
Ladies fashion, perhaps?
Oh, yes, please.
Where would you like us?
Just there, please.
I love her dress.
Oh, she's the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen in my life.
Don't you think, Kitty? Second only
to those jewels round her neck.
Wherever could your mother be?
Well, if Ma's not going, I'm not
either.
Maybe Ma's waiting for us there.
I'm surprised
she hasn't telephoned.
You are coming to.
Right, then. Off we go.
Goodbye.
Thank you for
a wonderful afternoon.
Mrs Buckingham, you simply cannot
miss what we are going to see.
It's history in the making. She's
right.
I can't, I really can't.
Help me, everybody.
We're going to have manhandle
Mrs Buckingham all the way there.
No, no, no. Tell her, Roddy. Tell
her.
Very well.
We're going to see Pavlova in the
flesh.
See? I told you you'd thank me.
Kidnap the lady, my friends.
No. No, Roddy! Roddy, a word.
Go ahead. Go ahead, we'll catch up.
Is everything OK?
What is it?
Why wouldn't you want to come to
the biggest event in town?
Because I'm supposed to be there
already.
I'm Mrs Selfridge.
They're not here for very long,
so get 'em while you can.
Follow me, Miss Pavlova.
Oh, my family's here. Excuse me.
There they are.
Hi, Mom.
Where's Rose?
I thought she'd be here.
No.
Come meet Miss Pavlova.
Miss Pavlova, this is my mother,
Madam Selfridge.
How do you do? Anna Pavlova...
I say, she's every bit as perfect
as the chief said.
Some night this week, Roger, yes?
Depends, my dear. Some of
the nurses do require supervision.
It is really about the nurses
though, isn't it? It's not me.
Of course not.
We can't talk now, Josie, you know
that. Yes.
It was wrong, I should've just told
you the truth.
Yes, you should've.
It's just... everybody know the
Selfridge name and I just...
I guess, I just wanted to have
something that was, well, my own.
Do you know, my father's right?
I am an idiot. Oh, don't say that.
No, I am. You're so kind and
talented. Kind and talented?
I love our time together. Please,
say we can still be friends.
Friends? Yes.
It's no match for the famous Mr
Selfridge though, is it?
You knew I was falling in love with
you.
What was it? What? Was it revenge
for Ellen Love? Was that it?
Half of London knows, don't tell me
you don't.
Harry and I have our bond.
How could he risk losing you?
It's in his nature, he risks the
things that he loves.
And it's my nature
to remain in love with me.
I should go.
Rose, please.
Ellen Love, I didn't...
Please, forgive me.
I was tempted, Roddy.
I owe you that much honesty, at
least.
Gentlemen, it's Miss Love.
Miss Love, this way. Miss Love.
Over here, Miss Love, and a nice,
big smile.
Over here, please, Miss Love.
Now, are you sure this is a good
idea?
Don't be silly, Frank.
Mr Selfridge.
Miss Pavlova, I had to come and see
you.
Ellen Love, the Spirit of
Selfridges.
I don't think I...
Do you dance, Miss Love?
Oh, I surely do. What fun.
Another dancer, Mr Selfridge.
Miss Love is of a contemporary
variety. Doris. Doris, look.
I'm fascinated by this new dance
movement in Europe.
I visited the Isadora Duncan School
in Paris.
It was quite extraordinary.
Or do you favour this more modern,
Bohemian style?
Miss Love sings as well as dances.
Don't you, Miss Love? Yes.
It's so very kind of you to welcome
Miss Pavlova,
but we can't keep you any longer,
Miss Love, please.
Oh, no. No!
Not at all. I have to a photograph
with Miss Pavlova.
Miss Pavlova.
Good publicity.
So sorry about this, Harry.
Coo-ee, boys! Over here!
Dad... A little Champagne?
I'm a customer. Please, Dad.
I've come in to do some shopping.
Dad, people are...
You boys do make me smile.
Beauty and elegance,
that's what the store is all about.
Please - You're a shop girl!
Get that drunk out of our store.
Yes, sir.
You bitch! You should be ashamed of
yourself.
I'm your father, anyhow.
You little bitch.
Happy now?
Thank you, boys. That's enough.
Ellen, with me, now, please.
Mother, will you take the children
to the restaurant?
Come along, children. Go ahead,
we'll see you soon.
Aggie!
Aggie! Agnes, you call this urchin
off me, or you'll be sorry, girl.
Will you please just go?
Lost your job, have you?
See, you're no better than me, my
girl.
You and that stupid, little chump.
You're right. You've ruined
everything.
You've done your damage, now what
more do you want?
I want...
I want some respect from my own
flesh and blood.
I will never respect you.
I hate you.
Now get out of here.
Your Pa is the reason you didn't
want me coming round your place.
I thought it was me.
It'll be all right, Agnes.
No, it won't, Victor.
He'll keep coming back.
Miss Bunting got sacked for a lot
less.
Go to him. Explain.
Mr Selfridge'll understand.
How could he understand what it's
like to have a father like that?
He'll think I'm scum.
Hey.
No-one would ever think that about
you.
I'll look after you, Agnes.
Honest, I will.
You've got your own family to look
after, Victor...
..but thank you.
Oi! Walk your sister upstairs
is what you need to do -
But I have to - ..or there'll be
two of you looking for a job.
And to show you the extent of our
gratitude to Miss Pavlova,
we have one more gift to bestow.
What could it be, Sonya? I can't
imagine, Madame.
You were saying about
a new sable...
You shall have a new sable too.
And there is more? Ah, yes.
The most prestigious gift our store
could offer.
Your very own window.
I think a photo is in order.
You've given her a window?
Keep your voice down.
Please - But, Harry - Let's get you
out of here, Ellen, right now.
Will you call on me, this evening?
Listen, your contract with
Selfridges is over.
All right? Come on. Harry.
Harry, why would you say that?
You've crossed the line.
My family is here.
I don't see your wife anywhere.
My wife is not your concern. The
point is, your reckless nature.
Please, Harry. Please don't leave
me. Please, Harry.
You can keep the flat and whatever
you want. Goodbye, Ellen.
I'm sorry. No. Frank, take her home,
please. Please.
I'm sorry.
Come on, Ellen.
Come on, dear.
Henri? Would you excuse me?
I wanna talk to you about Miss
Pavlova's window.
Indeed, Mr Selfridge.
I know exactly what I want and I'm
gonna work on it with you myself.
I want it to be the talk of London
and I need it on display -
Let me guess, this evening?
Exactly.
Now, if anyone could tell me
where the hell Rose is...
I'm sure you will love it.
Mom? Where's Mom?
Thank you, Fraser.
Mom!
I danced with Anna Pavlova.
Lady Mae clapped her hands off.
I brought you a Pavlova cape
with your initials on it.
Where were you, Ma? Have you any
idea what you've missed? I do.
I'm sorry, everyone,
I wasn't feeling very well.
Right, everyone get ready
for dinner, please.
Better now, Mama? I'm much better.
Thank you.
Come on, dear.
Should I be worried? No, no, I'm
feeling... I'm much better.
You must have been feeling very bad
to miss tea with Pavlova.
I appreciate your arranging that
for me, Harry...
..but I couldn't make it.
From the shop you love,
on Marylebone Street.
Violet creams. Your favourite.
Yeah.
And I've arranged to stay
the night, after all.
I'll get fat.
You're lovely.
Very lovely.
The window.
It's beautiful, Madame.
All in.
Are you sure, Harry, old chap?
Why aren't you at the store? I left.
Who the bloody hell are you?
I have certain conditions to put
before you.
I'm here to tell you
that your husband has not been
faithful to you.
Oh, no, you don't. We need to have
this out.
I'm meant to feel sorry for you?
Well, maybe I will tomorrow,
but tonight you can go to hell!
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.