You don't steal
from your work family!
I'm so sorry, Mr Selfridge.
I don't see the Selfridge's
livery on the side.
It's always you that loads it?
I do what Alfie and Sam tell me.
You're a shop girl.
Lost your job, have you? You've done
your damage. What more do you want?
I am Selfridge.
You knew I was falling
in love with you.
Was it revenge for Ellen Love,
was that it?
Your contract with Selfridge's
is over.
I don't see your wife anywhere!
My wife is not your concern.
Goodbye, Ellen.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
This seems a rather expensive
enterprise, Mr Selfridge.
It will more than pay for itself.
How will we get it in the window?
Don't worry about that.
Henri's an old hand.
We'll dismantle it
and then put it together.
My God! It worked like a dream
for us at Marshall Field.
But back then,
there were only 1,500 registered
drivers in the whole of Chicago.
In London today, there are over
36,000. They'll come, they'll see,
they'll walk inside
and they'll buy the products.
Isn't she a beauty?
This automobile is not insured
for anyone to drive.
Not even you, Mr Selfridge.
Ah!
What do you think?
Magnificent!
How is the window shaping up?
"Motoring for the Modern Age!"
Well, I miss Agnes Towler's
keen eye.
So get her to work with you.
I can't. She's gone.
Gone?
What? Didn't you know?
After that business with her father,
she has left.
Well, at least
George is still in work.
Without his wages,
I don't know where we'd be.
You'll look out for him, won't you?
Course I will.
My dad's come back.
I thought you'd changed the locks?
He turned up last night, drunk,
passed out on the stairs.
My landlady told me
if I didn't get him out of the way,
that we'd all be out.
We'll have to work out something.
He can't stay here forever.
I've been thinking...
maybe it's not so bad
you left your job.
What?
Well, for you and me.
We can go out together now.
How about we go down
to Brighton this weekend?
Brighton? What would we do there?
Walk on the beach, go down the pier,
hold hands in the moonlight.
I know you're trying to cheer me up,
but I'm not in the mood.
I'm asking if I can court you.
That's what I'm doing!
Oh, I see.
Hadn't it crossed your mind at all?
Not really.
Well, maybe a bit...
A bit?
Well, I suppose that's a start.
I like you, Victor, you know I do.
But I'm more trouble than I'm worth.
What with George and my dad,
and me without a job.
You don't want to court me.
I do. More than anything.
Are you my girl then?
I think I must be.
Miss Towler available?
I always deal with Miss Towler!
I can't imagine wearing
that over my face.
Keeps the flies out of your mouth,
I suppose.
Lady Carlyle's here, Miss Mardle.
She wants to see all the
motoring gloves that we've got.
Well, show them to her!
She's asking for Miss Towler.
Tell her Miss Towler has left,
but you can help her.
Shoulders back, good diction.
Those are the most supple leather
we have, Lady Carlyle.
The abrasions on the palm allow the
driver to grip the steering wheel.
What are we to say to customers
about Agnes, Miss Mardle?
You'll be courteous and assist them
with whatever they are looking for.
Now get on with your work, Doris.
It must say 'Motoring',
at a glance. What do you have?
This is the Dorothy Levitt blazer,
inspired by the great motorist
herself.
A woman could wear this anywhere,
walking, bicycling,
even to a garden party. No?
I have just the coat.
It's new in.
It also comes in leather.
A lady in leather -
does that appeal, Mr Leclair?
Very much, Miss Ravillious.
Leather is good, thank you.
Do you have an appointment
to see Mrs Selfridge?
She'll see me.
Just tell her I'm here.
Rose!
Mrs Selfridge.
It's alright, Fraser.
Apologies, Mr Temple. I'd forgotten
that I was expecting you.
I see you've brought the painting.
Please, come in.
What are you doing here?
Look, I, erm... I came to apologise
for the other day.
I was rude to you and...
Well, I've been feeling awful
about it.
I'm sorry too. I shouldn't
have lied about who I was.
No.
Friends?
Mm. It depends.
On what?
On this!
Come on, I'm dying to see it!
Can I?
Yes. Please...
I can't believe you've finished it!
What do you think?
It's nothing like
you've done before.
I told you, you inspire me.
It's good. It's really good.
Thank you.
Harry will like it.
I don't want him to have it.
Don't you see?
Now you've brought it into the
house, I have to give it to him.
I have responsibilities and
I've been pretending I haven't -
Your husband neglects you.
No, I love him and...
he loves me too, in his own way.
Not like I could.
Who are you?
Erm... I'm a friend of
your mother's.
This is Mr Temple, and...
he's been painting my picture.
I'm gonna give it to Pa
as a present.
Your painting!
Yes, I used to paint,
before you came along.
Now, run along to Grandma.
I'm just gonna see Mr Temple out.
Oh, and Beatrice darling, erm...
don't tell anyone about this.
It's a surprise.
Oh no!
Will she say anything?
I don't know. You have to go.
You have to go!
I can't.
You're not a conventional person
at heart.
Don't stifle your true self.
This may be your last chance.
No...
No.
You'll see me again.
You can depend on that.
How fast does it go?
Forty, fifty miles an hour.
When you're behind the wheel
of one of these,
you feel like you're going so fast,
that nothing can touch you.
Wow! I wanna drive one.
You will one day.
Uh-oh!
We've been spotted, Gordon!
Be brave, prepare for....
Come here, you!
I've got a secret
that I can't tell you.
You do? Well, I'm gonna
tickle it out of you! Come on!
What is it?
What time is it? Is it late?
Harry, you shouldn't have opened it.
It was a present for you.
I didn't realise
that you missed painting.
Yeah, I don't think
I realised it either.
Who's the artist?
He's called Roderick Temple.
He caught you well.
Where did you meet him?
At the National Gallery.
And where did he paint you?
In his studio.
Harry, he's just a boy.
If I'd considered it at all
inappropriate to be painted by him,
I wouldn't have gone ahead with it!
I thought you could
hang it in your office,
on the wall opposite your desk.
But if you don't like it...
I just wish I'd known, that's all.
If you had, it wouldn't have been
a surprise, would it?
You know I value you,
more than anything.
Yes Harry, I know that.
Where are you off to so early?
There's something I need to do.
I got it.
Wait right here for me, thank you.
Give me money! Give me money!
Oh, is that the biggest one?
There we go. You had the money
the whole time, right there!
Ha ha! I'm outnumbered!
Of course, you'll have to
get yourself another job.
I mean, we can't all three of us
live off George's wages.
Who are you?
The front door was open.
I'm looking for Agnes Towler.
We don't accept gentlemen callers.
Wait in there.
Here, I've got a mate,
and he owns this pub in Poplar,
and he's looking for a bar maid.
A bar maid? What's wrong with that?
You're lucky to get the offer.
Swell downstairs for you.
I put him in the front parlour.
Mr Selfridge!
What are... What are you doing here?
I could say the same for you.
Why aren't you at the store?
I left. I won't accept it.
I'm here to take you back.
You show great potential.
You remind me of myself
when I started out.
Grasping for every chance,
keen as mustard to learn.
You love it, don't you?
The customers, the selling, the feel
of the merchandise under your hands.
I love it more than anything.
That's why I don't wanna lose you.
Come back. Who cares what happened
with your father?
If you don't, no one else will.
But Mr Selfridge, don't you?
You're not him.
All the, erm...
I can't seem to find my way
out of it, that's the trouble.
Every time I try to set myself and
George up without him, he finds us.
Thank you.
Is he in the house now?
Let me go talk to him.
Who the bloody hell are you?
Harry Gordon Selfridge.
I have certain conditions
to put before you.
What conditions?
Leave London immediately.
Live anywhere you like as long
as it's a good distance from here.
Who the hell do you think you are?
You come round here,
and you think that
you can tell me what to do?
This should pay for your travel,
keep food in your stomach
while you look for work.
Oh, I get it.
You have taken a bit of a shine
to my Aggie.
Tell me, has she offered
her services to you?
Argh!
Understand me!
If you drink your way through this
and end up on the street,
you will not return to London
to bother your daughter!
You will not contact her,
you will not come to my store
and seek her out.
I will not let you ruin her life!
All right, stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop! Stop! Please! Stop!
Please!
Do we have an agreement?
Hello, son.
'Your pa ain't no war hero.
He ain't dead either!'
'My ma says he's alive
and living in Freemont...'
Pa?
Who is that lady, Pa?
Why aren't you at home
with Ma and me?
Your ma's high-toned bullshit
did it for me,
that's why I never came home.
But I'm your blood and you're mine,
whether you like it or not...
Mr Selfridge? Mr Selfridge?
Mr Selfridge?
Is everything all right?
He'll be gone by the time you
get back from work this evening.
What do you mean?
Just what I say - gone.
In this type of situations,
it's best to make a clean break.
No fond farewells. You understand?
Grab your coat and hat.
I'll give you a ride into the store.
Well, did you enjoy the ride?
It felt like flying!
Who knows?
One day, you may do that as well.
Thank you, Mr Selfridge.
Now, you remember.
Don't apologise, don't explain.
As a tactic, it's always
worked well for me.
Thank you.
That's all right.
Look!
What's she doing back?
Can I help you, Miss Towler?
I've come back, Miss Mardle.
Well, I'm afraid
that's not possible, my dear.
It was a mistake.
I didn't hand in my notice.
If you check, I'm still employed
by Selfridge's, by Mr Selfridge.
Right, well, I will have to confirm
that with Mr Grove of course.
But in the meantime,
we can put you to use.
You can unpack the new stock.
We are embarking on
a motor driving promotion
and those lap robes
have just come in.
Very good, Miss Mardle.
You can't just swan back in.
Looks like I just have.
Miss Towler!
Hello.
You've returned to us.
That is wonderful.
Welcome back.
George lad.
Give us an 'and over here.
I'll just finish this.
Now!
Thank you.
Miss Ellen Love,
to see Mrs Selfridge.
Miss Love, what a pleasant surprise.
I'm afraid this isn't
a social visit, Mrs Selfridge.
Oh? What a pity.
Er, please,
can I offer you some coffee?
I'm here to tell you
that your husband has not
been faithful to you.
He's having an affair with me.
Well, I think I'll have some,
anyhow.
Is that all you can say?
Well, this news isn't a surprise
to me.
I knew from the moment
I first saw you two together.
But the fact that you are here,
telling me about it...
Well, that is of interest.
It suggests that
it's almost certainly over.
You're so cold.
No wonder Harry looks for
his passions elsewhere.
You've got him bad, haven't you?
He loves me.
Mm, I very much doubt that.
Harry has had many similar liaisons.
You are the latest
in a long line of chorus girls.
I'm not a chorus girl!
That, I admit, could be
a mistake on my husband's part.
Unless there is anything else...
..today is my housekeeping day.
Oh, Miss Love was just leaving,
Fraser.
And I'll have a coffee please.
Tell him I came.
And I will not be got rid of
that easily.
Is the chief in?
How's his mood?
My mood is just fine, Mr Grove.
Why? What's the problem?
Thieving in the loading bay?
What the hell
is wrong with this store?
Catch them red-handed
and throw them out on their ear.
How did you discover this?
Victor Colleano,
a waiter in the Palm Court,
came to me, voiced his suspicions.
Well, at least there's some loyalty.
I'll deal with it, Mr Selfridge.
Oh, and Mr Grove...
Miss Towler is back on the pay roll.
But she left.
If she hadn't,
I'd have dismissed her.
That would have been a mistake.
Her father behaved disgracefully.
The parent is not the child.
Not in my store anyway.
So am I to allow Miss Bunting
to return,
and turn a blind eye to
these loading bay workers?
That is different.
They stole from us.
The staff will not understand
why she has been allowed to return.
Well, then I will explain it.
Call a staff meeting this evening.
Let the heads of each department
know.
George, load that stuff
an' all.
George, I need to talk to you,
urgent! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
It's a fiddle. Don't you get it?
Bloody hell!
That is the property of Mr Harry
Selfridge! Out on your ear! Get out!
I've been loading that van!
Don't say anything. If anyone
asks, keep your mouth shut.
And I thought Alf was my friend.
I'll be your friend, alright?
Thanks, Victor.
But you need to wise up.
Your sister's out of a job,
feeling cut up.
She's ain't out of a job no more!
She found something?
She's back here, isn't she?
She's back at Selfridges.
I want to put a whole family
in it.
Father, mother, children.
And the motor will be at an angle,
so it is almost flying.
You know for the children,
it has to be like a fairy tale.
They are going to the park, straw
hats, which they wave in the air.
Scarves, flowing out behind them.
A sailor suit for the boy.
A little white pinafore
for the girl.
It's going to be beautiful!
I'm glad you're back.
This could be an exciting time
for you.
Mr Selfridge has brought you
back personally.
Mr Selfridge is THE best man
in the world!
He is?
He hasn't just given me my job back.
He's, erm... He's persuaded my dad
to leave town.
I can't tell you
how good that feels.
You know, the world is opening up
to you.
There is so much to learn,
if you reach out and take it.
So, Miss Love's day is over.
The question is -
who will take her place?
He overrides
every decision I make.
I'm his Chief of Staff!
In an emergency,
I would take over running the store.
But he doesn't value me.
Roger, I'm sure
that's just not true.
Perhaps it is I
who should tender my resignation.
No, you mustn't!
You're the only one
who really understands me.
Miss Mardle.
Lady Loxley.
How can I help you today?
I'd like to see your collection
of foot muffs, for motoring.
Very good!
Thank you!
Staff meeting, 6 o'clock, downstairs.
Mr Selfridge.
Lady Mae, what a pleasure!
Tony Travers.
How's the family?
How's the charming Rosalie?
Oh, she's well, thank you.
Good. And dear Mrs Selfridge?
Oh, she's well too.
I didn't know you wife was
the artistic sort, Selfridge.
I saw her at the Chelsea Arts Club
the other day.
She was having a pretty good time
with Roddy Temple.
He's been painting
a portrait of Rose.
Oh, how wonderful.
I didn't get a chance to thank you -
He's a Bohemian sort of chap,
and The Arts Club
is a pretty racy place.
I wasn't expecting to see
Mrs Selfridge there.
Tony, you are so behind the times.
Since the Duchess of Rutland
started to frequent it,
everyone who's anyone
wants to be seen there.
How clever of Mrs Selfridge
to gain entrance.
And now, if you'll excuse me.
That was childish.
Well, I enjoyed myself.
If you're going to do something
like that, tell me first.
Aren't I even allowed
to think for myself?
No! That's not the point of you
at all.
In fact I'm no longer sure
what the point is.
Well then, if you'll excuse me.
You're a man of many talents.
You can't want to work here forever.
Do you have ambitions?
I want to open my own restaurant
in Soho.
I have friends and some influence.
I also have a chef
with whooping cough.
Come and cook for me this evening.
We could perhaps discuss this matter
further?
What an interesting painting
of Mrs Selfridge.
Miss Blenkinsop!
I'd like 40 white roses
sent round to my wife.
No, make it 50.
I thought we decided yesterday,
it was a good thing
you don't work here - for us.
Mr Selfridge came over himself.
He asked me back,
gave me a ride in his motor!
Victor, I've never felt so proud!
I suppose we can court anyway,
on the quiet.
Come on, get your coat.
Let's get out of here.
Oh, Mr Selfridge is giving a talk.
He won't miss us.
I have to stay.
After, then.
How about I take you out for a meal?
My uncle's got this place in
Clerkenwell. I can't, not tonight.
I said to Mr Leclair that I'd
help with the window for tomorrow.
That man snaps his fingers,
you come running.
I want to be with you.
I want that too.
But I promised Mr Leclair.
If I let him down, it'd be as if
I was letting Mr Selfridge down.
What about letting me down?
You'll say anything to get your way.
You know, I'm fed up
of being told what to do.
I'm not telling you what to do.
You have to wear white
to be presented, Lady Mae says.
All the young girls do.
This one's pretty, don't you think?
I'm not sure about the train.
You must have a train!
And I have to get used to them.
When I eventually get presented,
the train has to be no less
than three yards in length
from the shoulders.
It sounds rather ornate.
It's tradition.
For you, Mrs Selfridge.
Oh!
White roses, they are so beautiful!
From Harry?
Thank you, Fraser. Will you put them
in water? I'll arrange them later.
How lovely they are!
I hope I find a husband like Pa.
I wanted to talk to you
about something
that's very important to me.
Honesty.
We believe in upright behaviour
in this store.
Every customer can trust
they are getting exactly
what they're paying for.
They make a lovely couple,
don't they?
I am proud of that!
I hope you are proud too.
But even here, standards can slip.
You steal from this store,
you steal from yourselves.
Now, you all probably know
I started off as an errand boy.
I was ten years old,
I earned a dollar fifty a week.
The day they promoted me to
stock boy, I damn near cried.
And then when they gave me the key
to open up the store
in the morning...
that's the day that I...
I won't forget.
The manager trusted me.
Without trust,
you can't run anything.
I guess what I'm trying to say is,
I won't tolerate dishonesty.
But I'm here for you,
if you need my help.
Recently, a member of our staff
thought she had to leave her position
because a member of her family
behaved foolishly.
Now, it wasn't her fault, so
I refused to accept her resignation.
I would have done the same for
any of you in the same situation.
If you are in trouble,
come to me, don't steal from me.
Honest endeavour, together.
This is the Spirit of Selfridge's.
Your ladyship,
Mr Colleano to see you.
I'd given up on you.
Shame. I've got some
spatch-cock quail in here.
You've brought spatch-cock quail
into my sitting room?!
Thought I'd serve it up
with a salsa verde.
But if you don't want it...
Well, you're here now.
Show Mr Colleano the kitchen.
Brooooom!
Hey, Pa!
Is the motor in the window yet?
Going in tomorrow.
Can I come see it?
You sure can.
See ya!
Alright!
Humphrey was now after something
else. He had made several traps -
Did you like the flowers?
I loved them.
I meant every word of the message.
You're blushing.
I am not!
Not like you did when
the painter man kissed you.
Then you went really red.
You're a good cook.
Sit down.
Help yourself to a glass of wine.
So Mr Colleano...
Or may I call you...? Victor.
Victor. Tell me all about yourself.
Start from the beginning.
It suits you.
You should wear more colour.
Mr Leclair!
I'd like to give it to you
for all your hard work tonight.
I couldn't accept this!
Take it. I'll pay for it tomorrow.
Goodnight.
Thank you.
Good night.
Oh no, you don't!
We need to have this out.
It's bad enough that you kiss him
in this house -
but you do it in front of Beatrice!
Her own mother.
And then, you lied to me.
You said that everything
was gonna be alright.
But you're having an affair,
with some two-bit painter!
You even sent the portrait
to my office!
What's happened to you, Rose?
Ellen Love paid me a visit
this morning.
Ellen? What did she want?
Why does it have to be one rule for
you and another for the rest of us?
Whatever she said, it's not true.
So you're telling me you're
not having a relationship
with Miss Love?
It's over.
And what about you?
Have you been with him?
No.
But would you blame me if I had?
I'd just be following your example.
Don't say that.
All these years I have sat at home,
while you've gone out
and had your fun!
Do you think that
I want to be this way?
Do you think that it makes me happy?
Now I'm meant to feel sorry for you,
is that right?
Well, maybe I will tomorrow.
But tonight - you can go to hell!
Another one.
Drinking, old boy?
Yeah.
Not like you.
And losing too.
I've lost a packet.
What can I get you?
Whiskey.
What happened?
Well... Ellen paid my wife a visit
today.
Uh-oh!
Rose thinks I'm no damn good.
She may be right.
Normally I stay off this poison.
My father had a penchant for it.
Really?
You mother paints the Major
as a bit of a saint.
Let's just say -
Ma likes to remember the good times.
What are we drinking to?
Anything you like.
To my father!
The Major.
To Pa and everything
that he stood for!
Cheers.
More cards, that's what I need.
Shouldn't you call it a night?
Mr Selfridge?
Yeah.
Someone to see you.
I'm sorry, I couldn't stop her.
What are you doing here?
I told your wife,
and I'll tell you -
I won't be cast off
like a piece of nothing.
You're doped up and you're not
thinking straight. Just go home.
The flat's not the same without you.
Please, Harry. Come with me.
One last time.
I'm sorry if I misled you,
I really am.
But you have to understand,
I have a family.
You're just the same
as all the others!
You are a whore mongering,
low-life bastard!
Time to go, old thing. Time to go.
Please don't do this to me, Harry.
I love you. Come on!
I love you.
Let's go.
Thank you, son.
Harry, old chap? I put her in a cab.
I'll go and check on her later,
see she's all right.
Go home. Get some sleep.
'I've got a secret
that I can't tell you!'
Ellen?
Jesus!
Harry. You came.
Come on, let's get you up.
'Your father's no war hero.'
'I can't seem to find my way
out of it.'
'Dad, you're nothing
but a common huckster.'
'But I'm your blood and you're
mine whether you like it or not.'
'Come with me... with me...'
Not like you did
when the painter man kissed you.
'All these years
I have sat at home!'
'..low-life bastard!'
'Have your fun!'
'You're nothing
but a common huckster.'
'Nothing but a common huckster.'
'Who are you?'
As you all must have heard
by now,
the Chief had a serious
automobile accident.
I am Chief Of Staff.
This ship needs a Captain.
I am that man.
Taking it bad, isn't he,
your Mr Leclair?
He's not MY Mr Leclair.
The Suffragettes are walking past
the building tomorrow.
Some of the stores
are very worried about it.
They are not to set foot within
these four walls. Is that clear?
We've got a real problem
on our hands tomorrow.
Unless we do something about it,
the store could be in real trouble.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.