1
00:00:02,010 --> 00:00:03,420
《下一站歌后》前情提要
Previously on "Nashville"...

2
00:00:03,420 --> 00:00:04,950
这绝对是轰动性的
This is gonna be huge.

3
00:00:04,950 --> 00:00:06,090
我觉得我做不到
I don't think I can do this.

4
00:00:06,090 --> 00:00:07,530
你能做到  你可以的
You can. You know you can.

5
00:00:07,530 --> 00:00:09,860
我应该放你走
I need to be lettin' you go.

6
00:00:09,860 --> 00:00:11,740
所以你来找我是想重寻心声
So you came to me to find your voice again?

7
00:00:11,740 --> 00:00:13,740
有时候你得打破常规
Sometimes you gotta blow up the box.

8
00:00:13,840 --> 00:00:14,980
你来这儿做什么
What the hell are you doing here?

9
00:00:14,980 --> 00:00:16,470
我来接我哥哥
I came to pick up my big brother.

10
00:00:16,470 --> 00:00:17,110
我吉他哪儿去了
Where's my guitar?

11
00:00:17,110 --> 00:00:19,580
我很快就会还你的  我保证
I'm gonna get it back for you real soon, I promise.

12
00:00:20,370 --> 00:00:22,520
恭喜你  市长先生
Congratulations, Mr. Mayor.

13
00:00:22,520 --> 00:00:24,370
你总是能迷得这些女孩围着你团团转
Well, you just got all the girls following you around here.

14
00:00:24,370 --> 00:00:25,770
这是我的侄女  赛
This is my niece, Cy.

15
00:00:25,770 --> 00:00:26,880
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.

16
00:00:26,880 --> 00:00:28,700
请你别这样
Okay, please don't do that.

17
00:00:30,160 --> 00:00:31,270
我不干了
I quit.

18
00:00:32,120 --> 00:00:33,650
*他不知道自己拥有了什么*
*Who didn't know what he had*

19
00:00:33,650 --> 00:00:37,170
*直到一切消失  消失了  消失了*
*Till it was gone gone gone*

20
00:00:37,170 --> 00:00:39,580
*你找错人了*
*You've got the wrong girl*

21
00:00:39,590 --> 00:00:41,350
*因为我太了解你*
*'cause I got your number*

22
00:00:41,350 --> 00:00:44,190
*不知道你以为我中了什么咒语*
*Don't know what kind of spell you think I'm under*

23
00:00:44,190 --> 00:00:50,020
*合唱《一切会好的》  这感觉一点也不好*
*This ain't a feel-good, "Everything's fine" Sing-along*

24
00:00:50,490 --> 00:00:54,350
*你挑错歌了*
*You got the wrong song*

25
00:00:55,000 --> 00:00:59,000
{\an8}翻译：贝壳  碧落  蔷薇  爱卿  喜乐  基恩  燕窝  vero

26
00:00:59,000 --> 00:01:03,000
{\an8}时间轴：JimmyBeck    安安     校对：爱卿  Vero

27
00:01:04,640 --> 00:01:08,040
*每个人都会犯错*
*Everybody makes mistakes*

28
00:01:08,040 --> 00:01:10,800
*我们可以解决*
*We can work it out*

29
00:01:11,350 --> 00:01:18,500
*若我现在唱这一句  不是会更好吗*
*Wouldn't it be nice if that's what I was singing now*

30
00:01:18,790 --> 00:01:21,080
*可你挑错歌了*
*But you got the wrong song*

31
00:01:21,080 --> 00:01:22,970
*你的耳机里唱*
*Coming through your speakers

32
00:01:22,970 --> 00:01:26,320
*这是一首撒谎人和骗子的歌*
*This one's about a liar and a cheater*

33
00:01:26,330 --> 00:01:28,660
*他不知道自己拥有了什么*
*Who didn't know what he had*

34
00:01:28,660 --> 00:01:32,130
*直到一切消失  消失了  消失了*
*Till it was gone gone gone

35
00:01:32,130 --> 00:01:34,630
*你找错人了*
*You've got the wrong girl*

36
00:01:34,630 --> 00:01:36,350
*因为我太了解你*
*'cause I got your number*

37
00:01:36,350 --> 00:01:39,190
*不知道你以为我中了什么咒语*
*Don't know what kind of spell you think I'm under*

38
00:01:39,190 --> 00:01:45,380
*合唱《一切会好的》  这感觉一点也不好*
*This ain't a feel-good, "Everything's fine" Sing-along*

39
00:01:48,860 --> 00:01:52,240
*你挑错歌了*
*You got the wrong song*

40
00:01:52,450 --> 00:01:55,500
*你挑错歌了*
*You got the wrong song*

41
00:01:55,500 --> 00:01:59,590
*你挑错歌了*
*You got the wrong song, yeah*

42
00:02:06,210 --> 00:02:07,800
谢谢
Thank you!

43
00:02:10,440 --> 00:02:12,440
谢谢  达拉斯的朋友们
Thank you, Dallas!

44
00:02:10,440 --> 00:02:12,440
{\an8}美国南部工业城市

45
00:02:12,440 --> 00:02:15,060
我们爱你  蕾娜
We love you, Rayna!

46
00:02:15,060 --> 00:02:17,300
这种状况已经是第三场了
That is the third night that this has happened, okay?

47
00:02:17,300 --> 00:02:18,840
在他们眼里  好像我根本不存在一样
They're acting like I'm not even there.

48
00:02:18,840 --> 00:02:20,760
他是她的吉他手  你能怎么办
I mean, look, he's her guitar player. What are you gonna do?

49
00:02:20,760 --> 00:02:22,800
那又如何  这也算理由吗
So what? Is that some sort of excuse?

50
00:02:22,800 --> 00:02:23,920
好吧  我去和他们谈一下
Okay, I'll say something.

51
00:02:23,920 --> 00:02:25,260
但我们要走了  你的飞机要起飞了
But we gotta go. Your plane's waiting.

52
00:02:25,260 --> 00:02:26,450
帮帮忙  请你告诉我
Just do me a favor. Please tell me that

53
00:02:26,450 --> 00:02:28,590
庆功会之前我不用再见到她了
I don't have to deal with her until the party.

54
00:02:28,590 --> 00:02:29,600
这个...
Actually...

55
00:02:30,950 --> 00:02:32,770
她搭我们的飞机一起回纳什维尔
we're giving her a ride to Nashville.

56
00:02:32,770 --> 00:02:35,120
你开玩笑吧
You've got to be kiddin' me.

57
00:02:36,360 --> 00:02:38,270
蕾娜  精彩绝伦
Rayna. Fantastic!

58
00:02:38,270 --> 00:02:40,250
-你嗨翻了全场  -我已经忘情了
- You killed it out there! - I don't even know what that was.

59
00:02:40,250 --> 00:02:43,270
这绝对是几年来我看过最好的演唱会
Wow! Just the best concert I've seen in years.

60
00:02:43,270 --> 00:02:45,890
当然  之前最好的也是蕾娜·詹姆斯的
Actually, since my last Rayna James concert.

61
00:02:45,890 --> 00:02:47,410
2009年  在麦迪逊广场花园
Madison Square Garden, '09.

62
00:02:47,410 --> 00:02:48,890
这位是卡莉斯塔·里弗斯
And this is Calista Reeves.

63
00:02:48,890 --> 00:02:50,580
无尽唱片公司的董事长
She's the president of Countless Records.

64
00:02:50,580 --> 00:02:52,490
-见到你很高兴  -她从洛杉矶飞来见你
- Oh, nice to meet you. - Uh, she flew in from L.A. to see you.

65
00:02:52,490 --> 00:02:54,910
亲爱的  你是来见她还是我  
Came to see her or me, love? 

66
00:02:54,910 --> 00:02:56,120
见她  利亚姆
Ah. Her, Liam.

67
00:02:57,630 --> 00:02:59,700
蕾娜  我很希望能和你聊一聊
I would love to talk with you, Rayna,

68
00:02:59,700 --> 00:03:00,930
关于你下一步的计划
about what's next.

69
00:03:00,930 --> 00:03:03,650
我也想和你聊一下  不过我们的下一步
Oh. Well, I'd love to talk to you, but what's next for us

70
00:03:03,650 --> 00:03:05,660
是要坐茱莉亚的飞机
is we're about to hop on Juliette's plane

71
00:03:05,660 --> 00:03:06,750
飞回纳什维尔
and fly back to Nashville

72
00:03:06,750 --> 00:03:09,230
边山公司因为这首《选错歌》举办了庆功会
'cause Edgehill's throwing us a party for "Wrong song".

73
00:03:09,230 --> 00:03:11,360
-榜单状元  恭喜  -谢谢
- It hit number one. Congrats. - Thank you.

74
00:03:11,360 --> 00:03:13,690
好吧  一路平安  保持联系
Well, you have a safe flight, and I'll be in touch.

75
00:03:14,300 --> 00:03:15,490
见到你很高兴
Great to meet you.

76
00:03:15,490 --> 00:03:16,140
-利亚姆  -拜拜
- Liam. - See you.

77
00:03:16,140 --> 00:03:17,440
-送我一下吧  -好
- Walk with me? - Yep.

78
00:03:18,300 --> 00:03:19,860
天呐
Oh, my gosh.

79
00:03:21,030 --> 00:03:21,840
刚才感觉太棒了
That felt good.

80
00:03:21,850 --> 00:03:22,910
没错
Oh, yeah.

81
00:03:24,200 --> 00:03:25,440
她想签你
She wants you.

82
00:03:26,970 --> 00:03:28,380
挺有眼光的
Can't say I blame her.

83
00:03:29,440 --> 00:03:30,480
同志们
Guys?

84
00:03:31,510 --> 00:03:33,460
-飞机在等我们  -来了
- We got the plane waiting. - Okay.

85
00:03:38,600 --> 00:03:41,790
*剩一个引擎  飞机也能飞*
*This plane can fly on just one engine*

86
00:03:41,800 --> 00:03:45,580
*没有了爱情  我一样能活*
*This heart can beat without affection*

87
00:03:45,580 --> 00:03:50,360
*不是你不要我  是我自己退出*
*I'm not a choice, I'm a natural selection*

88
00:03:51,670 --> 00:03:54,910
*房子空荡荡也无所谓*
*Well, this house can stand just fine on its own*

89
00:03:54,910 --> 00:03:56,210
*没有你手心的温...*
*This hand's gonna move--*

90
00:03:56,210 --> 00:03:56,940
该死
Damn it.

91
00:03:56,940 --> 00:03:57,470
怎么了
What?

92
00:03:57,470 --> 00:03:59,660
这该死的吉他老是跑调  我
The damn thing keeps going out of tune. I...

93
00:03:59,910 --> 00:04:01,570
我觉得琴马有点短
I think the bridge is shot.

94
00:03:59,910 --> 00:04:01,570
{\an8}琴面板的一块桥型木片  用于支撑琴弦

95
00:04:02,480 --> 00:04:04,060
你的吉普森吉他呢
Where is your Gibson at?

96
00:04:02,480 --> 00:04:04,060
{\an8}知名乐器品牌

97
00:04:05,490 --> 00:04:09,400
我  借给一个人
I sort of, uh... loaned it to somebody who...

98
00:04:09,920 --> 00:04:11,360
他又借给了另一个人
loaned it to somebody.

99
00:04:12,870 --> 00:04:15,300
加纳  你真是好人中的老好人
That's because you're one of the good ones, Gunnar.

100
00:04:15,310 --> 00:04:17,200
你是知道好人的下场的
Well, you know what they say about the nice guys.

101
00:04:17,200 --> 00:04:18,920
好人没好报
They finish last and...

102
00:04:18,970 --> 00:04:20,360
只能跟吉普森一起终老
down a Gibson.

103
00:04:20,380 --> 00:04:22,610
如果我们继续这样写歌  你就不会啦
Not if we keep writin' songs like that, you don't.

104
00:04:22,610 --> 00:04:24,290
我只希望
Yeah, well, I just hope somebody...

105
00:04:24,870 --> 00:04:26,300
公司别只是签了我们的歌
will do more than just put a hold on it

106
00:04:26,300 --> 00:04:27,810
能赶紧开始录音
and cut the damn thing.

107
00:04:28,070 --> 00:04:30,070
我们也可以自己演出
Or we could perform it ourselves.

108
00:04:31,420 --> 00:04:32,870
冬季音乐节就要来了
Winter Fest is coming up.

109
00:04:35,150 --> 00:04:36,870
你不会想去的
Yeah, you--you don't want to be going to that.

110
00:04:36,870 --> 00:04:38,770
那不是你的菜
It's not your thing.

111
00:04:39,900 --> 00:04:41,540
有什么不能的
Why is it not my scene?

112
00:04:42,360 --> 00:04:43,780
艾弗里在那边演出
Avery's playing it.

113
00:04:45,910 --> 00:04:47,060
真的吗
Seriously?

114
00:04:47,230 --> 00:04:48,270
好极了
Awesome.

115
00:04:52,810 --> 00:04:54,100
你明天的贝尔蒙演出
I got you a $1,000 guarantee

116
00:04:54,100 --> 00:04:55,630
起码可以拿到一千美金
for the Belmont show tomorrow.

117
00:04:55,920 --> 00:04:56,910
还不错嘛
Hell, yeah.

118
00:04:56,910 --> 00:04:59,050
比上一场演出多了一千
It's a grand more than the last gig paid.

119
00:04:59,090 --> 00:05:01,340
明天晚上有什么宴会
What's the, uh, party tomorrow night?

120
00:05:01,550 --> 00:05:02,770
庆祝蕾娜·詹姆斯和茱莉亚·巴尼斯
The number one party for the song

121
00:05:02,770 --> 00:05:05,280
在莱曼大舞台唱的歌  夺得榜首
Rayna James and Juliette Barnes sang at the Ryman.

122
00:05:05,280 --> 00:05:06,360
对你来说  有机会见到
For you, it's a chance to meet

123
00:05:06,360 --> 00:05:08,420
音乐界所有的重要人物
everyone you need to know in music city.

124
00:05:09,340 --> 00:05:11,250
你是在和多米尼克一争高下吗
You giving Dominic a run for his money?

125
00:05:12,070 --> 00:05:13,610
他也许能给你辆车
He may give you a car.

126
00:05:13,610 --> 00:05:14,950
我却能给你前程似锦的未来
I'm giving you a career.

127
00:05:16,310 --> 00:05:17,670
这个背景布怎么样
What do you think of the backdrop?

128
00:05:17,340 --> 00:05:19,340
{\an8}艾弗里·巴克利乐队

129
00:05:19,330 --> 00:05:20,750
要把你的照片放前面吗
Want your picture in front of it?

130
00:05:20,760 --> 00:05:24,200
{\an8}艾弗里·巴克利乐队

131
00:05:21,680 --> 00:05:22,190
这样吧
You know what?

132
00:05:22,190 --> 00:05:25,250
把"的"和"乐队"去了
Lose the "The" and "Band."

133
00:05:26,570 --> 00:05:28,590
从此以后  只有艾弗里·巴克利
From now on, it's just Avery Barkley.

134
00:05:30,420 --> 00:05:31,500
好了  各位
All right, guys.

135
00:05:32,690 --> 00:05:33,840
咱们开始吧
Let's do this.

136
00:05:38,550 --> 00:05:40,110
有人看见我的豆酱吗
Has anyone seen my bean dip?

137
00:05:40,200 --> 00:05:41,230
什么样的啊
What's it look like?

138
00:05:41,480 --> 00:05:43,890
就是个罐头  侧面写着"豆酱"
Like a can that has "Bean dip" on the side.

139
00:05:43,890 --> 00:05:45,470
卡莉斯塔·里弗斯
Calista Reeves.

140
00:05:45,900 --> 00:05:47,010
可是比大买卖
Pretty big deal.

141
00:05:47,020 --> 00:05:50,310
她是业内最具实力的唱片公司巨头之一
Yeah. She's one of the most powerful label heads in the industry.

142
00:05:50,690 --> 00:05:52,500
也许就是最有实力的
Maybe the most powerful.

143
00:05:52,500 --> 00:05:54,890
但我下一张唱片必须给边山公司做
Well, I have to do my next record with Edgehill.

144
00:05:55,040 --> 00:05:56,860
她要的可是你未来五张唱片
Well, she wants your next five records.

145
00:05:57,410 --> 00:05:59,130
《挑错歌》引起了她的关注
"Wrong song" got you back on her radar.

146
00:05:59,130 --> 00:06:01,060
她超爱你的演绎
She loves what you did with it.

147
00:06:01,930 --> 00:06:03,060
我们合写的
We co-wrote it.

148
00:06:03,070 --> 00:06:04,390
"合"意味着"两个"
"Co-" means "Two."

149
00:06:04,490 --> 00:06:06,630
"合"其实是说"和"
"Co-" actually means "With."

150
00:06:07,590 --> 00:06:08,870
她怎么在我飞机上
Why's she on my plane?

151
00:06:09,340 --> 00:06:11,430
对了  因为她自己买不起飞机
Oh, right. 'Cause she can't afford her own.

152
00:06:12,380 --> 00:06:14,870
我离你就三英尺  我听得见
I'm 3 feet away from you. I can hear you.

153
00:06:15,670 --> 00:06:16,630
是吗
Can you?

154
00:06:16,630 --> 00:06:18,220
有意思  咱俩在台上的时候
That's interesting, 'cause when we're onstage,

155
00:06:18,230 --> 00:06:19,910
你们一副我不存在的样子
y'all act like I don't even exist.

156
00:06:19,910 --> 00:06:21,220
相信我
Oh, believe me.

157
00:06:21,220 --> 00:06:24,110
我们都痛苦地感受到你的存在
We're both painfully aware of your existence.

158
00:06:25,670 --> 00:06:27,510
那是我的豆酱
That is my bean dip!

159
00:06:27,510 --> 00:06:29,000
各位  我们是要回去参加庆功会
Guys, we are going back for a party.

160
00:06:29,000 --> 00:06:32,200
你们就  享受当下吧  拜托了
Can we--look, just have some fun, for crying out loud.

161
00:06:33,280 --> 00:06:36,050
不是回去参加茱莉亚她妈的庭审吗
I thought we were going back for Juliette's mom's court hearing.

162
00:06:36,090 --> 00:06:37,890
别说了
Stop talking.

163
00:06:40,180 --> 00:06:42,430
你看到这个没有
Hey. Have you seen this?

164
00:06:42,800 --> 00:06:45,740
《吉他手迪康·克莱伯恩被炒》
"The axe falls hard on guitarman Deacon claybourne."

165
00:06:49,390 --> 00:06:51,650
{\an8}吉他手迪康·克莱伯恩被炒

166
00:06:50,280 --> 00:06:51,780
不  不  我知道自己怎么想
No. No, no, no, no. I know what I think about it.

167
00:06:51,780 --> 00:06:53,290
我只想知道你怎么想
I just wanna know what you think about it.

168
00:06:53,520 --> 00:06:55,340
不  对  就是那篇报导
No--yeah! The article!

169
00:06:55,340 --> 00:06:55,680
是吗  
You think so? 

170
00:06:55,680 --> 00:06:57,130
你难道相信赛说
You think it's true when Cy says,

171
00:06:57,130 --> 00:06:59,470
"我们给过他机会  但是没成"
"We tried to give him a chance. It just didn't pan out"?

172
00:06:59,470 --> 00:07:02,410
不  卡门  应该是我说  确实没成
No! No, Carmen, that's what I'm saying. It didn't not pan out.

173
00:07:02,410 --> 00:07:04,380
因为我抓到他骚扰我侄女
I caught the guy mauling my niece.

174
00:07:04,380 --> 00:07:04,980
我说"无可奉告"
I said "No comment"

175
00:07:04,980 --> 00:07:06,320
是因为我想保护她的隐私
because I want her to have her own privacy.

176
00:07:06,330 --> 00:07:07,420
她应该受到保护
She deserves some privacy.

177
00:07:07,420 --> 00:07:08,510
我不想把她牵扯进来
I don't want to drag her into it.

178
00:07:08,510 --> 00:07:10,120
等等  听我说
Hold on. Listen to me.

179
00:07:10,210 --> 00:07:11,970
"让他离开乐队  很让人难过
"Letting someone go is always hard,

180
00:07:11,970 --> 00:07:14,030
但更难过的是眼睁睁看着他酒瘾复发"
but watching him fall off the wagon, that's even harder."

181
00:07:14,030 --> 00:07:16,830
你信吗  你觉得是真的吗  不是
You believe that? You think that's true? No!

182
00:07:16,830 --> 00:07:19,490
我他妈已经12年没喝过酒了
I haven't had a drink in 12 damn years!

183
00:07:19,490 --> 00:07:23,500
我告诉你  确切地说是4420天
4,420 days, to be specific, if you gotta know.

184
00:07:24,820 --> 00:07:25,840
该死的
Damn it!

185
00:07:28,000 --> 00:07:30,100
{\pos(190,220)}下一站歌后

186
00:07:28,000 --> 00:07:30,100
{\pos(190,260)}第一季  第十一集

187
00:07:30,500 --> 00:07:35,500
{\pos(70,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

188
00:07:30,500 --> 00:07:35,500
{\pos(70,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

189
00:07:30,500 --> 00:07:35,500
{\pos(60,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

190
00:07:30,500 --> 00:07:35,500
{\pos(86,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

191
00:07:30,500 --> 00:07:35,500
{\pos(100,254)}人人影视
YYeTs.com

192
00:07:30,500 --> 00:07:35,500
{\pos(101,267)}原创翻译  双语字幕

194
00:07:30,500 --> 00:07:35,500
{\pos(240,267)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

195
00:07:35,500 --> 00:07:39,500
{\an8}后期：瓜瓜     总监：Vero

196
00:07:41,410 --> 00:07:42,460
你回来啦  回家啦
You're home! You're home!

197
00:07:42,460 --> 00:07:44,860
宝贝们  好啊 
Hi, my girls! Oh!

198
00:07:44,860 --> 00:07:47,540
-我怎么会有三个护胫和一只钉鞋呢  -不是吧
- How do I have three shin guards and only one cleat? - Oh, no.

199
00:07:47,540 --> 00:07:49,050
你走的时候我掉了一颗牙
I lost a tooth while you were gone.

200
00:07:49,050 --> 00:07:50,540
你们掉了一颗牙  和一只钉鞋
Lost a tooth and a cleat?

201
00:07:50,540 --> 00:07:52,720
我走了之后世界成什么样了啊
What is the world coming to when I leave town?

202
00:07:52,720 --> 00:07:54,270
早啊
Good morning.

203
00:07:54,270 --> 00:07:56,340
有人寄给你的  宝贝们
This came for you. Hey, kiddo.

204
00:07:56,730 --> 00:07:58,660
换衣服去上学  快点
Hey, go get dressed for school. Hustle up.

205
00:07:58,910 --> 00:08:01,250
好了  五分钟后吃早饭  
All right, breakfast in five. 

206
00:08:01,250 --> 00:08:02,500
我可忙活了一早上呢
I have slaved over this stove.

207
00:08:02,800 --> 00:08:04,760
天呐  这是什么
Oh, my lord. What is this?

208
00:08:04,910 --> 00:08:07,330
你昨晚不必在客房睡的
You know, you didn't have to sleep in the guest room last night.

209
00:08:07,330 --> 00:08:09,810
太晚了  我不想吵醒你
It was so late. I didn't wanna wake you up.

210
00:08:10,180 --> 00:08:11,650
-好吧  -"希望能找时间谈谈
- Right. - "Hope we get some time to talk.

211
00:08:11,650 --> 00:08:13,740
首先  你需要一架飞机"
For starters, you need your own plane."

212
00:08:14,190 --> 00:08:15,720
确实  我该有自己的飞机
Yes, I do need my own plane.

213
00:08:15,720 --> 00:08:16,950
是情敌送来的么
Should I be jealous?

214
00:08:16,950 --> 00:08:18,930
不是啦
I don't think so.

215
00:08:19,030 --> 00:08:20,670
天呐
Oh, my gosh.

216
00:08:21,030 --> 00:08:23,480
卡莉斯塔·里弗斯  无尽唱片公司
Calista Reeves. Countless records.

217
00:08:23,480 --> 00:08:24,740
天呐
Oh, my gosh.

218
00:08:24,750 --> 00:08:25,880
现在是什么情况
What's going on?

219
00:08:27,030 --> 00:08:28,260
她显然是要谈生意上的事
Well, clearly, she means business.

220
00:08:28,260 --> 00:08:29,790
不  我是说我们
No, I'm talking about us.

221
00:08:30,450 --> 00:08:31,420
我是说
I mean...

222
00:08:31,430 --> 00:08:33,470
我们为孩子们装出和睦的样子
We're putting on a good face for the girls.

223
00:08:34,560 --> 00:08:36,540
但我们分房睡
We're sleeping in separate bedrooms.

224
00:08:37,440 --> 00:08:39,630
已经好几个月没做过爱
You and I haven't made love in months.

225
00:08:41,010 --> 00:08:44,300
我们  到底要不要重归于好
I mean, are--are we trying to fix things between us or not?

226
00:08:44,840 --> 00:08:48,100
分开这段时间本来是为了想清楚
You know, I think we took this time apart to get some clarity.

227
00:08:51,080 --> 00:08:54,930
但  我还没想好答案
And...I don't have the answers yet.

228
00:09:07,590 --> 00:09:10,580
别走来走去行吗  都被你搞晕了
Would you stop pacing, please? You're making me dizzy.

229
00:09:11,090 --> 00:09:14,100
能再跟我解释一下这个认罪协议吗
Can you just explain this plea deal to me one more time?

230
00:09:14,100 --> 00:09:15,490
很简单  乔琳
It's simple, Jolene.

231
00:09:15,890 --> 00:09:16,560
今天你认罪
You plead guilty today,

232
00:09:16,560 --> 00:09:18,080
然后完成戒毒治疗
and as long as you complete rehab,

233
00:09:18,080 --> 00:09:19,140
指控就会撤销
the charges will be dropped...

234
00:09:19,140 --> 00:09:21,520
以后再不用上法庭了
And you won't have to set foot in this courtroom again.

235
00:09:21,570 --> 00:09:22,940
这样就好
That'd be a relief.

236
00:09:23,520 --> 00:09:24,570
迪康
Deacon.

237
00:09:25,550 --> 00:09:26,860
可以进了吧
Hey, you good?

238
00:09:28,230 --> 00:09:30,500
非常感谢
Hey. Thank you so much.

239
00:09:30,500 --> 00:09:32,940
-这位是迪康  他会替我辩护   -迪康
- This is Deacon. He's gonna be speaking on my behalf. - Deacon.

240
00:09:32,940 --> 00:09:35,120
这个  刚出了一篇关于我的报导
Listen, about that. I just had this article written about me.

241
00:09:35,120 --> 00:09:36,590
我  我不确定
I... I'm just not sure

242
00:09:36,590 --> 00:09:38,300
我来发言能有多大作用
how good it's gonna be, me talking for you.

243
00:09:38,300 --> 00:09:40,740
-你是说《震音》那篇报导吗  -是
- Are you talking about that "Tremolo" Thing? - Yeah.

244
00:09:40,960 --> 00:09:42,500
什么呀  一派胡言
What was that? That's crap.

245
00:09:42,500 --> 00:09:44,570
我很清楚"不清醒"是什么样  
I know what "Not sober" looks like, okay?

246
00:09:44,570 --> 00:09:46,760
我从小看到大  不是你这样子
I grew up with it. That's not you.

247
00:09:47,390 --> 00:09:49,220
谢谢你这么说  我只是
Well, I appreciate that. I just...

248
00:09:50,070 --> 00:09:52,360
我还是觉得今天由你来说比较好
I still think it might be better if you talk today.

249
00:09:53,080 --> 00:09:54,720
不  不要
No. No.

250
00:09:54,870 --> 00:09:56,190
我给她请了位好律师  
I got her a great lawyer. 

251
00:09:56,190 --> 00:09:57,510
你可以算得是她的担保人
You're practically her sponsor.

252
00:09:57,510 --> 00:09:58,750
为什么让我来说
Why would I do the talkin'?

253
00:09:58,760 --> 00:09:59,840
你是受你妈毒瘾
Well, you're the person most affected

254
00:09:59,840 --> 00:10:01,370
影响最大的人
by your mother's addiction.

255
00:10:01,450 --> 00:10:03,810
由你来说意义重大
It would mean a lot more coming from you.

256
00:10:09,070 --> 00:10:10,400
太逊了
That sucked.

257
00:10:10,470 --> 00:10:12,040
你确实太逊了
- Hey. - Or maybe you just did.

258
00:10:12,040 --> 00:10:14,160
别说了  你...
Hey, hey, hey, hey. You...

259
00:10:14,600 --> 00:10:16,070
别对自己这么严格
need to stop being so hard on yourself.

260
00:10:16,070 --> 00:10:17,860
你快去做家庭作业
And you need to go do your homework.

261
00:10:18,400 --> 00:10:19,520
好吗
All right?

262
00:10:20,950 --> 00:10:22,210
你家真漂亮
You have a beautiful home.

263
00:10:22,210 --> 00:10:23,130
谢谢
Thank you.

264
00:10:23,130 --> 00:10:25,090
蕾娜  真是谢谢你能见我一面
Rayna, thank you so much for seeing me.

265
00:10:25,090 --> 00:10:27,000
是我的荣幸
Oh, yeah. My pleasure.

266
00:10:27,270 --> 00:10:28,480
遇球不能怕
You just can't be afraid of the ball.

267
00:10:28,480 --> 00:10:30,910
-真是幸福的一家  -谢谢
- Such a sweet family. - Aw, thanks.

268
00:10:31,300 --> 00:10:33,860
可怜的麦迪遗传了我这个运动白痴
Poor Maddie does get her athletic ability from me.

269
00:10:33,860 --> 00:10:35,400
太可怜了
Ohh, so sad.

270
00:10:35,400 --> 00:10:37,480
但你有其他天赋
Oh, well, you have other talents.

271
00:10:37,480 --> 00:10:38,580
谢谢
Thank you.

272
00:10:38,670 --> 00:10:40,420
还有谢谢你今天到我家里来
And I appreciate you coming over to the house today

273
00:10:40,420 --> 00:10:42,400
我就可以和女儿多相处一会儿了
so I could have a little more time with my girls.

274
00:10:42,400 --> 00:10:45,240
你只能在家待一天  要是我也会这么安排
You only have 24 hours at home. I mean, I do the same thing.

275
00:10:45,240 --> 00:10:46,420
我也是个母亲
I'm a mom, too.

276
00:10:48,620 --> 00:10:51,110
而且负责养家糊口  我懂你
And the breadwinner. I get it.

277
00:10:51,110 --> 00:10:52,560
万分感谢
I appreciate that.

278
00:10:52,710 --> 00:10:55,190
已经数不清有多少年
I can't tell you how many years I felt like I was

279
00:10:55,190 --> 00:10:57,170
我试图让边山公司理解我
hitting my head against a wall with Edgehill,

280
00:10:57,170 --> 00:10:58,840
却都是徒劳
trying to get them to understand that.

281
00:10:58,850 --> 00:10:59,810
利亚姆也是这么说的
Yeah, that's what Liam said

282
00:10:59,810 --> 00:11:01,960
他把你们做好的半成品寄给我了
when he sent me the last roughs of what you guys cut.

283
00:11:01,960 --> 00:11:03,900
他  他把那些歌寄给你了
He--he sent you those tracks?

284
00:11:03,900 --> 00:11:05,280
那些歌还没准备好面市呢
Those tracks weren't ready to go out.

285
00:11:05,280 --> 00:11:06,530
-绝对够格  -不够
- Ready enough. - No.

286
00:11:06,530 --> 00:11:09,600
他觉得转型的时刻到来了
Uh, yeah, he thinks it's time for a change,

287
00:11:09,600 --> 00:11:10,880
我也这么认为
and I do, too.

288
00:11:11,130 --> 00:11:13,110
你需要彻底改变
You're reinventing yourself.

289
00:11:13,110 --> 00:11:16,200
《选错歌》让你成功回到了榜单首位
"Wrong song" is great to get you to the top of the charts again,

290
00:11:16,210 --> 00:11:18,890
但你绝对不能被迫
but the last thing you need is to be pressured

291
00:11:18,890 --> 00:11:22,680
与某些自大女歌手一起合唱
into doing duets with some prefab prima donna

292
00:11:22,680 --> 00:11:25,940
她也许一夜成名  却也会瞬间陨落
who came up overnight and... can be gone just as fast.

293
00:11:25,950 --> 00:11:27,170
无意冒犯
No offense.

294
00:11:28,840 --> 00:11:30,660
我知道离开公司有多难
I know how hard leaving is.

295
00:11:30,700 --> 00:11:34,560
相信我  我离开国会大厦里也十分困难
Believe me, it was hard when I broke off from capitol.

296
00:11:34,870 --> 00:11:36,810
但这并不代表留下是正确的
But it doesn't make staying right.

297
00:11:36,810 --> 00:11:37,850
胆小鬼
Chicken.

298
00:11:38,860 --> 00:11:40,490
我才不是胆小鬼呢
I'm not your chicken.

299
00:11:40,990 --> 00:11:42,380
你知道吗...
Well, you know...

300
00:11:43,200 --> 00:11:46,260
这感觉像是一生的投入
it does feel like I sort of have a lifetime investment.

301
00:11:46,260 --> 00:11:48,640
你想做什么  发挥创意吗
What you wanna do, creatively?

302
00:11:48,920 --> 00:11:51,350
在马歇尔的操控下是不可能的
It's not in Marshall's wheelhouse.

303
00:11:52,030 --> 00:11:54,920
他唯利是图  永远不会理解你的
He's a bean counter and he's never gonna get it.

304
00:11:54,920 --> 00:11:57,470
他进入这一行只想着怎样谋取利益
He came up in this business with his head in the books,

305
00:11:57,470 --> 00:11:59,100
却根本不懂音乐
not in the headphones.

306
00:11:59,100 --> 00:12:01,960
听着蕾娜  我不是要"贩卖"你赚钱
Look, Rayna, I don't want to "Sell" You.

307
00:12:02,380 --> 00:12:04,830
问利亚姆就知道了  他能证明
Ask Liam. He can vouch for me.

308
00:12:05,580 --> 00:12:08,660
我想做你的合作人
I want to be your partner.

309
00:12:13,230 --> 00:12:15,130
{\an8}贝尔蒙冬季音乐节

310
00:12:15,530 --> 00:12:19,870
*你手中掌握着全世界*
*You've got the whole world in your hands *

311
00:12:20,350 --> 00:12:24,540
*这也正是你所计划的*
*And this is really what you planned *

312
00:12:25,030 --> 00:12:28,870
*我翻过书页  读了标红的文字*
*Well, I turned the pages, read the words in red *

313
00:12:28,870 --> 00:12:31,620
*却还是不懂*
*I still don't understand*

314
00:12:34,570 --> 00:12:38,400
*接起电话  思绪却飘向远方*
*Sat on the phone but I can't hear *

315
00:12:39,490 --> 00:12:44,090
*打开每一扇窗户  却拨不开迷雾*
*Opened every window, but it's still not clear *

316
00:12:44,090 --> 00:12:47,830
*我曾请求原谅  寻找灵魂的救赎*
*Asked for forgiveness, restoration for my soul *

317
00:12:47,830 --> 00:12:50,540
*但我仍然捧着真心*
*But I'm still sincere *

318
00:12:53,220 --> 00:12:55,730
*我曾见过天使降临人间*
*I know I've seen an angel *

319
00:12:55,730 --> 00:12:57,900
*却也惹得我哭红了双眼*
*And I know it made me cry *

320
00:12:57,900 --> 00:12:59,820
*当我望向无边的天际*
*So when I look at heaven *

321
00:12:59,820 --> 00:13:03,110
*为何要一遍一遍  问为什么*
*Why do I keep asking why *

322
00:13:10,240 --> 00:13:11,750
抓到你了
Busted!

323
00:13:14,560 --> 00:13:16,060
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.

324
00:13:18,140 --> 00:13:21,000
乔琳·巴尼斯已吸取教训了  法官大人
Jolene Barnes has learned from her mistakes, your honor.

325
00:13:21,050 --> 00:13:22,370
她不是个罪犯
She's not a criminal.

326
00:13:22,770 --> 00:13:26,950
她只是身患疾病  想要寻求治疗
She's a-a person with a disease. She sought out treatment.

327
00:13:27,080 --> 00:13:31,130
现在离她的60天戒毒项目结束还有21天
And she only has 21 more days left on a 60-day program.

328
00:13:31,210 --> 00:13:33,530
她的女儿茱莉亚在此
Her daughter Juliette is here

329
00:13:33,600 --> 00:13:35,560
为她的母亲辩护
to speak on her mother's behalf.

330
00:13:39,320 --> 00:13:40,600
说你的真心话
Speak from your heart.

331
00:13:44,480 --> 00:13:47,130
自从我有记忆开始
Um, my mother has been an addict for...

332
00:13:47,370 --> 00:13:49,170
我的母亲就是个瘾君子
as long as I can remember,

333
00:13:50,030 --> 00:13:51,820
而我...
and I'm...

334
00:13:52,210 --> 00:13:55,440
很欣慰她得到了所需要的帮助
very glad that she is gettin' the help that she needs.

335
00:13:56,370 --> 00:14:00,950
我比任何人都希望治疗能成功
There's nobody who hopes this sticks more than I do.

336
00:14:02,460 --> 00:14:04,070
我只想说这些
That's all I have to say.

337
00:14:10,800 --> 00:14:12,270
谢谢你的证词  巴尼斯小姐
Thank you for your testimonial, Ms. Barnes.

338
00:14:12,270 --> 00:14:15,200
我会考虑你所说的  再作出判决
I'll take this under advisement and render a decision.

339
00:14:16,560 --> 00:14:17,850
很快会有结果
It shouldn't be long.

340
00:14:29,510 --> 00:14:31,330
刚才你说的很精彩
That was a hell of a speech in there.

341
00:14:31,620 --> 00:14:33,370
发自内心
I mean, really emotional.

342
00:14:33,620 --> 00:14:34,770
十分感人
You know, really moving.

343
00:14:34,770 --> 00:14:37,840
是你让我说真心话的  好吗
You told me to speak from the heart, okay?

344
00:14:38,980 --> 00:14:40,480
我只能说出这些
That's all I had.

345
00:14:42,580 --> 00:14:43,600
你还好吗
You okay?

346
00:14:44,850 --> 00:14:46,690
今天事儿太多了
Just a busy day.

347
00:14:47,150 --> 00:14:48,770
没错  你还要去
Oh, that's right. Y'all got that

348
00:14:48,790 --> 00:14:51,310
那个冠军单曲庆功派对  对吗
number one song party to go to, huh?

349
00:14:52,340 --> 00:14:54,240
我应该先说一声恭喜
I guess congratulations are in order.

350
00:14:54,880 --> 00:14:57,660
别恭喜我  恭喜蕾娜去吧
Don't congratulate me. Congratulate Rayna.

351
00:14:57,840 --> 00:15:00,580
很显然这是她一个人的功劳
Apparently she's the one who did it all by herself.

352
00:15:00,580 --> 00:15:02,150
她是超级大英雄
She's the superhero,

353
00:15:02,150 --> 00:15:05,750
我只是那个帮她举着战袍的小喽啰
and I'm the person who just came in and held her cape.

354
00:15:05,830 --> 00:15:06,840
不是这样的
Yeah, well, that's not what happened.

355
00:15:06,850 --> 00:15:08,500
我记得很清楚  我当时在场
I remember. I was there.

356
00:15:09,450 --> 00:15:10,490
没错
Yes.

357
00:15:12,060 --> 00:15:13,370
现在你在我身边
And now you're here.

358
00:15:15,120 --> 00:15:16,970
我之前的提议仍然有效
You know the offer still stands,

359
00:15:16,970 --> 00:15:19,240
你可以随时加入和我一起巡演
that you can come on tour with me anytime.

360
00:15:20,110 --> 00:15:22,170
谢谢你  但是我觉得
I appreciate it, but I think I'm just gonna

361
00:15:22,170 --> 00:15:24,150
我要暂时告别巡演的生活
come off the road for a little bit.

362
00:15:24,880 --> 00:15:26,460
有可能退出舞台
Maybe even the grid.

363
00:15:26,640 --> 00:15:27,930
什么  不要啊
What? No.

364
00:15:28,850 --> 00:15:31,630
不可以  你是个了不起的音乐人
No way. You are way too good of a musician

365
00:15:32,100 --> 00:15:36,100
不该隐退  把自己藏在凌乱的胡茬后面
to hole up and hide behind patchy facial hair.

366
00:15:38,470 --> 00:15:39,880
你要回办公室吗
You going back to the office?

367
00:15:44,100 --> 00:15:46,290
-法官怎么说  -请求失败了
- What'd they say? - Well, it didn't work, the plea.

368
00:15:46,290 --> 00:15:47,210
她必须完成她的戒毒疗程
She'll have to finish rehab.

369
00:15:47,210 --> 00:15:48,120
然后还将会有一场
Then there'll be another hearing

370
00:15:48,120 --> 00:15:50,340
请求撤销刑事起诉的听证会
to try to get the criminal charges dropped.

371
00:15:50,850 --> 00:15:52,540
这样  那就还得多待几周
All right. Couple more weeks then.

372
00:15:52,540 --> 00:15:55,170
好歹今天不用回去了  何不去放松一下
Still got a free pass today. Why don't we go do somethin' fun?

373
00:15:55,170 --> 00:15:57,500
不行  我还要去那个聚会
I can't. I have to go to that party.

374
00:15:57,690 --> 00:15:59,490
我还有一个女伴名额
That I have a plus-one to I'm not using.

375
00:15:59,490 --> 00:16:00,800
-要不要和我一起  -好啊
- Why don't you come with me? - Yeah?

376
00:16:00,800 --> 00:16:03,470
不行  我觉得你不该带着一个正在戒毒的人
No, I don't think it's a good idea to have a rehab patient

377
00:16:03,470 --> 00:16:06,070
去参加一个酒精无处不在的行业聚会
at a-an industry party where there's alcohol everywhere.

378
00:16:06,070 --> 00:16:07,840
世人都喝酒  茱莉亚
World's full of alcohol, Juliette.

379
00:16:07,840 --> 00:16:09,760
我总要出去见人的
I gotta do it sometime.

380
00:16:09,770 --> 00:16:12,100
所以上帝才发明了苏打水啊
I mean, isn't that why God created sparkling water?

381
00:16:12,550 --> 00:16:14,550
我也不可能陪你闲逛
I am not gonna be able to hang out either.

382
00:16:14,550 --> 00:16:15,630
我得去和人交际
I'm gonna have to socialize.

383
00:16:15,630 --> 00:16:16,930
还得去和很多人聊聊
I'm gonna have to talk to a bunch of people.

384
00:16:16,930 --> 00:16:18,590
反正我又不想聊  没事的
That I don't want to talk to. It's okay.

385
00:16:18,590 --> 00:16:19,760
好吗  我就在她身后待着
All right, I'll just hide behind her

386
00:16:19,760 --> 00:16:21,890
不藏在凌乱的胡茬后面了
instead of my patchy facial hair.

387
00:16:23,650 --> 00:16:24,670
谢谢
Thank you.

388
00:16:26,950 --> 00:16:28,190
那一起去吧
Let's all go.

389
00:16:28,850 --> 00:16:29,980
卡莉斯塔跟我说了合同的大概
Calista outlined the deal for me.

390
00:16:29,990 --> 00:16:31,840
边山公司很难给出更高的待遇
It's gonna be really hard for Edgehill to beat

391
00:16:31,850 --> 00:16:32,890
接近都很难
or even come close to.

392
00:16:32,890 --> 00:16:34,150
确实很诱人
Well, it's tempting.

393
00:16:34,150 --> 00:16:36,800
而且无尽公司过去的成绩能说明一切
You know, and Countless' track record speaks for itself.

394
00:16:36,800 --> 00:16:39,560
但怎么说呢  我就是觉得有点
But I don't know. There's something that doesn't feel...

395
00:16:39,630 --> 00:16:41,890
卡莉斯塔很有眼力  你很有实力
Calista's a visionary. You're a superstar.

396
00:16:41,890 --> 00:16:42,800
还有什么问题
What's the problem?

397
00:16:42,860 --> 00:16:46,200
问题是我觉得这一切来得太快了
The problem is that it just feels like it's happening too fast.

398
00:16:46,800 --> 00:16:48,700
要是你没有把那些声带给她就好了
And I wish you hadn't given her those tracks.

399
00:16:48,700 --> 00:16:50,700
那些声带还不够格面市
Those tracks were not ready to go out.

400
00:16:50,700 --> 00:16:52,660
你应该先跟我商量一下的
You should've consulted with me first.

401
00:16:52,660 --> 00:16:55,340
我只是想帮个忙
Well, you know, I'm just trying to help.

402
00:16:55,340 --> 00:16:55,980
可如果你想待在这个
But if you wanna stay

403
00:16:55,980 --> 00:16:58,900
陈腐  过时又无趣的地方  随便你
in something stale, old, and boring, go for it.

404
00:16:58,910 --> 00:17:00,200
也许正适合你
Maybe that's your thing.

405
00:17:00,870 --> 00:17:02,780
把边山公司想成你的婚姻
Think of Edgehill like your marriage.

406
00:17:03,570 --> 00:17:04,550
熬过去的唯一办法
The only way to get through it

407
00:17:04,550 --> 00:17:06,780
就是迷上另一个人
is by fantasizing about someone else.

408
00:17:12,630 --> 00:17:13,460
怎么了
What?

409
00:17:14,010 --> 00:17:17,060
昨天我在广播里三次听到他的歌
I heard his song three times on the radio yesterday.

410
00:17:17,370 --> 00:17:19,160
很显然他现在正当红
Apparently he's the number one most requested.

411
00:17:19,160 --> 00:17:21,130
难道音乐界就没有天理吗
Is there no music karma?

412
00:17:21,130 --> 00:17:24,430
像加纳  迪康和你这样的人怎么办
What about guys like Gunnar and Deacon, you guys?

413
00:17:24,820 --> 00:17:26,560
加纳说的没错  好人没好报
Gunnar's right. Nice guys finish last.

414
00:17:26,560 --> 00:17:27,840
你觉得我们该怎么办
Well, you know what we should do?

415
00:17:27,840 --> 00:17:29,770
用油布把他绑起来  丢进河里吗
Wrap him in a tarp, drop him in a river?

416
00:17:30,430 --> 00:17:31,750
或者组个乐队
Or band together.

417
00:17:32,250 --> 00:17:33,430
说真的
Literally.

418
00:17:33,850 --> 00:17:35,740
我真的很想再和你一起表演
You know I'm dying to play with you again.

419
00:17:36,140 --> 00:17:37,660
我不能丢下加纳
I can't bail on Gunnar.

420
00:17:37,660 --> 00:17:40,860
我也比不上那位风光的先生  所以
And I am not Mr. Fabulous over there, either, so...

421
00:17:41,110 --> 00:17:42,830
我说的是你和加纳一起
I'm talking about you and Gunnar.

422
00:17:42,830 --> 00:17:43,940
你知道我们缺个主唱
You know we need a singer,

423
00:17:43,940 --> 00:17:47,340
我们也可以再加一个超强的吉他手
and we could use a kick-ass guitar player as well.

424
00:17:48,340 --> 00:17:49,400
好好考虑一下
Think about it.

425
00:17:49,870 --> 00:17:52,240
你们的歌  配上我们的乐器
Your songs, our rhythm section.

426
00:17:52,240 --> 00:17:54,340
将会是好人团的巨大胜利
It'd be a huge win for the good guys.

427
00:17:54,880 --> 00:17:56,540
我和加纳商量一下
Just let me run it by Gunnar.

428
00:17:56,860 --> 00:17:59,100
我的乐手  我们的扬声器  你家的车库
My guys, our amps, your garage.

429
00:17:59,110 --> 00:18:01,100
就和从前一样
Oh, just like old times.

430
00:18:01,520 --> 00:18:02,750
祝我们有好报
To good karma.

431
00:18:02,910 --> 00:18:04,350
没错
Oh, yeah.

432
00:18:10,540 --> 00:18:12,060
了不起的蕾娜·詹姆斯
The great Rayna James!

433
00:18:12,070 --> 00:18:13,780
重回巅峰  回到家乡
Back on top, back in town.

434
00:18:13,780 --> 00:18:15,530
回来参加盛大聚会的吧
Back for the big party, huh?

435
00:18:15,530 --> 00:18:16,520
是啊
Yeah.

436
00:18:17,650 --> 00:18:18,790
你在干嘛
What are you doin'?

437
00:18:18,890 --> 00:18:20,760
我也要去参加聚会
Uh, well, I'm-a go to the party, too,

438
00:18:20,760 --> 00:18:24,580
然后回我的小木屋待一阵子
And then I'm gonna go to the cabin for a while.

439
00:18:24,580 --> 00:18:25,960
貌似是很长一阵子啊
Looks like a long while.

440
00:18:26,730 --> 00:18:28,580
是啊
Oh, yeah. Well...

441
00:18:29,590 --> 00:18:31,540
其实  我觉得这是个机会改变一下
You know, I just thought I could use a change, you know?

442
00:18:34,120 --> 00:18:35,720
你应该看了那篇报道吧
Guess you read the article, huh?

443
00:18:35,920 --> 00:18:37,260
一堆废话  对吧
Bunch of crap, right?

444
00:18:37,260 --> 00:18:38,530
可不是嘛
That's what I said.

445
00:18:40,580 --> 00:18:41,760
想跟我聊聊吗
You wanna talk about it?

446
00:18:42,520 --> 00:18:44,880
赛是个混蛋  我不干了
CY's a horse's ass. I quit the band.

447
00:18:45,320 --> 00:18:46,420
说完了
End of story.

448
00:18:47,080 --> 00:18:48,340
还真简短
That's a short story.

449
00:18:51,800 --> 00:18:53,270
最近和科尔曼聊过吗
You talk to Coleman lately?

450
00:18:54,250 --> 00:18:56,670
什么意思  在你家踩碎他的梦想之后吗
What do you mean? Since your family stomped all over his dreams?

451
00:18:56,670 --> 00:18:58,250
我没有
No.

452
00:18:58,640 --> 00:19:00,410
小蕾  你要是有事想问我就直说
Ray, you wanna ask me somethin', just ask me.

453
00:19:00,640 --> 00:19:01,520
好吧
Uh, all right.

454
00:19:01,520 --> 00:19:04,450
大概是看到你这个样子
Well, you know, I guess seeing you like this and all...

455
00:19:05,460 --> 00:19:07,420
我有点怕了  所以
It kinda scares the hell out of me, so...

456
00:19:07,950 --> 00:19:09,550
我想看看你好不好
I wanna make sure you're all right--

457
00:19:10,020 --> 00:19:11,900
是不是还在表演节目  参加会面
You're doing your program, going to your meetings,

458
00:19:11,900 --> 00:19:13,140
之类的
Stuff like that.

459
00:19:13,170 --> 00:19:15,340
那么好消息是  这不是12年前了
Well, the good news is, it's not 12 years ago,

460
00:19:15,340 --> 00:19:17,480
你也不用再对我负责
so I'm not your responsibility anymore.

461
00:19:17,480 --> 00:19:18,390
我知道
I know.

462
00:19:20,830 --> 00:19:22,070
我很关心你
I care about you.

463
00:19:22,700 --> 00:19:23,960
好得很
That's awesome.

464
00:19:25,380 --> 00:19:26,580
你为什么这么生我的气
Why are you so angry with me?

465
00:19:26,580 --> 00:19:29,090
-我  为什么生你的气  你不  -是
- I'm--why am I angry with you? You don't... - Yeah.

466
00:19:29,260 --> 00:19:29,830
我不知道  小蕾
I don't know, Ray.

467
00:19:29,830 --> 00:19:31,430
也许是因为每次我转过身
Maybe it's 'cause every time I turn around,

468
00:19:31,430 --> 00:19:35,130
你要么是开除我  和我分手
you're, like, firing me or breaking up with me

469
00:19:35,670 --> 00:19:36,530
要么是对我说
or telling me I need to go see

470
00:19:36,530 --> 00:19:38,590
我该换个环境看看
what's around the next bend in the river,

471
00:19:38,590 --> 00:19:40,840
之类的废话  可能是这个原因吧
some crap like that. Maybe that's why.

472
00:19:41,340 --> 00:19:42,980
那是因为我希望你快乐
It's 'cause I want you to be happy.

473
00:19:43,850 --> 00:19:45,750
怎么  就像你和泰迪的那种快乐吗
What, like you're happy with Teddy?

474
00:19:46,250 --> 00:19:47,450
别提这个
Don't do that.

475
00:19:50,690 --> 00:19:51,430
忘了问你
I forgot to ask you.

476
00:19:51,430 --> 00:19:53,480
你到底知不知道他背叛你没有
Did you ever find out if he was cheatin' on you?

477
00:19:53,660 --> 00:19:54,720
他没有
He isn't.

478
00:19:55,910 --> 00:19:56,850
那么
Well...

479
00:19:58,010 --> 00:19:59,890
看来你是做出了正确的选择
I guess you made the right choice then, huh?

480
00:20:00,490 --> 00:20:01,640
舍我选他
Him over me?

481
00:20:03,090 --> 00:20:05,790
你知道我那时没得选择
Well, you know I didn't have much choice in that matter,

482
00:20:06,210 --> 00:20:07,740
你无法保持清醒
'cause you couldn't stay sober.

483
00:20:08,050 --> 00:20:10,210
我只知道你刚把我送进治疗所
All I know is that you put me in rehab,

484
00:20:10,210 --> 00:20:12,420
然后你们俩就结婚了
and the next thing I know, you two are gettin' married.

485
00:20:12,720 --> 00:20:13,320
我只知道这个
All right, that's why I know.

486
00:20:13,330 --> 00:20:14,300
我只知道
I know...

487
00:20:15,460 --> 00:20:16,730
你本来可以等我的
You could've waited for me,

488
00:20:18,510 --> 00:20:19,580
然而你没有
And you didn't.

489
00:20:20,250 --> 00:20:22,430
我还要找你多少次
How many times did I have to go lookin' for you?

490
00:20:22,430 --> 00:20:23,050
我还要多少次
How many times

491
00:20:23,050 --> 00:20:25,200
把你从酒店房间里拉出来
did I have to drag you out of hotel rooms

492
00:20:25,200 --> 00:20:26,600
因为你已经烂醉如泥
'cause you were so wasted

493
00:20:26,610 --> 00:20:29,180
而我不知道你是醉了还是死了
I didn't know if you were drunk or dead?

494
00:20:32,010 --> 00:20:34,320
我不知道第五次去治疗所
I didn't know that the fifth time in rehab

495
00:20:34,320 --> 00:20:35,670
会不会起作用
was actually gonna take.

496
00:20:35,710 --> 00:20:36,840
你对我失去信心了
You lost faith in me.

497
00:20:37,760 --> 00:20:39,180
那时是  现在也是
You did then, you did now.

498
00:20:39,990 --> 00:20:41,290
我从没对你失去信心
I never lost faith in you.

499
00:20:42,550 --> 00:20:44,280
而我现在也没有对你失望
And I have not lost faith in you now.

500
00:20:44,630 --> 00:20:45,940
你已经清醒了
And you got sober.

501
00:20:47,330 --> 00:20:49,450
可是我要告诉你  正是这种对话
But I'll tell you what, it's conversations like this

502
00:20:49,450 --> 00:20:50,850
让我简直无法...
that make it so that I can't...

503
00:20:51,240 --> 00:20:52,680
我跟你无法交流了
I can't do this with you.

504
00:20:53,860 --> 00:20:55,190
那就不要来找我了
Then don't do it.

505
00:21:17,170 --> 00:21:18,180
所以你永远也不会知道  
So you never know. 

506
00:21:18,180 --> 00:21:18,940
你只是需要一首歌来压台
You need a song to close the show...

507
00:21:18,940 --> 00:21:19,870
结果一炮而红  成了榜首
Boom. Number one.

508
00:21:20,170 --> 00:21:21,930
你已经上过多少次榜首了
So how many number ones is this now?

509
00:21:21,930 --> 00:21:23,180
我敢打赌你都数不清
I bet you've lost count.

510
00:21:23,180 --> 00:21:24,810
天啊  这个数我可算得清清楚楚
Oh, my gosh. You don't lose count.

511
00:21:24,810 --> 00:21:25,630
不过我要告诉你
But I will tell you,

512
00:21:25,630 --> 00:21:28,190
每一次都感觉棒极了
every single time, it feels damn good.

513
00:21:28,190 --> 00:21:29,330
再来一张  巴尼斯女士
Just one more, Ms. Barnes.

514
00:21:29,330 --> 00:21:30,650
好了 非常感谢
There you go. Thank you very much.

515
00:21:34,930 --> 00:21:36,190
那是什么玩意儿
What the hell is that?

516
00:21:36,790 --> 00:21:38,330
茱莉亚
Oh. Uh, Juliette,

517
00:21:38,330 --> 00:21:40,200
我想向你介绍亚当·维格里斯
I-I want you to meet, uh, Adam Wergeles.

518
00:21:40,200 --> 00:21:42,340
他是乡村音乐迷网站的博客写手
He blogs for "Country Fandom" web site.

519
00:21:42,450 --> 00:21:42,850
茱莉亚  认识你很高兴  
Hi, Juliette. Great to see you. 

520
00:21:42,850 --> 00:21:43,370
认识你很高兴
Hi. Good to see you.

521
00:21:43,370 --> 00:21:44,710
祝贺
Congratulations. Uh...

522
00:21:45,220 --> 00:21:46,340
这首歌太红了
This song is such a hit.

523
00:21:46,340 --> 00:21:48,030
我们的  我们的读者们都非常想知道
Our--our readers are dying to know,

524
00:21:48,290 --> 00:21:51,090
和乡村音乐女王一起写歌你紧张吗
were you intimidated by writing with the queen of country?

525
00:21:51,370 --> 00:21:52,360
紧张
Intimidated?

526
00:21:52,370 --> 00:21:53,400
没有
Um, no.

527
00:21:53,820 --> 00:21:56,390
总之那感觉还是很棒吧
Well... it must've been great, though.

528
00:21:56,730 --> 00:22:00,250
看到她写那首歌的过门  确实挺兴奋的
It was a thrill to see her contribute a bridge to the song.

529
00:22:00,250 --> 00:22:01,830
马歇尔  马歇尔
Oh! Hey, look. Marshall. Marshall, hey.

530
00:22:02,120 --> 00:22:03,280
马歇尔  这位是亚当
Marshall, this is Adam.

531
00:22:03,520 --> 00:22:04,130
你好  马歇尔
Hi, Marshall.

532
00:22:04,780 --> 00:22:06,860
{\an8}蓝鸟咖啡馆

533
00:22:18,280 --> 00:22:19,090
杰森
Jason?

534
00:22:19,500 --> 00:22:21,430
不是  不过是关于他的  你是他弟弟吗
Nope. I'm calling about him, though. This his brother?

535
00:22:23,000 --> 00:22:24,150
你哪位 
Who's this? 

536
00:22:24,150 --> 00:22:25,920
普郡假释科的维嘉警官
Officer Vega with the Bastrop county parole division.

537
00:22:25,920 --> 00:22:28,110
杰森从没去过教习所
Uh, Jason never made it to his halfway house.

538
00:22:28,820 --> 00:22:30,610
是你把他从监狱接走的吧
You picked him up from prison, correct?

539
00:22:32,550 --> 00:22:33,550
是的  警官
Yes, sir, I did,

540
00:22:34,390 --> 00:22:36,290
我一接到他就把他送去了教习所
And I dropped him right off at the halfway house.

541
00:22:36,560 --> 00:22:38,340
路上恰好停在了某个当铺门口吗
Happen to stop at any pawnshops along the way?

542
00:22:42,740 --> 00:22:43,950
没有  警官
No, sir, I did not.

543
00:22:50,130 --> 00:22:51,570
我现在正在工作
I'm in the middle of work right now.

544
00:22:52,210 --> 00:22:53,230
还有别的事吗
Is there anything else?

545
00:22:53,410 --> 00:22:54,750
你哥哥是个逃犯
Your brother's a fugitive.

546
00:22:54,930 --> 00:22:56,380
如果你想妨碍我们
If there's anything you might be keeping from us

547
00:22:56,380 --> 00:22:57,540
抓到他
to help us bring him in,

548
00:22:58,540 --> 00:23:00,180
你也违反了法律  孩子
you're in violation of the law, too, son.

549
00:23:02,160 --> 00:23:03,190
我明白
Copy that.

550
00:23:06,740 --> 00:23:08,270
-你还好吗  -我很好
- How are you? - I'm all right.

551
00:23:09,000 --> 00:23:10,210
我以为你今晚休息
Uh, I thought you had the night off tonight.

552
00:23:10,210 --> 00:23:11,070
确实
I do,

553
00:23:11,450 --> 00:23:13,390
不过我有个提议
but I also have a proposition for you.

554
00:23:15,030 --> 00:23:16,020
好吧
Okay.

555
00:23:16,580 --> 00:23:18,090
榜单冠军曲目
Number one with a bullet, huh?

556
00:23:18,340 --> 00:23:20,090
很高兴认识你  多谢你能来
It's so nice to see you. Thanks for coming.

557
00:23:20,130 --> 00:23:20,520
那当然  
Of course. 

558
00:23:20,530 --> 00:23:22,960
他从不错过任何一个免费喝酒的机会
He never misses a chance for a free cocktail.

559
00:23:22,960 --> 00:23:24,370
所有带"派对"字眼的活动
Hey, anything with "Party" in the title,

560
00:23:24,370 --> 00:23:25,390
我从不放过
I'm all about it.

561
00:23:25,890 --> 00:23:27,200
顺便问一句  你的新专辑怎么样了
By the way, how's your album coming?

562
00:23:27,410 --> 00:23:27,860
还不错  
It's good. 

563
00:23:27,860 --> 00:23:30,400
歌词和旋律都在斟酌中
You know, line by line, chord by chord.

564
00:23:30,400 --> 00:23:31,700
而且你有利亚姆·麦克金尼斯
And you got Liam Mcguinnis, right?

565
00:23:31,700 --> 00:23:33,030
是的  没错  他很棒
Yeah, yeah. He's great.

566
00:23:33,030 --> 00:23:35,020
他很好  曲风不同  声音也不同
He's good. It's kinda different. It's different sounds.

567
00:23:35,020 --> 00:23:37,240
我丈夫来了
Uh... there's my husband.

568
00:23:37,450 --> 00:23:39,050
-去吧  -好的
- Get on over there. - All right.

569
00:23:40,870 --> 00:23:41,890
看看你
Hi. Well, look at you.

570
00:23:45,030 --> 00:23:46,090
多谢你能来
Thank you for being here.

571
00:23:46,510 --> 00:23:47,800
那当然  职责所在
You bet. Duty calls.

572
00:23:48,440 --> 00:23:49,990
你能来颁这个奖对我来说
It means a lot to me that you're here

573
00:23:50,000 --> 00:23:51,000
很重要
to give the award.

574
00:23:51,010 --> 00:23:52,810
你知道除了颁奖我还有别的事要做
You know I'm here for more than just giving that award.

575
00:23:52,810 --> 00:23:53,990
我为那些动摇的选民来的
I'm here for those sliders.

576
00:23:55,440 --> 00:23:57,100
-咱们去庆祝吧  -好
- Come on. Let's go celebrate. - Okay.

577
00:23:57,100 --> 00:23:57,730
今晚你是女王
This is your night.

578
00:23:58,060 --> 00:23:59,960
{\an8}*动人的笑*
*Pretty smile,*

579
00:24:00,890 --> 00:24:02,200
{\an8}*我的直觉*
*My intuition*

580
00:24:02,000 --> 00:24:02,840
迪康在哪
Where is Deacon?

581
00:24:02,840 --> 00:24:04,320
他本该来看着她的
He is supposed to be watching her.

582
00:24:05,460 --> 00:24:06,530
打扰一下  茱莉亚
Excuse me, Juliette.

583
00:24:07,380 --> 00:24:10,120
妈  你不能碰任何食物
Mom, you cannot touch every touch piece of food.

584
00:24:09,150 --> 00:24:12,680
{\an8}*你躲不开我*
*You can't hide from me*

585
00:24:11,370 --> 00:24:12,230
怎么了
What?

586
00:24:13,160 --> 00:24:14,080
我只是想打个招呼
I was just saying hi.

587
00:24:14,080 --> 00:24:15,290
跟茱莉亚·巴尼斯
To Juliette Barnes?

588
00:24:15,300 --> 00:24:16,190
是啊  为什么不呢
Yeah. Why not?

589
00:24:16,710 --> 00:24:17,320
我一整晚都在等你
I mean, I've been waiting for you

590
00:24:17,320 --> 00:24:18,880
把我介绍给大家
to introduce me to people all night.

591
00:24:19,160 --> 00:24:20,720
我已经那么做了
I have been doing that.

592
00:24:21,010 --> 00:24:23,210
不是那些星探  我已经有唱片合约了
Not to A&R guys. I already have a record deal.

593
00:24:23,210 --> 00:24:24,180
还需要他们做什么呢
What do I need them for?

594
00:24:24,490 --> 00:24:25,860
我只是建议你
I just don't recommend

595
00:24:25,860 --> 00:24:27,670
不要接近茱莉亚·巴尼斯  没有理由
approaching Juliette Barnes for no reason.

596
00:24:27,860 --> 00:24:29,730
我和她一样都是艺人
I'm an artist like she is.

597
00:24:30,490 --> 00:24:31,350
这是我的理由
There's my reason.

598
00:25:12,400 --> 00:25:14,240
等下  你去看艾弗里演出了
Wait. You went to see Avery play?

599
00:25:14,300 --> 00:25:17,130
就一会儿  我一共只听了  半首歌
Oh, barely. I stayed for, like, half a song.

600
00:25:17,150 --> 00:25:18,810
不过我在想
Gross. But I was thinking,

601
00:25:19,770 --> 00:25:21,660
我们  J.T.和乐队
Us and J.T. And the band,

602
00:25:21,660 --> 00:25:23,180
他们欣赏你的演奏
Like, they love the way you play,

603
00:25:23,180 --> 00:25:24,700
之后咱们可以在五点俱乐部演出
and then we could do gigs at the 5 spot

604
00:25:24,700 --> 00:25:26,540
-然后  -我不清楚  斯嘉丽
- and things like-- - Yeah, look, I don't know, Scarlett.

605
00:25:26,540 --> 00:25:28,150
我还有事要忙
Um, I'm in the middle of work,

606
00:25:28,150 --> 00:25:30,240
给我点时间考虑
and I just need some time to think on it.

607
00:25:30,240 --> 00:25:31,320
好的
Okay. Uh...

608
00:25:32,300 --> 00:25:33,940
是因为这个乐队以前是艾弗里的吗
Is it because it's Avery's old band?

609
00:25:34,030 --> 00:25:35,560
跟他无关
This is not about Avery.

610
00:25:35,780 --> 00:25:37,450
是我现在有很多事要处理
I've got a lot on my plate right now.

611
00:25:37,680 --> 00:25:39,690
我知道  为此我很担心你
I know, and I'm worried about you.

612
00:25:40,460 --> 00:25:41,790
自从离开奥斯丁  你就有点怪怪的
You've been funny since Austin,

613
00:25:41,790 --> 00:25:43,250
我在想是否能帮你做些什么
and I'm wondering if there's anything I can do to help,

614
00:25:43,250 --> 00:25:44,750
或者  你愿不愿意跟我聊聊
Or can I--do you wanna talk about it.

615
00:25:44,750 --> 00:25:46,530
这件事你完全无法理解
You know, you wouldn't even begin to understand.

616
00:25:46,910 --> 00:25:47,970
我说真的
It's serious.

617
00:25:48,700 --> 00:25:49,410
而我是说着玩吗
And I'm not?

618
00:25:49,410 --> 00:25:51,050
我没这么说  你突然冒出来
No. You--you come bouncin' in here

619
00:25:51,050 --> 00:25:52,330
就好像加入乐队
like this--this band thing

620
00:25:52,330 --> 00:25:53,560
是全世界最重要的事
is the most important thing in the world.

621
00:25:53,560 --> 00:25:54,380
不是的  我没那么想
No, I didn't think that.

622
00:25:54,380 --> 00:25:56,870
我只是觉得你可能会  为此而兴奋
I just thought maybe you'd-- you'd find it exciting

623
00:25:56,870 --> 00:25:58,970
我问过迪康  他说那几名成员棒极了
I checked with Deacon. He said the boys are really good.

624
00:25:58,970 --> 00:25:59,960
听起来不错
Well, that sounds great.

625
00:25:59,960 --> 00:26:01,840
那为什么迪康不去跟他们合作
Why doesn't Deacon go play with 'em then, huh?

626
00:26:02,060 --> 00:26:04,170
反正他现在也孤身一人
It's not like he's playin' with somebody else.

627
00:26:05,810 --> 00:26:08,990
算了  就当我没提过好了
Um... You know what? Forget I said anything.

628
00:26:08,990 --> 00:26:10,060
别再烦恼这事了
Don't--don't worry about it.

629
00:26:10,470 --> 00:26:11,310
斯嘉丽
Scarlett.

630
00:26:12,100 --> 00:26:12,990
等等  别走
Wait, hold on.

631
00:26:13,680 --> 00:26:16,140
加纳  哥们  有人送了东西给你
Hey, Gunnar. Hey, man, this got dropped off for you.

632
00:26:21,370 --> 00:26:22,900
什么  谁送来的
What? By who?

633
00:26:22,900 --> 00:26:24,120
一个叫杰森的家伙
Some guy named Jason.

634
00:26:25,260 --> 00:26:26,080
什么时候送来的
When?

635
00:26:26,090 --> 00:26:27,120
几小时前
Couple hours ago.

636
00:26:27,810 --> 00:26:29,010
说是恰好路过
Said he was just passin' through.

637
00:26:33,050 --> 00:26:34,440
作为新一届市长
So as mayor elect

638
00:26:34,440 --> 00:26:36,900
和音乐之城委员会的联合主席
and co-chair of the Music City Music Council,

639
00:26:37,380 --> 00:26:39,180
感谢你们成为
we thank you for being ambassadors

640
00:26:39,180 --> 00:26:40,410
我们这座城市的使者
on behalf of our city,

641
00:26:40,760 --> 00:26:41,510
同时感谢你们奉上了
and for your contributions

642
00:26:41,510 --> 00:26:43,760
我们最棒的输出品  那就是音乐
to our greatest export, music.

643
00:26:43,990 --> 00:26:46,580
很荣幸能为你们俩颁奖
And it is my honor to present these awards to you both.

644
00:26:46,990 --> 00:26:48,510
另外  茱莉亚  我无意冒犯
And nothing personal, Juliette,

645
00:26:48,510 --> 00:26:51,990
但这个奖尤其要献给一位女士  她永远是第一
but especially to the woman who is always number one--

646
00:26:52,830 --> 00:26:54,150
她就是我妻子蕾娜·詹姆斯
My wife Rayna Jaymes.

647
00:26:55,410 --> 00:26:56,530
*难道*
*Don't*

648
00:26:57,470 --> 00:26:59,430
*你不觉得我在下面*
*You think I'm under*

649
00:26:59,430 --> 00:27:01,090
*感觉很糟*
*This ain't a feel-good*

650
00:27:01,130 --> 00:27:05,250
*没事  没事*
*Everything's fine*

651
00:27:07,290 --> 00:27:09,270
你好  打扰了  你没事吧
Whoa. Hey. Excuse me. You okay?

652
00:27:09,270 --> 00:27:10,230
没事
Uh, yeah.

653
00:27:10,230 --> 00:27:11,040
要知道  这并不是
You know, this isn't actually

654
00:27:11,040 --> 00:27:12,640
我们第一次见面
the--the first time that we've met.

655
00:27:12,640 --> 00:27:15,550
我在剧场后台撞见了你
I-I ran into you backstage, uh, at the opry.

656
00:27:15,570 --> 00:27:16,480
是真的撞到
Literally.

657
00:27:17,150 --> 00:27:19,140
我懂  这种事你见惯了
I mean, I get it. Must happen to you all the time.

658
00:27:19,140 --> 00:27:20,620
我自己也在慢慢适应
I'm just kind of getting used to it myself.

659
00:27:20,630 --> 00:27:22,040
成为明星这件事
You know, the whole star thing.

660
00:27:22,640 --> 00:27:24,060
我签约在多米尼克旗下
I signed with Dominic's label.

661
00:27:24,060 --> 00:27:26,500
-他喜欢都市元素的音乐  -抱歉
- He's got kind of this urban take on the music... - Oh, sorry.

662
00:27:26,530 --> 00:27:27,780
尽量增强音效感
Trying to mix it up some.

663
00:27:27,990 --> 00:27:29,900
-我十分希望你有空能听一听  -你好
- You know, I-I'd love for you to hear it sometime... - Hi.

664
00:27:29,950 --> 00:27:30,780
如果你愿意的话
If you'd like.

665
00:27:30,790 --> 00:27:32,270
我是艾弗里·巴克利
I'm Avery Barkley.

666
00:27:32,320 --> 00:27:34,090
《一吻》就是我唱的
I sing that song "Kiss."

667
00:27:34,700 --> 00:27:35,670
你好  詹姆斯小姐  你好
Hello. Miss Jaymes, hi.

668
00:27:35,670 --> 00:27:36,420
你好
Hi.

669
00:27:36,420 --> 00:27:38,200
我是你的超级粉丝
I'm such a big fan of yours.

670
00:27:38,200 --> 00:27:40,080
多谢
Oh, thank you so much.

671
00:27:40,100 --> 00:27:41,620
抱歉  我从没听说过
I'm sorry, I've never heard of it.

672
00:27:41,920 --> 00:27:42,640
妈
Mama.

673
00:27:42,640 --> 00:27:44,640
我叫乔琳  茱莉亚的妈妈
I'm Jolene. I'm Juliette's mama.

674
00:27:44,640 --> 00:27:47,730
-真没想到  -抱歉  我  抱歉
- Oh, my goodness. - I'm sorry. Um, sorry. I-I--

675
00:27:47,740 --> 00:27:49,200
妈  别闹了
Mama, stop.

676
00:27:50,420 --> 00:27:51,600
我不过是想谢谢她
I just wanted to thank her.

677
00:27:51,600 --> 00:27:52,860
幸会
Nice to meet you.

678
00:27:53,040 --> 00:27:55,200
你用不着谢她
You do not need to thank her for anything.

679
00:27:55,540 --> 00:27:57,630
给我听着  她从没帮过我任何事
Listen to me. She did not do me any favors.

680
00:27:57,630 --> 00:27:59,280
我就是想表现得友善些
I was just trying to be nice.

681
00:27:59,280 --> 00:28:00,910
都给我省省吧
Don't try to be anything.

682
00:28:01,070 --> 00:28:02,700
你甚至都不该来这
You're not even supposed to be here.

683
00:28:03,230 --> 00:28:04,800
你是不是什么事都要给我毁了
Is there anything you don't ruin?

684
00:28:09,670 --> 00:28:11,330
-蕾娜  -利亚姆
- Rayna. - Liam.

685
00:28:11,880 --> 00:28:13,380
看来一晚上躲着你
Well, I wondered if I'd be able

686
00:28:13,380 --> 00:28:14,880
是不太可能了
to successfully avoid you all night.

687
00:28:14,880 --> 00:28:17,520
马歇尔  派对办得不错
Hey, Marshall. Nice party.

688
00:28:17,520 --> 00:28:19,280
下载量超过两百万
Well, over 2 million downloads,

689
00:28:19,280 --> 00:28:20,400
我才该谢你
I should be thanking you.

690
00:28:21,280 --> 00:28:22,560
这家公司是你一手打造的  蕾娜
You built this label, Rayna.

691
00:28:22,740 --> 00:28:23,670
我们不想失去你
We don't wanna lose you.

692
00:28:23,670 --> 00:28:25,040
消息传得挺快啊
Word travels fast, huh?

693
00:28:25,350 --> 00:28:26,400
别白费口舌了
Well, save your breath,

694
00:28:26,400 --> 00:28:28,900
你们的钱不够留住我俩
'cause you're not gonna be able to offer enough to keep us.

695
00:28:28,900 --> 00:28:29,940
我尊敬你  利亚姆
Well, respectfully, Liam,

696
00:28:29,940 --> 00:28:31,630
但我要签的是蕾娜  不是你
my contract's with Rayna, not with you.

697
00:28:31,920 --> 00:28:33,240
我也尊敬你  马歇尔  
Well, respectfully, Marshall, 

698
00:28:33,240 --> 00:28:34,230
可我们是搭档
we are partners.

699
00:28:34,230 --> 00:28:36,080
我想你还不知道
I'm guessing you don't know about the imprint

700
00:28:36,080 --> 00:28:37,840
无尽公司答应给你的搭档多少酬金
that Countless has offered your partner

701
00:28:37,860 --> 00:28:39,580
只要他让你成功签过去
if he brings you on as an artist.

702
00:28:40,080 --> 00:28:40,860
什么
What?

703
00:28:41,840 --> 00:28:42,940
这也算搭档吗
Not much of a partnership

704
00:28:42,940 --> 00:28:45,380
一方两头捞钱  而另一方全然不知
if one half's double-dipping and the other half doesn't know.

705
00:28:49,350 --> 00:28:50,190
你没跟我说实话
Did you lie to me?

706
00:28:50,190 --> 00:28:52,360
那家伙真是混蛋
That guy is such an ass.

707
00:28:52,670 --> 00:28:54,680
没错  但谁在撒谎  你还是那混蛋
Well, yeah, but who lied, you or the ass?

708
00:28:54,680 --> 00:28:56,120
也不算是骗你
It's not really a lie.

709
00:28:56,390 --> 00:28:58,100
况且  那样对你来说也不错
Besides, it's still great for you.

710
00:28:58,430 --> 00:29:00,180
-对我而言糟透了  -我是在帮你
- This isn't great for me. - I'm helping you.

711
00:29:00,190 --> 00:29:01,320
这不是你想要的吗
That's what you wanted, right?

712
00:29:01,320 --> 00:29:03,250
你跑来敲我的门  还记得吗
You came knocking on my door, remember?

713
00:29:03,480 --> 00:29:06,010
你能重回事业顶峰  全仰仗我
The whole reason you have a career again is because of me.

714
00:29:06,010 --> 00:29:07,680
-你这么认为  -对
- Is that what you think? - Mm-hmm.

715
00:29:08,200 --> 00:29:10,300
但我认为这是我俩合作的结果
'cause my feeling was it was 'cause of us,

716
00:29:10,300 --> 00:29:11,490
我以为我们是搭档
'cause we're partners.

717
00:29:11,870 --> 00:29:13,430
搭档之间不能撒谎
You don't lie to your partner.

718
00:29:14,120 --> 00:29:14,760
是啊
Yeah.

719
00:29:14,760 --> 00:29:16,050
这话留着给你丈夫说吧
Tell that to your husband.

720
00:29:18,070 --> 00:29:19,720
别这样  我们是搭档
Come on. We are partners.

721
00:29:22,090 --> 00:29:23,110
我不干了
I'm not doing this.

722
00:29:23,130 --> 00:29:23,830
什么
What?

723
00:29:23,830 --> 00:29:25,530
合作关系解除
This partnership is dissolved.

724
00:29:25,960 --> 00:29:28,120
别这样  你好不容易事业有了进展
Come on. You're finally getting something going.

725
00:29:28,990 --> 00:29:30,330
-是我们  -没戏了
- We are. - We aren't.

726
00:29:31,080 --> 00:29:32,610
你不能这样一走了之
You can't just walk away from me.

727
00:29:33,080 --> 00:29:34,480
离开你  我可以
From you? Yes, I can.

728
00:29:48,910 --> 00:29:50,560
你跟利亚姆之间发生什么事了
Is there something going on with you and Liam?

729
00:29:53,920 --> 00:29:54,700
没有
No.

730
00:29:56,910 --> 00:29:58,140
除了我把他炒了
Except I fired him

731
00:29:58,590 --> 00:29:59,400
因为他
'cause he was...

732
00:29:59,760 --> 00:30:02,150
在我背后搞了一些小动作
doing some kind of deal behind my back.

733
00:30:03,130 --> 00:30:03,960
就这样吗
That's it?

734
00:30:04,330 --> 00:30:06,010
你俩看似不止这点矛盾
Because it looked like a lot more than that.

735
00:30:06,240 --> 00:30:08,130
也许只是我生命中另一个骗我的男人
I guess another man in my life lying to me

736
00:30:08,130 --> 00:30:09,250
觉得不止这点矛盾
feels like a lot more than that.

737
00:30:09,250 --> 00:30:10,870
蕾娜  你够了吧
Rayna, enough already, okay?

738
00:30:12,130 --> 00:30:13,410
我要为做过的事
Look, how many times do I have to apologize 

739
00:30:13,410 --> 00:30:15,070
道歉多少回你才满意
for what I did?

740
00:30:15,130 --> 00:30:16,410
是我搞砸了  行吗
I screwed up, okay?

741
00:30:16,420 --> 00:30:18,540
你知我知  我还能怎么办
You know it, I know it. But what else can I do?

742
00:30:19,490 --> 00:30:21,310
即便这样我还在家里抱着希望
You know, I'm here at home holding out hope

743
00:30:21,310 --> 00:30:22,540
想与你和好如初
that we can fix things,

744
00:30:22,540 --> 00:30:23,460
而你却在外面巡演  
while you're out there on the road 

745
00:30:23,460 --> 00:30:24,720
天知道你在外面做了什么
doing god knows what.

746
00:30:24,720 --> 00:30:26,520
天知道我在外面做了什么
I'm out there on the road doing god knows what?

747
00:30:26,520 --> 00:30:27,530
你知道我在外面做了什么吗
You know what I'm out there doing?

748
00:30:27,530 --> 00:30:28,560
别的不说  首先是辛苦赚钱还房贷  
Paying for this house, among other things.

749
00:30:28,560 --> 00:30:30,720
没错  可我在家照料女儿们
Well, yeah. Yeah, and I'm home raising our daughters,

750
00:30:30,720 --> 00:30:31,820
都是我做的  
that's what I'm doing. 

751
00:30:31,820 --> 00:30:32,920
我一直陪在你身边
Well, I'm standing by you.

752
00:30:33,840 --> 00:30:35,080
不会跟你离婚
I'm not divorcing you

753
00:30:35,240 --> 00:30:36,680
也不会报警抓你
or calling the cops on you.

754
00:30:37,070 --> 00:30:38,220
这都是我做的
That's what I'm doing.

755
00:30:39,180 --> 00:30:40,060
我只是
I just...

756
00:30:42,060 --> 00:30:43,380
我只想知道你我的关系到了何种境地
I just wanna know where we stand.

757
00:30:44,990 --> 00:30:46,100
我想更进一步
I wanna move forward.

758
00:30:46,860 --> 00:30:49,070
而我却要盯着身边每一个人
And instead, I'm watching everyone in the world--

759
00:30:49,070 --> 00:30:50,320
利亚姆  新公司的人
Liam, that new label--

760
00:30:50,320 --> 00:30:51,580
每一个想把你抢走的人
everyone's trying to win you over,

761
00:30:51,580 --> 00:30:52,840
而我只想赢回你的心
and all I wanna do is win you back.

762
00:31:00,200 --> 00:31:02,170
这很复杂
You know, I think it's complicated.

763
00:31:04,430 --> 00:31:05,480
是很复杂
It's complicated.

764
00:31:10,700 --> 00:31:12,730
我遇见你的时候  迪康把你毁了
Yeah, when I met you, Deacon had destroyed you.

765
00:31:15,090 --> 00:31:16,950
你有多少次送他进勒戒所
You'd put him in rehab how many times?

766
00:31:18,850 --> 00:31:20,070
-五次  -对
- Five. - Right.

767
00:31:20,610 --> 00:31:21,450
五次
Five.

768
00:31:22,640 --> 00:31:23,450
你当时孤身一人
You were alone.

769
00:31:23,760 --> 00:31:25,180
我记得你跟我说过
I remember you told me you just...

770
00:31:27,020 --> 00:31:28,560
你只想找个靠得住的人
all you wanted was someone solid,

771
00:31:30,060 --> 00:31:31,900
一个能安稳过日子的人  我做到了
a guy who had his life together, and I did.

772
00:31:36,790 --> 00:31:38,740
后来我的财政状况出现了问题
You know, then when things fell apart for me financially

773
00:31:38,740 --> 00:31:41,010
情况急转直下  我就失去了方向
and kept falling apart, I-I guess I lost my way.

774
00:31:41,630 --> 00:31:44,160
我只想成为你心目中理想的丈夫
I just wanted to be the guy that I thought you wanted me to be.

775
00:31:45,380 --> 00:31:47,490
虽然这不能成为我犯错的借口  但是
And god knows it doesn't excuse what I did, but...

776
00:31:50,740 --> 00:31:51,760
我想那时候
I guess at the time,

777
00:31:52,960 --> 00:31:54,670
我觉得自己的行为是情有可原的
I thought I was doing it for the right reason.

778
00:31:56,140 --> 00:31:57,770
蕾娜  也许我们没太大差别
Maybe we're not all that different, Rayna.

779
00:31:59,750 --> 00:32:02,170
初衷是好的  却做了错误的抉择
Wrong choice, right reason.

780
00:32:05,020 --> 00:32:06,590
也许这就是我们当初在一起的原因
Maybe that's how we ended up together.

781
00:32:13,020 --> 00:32:15,490
佩吉和普兰特吗[摇滚巨星]  对
Page and Plant? Right.

782
00:32:16,270 --> 00:32:17,520
少男杀手你来啦
Hey, hey, hey, killer.

783
00:32:17,580 --> 00:32:18,860
-你好吗  -你好吗
- How you doin'? - How you doin'?

784
00:32:18,860 --> 00:32:20,350
-我很好  -很好
- I'm good. - Good.

785
00:32:22,350 --> 00:32:24,800
伙计们  你们好像都布置好了
Hey, guys, I know, like, you're all set up.

786
00:32:24,800 --> 00:32:26,340
你们想在这练多久都可以
You should play here long as you want,

787
00:32:26,340 --> 00:32:27,580
我跟加纳说过了
but I did talk to Gunnar about it.

788
00:32:27,580 --> 00:32:28,850
他不太赞成我们
He said the whole joining forces thing

789
00:32:28,850 --> 00:32:30,830
组乐队这个想法  抱歉
wasn't gonna work out. I-I'm sorry.

790
00:32:31,280 --> 00:32:32,860
他才教我们弹了《一个人更好》
He just taught us "One works better."

791
00:32:33,380 --> 00:32:34,430
你来这干嘛
What are you doing here?

792
00:32:35,460 --> 00:32:36,800
希望好人有好报
Wanted the good guys to win,

793
00:32:37,570 --> 00:32:39,930
虽然我有时候看起来不太像好人
even if I don't act like one myself sometimes.

794
00:32:40,560 --> 00:32:41,520
不管你是因为什么而烦恼
Whatever it is that's bothering you,

795
00:32:41,520 --> 00:32:42,830
我都希望你能跟我谈谈
I sure wish you'd talk about it.

796
00:32:43,890 --> 00:32:45,630
不介意的话  我更想弹吉他
I'd rather just play, if that's all right.

797
00:32:47,590 --> 00:32:49,220
你的吉普森回来了真好
It's good to see you got your Gibson back.

798
00:32:51,450 --> 00:32:52,520
好了  你们准备好了吗
All right, you boys ready?

799
00:32:52,640 --> 00:32:53,800
倒数开始
Count it off. Mm-hmm.

800
00:32:54,570 --> 00:32:55,940
三  四
Three, four.

801
00:32:59,220 --> 00:33:00,190
迪康
Deacon?

802
00:33:03,870 --> 00:33:04,960
迪康
Deacon?!

803
00:33:05,990 --> 00:33:07,280
快开门
Open the damn door!

804
00:33:07,510 --> 00:33:08,550
我知道你在家
I know you're in there!

805
00:33:08,550 --> 00:33:10,790
你那辆破洞烂铁停在门外
Your piece-of-crap truck's out here!

806
00:33:12,420 --> 00:33:13,560
你死哪去了
Where the hell have you been?!

807
00:33:16,860 --> 00:33:17,640
迪康
Deacon?

808
00:33:18,360 --> 00:33:19,240
走开
Just go away.

809
00:33:19,360 --> 00:33:20,620
我不会走的
That's not gonna happen.

810
00:33:30,940 --> 00:33:32,120
走调了
It was out of tune.

811
00:33:38,650 --> 00:33:40,930
酒都不喝你一定很痛苦
Well, you're too miserable to be drunk.

812
00:33:42,890 --> 00:33:44,680
你懂得还不少
You know so much, don't you?

813
00:33:45,430 --> 00:33:47,670
"干醉"的人我一眼就能看出来
I know a dry drunk when I see one.

814
00:33:45,430 --> 00:33:47,670
{\an8}"干醉"  虽已戒酒  但因大脑长期受酒精侵害
会有特定的精神状态

815
00:33:56,090 --> 00:33:58,390
看着我  跟我走吧
Look at me. Come with me.

816
00:33:58,870 --> 00:34:00,520
你应该上路巡演
You should be on the road.

817
00:34:00,710 --> 00:34:02,850
你应该去演奏  做音乐
You need to be playin', writin' music,

818
00:34:03,160 --> 00:34:05,560
去开会  去编曲
going to meetings, working the program.

819
00:34:05,820 --> 00:34:07,330
我团队里有一组人
Look, there's a group in my crew.

820
00:34:07,420 --> 00:34:08,580
他们每周会面两次
They meet twice a week.

821
00:34:09,500 --> 00:34:10,900
讨厌死了
It's a pain in my ass.

822
00:34:13,510 --> 00:34:15,170
但你应该去做所爱的事
But you need to do what you love.

823
00:34:18,460 --> 00:34:19,800
难道这不是你戒酒的原因吗
Isn't that why you got sober?

824
00:34:22,410 --> 00:34:23,860
你不是为了这个保持清醒的吗
Isn't that what kept you sober?

825
00:34:26,620 --> 00:34:27,510
说来好笑
You know, it's funny.

826
00:34:27,510 --> 00:34:29,180
我一直这么说
I always used to say that, uh,

827
00:34:29,190 --> 00:34:31,620
我是为自己而戒酒
I got sober for myself, you know?

828
00:34:32,470 --> 00:34:33,720
好像就应该这么说
That's what you're supposed to say.

829
00:34:36,810 --> 00:34:37,960
但这不是事实
It was never true.

830
00:34:45,040 --> 00:34:46,390
我是为了蕾娜而戒酒
I got sober for Rayna.

831
00:34:49,520 --> 00:34:50,710
让我保持清醒的
What kept me sober...

832
00:34:57,160 --> 00:34:59,520
是我永远也得不到的
was hoping for something that ain't never gonna happen.

833
00:35:01,290 --> 00:35:03,130
你真觉得是她救了你的命
You really think she saved your life?

834
00:35:06,720 --> 00:35:08,400
从一个旁观者的角度
From an outsider's perspective,

835
00:35:09,110 --> 00:35:11,370
她恰恰是你最不需要的
she is the opposite of what you need.

836
00:35:13,000 --> 00:35:14,490
你来告诉我需要什么吗
You gonna tell me what I need now?

837
00:35:18,000 --> 00:35:20,140
你不是还有个瘾君子要照看吗
Don't you got another addict to go take care of?

838
00:35:20,610 --> 00:35:21,650
我是说真的  好好想想
I'm serious. I mean, look it.

839
00:35:21,650 --> 00:35:24,580
你对我无比关心在乎
You got all the care and concern in the world for me,

840
00:35:24,580 --> 00:35:26,860
可她呢  你不闻不问
but what about her, nothin'?

841
00:35:30,050 --> 00:35:30,920
我真不明白
See, I don't get that,

842
00:35:30,920 --> 00:35:32,510
我和她  我们是同类人
'cause she and me, we're the same.

843
00:35:34,040 --> 00:35:35,010
是啊
Yeah.

844
00:35:35,880 --> 00:35:37,550
我们在做同一场抗争
We're fightin' the exact same battle.

845
00:35:39,480 --> 00:35:40,870
现在唯一的区别是
Right now, only difference is...

846
00:35:43,320 --> 00:35:44,940
她比我做得好多了
she's doing a whole lot better than me.

847
00:36:01,410 --> 00:36:03,490
你在这儿啊
Hey. There you are.

848
00:36:06,450 --> 00:36:07,490
宝贝  抱歉
Baby, I'm sorry.

849
00:36:08,180 --> 00:36:11,180
不  不  是我抱歉才对
No. No, I'm sorry.

850
00:36:12,760 --> 00:36:14,270
迪康状况很不好
Deacon's in bad shape.

851
00:36:14,900 --> 00:36:16,060
他没喝酒  但是...
He didn't drink, but he...

852
00:36:17,460 --> 00:36:18,560
很可能酒瘾复发
easily could've.

853
00:36:21,080 --> 00:36:23,620
我觉得如果这世上连他
I just feel like if he, of all people,

854
00:36:23,620 --> 00:36:25,120
都能酒瘾复发
can fall off the wagon...

855
00:36:26,580 --> 00:36:27,780
那我就没有希望了
Then there's no hope for me.

856
00:36:34,230 --> 00:36:35,490
听我说  我
Listen to me. I...

857
00:36:36,930 --> 00:36:39,460
我本该告诉法官  你进步有多大
I should have told the judge how far you've come.

858
00:36:40,080 --> 00:36:42,880
你已经能保持清醒了
I mean, that you've stayed in rehab,

859
00:36:43,380 --> 00:36:45,680
其实你当初来的时候  就已经戒了
the fact that you're even here in the first place.

860
00:36:46,950 --> 00:36:48,350
我真该告诉你
I should have told you that I'm...

861
00:36:49,220 --> 00:36:51,840
我真的为你骄傲
really, really proud of you.

862
00:36:59,450 --> 00:37:01,100
你不知道这对我意义有多大
You don't know what that means to me.

863
00:37:02,270 --> 00:37:03,560
你这样的人
Somebody like you being...

864
00:37:04,180 --> 00:37:05,450
会为我这样的人骄傲吗
proud of somebody like me?

865
00:37:06,450 --> 00:37:08,220
我这样的人  你在说什么啊
Somebody like me? What are you talking about?

866
00:37:08,220 --> 00:37:09,510
宝贝  我很敬畏你
Baby, I'm in awe of you.

867
00:37:10,480 --> 00:37:12,730
今晚我看到你和传奇人物同台
I saw you up on that stage tonight with the legend,

868
00:37:12,730 --> 00:37:14,110
你和你从小
with the woman that you've admired

869
00:37:14,110 --> 00:37:15,610
就一直崇拜的女星站在一起
since you were a little girl, and...

870
00:37:16,180 --> 00:37:17,420
现在你和她是平等的
now you're her equal.

871
00:37:18,910 --> 00:37:20,000
你觉得我和蕾娜是平等的
You think I'm Rayna's equal?

872
00:37:20,000 --> 00:37:22,830
对啊  甚至不止如此
Oh, yeah, and then some.

873
00:37:24,070 --> 00:37:26,710
宝贝  她是从贝尔米德富人区长大的
Baby, she... she grew up in Belle Meade,

874
00:37:26,710 --> 00:37:28,570
而你...
And, well, you came from...

875
00:37:29,480 --> 00:37:30,370
你是我生的
You came from me.

876
00:37:31,480 --> 00:37:34,480
你是如此美丽  才华横溢
And you're so amazing and talented and beautiful.

877
00:37:34,480 --> 00:37:38,320
而你不过是我这样的人生下来的
And... if you can come from someone like me?

878
00:37:38,880 --> 00:37:41,170
那就说明  希望是存在的
Well, that just proves that there's hope.

879
00:37:44,140 --> 00:37:45,390
我不会说  我很自豪
I don't tell you that I'm proud,

880
00:37:45,400 --> 00:37:47,990
因为这听上去像是我在抢功劳
because then it sounds like I'm trying to take credit.

881
00:37:50,160 --> 00:37:52,810
但我真的为你自豪
But I am. I'm so proud of you.

882
00:37:55,540 --> 00:37:56,320
为你的今天自豪
All the you are

883
00:37:56,320 --> 00:37:58,220
为你成就的一切自豪  宝贝
and--and everything you've become, honey,

884
00:37:58,220 --> 00:38:00,010
这都不是因为我
That's... that's not because of me.

885
00:38:01,230 --> 00:38:02,150
跟我没关系
It's in spite of me.

886
00:38:04,020 --> 00:38:06,090
你今天的身份地位  宝贝
Who you are and where you are, honey...

887
00:38:08,910 --> 00:38:09,960
宝贝  都是你的功劳
Baby, that's all you.

888
00:38:15,490 --> 00:38:16,130
我早该告诉你
I'd have told you,

889
00:38:16,130 --> 00:38:17,710
但我觉得我的想法
but I didn't think that what I thought

890
00:38:18,080 --> 00:38:19,180
对你没有任何意义
meant anything to you.

891
00:38:28,340 --> 00:38:29,400
是有意义的
It means somethin'.

892
00:38:45,680 --> 00:38:48,930
*你一直努力*
*You been working*

893
00:38:48,930 --> 00:38:52,100
*改变已太迟*
*It's too late to change*

894
00:38:52,100 --> 00:38:56,150
*请让我知道*
*Please let me know*

895
00:38:56,150 --> 00:38:57,820
*什么*
*What*

896
00:38:57,910 --> 00:39:01,850
*你刚说过*
*You just said*

897
00:39:02,160 --> 00:39:06,250
*姑娘  你走路姿态*
*Oh, girl, when you walk*

898
00:39:06,430 --> 00:39:07,880
*讲话的神态*
*Talk like that*

899
00:39:07,890 --> 00:39:09,600
*还有那仪态*
*Look like that*

900
00:39:09,630 --> 00:39:12,380
*牢牢操控着我*
*I'm chained to your will*

901
00:39:12,380 --> 00:39:13,360
*甜心*
*So, honey,*

902
00:39:13,360 --> 00:39:15,240
*现在靠近点*
*Come on closer*

903
00:39:19,200 --> 00:39:22,120
*只是获胜和幸存*
*Just winning and survival*

904
00:39:22,650 --> 00:39:25,470
*我有发言权  也做出了选择*
*I've got a voice and I made my choice*

905
00:39:25,470 --> 00:39:28,530
*在心碎和复活之间*
*Between heartbreak and revival*

906
00:39:28,630 --> 00:39:31,890
*我知道你讨厌*
*I know you hate how I make*

907
00:39:31,890 --> 00:39:34,690
*我一切轻松的样子*
*Everything look easy to do*

908
00:39:35,030 --> 00:39:36,680
*但这是我的荣幸*
*Oh, but it's my pleasure*

909
00:39:36,680 --> 00:39:39,570
*没有你  一切做得更好*
*Doing everything better without you*

910
00:39:39,850 --> 00:39:42,580
*因为我一个人努力  好过两个*
*'cause this one works better than two*

911
00:39:46,420 --> 00:39:49,250
*因为我一个人努力  好过两个*
*'cause this one works better than two*

912
00:39:54,660 --> 00:39:57,260
你们都要乖乖听爸爸的话  好吗
Ohh. Y'all be good for your daddy, okay?

913
00:39:57,270 --> 00:39:57,930
-好啊  -好的  妈妈
- Okay. - Okay, mom.

914
00:39:58,020 --> 00:39:59,580
-几周后见啦  -好吧
- See you in a couple weeks. - All right.

915
00:39:59,580 --> 00:40:01,350
-好吗  -我们去看看飞机
- Okay? - Let's go look at the planes.

916
00:40:06,890 --> 00:40:07,870
你也要保重
You be good, too.

917
00:40:10,030 --> 00:40:12,730
据我所知  我们的婚姻还有效
Listen, as far as I'm concerned, we're still married,

918
00:40:13,440 --> 00:40:16,630
无论我是在纳什维尔还是在外巡演
Whether I'm here in Nashville or whether I'm out on tour.

919
00:40:21,650 --> 00:40:24,310
我当初选择了你  那不是错误的选择
I chose you. That was never a wrong choice.

920
00:40:28,140 --> 00:40:29,240
我想我们现在只是
I think now we're just...

921
00:40:30,030 --> 00:40:31,610
在选择我们的未来要怎么过
choosing what our future's gonna be.

922
00:40:32,900 --> 00:40:33,750
好吧
Right.

923
00:40:48,330 --> 00:40:49,430
马歇尔一直打来电话
Marshall keeps calling.

924
00:40:50,460 --> 00:40:51,560
卡莉斯塔也是
So does Calista.

925
00:40:52,280 --> 00:40:53,750
他们都想知道你的立场
They both wanna know where you stand.

926
00:40:54,640 --> 00:40:55,780
我想要我自己的公司
I want my own label.

927
00:40:56,220 --> 00:40:58,220
告诉马歇尔  如果他同意的话
Tell that to Marshall, and if he says yes,

928
00:40:58,220 --> 00:40:59,670
我就留在边山公司
then I will stay at Edgehill.

929
00:41:00,520 --> 00:41:01,670
好的  那就不考虑卡莉斯塔了
Okay, so no Calista?

930
00:41:01,930 --> 00:41:03,620
不  暂时不了
No. Not yet.

931
00:41:04,460 --> 00:41:07,530
我们为何做什么事都要挤在一起
Why do we have to do everything at the crack of butt?

932
00:41:10,160 --> 00:41:11,970
请你再告诉他  我想要我自己的飞机
Will you please also tell him I want my own plane?

933
00:41:13,090 --> 00:41:15,710
好吧  我们出发去堪萨斯了
All right. So, hey, we goin' to kansas city?

934
00:41:16,710 --> 00:41:18,020
现在还不能起飞
Not quite yet.

935
00:41:19,030 --> 00:41:20,450
还要等一个人
We're waitin' for one more.

936
00:41:26,210 --> 00:41:27,040
抱歉
Excuse me.

937
00:41:28,010 --> 00:41:29,310
-迪康  -你们还好吗
- Deacon. - How y'all doing?

938
00:41:29,540 --> 00:41:30,960
-你们都保重好吗  -好啊
- Y'all take care, okay? - Okay.

939
00:41:47,620 --> 00:41:48,750
抱歉久等
Sorry for the hold-up.

940
00:41:52,800 --> 00:41:54,740
你雇了他来代替利亚姆
Did you hire him to replace Liam

941
00:41:54,740 --> 00:41:55,820
却没跟我说一声吗
and not talk to me about it?

942
00:41:55,860 --> 00:41:57,100
不  当然不是
No. Of course not.

943
00:41:58,160 --> 00:41:59,290
我不是来加入你的乐队
I'm not here for your band.

944
00:42:02,340 --> 00:42:03,410
他是要加入我的
He's joining mine.

