Previously on "Nashville"...
This is gonna be huge.
I don't think I can do this.
You can. You know you can.
I need to be lettin' you go.
So you came to me to find your voice again?
Sometimes you gotta blow up the box.
What the hell are you doing here?
I came to pick up my big brother.
Where's my guitar?
I'm gonna get it back for
you real soon, I promise.
Hey! Congratulations, Mr. mayor.
Well, you just got all the girls
following you around here.
This is my niece, Cy.
Hi. Hi.
Okay, please don't do that. No, no, no.
I quit.
?...What he had till it was gone
?You got the wrong girl
?'Cause I got your number
♪Don't know what kind of
spell you think I'm under♪
♪This ain't a feel-good,
everything's fine sing-along♪
?You got the wrong song
?Everybody makes mistakes
?We can work it out
?Wouldn't it be nice
♪lf that's what I was singing now♪♪
♪But you got the wrong song
coming through your speakers♪
♪This one's about a liar and a cheater♪
♪Who didn't know what he had
till it was gone, gone, gone♪
?You got the wrong girl
?'Cause I got your number
♪Don't know what kind of
spell you think I'm under♪
♪This ain't a feel-good,
everything's fine sing-along♪
?You got the wrong song
?You got the wrong song?
3500:01: 00:01:57,616
?You got the wrong song, yeah
thank you!
Thank you, Dallas!
We love you, Rayna!
That is the third night that
this has happened, okay?
They're acting like I'm not even there.
I mean, look, he's her guitar player.
What are you gonna do?
So what? Is that some sort of excuse?
Okay, I'll say something.
But we gotta go. Your plane's waiting.
Just do me a favor. Please tell me that
I don't have to deal with
her until the party.
Actually...
We're giving her a ride to Nashville.
You've got to be kiddin' me.
Rayna. Fantastic!
You killed it out there! I
don't even know what that was.
Wow! Just the best concert
I've seen in years.
Actually, since my last
Rayna James concert.
Madison square garden, '09. Oh!
And this is Calista Reeves.
She's the president of
countless records. Oh.
Oh, nice to meet you. Uh, she
flew in from L.A. to see you.
Came to see her or me, love? Ah. Her, Liam.
I would love to talk with you, Rayna,
about what's next.
Oh. Well, I'd love to talk to
you, but what's next for us
is we're about to hop on Juliette's plane
and fly back to Nashville
'cause Edgehill's throwing
us a party for "wrong song."
It hit number one. Congrats. Thank you.
Well, you have a safe flight,
and I'll be in touch.
Great to meet you.
Liam. See you.
Walk with me? Yep.
Oh, my gosh.
That felt good.
Oh, yeah.
She wants you.
Can't say I blame her.
Guys?
We got the plane waiting. Okay.
♪This plane can fly on just one engine♪
♪This heart can beat without affection♪
♪I'm not a choice, I'm a natural selection♪
♪Well, this house can stand
just fine on its own♪
?This hand's gonna move... damn it.
What?
The damn thing keeps
going out of tune. I...
I think the bridge is shot.
Where is your Gibson at?
I sort of, uh... loaned
it to somebody who...
Loaned it to somebody.
That's because you're one
of the good ones, Gunnar.
Well, you know what they
say about the nice guys.
They finish last and...
Down a Gibson.
Not if we keep writin' songs
like that, you don't.
Yeah, well, I just hope somebody...
Will do more than just put a hold on it
and cut the damn thing.
Or we could perform it ourselves.
Winter fest is coming up.
Yeah, you... you don't want
to be going to that.
It's not your thing.
Why is it not my scene?
Avery's playing it.
Seriously?
Awesome.
I got you a $1,000 guarantee
for the belmont show tomorrow.
Hell, yeah.
It's a grand more than the last gig paid.
What's the, uh, party tomorrow night?
The number one party for the song
Rayna James and Juliette
Barnes sang at the Ryman.
For you, it's a chance to meet
everyone you need to know in music city.
You giving Dominic a run for his money?
He may give you a car.
I'm giving you a career.
What do you think of the backdrop?
Want your picture in front of it?
You know what?
Lose the "the" and "band."
From now on, it's just Avery Barkley.
All right, guys.
Let's do this.
Has anyone seen my bean dip?
What's it look like?
Like a can that has "bean dip" on the side.
Calista Reeves.
Pretty big deal.
Yeah. She's one of the most powerful
label heads in the industry.
Maybe the most powerful.
Well, I have to do my next
record with Edgehill.
Well, she wants your next five records.
"Wrong song" got you back on her radar.
She loves what you did with it.
We co-wrote it.
"Co-" means "two."
"Co-" actually means "with."
Why's she on my plane?
Oh, right. 'Cause she can't afford her own.
I'm 3 feet away from you. I can hear you.
Can you?
That's interesting, 'cause
when we're onstage,
y'all act like I don't even exist.
Oh, believe me.
We're both painfully
aware of your existence.
That is my bean dip!
Guys, we are going back for a party.
Can we... look, just have some
fun, for crying out loud.
I thought we were going back for
Juliette's mom's court hearing.
Stop talking.
Hey. Have you seen this?
"The axe falls hard on
guitarman Deacon Claybourne."
No. No, no, no, no. I know
what I think about it.
I just wanna know what you think about it.
No... yeah! The article!
You think so? You think
it's true when Cy says,
"we tried to give him a chance.
It just didn't pan out"?
No! No, Carmen, that's what I'm saying.
It didn't not pan out.
I caught the guy mauling my niece.
I said "no comment"
because I want her to have her own privacy.
She deserves some privacy.
I don't want to drag her into it.
Hold on. Listen to me.
"Letting someone go is always hard,
but watching him fall off the
wagon, that's even harder."
You believe that? You
think that's true? No!
I haven't had a drink in 12 damn years!
4,420 days, to be specific,
if you gotta know.
Damn it!
Sync by YYeTS
Corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
You're home! You're home!
Hi, my girls! Oh! Okay.
How do I have three shin guards
and only one cleat? Oh, no.
I lost a tooth while you were gone.
Lost a tooth and a cleat?
What is the world coming
to when I leave town?
Good morning. Hey.
This came for you. Hey, kiddo.
Hey, go get dressed for school. Hustle up.
All right, breakfast in five. I
have slaved over this stove.
Oh, my lord. What is this?
You know, you didn't have to sleep
in the guest room last night.
It was so late. I didn't wanna wake you up.
Right. "Hope we get some time to talk."
For starters, you need your own plane."
Yes, I do need my own plane.
Should I be jealous?
I don't think so.
Oh, my gosh.
Calista Reeves. Countless records.
What's going on?
Well, clearly, she means business.
No, I'm talking about us.
I mean...
We're putting on a good face for the girls.
We're sleeping in separate bedrooms.
You and I haven't made love in months.
I mean, are... are we trying to
fix things between us or not?
You know, I think we took this
time apart to get some clarity.
And...
I don't have the answers yet.
Would you stop pacing, please?
You're making me dizzy.
Can you just explain this plea
deal to me one more time?
It's simple, jolene.
You plead guilty today,
and as long as you complete rehab,
the charges will be dropped...
And you won't have to set
foot in this courtroom again.
That'd be a relief.
Deacon.
Hey, you good?
Hey. Thank you so much.
This is Deacon. He's gonna be
speaking on my behalf. Deacon.
Listen, about that. I just had
this article written about me.
I... I'm just not sure
how good it's gonna be, me talking for you.
Are you talking about that
"tremolo" thing? Yeah.
What was that? That's crap.
I know what "not sober" looks like, okay?
I grew up with it. That's not you.
Well, I appreciate that. I just...
I still think it might be
better if you talk today.
No. No.
I got her a great lawyer.
You're practically her sponsor.
Why would I do the talkin'?
Well, you're the person most affected
by your mother's addiction.
It would mean a lot more coming from you.
That sucked.
Hey. Or maybe you just did.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. You...
Need to stop being so hard on yourself.
And you need to go do your homework.
All right?
You have a beautiful home.
Thank you.
Rayna, thank you so much for seeing me.
Oh, yeah. My pleasure.
You just can't be afraid of the ball.
Such a sweet family. Aw, thanks.
Poor Maddie does get her
athletic ability from me.
Ohh, so sad.
Oh, well, you have other talents.
Thank you.
And I appreciate you coming
over to the house today
so I could have a little
more time with my girls.
You only have 24 hours at home.
I mean, I do the same thing.
I'm a mom, too.
And the breadwinner. I get it.
I appreciate that.
I can't tell you how many
years I felt like I was
hittin' my head against
a wall with Edgehill,
trying to get 'em to understand that.
Yeah, that's what Liam said
when he sent me the last
roughs of what you guys cut.
He... he sent you those tracks?
Those tracks weren't ready to go out.
Ready enough. No.
Uh, yeah, he thinks it's time for a change,
and I do, too.
You're reinventing yourself.
"Wrong song" is great to get you
to the top of the charts again,
but the last thing you
need is to be pressured
into doing duets with
some prefab prima Donna
who came up overnight and...
Can be gone just as fast.
No offense.
I know how hard leaving is.
Believe me, it was hard when
I broke off from capitol.
But it doesn't make staying right.
Chicken.
I'm not your chicken.
Well, you know...
It does feel like I sort of
have a lifetime investment.
What you wanna do creatively,
it's not in Marshall's wheelhouse.
He's a bean counter and
he's never gonna get it.
He came up in this business
with his head in the books,
not in the headphones.
Look, Rayna, I don't want to "sell" you.
Ask Liam. He can vouch for me.
I want to be your partner.
♪You've got the whole world in your hands♪
♪And this is really what you planned♪
♪Well, I turned the pages,
read the words in red♪
?I still don't understand
♪Sat on the phone but I can't hear♪
♪Opened every window, but
it's still not clear♪
♪Asked for forgiveness,
restoration for my soul♪
?But I'm still sincere
?I know I've seen an angel
?And I know it made me cry
?So when I look at heaven
♪Why do I keep asking why♪
Busted!
Let's get out of here.
Jolene Barnes has learned from
her mistakes, your honor.
She's not a criminal.
She's a-a person with a disease.
She sought out treatment.
And she only has 21 more days
left on a 60-day program.
Her daughter Juliette is here
to speak on her mother's behalf.
Speak from your heart.
Um, my mother has been an addict for...
As long as I can remember,
and I'm...
Very glad that she is gettin'
the help that she needs.
There's nobody who hopes
this sticks more than I do.
That's all I have to say.
Thank you for your testimonial, Ms. Barnes.
I'll take this under advisement
and render a decision.
It shouldn't be long.
That was a hell of a speech in there.
I mean, really emotional.
You know, really moving.
You told me to speak from the heart, okay?
That's all I had.
You okay?
Just a busy day.
Oh, that's right. Y'all got that
number one song party to go to, huh?
I guess congratulations are in order.
Don't congratulate me. Congratulate Rayna.
Apparently she's the one
who did it all by herself.
She's the superhero,
and I'm the person who just
came in and held her cape.
Yeah, well, that's not what happened.
I remember. I was there.
Yes.
And now you're here.
You know the offer still stands,
that you can come on tour with me anytime.
I appreciate it, but I think I'm just gonna
come off the road for a little bit.
Maybe even the grid.
What? No.
No way. You are way too good of a musician
to hole up and hide behind
patchy facial hair.
You going back to the office?
What'd they say? Well, it
didn't work, the plea.
She'll have to finish rehab.
Then there'll be another hearing
to try to get the criminal charges dropped.
All right. Couple more weeks then.
Still got a free pass today. Why
don't we go do somethin' fun?
I can't. I have to go to that party.
That I have a plus-one to I'm not using.
Why don't you come with me? Yeah?
No, I don't think it's a good
idea to have a rehab patient
at a-an industry party where
there's alcohol everywhere.
World's full of alcohol, Juliette.
I gotta do it sometime.
I mean, isn't that why God
created sparkling water?
I am not gonna be able to hang out either.
I'm gonna have to socialize.
I'm gonna have to talk
to a bunch of people.
That I don't want to talk to. It's okay.
All right, I'll just hide behind her
instead of my patchy facial hair.
Thank you.
Let's all go.
Calista outlined the deal for me.
It's gonna be really hard
for Edgehill to beat
or even come close to.
Well, it's tempting.
You know, and countless' track
record speaks for itself.
But I don't know. There's
something that doesn't feel...
Calista's a visionary. You're a superstar.
What's the problem?
The problem is that it just feels
like it's happening too fast.
And I wish you hadn't
given her those tracks.
Those tracks were not ready to go out.
You should've consulted with me first.
Well, you know, I'm just trying to help.
But if you wanna stay
in something stale, old,
and boring, go for it.
Maybe that's your thing.
Think of Edgehill like your marriage.
The only way to get through it
is by fantasizing about someone else.
What?
I heard his song three times
on the radio yesterday.
Apparently he's the number
one most requested.
Is there no music karma?
What about guys like Gunnar
and Deacon, you guys?
Gunnar's right. Nice guys finish last.
Well, you know what we should do?
Wrap him in a tarp, drop him in a river?
Or band together.
Literally.
You know I'm dying to play with you again.
I can't bail on Gunnar.
And I am not Mr. fabulous
over there, either, so...
I'm talking about you and Gunnar.
You know we need a singer,
and we could use a kick-ass
guitar player as well.
Think about it.
Your songs, our rhythm section.
It'd be a huge win for the good guys.
Just let me run it by Gunnar.
My guys, our amps, your garage.
Oh, just like old times.
To good karma.
Oh, yeah.
The great Rayna James!
Back on top, back in town.
Back for the big party, huh?
Yeah.
What are you doin'?
Uh, well, I'm-a go to the party, too,
and then I'm gonna go to
the cabin for a while.
Looks like a long while.
Oh, yeah. Well...
You know, I just thought I
could use a change, you know?
Guess you read the article, huh?
Bunch of crap, right?
That's what I said.
You wanna talk about it?
Cy's a horse's ass. I quit the band.
End of story.
That's a short story.
You talk to Coleman lately?
What do you mean? Since your family
stomped all over his dreams?
No. Well...
Ray, you wanna ask me
somethin', just ask me.
Uh, all right.
Well, you know, I guess seeing
you like this and all...
It kinda scares the hell out of me, so...
I wanna make sure you're all right...
you're doing your program,
going to your meetings,
stuff like that.
Well, the good news is,
it's not 12 years ago,
so I'm not your responsibility anymore.
I know.
I care about you.
That's awesome.
Why are you so angry with me?
I'm... why am I angry with you?
You don't... yeah.
I don't know, ray.
Maybe it's 'cause every time I turn around,
you're, like, firing me
or breaking up with me
or telling me I need to go see
what's around the next bend in the river,
some crap like that. Maybe that's why.
It's 'cause I want you to be happy.
What, like you're happy with Teddy?
Don't do that.
I forgot to ask you.
Did you ever find out if
he was cheatin' on you?
He isn't.
Well...
I guess you made the
right choice then, huh?
Him over me?
Well, you know I didn't have
much choice in that matter,
'cause you couldn't stay sober.
All I know is that you put me in rehab,
and the next thing I know,
you two are gettin' married.
All right, that's why I know.
I know...
You could've waited for me,
and you didn't.
How many times did I have
to go lookin' for you?
How many times
did I have to drag you out of hotel rooms
'cause you were so wasted
I didn't know if you were drunk or dead?
I didn't know that the fifth time in rehab
was actually gonna take.
You lost faith in me.
You did then, you did now.
I never lost faith in you.
Mm-hmm.
And I have not lost faith in you now.
And you got sober.
But I'll tell you what, it's
conversations like this
that make it so that I can't...
I can't do this with you.
Then don't do it.
So you never know. You need
a song to close the show...
Boom. Number one.
So how many number ones is this now?
I bet you've lost count.
Oh, my gosh. You don't lose count.
But I will tell you,
every single time, it feels damn good.
Just one more, Ms. Barnes.
There you go. Thank you very much.
Hey!
What the hell is that?
Oh. Uh, Juliette,
I-I want you to meet, uh, Adam Wergeles.
He blogs for "country fandom" web site.
Hi, Juliette. Great to see you.
Hi. Good to see you.
Congratulations. Uh...
This song is such a hit.
Our... our readers are dying to know,
were you intimidated by writing
with the queen of country?
Intimidated?
Um, no.
Well... it must've been great, though.
It was a thrill to see her
contribute a bridge to the song.
Oh! Hey, look. Marshall. Marshall, hey.
Marshall, this is Adam.
Hi, Marshall.
Jason?
Nope. I'm calling about him, though.
This his brother?
Who's this? Officer vega
with the bastrop county parole division.
Uh, Jason never made it
to his halfway house.
You picked him up from prison, correct?
Yes, sir, I did,
and I dropped him right
off at the halfway house.
Happen to stop at any
pawnshops along the way?
No, sir, I did not.
Hi.
Listen, um,
I'm in the middle of work right now.
Is there anything else?
Your brother's a fugitive.
If there's anything you
might be keeping from us
to help us bring him in,
you're in violation of the law, too, son.
Copy that.
Hey. Hey.
How are you? I'm all right.
Uh, I thought you had
the night off tonight.
I do,
but I also have a proposition for you.
Okay.
Number one with a bullet, huh?
It's so nice to see you. Thanks for coming.
Of course. He never misses a
chance for a free cocktail.
Hey, anything with "party" in the title,
I'm all about it.
By the way, how's your album coming?
It's good. You know, line
by line, chord by chord.
And you got Liam McGuinnis, right?
Yeah, yeah. He's great.
He's good. It's kinda different.
It's different sounds.
Uh... there's my husband.
Get on over there. All right.
Hi. Well, look at you.
Hey.
Thank you for being here.
You bet. Duty calls.
It means a lot to me that you're here
to give the award.
You know I'm here for more
than just giving that award.
I'm here for those sliders.
Come on. Let's go celebrate. Okay.
This is your night.
?Pretty smile,
?My intuition
where is Deacon?
He is supposed to be watching her.
Excuse me, Juliette.
Mom, you cannot touch every
touch piece of food.
?You can't hide from me
what?
I was just saying hi.
To Juliette Barnes?
Yeah. Why not?
I mean, I've been waiting for you
to introduce me to people all night.
I have been doing that.
Not to a&r guys. I already
have a record deal.
What do I need them for?
I just don't recommend
approaching Juliette Barnes for no reason.
I'm an artist like she is.
There's my reason.
Wait. You went to see Avery play?
Oh, barely. I stayed
for, like, half a song.
Gross. But I was thinking,
us and J.T. and the band,
like, they love the way you play,
and then we could do gigs at the 5 spot
and things like... yeah, look,
I don't know, Scarlett.
Um, I'm in the middle of work,
and I just need some time to think on it.
Okay. Uh...
Is it because it's Avery's old band?
This is not about Avery.
I've got a lot on my plate right now.
I know, and I'm worried about you.
You've been funny since Austin,
and I'm wondering if there's
anything I can do to help,
or can I... do you wanna talk about it.
You know, you wouldn't
even begin to understand.
It's serious.
And I'm not?
No. You... you come bouncin' in here
like this... this band thing
is the most important thing in the world.
No, I didn't think that.
I just thought maybe you'd...
you'd find it exciting
I checked with Deacon. He said
the boys are really good.
Well, that sounds great.
Why doesn't Deacon go
play with 'em then, huh?
It's not like he's playin'
with somebody else.
Um... you know what?
Forget I said anything.
Don't... don't worry about it.
Scarlett.
Wait, hold on.
Hey, Gunnar. Hey, man, this
got dropped off for you.
What? By who?
Some guy named Jason.
When?
Couple hours ago.
Said he was just passin' through.
So as mayor elect
and co-chair of the music
city music council,
we thank you for being ambassadors
on behalf of our city,
and for your contributions to
our greatest export, music.
And it is my honor to present
these awards to you both.
And nothing personal, Juliette,
but especially to the woman
who is always number one...
my wife Rayna Jaymes.
?Don't
?You think I'm under
?This ain't a feel-good
?Everything's fine
whoa. Hey. Excuse me. You okay?
Uh, yeah.
You know, this isn't actually
the... the first time that we've met.
I-I ran into you backstage,
uh, at the opry.
Literally.
I mean, I get it. Must
happen to you all the time.
I'm just kind of getting used to it myself.
You know, the whole star thing.
I signed with Dominic's label.
He's got kind of this urban
take on the music... oh, sorry.
Trying to mix it up some.
You know, I-I'd love for you
to hear it sometime... hi.
If you'd like.
I'm Avery Barkley.
I sing that song "kiss."
Hello. Miss Jaymes, hi.
Hi.
I'm such a big fan of yours.
Oh, thank you so much.
I'm sorry, I've never heard of it.
Mama.
I'm jolene. I'm Juliette's mama.
Oh, my goodness. I'm sorry.
Um, sorry. I-I...
mama, stop.
I just wanted to thank her.
Nice to meet you.
You do not need to thank her for anything.
Listen to me. She did not do me any favors.
I was just trying to be nice.
Don't try to be anything.
You're not even supposed to be here.
Is there anything you don't ruin?
Rayna. Liam.
Well, I wondered if I'd be able
to successfully avoid you all night.
Hey, Marshall. Nice party.
Well, over 2 million downloads,
I should be thanking you.
You built this label, Rayna.
We don't wanna lose you.
Word travels fast, huh?
Well, save your breath,
'cause you're not gonna be able
to offer enough to keep us.
Well, respectfully, Liam,
my contract's with Rayna, not with you.
Well, respectfully,
Marshall, we are partners.
I'm guessing you don't
know about the imprint
that countless has offered your partner
if he brings you on as an artist.
What?
Not much of a partnership
if one half's double-dipping and
the other half doesn't know.
Did you lie to me?
That guy is such an ass.
Well, yeah, but who lied, you or the ass?
It's not really a lie.
Besides, it's still great for you.
This isn't great for me. I'm helping you.
That's what you wanted, right?
You came knocking on my door, remember?
The whole reason you have a
career again is because of me.
Is that what you think? Mm-hmm.
'Cause my feeling was it was 'cause of us,
'cause we're partners.
You don't lie to your partner.
Yeah.
Tell that to your husband.
Come on. We are partners.
I'm not doing this.
What?
This partnership is dissolved.
Come on. You're finally
getting something going.
We are. We aren't.
You can't just walk away from me.
From you? Yes, I can.
Is there something going
on with you and Liam?
No.
Except I fired him
'cause he was...
Doing some kind of deal behind my back.
That's it?
Because it looked like
a lot more than that.
I guess another man in my life lying to me
feels like a lot more than that.
Rayna, enough already, okay?
Look, how many times do I have
to apologize for what I did?
I screwed up, okay?
You know it, I know it.
But what else can I do?
You know, I'm here at home holding out hope
that we can fix things,
while you're out there on the
road doing God knows what.
I'm out there on the road
doing God knows what?
You know what I'm out there doing?
Paying for this house, among other things.
Well, yeah. Yeah, and I'm
home raising our daughters,
that's what I'm doing.
Well, I'm standing by you.
I'm not divorcing you
or calling the cops on you.
That's what I'm doing.
I just...
I just wanna know where we stand.
I wanna move forward.
And instead, I'm watching
everyone in the world...
Liam, that new label...
everyone's trying to win you over,
and all I wanna do is win you back.
You know, I think it's complicated.
It's complicated.
Yeah, when I met you,
Deacon had destroyed you.
You'd put him in rehab how many times?
Five. Right.
Five.
You were alone.
I remember you told me you just...
All you wanted was someone solid,
a guy who had his life together, and I did.
You know, then when things
fell apart for me financially
and kept falling apart,
I-I guess I lost my way.
I just wanted to be the guy that
I thought you wanted me to be.
And God knows it doesn't
excuse what I did, but...
I guess at the time,
I thought I was doing it
for the right reason.
Maybe we're not all that different, Rayna.
Wrong choice, right reason.
Maybe that's how we ended up together.
Are you gonna answer me?
Page and plant? Right.
Well, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, killer.
How you doin'? How you doin'?
I'm good. Good.
Hey, guys, I know, like, you're all set up.
You should play here long as you want,
but I did talk to Gunnar about it.
He said the whole joining forces this
wasn't gonna work out. I-I'm sorry.
He just taught us "one works better."
What are you doing here?
Wanted the good guys to win,
even if I don't act like
one myself sometimes.
Whatever it is that's bothering you,
I sure wish you'd talk about it.
I'd rather just play, if that's all right.
It's good to see you got your Gibson back.
All right, you boys ready?
Count it off. Mm-hmm.
Three, four.
Deacon?
Hey!
Deacon?!
Open the damn door!
I know you're in there!
Your piece-of-crap truck's out here!
Where the hell have you been?!
Deacon?
Just go away.
That's not gonna happen.
It was out of tune.
Well, you're too miserable to be drunk.
You know so much, don't you?
I know a dry drunk when I see one.
Look at me. Come with me.
You should be on the road.
You need to be playin', writin' music,
going to meetings, working the program.
Look, there's a group in my crew.
They meet twice a week.
It's a pain in my ass.
But you need to do what you love.
Isn't that why you got sober?
Isn't that what kept you sober?
You know, it's funny.
I always used to say that, uh,
I got sober for myself, you know?
That's what you're supposed to say.
It was never true.
I got sober for Rayna.
What kept me sober...
Was hoping for something that
ain't never gonna happen.
You really think she saved your life?
From an outsider's perspective,
she is the opposite of what you need.
You gonna tell me what I need now?
Don't you got another
addict to go take care of?
I'm serious. I mean, look at
you got all the care and
concern in the world for me,
but what about her, nothin'?
See, I don't get that,
'cause she and me, we're the same.
Yeah.
We're fightin' the exact same battle.
Right now, only difference is...
She's doing a whole lot better than me.
Hey. There you are.
Baby, I'm sorry.
No. No, I'm sorry.
Deacon's in bad shape.
He didn't drink, but he...
Easily could've.
I just feel like if he, of all people,
can fall off the wagon...
Then there's no hope for me.
Listen to me. I...
I should have told the
judge how far you've come.
I mean, that you've stayed in rehab,
the fact that you're even
here in the first place.
I should have told you that I'm...
Really, really proud of you.
You don't know what that means to me.
Somebody like you being...
Proud of somebody like me?
Somebody like me? What
are you talking about?
Baby, I'm in awe of you.
I saw you up on that stage
tonight with the legend,
with the woman that you've admired
since you were a little girl, and...
Now you're her equal.
You think I'm Rayna's equal?
Oh, yeah, and then some.
Baby, she... she grew up in belle Meade,
and, well, you came from...
You came from me.
And you're so amazing and
talented and beautiful.
And... if you can come
from someone like me?
Well, that just proves that there's hope.
I don't tell you that I'm proud,
because then it sounds like
I'm trying to take credit.
But I am. I'm so proud of you.
All th you are
and... and everything you've become, honey,
that's... that's not because of me.
It's in spite of me.
Who you are and where you are, honey...
Baby, that's all you.
I'd have told you,
but I didn't think that what I thought
meant anything to you.
It means somethin'.
?You been working
?lt's too late to change
?Please let me know
?What
?You just said
?Oh, girl, when you walk
?Talk like that
?Look like that
?I'm chained to your will
?So, honey,
?Come on closer
♪Just winning and survival♪
♪I've got a voice and I made my choice♪
♪Between heartbreak and revival♪
♪I know you hate how I make♪
♪Everything look easy to do♪
?Oh, but it's my pleasure
♪Doing everything better without you♪
♪'Cause this one works better than two♪
Ohh. Y'all be good for your daddy, okay?
Okay. Okay, mom.
See you in a couple weeks. All right.
Okay? Let's go look at the planes.
You be good, too.
Listen, as far as I'm
concerned, we're still married,
whether I'm here in Nashville
or whether I'm out on tour.
I chose you. That was never a wrong choice.
I think now we're just...
Choosing what our future's gonna be.
Right.
Marshall keeps calling.
So does Calista.
They both wanna know where you stand.
I want my own label.
Tell that to Marshall, and if he says yes,
then I will stay at Edgehill.
Okay, so no Calista?
No. Not yet.
Why do we have to do everything
at the crack of butt?
Will you please also tell
him I want my own plane?
All right. So, hey, we
goin' to Kansas City?
Not quite yet.
We're waitin' for one more.
Excuse me.
Deacon. How y'all doing?
Y'all take care, okay? Okay.
Hey.
Sorry for the hold-up.
Did you hire him to replace Liam
and not talk to me about it?
No. Of course not.
I'm not here for your band.
He's joining mine.
Sync by YYeTS
Corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com