♪
(tires squealing, horn honks)
(tires squealing)
(horn honks)
Yo, we good up there?
(beeping)
DRIVER: That's a bomb! We got to go!
No! Stay in the truck.
(panicked screams, clamoring)
216 under automatic gunfire.
Possible robbery attempt.
Send backup immediately.
WOMAN (over radio):
Copy that.
Hurry, they're coming in.
(clown grunting in pain)
(engine revving,
tires squealing)
(crowd screaming)
♪ NCIS: LA 4x09 ♪
The Gold Standard
Original Air Date on December 11, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
After action reports?
You were supposed
to help me with this.
I told you to call me.
I did.
What time?
About half past you ignoring me
because you didn't want
to do this again.
KENSI:
Sorry, sorry,
sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Understatement of the year.
I'm so sorry, Sam,
but I will take it from here.
Save it. I'm already done.
I was supposed
to carpool with Deeks,
but he never showed up.
I will do them next time,
I promise.
Me, too. I owe you one.
You both will excuse me
if I don't hold my breath.
There's a serious lack
of professionalism around here.
Yeah, speaking of,
where is Deeks?
Arms trafficker Nelson Sanders
has been implicated
on additional charges.
Deeks has been called in
to testify.
The guy his buddy Ray
helped put away?
Who says this isn't a crack team
of investigators?
In Detective Deeks' absence,
I will accompany you
into the field
if necessary,
Agent Blye.
Oh, no, no.
I don't want you
to have to do that.
You know I would love
to learn the ropes
from a grizzled veteran
such as yourself.
"Grizzled veteran," Ms. Blye?
Um, what I meant was that...
the extensive years
of experience...
"Extensive years."
You don't think I can hack it
in the field, do you,
Agent Blye?
What I meant was...
it would be my honor to ride
along with you, sir.
Good.
(Eric whistling a reveille)
Eric, please.
What is this, boot camp?
See you in a little bit.
Are you not coming?
I'm the assistant director.
I've been briefed.
Of course.
NELL:
A heist crew
wreaked havoc at the LA Live
Entertainment Center today,
knocking over an armored truck.
Thanks to traffic cams and
the smart phone revolution,
we've got plenty of footage
of what went down.
They used the tourist traffic
to their advantage.
Looks like the circus
is in town.
SAM:
These guys are pros.
Fast, organized, and ruthless.
Fortunately, one of the guards
inside the truck survived,
despite suffering a head wound.
What was the cargo?
100 Good Delivery gold bars,
the type used
in major international markets,
central banks, and the IMF.
The bars were en route
from the Federal Reserve
to the People's Bank of China.
How much we talking?
ERIC: The gold bars
weigh 12.4 kilos.
At $1,750 an ounce...
That's $700,000 a bar
or roughly...
$70 million.
(shudders)
Just got a gold rush.
What are we buying?
Time.
The gold is an interest payment
on a trillion dollar plus loan
we have with China.
If we can't recover it,
well, let's just say
we don't want them
to repossess Hawaii.
MAN: So we'll
keep you posted, okay?
Thanks.
Okay.
What do you think?
I think you got
to have some big ones
to pull off a heist like this
in the middle of the day.
Yeah, no joke.
You find anything useful?
Not yet. You?
They had to have
left something.
ATM, traffic,
security cams--
it's an odd location
for a heist.
There's more surveillance
than LAX.
The motor home stops here.
Blocks off the armored car.
Bozo bounds from the curb.
Captain Sparrow wannabe points
his assault rifle,
then monkey boy
pulls up the cargo van.
Pretty sure
it was actually a gorilla.
Monkeys usually have tails.
They can't swing from branch
to branch like apes can.
They also can't drive
a cargo van.
I saw one drive a motorcycle
one time, so he probably could.
And I knew one that worked
in a bar in Huntington Beach
who could make a martini.
I'm not saying it was
a good martini.
We got blood.
He could have jumped into
their car or grabbed a cab.
Or dumped his disguise
and lost himself in the crowd.
Aw, damn!
You got to be kidding me.
What?
I hate clowns.
Yep, not nearly as funny
when they're dead, are they?
This clown is Clive Mayfield.
He's a well-known criminal
who's bounced around the country
with a number
of different heist crews.
He did time for armed robbery
at USP Atlanta.
We put together
a list of former associates,
some of whom are
from the LA area.
Hopefully one or more
were involved in the heist
and can lead us to the gold.
What's the word
on the guard he shot?
Lucky. Hospital says
he's up and around.
Kensi's on her way
to talk to him.
Well, hopefully he can
tell us something.
Sam and I will run down
Clive Mayfield
and his criminal buddies.
Maybe we'll get lucky, too.
Uh, where is Sam?
He's... dealing with something.
Coulrophobia.
Fear of clowns?
Is that even a real thing?
It is with Sam.
Weird.
Oh, yeah.
You don't, uh,
have any irrational phobias
I should know about, do you?
Well...
do you think hand puppets
are creepy?
Not particularly.
Yeah, me neither.
Ventriloquist dummies,
on the other hand...
Creepy, right?
Totally.
I used to have this nightmare
when I first
started working here.
It's the middle
of the night.
I'm here all alone.
I come up to Ops...
and there's somebody sitting
in the shadows.
And I can't see their face
'cause they're...
they're turned away from me,
but I can tell that there's...
There's something in their lap,
and I want to run,
but I can't.
And slowly they turn around,
and I see what they're holding.
It's...
Hetty.
The Treasury Department
is about to have
a China Syndrome meltdown.
So if you don't want
your paychecks
to bounce this week...
I suggest you forgo story time
and get cracking.
We are... cracking.
Crack, crack, cracking.
(chuckles)
That was weird.
Do you two need to be separated?
No.
SAM (muffled):
Federal agents!
Clear.
Looks like Clive Mayfield
left in a hurry.
Yeah, $70 million,
I'd be on my way
to my own private island.
What, you don't spend
enough time alone?
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna buy you a yacht,
so you can come visit me.
Make it a private jet
and I just might.
You'd buy a jet?
No, I'd make you buy me a jet.
I'd open up an auto body shop.
$70 million, and you're gonna
become a mechanic?
Auto science specialist.
It's a calling.
I'd open a place
where people could go
without getting ripped off.
Yeah, no need for cars
on the island.
What, you and Gilligan gonna
build a bike out of coconuts?
Think there's anything
in there?
Nope.
What, is this for
hamsters or something?
Only if they're food.
This is for a snake.
By the size of this tank,
I'd say a big one.
You think the owner took it
with him?
I sure as hell hope so.
You seen enough?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
G?
It's okay.
Just a false alarm.
(indistinct announcement
over P.A.)
Jack?
Jack Williams?
Yeah, that's what
they're telling me.
I'm Special Agent Blye.
I was hoping to talk to you
about the robbery this morning.
I watched it on the news but
I... I still don't remember it.
It's not unusual
in traumatic situations.
Yeah, they said that, too.
They also said
I'm lucky to be alive, but...
I don't feel too lucky.
You may feel it's insignificant,
but any little detail
that you could recall
from this morning's heist
would be useful.
Accent of the thieves,
jargon they used,
even the smell of their cologne
would be helpful.
They say I killed a man.
And I don't remember
firing my gun.
I don't remember anything.
You see that woman
and those kids?
They say that's my wife
and-and children.
But I don't recognize them.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm... I'm-I'm sorry.
Look, I'd like to help you,
but I can't.
And to be honest, I...
All I want to do right now is
just remember who the hell I am.
Okay.
Jack...
when you do remember
something.
Well?
He says he doesn't
remember anything.
You believe him?
Sounds pretty convincing.
That heist was
pretty damn slick.
It'd pay to have a man
on the inside.
They shot him in the head.
What better way
to cover your tracks.
That would explain
the sudden amnesia.
Put a guard on him.
In case he runs?
Or they come back
and finish the job.
Copy that.
So, I'll see you back at Ops?
Nice try-- you're my ride.
Besides, you and I could use
some quality time.
Awesome.
(phone ringing)
Yeah, what do
you got, Nell?
I got a hit
on a clown costume.
Yeah, pass that
one on to Kensi.
She can check it out
on her way back.
Also, can you run a search
of recent purchases
of snake supplies
in the area?
What kind of snake?
A big one.
NELL: Okay.
Thanks.
I know
it's irrational.
I didn't say anything.
(electronic door bell chimes)
Assistant Director,
do you not trust me
to handle this on my own?
Don't like being under the
microscope, Agent Blye?
No, it's not that--
Because you are.
What?
I'm kidding.
Okay, you're
a very busy man.
I'm just maintaining
protocol, Agent Blye.
Don't take it personally.
Besides, performance
reviews are due.
Oh...
Great choice.
Comes with tear-away trousers,
bow tie, collar, cuffs.
Six-pack not included.
But we should
have your size.
Nothing like a little
role-play to spice up
the bedroom.
We're Federal agents.
I don't judge.
Uh, yesterday we had
a couple nuns in here,
bought leather cat suits.
All right, that's just weird.
You sold some costumes
to a guy a few days ago:
a gorilla, a clown, a pirate...
No refunds, exchange only.
We don't need a refund--
we need some answers.
Do you recognize
this guy?
Nope.
You recognize him
in your costume?
No exchanges once it's worn.
That guy's dead.
No exceptions.
Who bought the costume?
It wasn't the guy
who was wearing it?
Look...
I sell a lot of costumes.
I'm still restocking
from Halloween.
Okay, we're gonna need your
credit card records then.
(scoffs) Transaction
fees are murder
on a small business
owner-- cash only.
Fine, we'll take your
surveillance tapes.
40 bucks.
We're not buying them from you,
we're Federal Agents.
Okay, 20 bucks.
How about we shut your shop down
for running a meth lab
out of the basement?
Meth lab?!
There's no meth lab here.
Uh, there's no basement here.
Maybe not, but can
a small business owner
such as yourself
survive the red tape?
Hm?
I'll be right back.
Wonderful.
"Grizzled vet," huh?
Meet Duncan Welch,
full-time criminal,
part-time pirate.
His rap sheet reads
like a companion piece
to our dead clown
Clive Mayfield.
Do you think these guys
pick out their own costumes?
Like, maybe two
of 'em wanted
to be the pirate,
and then one of 'em's like,
"I called it," and the other
one's like, "You always
get to be the pirate.
I never get to be the pirate."
And the other one's
like, "Whoa, whoa, whoa,
"you got to be
the pirate last time.
"This time I'm gonna
be the pirate,
and you get to be
the clown, sucker."
Just, you know, thinking maybe
their choice of disguise
might give you some insight
into these guys.
Psychological profiling
through costume choice?
Sounds silly when you say it like that.
NELL: No, it's...
it's an interesting theory,
but I think it might just be...
easier to check
his last known address.
Uh, 1274
Hillcrest Road, Sylmar.
Or you could do that.
Thank you, guys.
Mm-hmm.
If I robbed a bank,
I'd totally be the cowboy.
You?
Well, I...
wouldn't rob a bank,
but, clearly, you've
given this some thought.
(scoffs)
(engine roaring,
tires screeching)
Federal agents!
All clear.
Looks like they
were executed.
Is that everyone?
Everyone but Duncan Welch,
the guy we're
looking for.
He was here.
KENSI: Nell and Eric
confirmed the I.D.s
of the heist crew.
We have Patrick Rodgers,
Derrick Stovall,
and Marcus Terry.
Duncan Welch took the gold,
killed his buddies.
KENSI:
It's easier
to divide by one than by four.
Five.
Still need to find Duncan
and the cargo van driver.
KENSI: Okay.
I'll put out a BOLO:
male, six feet tall,
dark hair...
covering his entire body,
partial to bananas...
Duncan's partner
in the double cross?
Well, unless there's another
Dumpster out there
with a dead monkey in it.
Gorilla.
Apparently monkeys have tails.
Okay. Well, according
to his bank records,
Duncan Welch was spending a lot
of money before the heist.
Confident man.
Either that or someone was
bankrolling the heist.
Someone who's willing to piss
off the Treasury Department
and the Chinese government.
What was he buying?
Um, that's where it
gets interesting.
KENSI:
Check this out.
Lots of dinners,
jewelry,
women's lingerie.
Sounds like Duncan's
got a girlfriend.
Or a cross-dressing fetish.
Hey, we know he likes
to dress up.
You got his phone records?
KENSI:
Yes, I do.
CALLEN:
Hello, Gloria Bryant.
Could be a business associate.
From 9:00 a.m.
to 7:00 p.m., maybe.
But from midnight to 3:00 a.m.--
that's a booty call.
Well, you know,
when two people call each other
in the middle of the night
and they're lonely
and they want to...
Is that what that's called?
I'm gonna shut up now.
Have an address, I got this.
Uh-huh.
I'm gonna go.
Ms. Blye?
Let me guess: more quality time?
No, I was gonna say
be safe, but...
I can join you if you like.
No, no.
I'm good.
I'm out.
Gloria Bryant?
Federal agent.
Um...
It's okay.
I'm looking for Duncan Welch.
GLORIA:
Oh, uh...
I haven't seen him.
Which, unfortunately,
is par for the course.
He just disappears
without a word
and then...
pops back up
like nothing's wrong.
Men.
Yeah, right?
I mean, I just figured
he was seeing somebody else.
Never thought it was
something illegal.
Gran Gran loved him.
Is that your grandmother?
Uh, yeah.
He'd sit with her sometimes
during her game shows.
Aw. Do you know
where I can find him?
No.
Although I might know
somebody who might.
He used to go fishing
with his buddy, Oki.
Lives in Ojai.
I might have, like,
a birthday card or something
with his return address.
Great.
I'll go get it.
Thanks.
Gran Gran would be
so disappointed right now.
Where's Duncan?
I don't know.
And yet you ran.
Do you recognize
any of these men?
Oh, my God.
No.
No?
Well, I'll give you a hint.
They all had two things
in common.
One, they were all friends
of Duncan.
Two, as you can see,
they're all dead.
Now that means that either
Duncan is a murderer,
or he's next on the killer's
list, do you understand that?
That means he's
in serious trouble,
and the only way
you can help him
is if you tell me where he is.
(sipping)
Are you going to tell me?
Tell you what?
(chuckles)
Oh, you've gotten better.
I'll grant you that.
I had a good teacher.
You're in my house now, Owen.
I hope you don't truly
believe that, Henrietta.
He's not an NCIS agent.
Then he really isn't
your concern, is he?
So much for our detente.
Are we done?
He may not be NCIS,
but Mr. Deeks is one of my team.
If anything should
happen to him,
I would take it most personally.
Duncan Welch?
Federal agents!
Hands where we
can see them.
Got a body.
SAM:
He bled out.
Looks like hours.
(crash, then clattering)
Guys?
Apparently this is
the end of the rainbow.
Always thought it'd be
a little more festive.
HETTY:
Well done.
Assistant Director
Granger called
to congratulate all of you
on solving the
case so quickly.
There's still one
person unaccounted for.
We still don't know if he was
Duncan's partner in all this
or if he killed Duncan
and the others.
Well, take it from me,
they were more concerned
about their precious gold.
Ms. Blye, with me.
Something's not right.
That was too easy.
We're good, but we're
not that good.
Whoever killed Duncan
left him with the gold.
Why?
He was at death's door.
The shooter could have casually
hauled away the gold.
Why not take it?
We could've spooked him.
Got there before
they had a chance.
Or maybe they
wanted us to find it.
(drill whirring)
(drill stops)
Tungsten.
It's bogus.
Tungsten: It's the 74th element
on the periodic table.
Its name derives from
the Swedish tung sten,
meaning "heavy stone."
Uh, its chemical
symbol is a "W"
because it was formerly
known as wolfram.
AKA my favorite element.
Nell's is ununoctium.
Don't.
SAM:
Ah...
young geek love.
But I digress.
NELL:
Tungsten and gold are
similar in weight, making it
the perfect
counterfeit substance.
Well, who would want
to steal fake gold?
SAM:
Maybe they didn't know,
or maybe it wasn't fake.
Whoever stole it
pulled a switch.
Okay, well, then
where's the real gold?
Comes back to the
cargo van driver.
CALLEN:
If they melted the real gold
to coat more bars of tungsten...
You could duplicate the gold
bars several times over.
Turning millions into billions
before anyone got caught.
Why didn't I think of that?
Um, so I could
solve the case.
I'm not a thief.
Is there something we should
know about you, Eric?
(clears throat)
Uh, what do you,
what do you got for us, Nell?
Anyway...
tungsten is about
50 bucks a kilo
and the gold bars
are 12.4 kilos each,
so we're talking about
a loof weight.
Eric, we're gonna need to know
who's been buying tungsten.
And we're gonna need somewhere
where we can smelt it.
(snickering)
I'm sorry, it's just...
it's just, like,
one of those words.
I can't explain it.
Well, I will investigate
the smelting operation.
(laughing):
Smelting.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
I just can't explain it.
Mr. Callen? A word.
You know there's
more going on here
than catching a thief.
You mean how this could
affect our economy?
If it were to get out
that America's gold
reserves were compromised,
it would wreak havoc
on our banking system.
I'm wondering if that's
been the plan all along.
If it is, we're not looking
for a heist crew.
This could be an economic
terrorist attack.
How's the world gonna react
if we try to pay off a debt
to China using fake gold?
Not very well indeed.
So who benefits
from sowing discontent
between two superpowers?
Exactly.
Who and why is just as
important as finding the gold.
The country's already facing
a fiscal challenge.
If this were to get out,
it could destroy the economy
once and for all.
Wolfram, you get any hits
on the tungsten?
Too many to count.
I'm trying to
narrow it down.
What about the smelting?
(snorts, snickers)
(chuckling):
Smelting.
How is it that you find
"smelting" to be so funny
and "frelting" to be
absolutely horrifying?
Did you find anything?
No, uh, not on the furnace,
but have you heard of
the Reptile Super Show?
Yeah.
It's in Pomona next month.
It's, like, world's largest.
I'm sorry,
you know this how?
Yeah, I went with my ex...
(clears throat):
With my friend.
Oh. Interesting.
So, what, is it like a dog show?
Do they dress their lizards up
in little outfits
and parade 'em around a ring?
No, and there's no outfits
in dog shows either.
We only do that to children.
Great.
Well, short of being
a herpetologist,
I never understood
the allure of owning a snake.
You don't like pets?
I mean, shouldn't a pet
be something you can,
I don't know, pet?
Hence the name.
You can pet a snake.
Can if you wanted to.
Do snakes like being petted?
This just took a really
weird turn, didn't it?
Yeah.
I'm think I'm gonna go
catch up with the guys.
But maybe we should run
a multivariable search
where you cross-reference
the tungsten
with the smelting
facilities?
(snickers)
(laughs)
Sorry.
Yeah.
(snickering)
Agent Blye, how did it go
with Gloria Bryant?
She tried to give me the slip,
"tried" being the
operative word,
but you're the
Assistant Director.
I'm sure you've
been briefed, sir.
Touché. Any new leads?
Yes. There are some details
that need to be run down.
Hopefully, they'll pan out.
All right, good job.
Keep me posted.
Oh, uh, I hope I get
that gold star
in my performance review, sir.
P-Rs are below my pay grade.
Oh. But before, you said that...
Disregard that.
Okay, then what was all that
ride-along, quality-time
stuff all about?
Just keeping you on your toes.
Think of it more as
an evaluation.
For...?
I'm an ambitious man,
Agent Blye,
who won't be
Assistant Director forever,
and you need to think
about the future.
You never know.
Good luck with the case.
I just had the strangest
encounter with Granger.
Everything about Granger is
strange, if you ask me.
What do you have?
Um, a cargo van was stolen
from a rental lot in
Toluca Lake last month.
Surprise, surprise.
Hey, Sam, do you still
want me looking
for reptile supplies?
No.
Okay.
Where are we?
Nowhere.
Come on, guys,
we're missing something.
Everyone leaves a trail
everywhere they go
whether they know it or not.
We know they have a cargo van,
guns, ammo...
Costumes.
They paid for parking,
paid for gas.
They could have stopped
for Starbucks.
Somebody has to have
left a clue somewhere.
Tungsten.
Who needs it?
What's it used for?
NELL:
Everything,
from electronics to
chemical catalysts.
That's part of the problem.
We need to focus on anomalies.
Cross-reference
everything we have
on Duncan, his crew, the heist,
and find the guy behind
the gorilla mask.
He's the key.
But what if they've already
moved the gold out of L.A.?
ERIC:
Hey, guys.
Found something.
A company called
Carlisle Industries purchased
a tilting smelting
furnace for $37,000.
That's one expensive
turkey fryer.
According to this, Carlisle
Industries manufactures
custom tungsten
alloy crankshafts
for the after-market
auto industry.
So it could be
a legitimate purchase.
Possible, but unlikely.
Carlisle Industries didn't
exist a month ago.
And here's the clincher:
Last week, Carlisle
Industries received
a half-ton shipment of tungsten.
There's our anomaly.
What are we thinking, Kens?
1,700 degrees.
They're cooking something.
You ready?
Yup.
Okay, we are up and running.
Where's she hiding
the camera?
Somewhere she's sure to have
his full attention.
You know I can hear you, right?
KENSI:
Hi.
Can I, uh...
help you?
Yes, I am Wendy
with the IPA.
Industrial Park Association.
Our records show that
Carlisle Industries is overdue
for an OSHA safety inspection.
Yeah. Okay, uh...
The thing is, my boss,
he isn't here right now.
Can you, um,
leave a card
or a number and...
I'll make sure he calls you back
to set up an appointment.
Nothing says welcome like having
a 300-pound Neanderthal
crammed behind a desk.
First impressions are important.
I'm sorry, Mr.--?
Remo.
Right. This is why
I'm here now, Mr. Remo.
This is my appointment.
Well, you're gonna
have to reschedule,
'cause I'm about to lock up.
Why don't you call your boss?
I don't know where he is.
Well, then find him.
Look... honey...
Shouldn't have said that.
Big mistake.
Excuse me?
My boss isn't here.
I'm about to lock up,
and you're leaving now.
I'm gonna put this in my report.
Oh, you do that.
Eric.
Looks like Kensi
could use a little help.
We're on it.
Colossus, line one
and a two and a three...
(phone lines ringing)
(chuckles)
Sorry about that, "honey."
All right.
(grunts, muffled shout)
(low, indistinct conversation)
(door clicks shut)
(clanging)
I'll check that way.
Shh.
(grunting)
(muffled grunt)
(gunshots)
(grunts)
I had him.
Course you did.
Obviously.
Whatever.
CALLEN: Forget armed robbery, assault,
economic terrorism,
and several prison lifetimes'
worth of lesser charges--
we got seven counts
of murder, gentlemen.
Seven.
But only one envelope.
In case you didn't already
know it, that gold you stole
was essentially the
vig Uncle Sam owes
on a loan to
the Chinese.
Why don't you tell them
what they won, Sam?
Well, in the interest
of international cooperation
and full disclosure,
we've agreed to send one
of you lucky contestants
back to Shanghai
for questioning.
That's right,
an all-expense-paid trip
to the land of Ping-Pong, panda,
and human rights violations.
But... only one
of you gentlemen can go.
So talk amongst yourselves,
and in 1,200 words or less,
tell us who is most deserving
to go and why.
CALLEN:
Good luck, gentlemen.
(door shuts)
(sighs)
How long do you think
before they rat each other out?
Man, as long as it takes
for Panda Express.
What was in the envelope?
Lakers tickets.
My Lakers tickets?
(sighs)
Come in.
Hey.
Hi.
Your family gone?
Yeah, Tracy had
to take the kids home.
It was past their bedtime.
So, you starting to remember?
Yeah, and doctors say I should
get more and more each day.
That's great.
I still don't remember
getting married
or my kids being born but...
But you will.
I hope so.
On the other hand,
I wish
I could forget
what happened today.
I had two tours in Afghanistan
and I never shot anybody before.
You got to take the good
with the bad.
It was self-defense.
Anyway, I just wanted
to check in
and let you know
that we caught the guys,
thanks in part to what you did.
Appreciate it.
Get some rest.
I will.
Thanks, Agent...
Um... I-I'm sorry.
Blye.
I know. I was just messin'
with you.
Bullet missed
your funny bone obviously.
Take care.
(laughs softly)
ERIC:
Guys, facial rec got a hit
on the man
behind the gorilla mask.
NELL: Jahveed Abbasi,
Iranian Nationalist.
ERIC:
Countless bombings
in Israel, Europe, Iraq.
Does not play well with others.
It sounds like this wasn't
just a heist
but a state-sanctioned
terrorist attack
on our financial infrastructure.
Either way, we stopped it.
This time.
Good work, guys.
Thanks. See you tomorrow.
Uh, you...
you two leaving?
Yeah.
Together?
Uh, I don't know.
Are we?
(chuckles)
I mean, we're going home
simultaneously.
Roughly the same
direction, so...
That wasn't meant to be
a skill-testing question.
(chuckles nervously)
Ha!
Nice.
What was that?
Don't ask, don't tell?
(chuckles)
HETTY:
"O accursed hunger
"of gold,
to what dost thou
not compel human hearts."
Virgil.
HETTY: Too bad
those two you put
in the boatshed
aren't as well versed
in the classics.
But they are singing
like the Vienna Boys' Choir
and pointing a finger
back at Iran.
Yeah, Tehran would love to see
us get into it with China.
It would take the heat off them.
Better luck next time.
Let's hope not.
And after this evening,
none of us ever need
speak of this again.
(quietly):
It's in the vault.
Speak about what?
"The man who can keep
a secret may be wise,
"but he is not half as wise
as the man who has
no secrets to keep."
Edgar Watson Howe.
And yet it's a necessary evil
in our business, I'm afraid.
Good night, Mr. Callen.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==