♪
Here you go,
ma'am.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
Welcome home,
Commander.
Hey, Joe.
How was the tour?
Too long.
Your house looks great.
Thanks.
I see my husband didn't exactly
knock himself out with ours.
Well, happy
holidays.
Noel!
What's that terrible smell?
...Dancer, Prancer,
Vixen, there we go.
♪ NCIS 10x10 ♪
You Better Watch Out
Original air date on December 18, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
I thought he'd
pick me up
at the airport
last night,
but when he didn't show,
I had to take a cab.
Where were you?
The Gulf.
Aboard the Stennis.
For the last
six months.
When was the last time
you spoke to your husband?
Thanksgiving.
When I called him.
That was almost a month ago.
Where'd your husband work?
Work?
He was an unemployed
Navy husband, Agent Gibbs.
Thank you, Commander.
Appreciate it.
Don't take this the
wrong way, Dr. Mallard.
I love my job--
I really do-- but I
will never
get used to
- the odor of a decomposed body.
- Ah, yes.
The pungent bouquet
of hydrogen sulfide
and methane.
With a faint hint of
corpus mercurium captans.
Well...
thank God there's
no maggots.
That would make it a
perfect day at the office.
Well, no sign of
forced entry, boss.
Nothing appears to be missing.
How's long has he
been here, Duck?
Educated guess?
Three or four weeks.
Well, that works.
Based on postmarks,
mail's been collecting
since November 27.
Anything else?
No visible wounds.
Hopefully,
cause of death
will be determined
at autopsy.
Neighbors we spoke to
hadn't seen him
in weeks, but they
said that wasn't
unusual.
His employment record
was spotty.
Sorry, it's my flight app.
Dad's plane's
been delayed.
Huffner never lasted
long on a job,
had not worked in over a year.
He was also
estranged
from the rest of his family.
Record?
Any criminal record?
No.
Uh, well,
I mean,
there was a DUI back in...
in 2009.
There's a storm in New York.
It's always complicated
with Senior.
Where's your
dad going?
Going? Oh, I wish.
He's coming. Here.
He says he wants to spend
Christmas with me.
You did not tell us your father
would be coming to town.
I didn't
really think
it was going to happen.
Because something
always comes up, doesn't it?
Well, I think it
sounds wonderful.
Well,
I don't.
We're not...
It doesn't...
It always ends up
in an argument.
♪
Still decorating?
Christmas is only
four days away.
No. No.
Christmas is three days,
14 hours, 27 minutes
and three seconds away.
What do you got?
Oh, uh, the contents
of the victim's pockets.
Where's his clothes?
Still in the air dryer.
Trust me, you do not want
to deal with them right now.
Oh, I like the addition
of the carolers.
Thank you.
Huffner's phone is dead.
Just like him.
He's got... two 20s,
one ten and two singles.
Men are so simple.
My wallet
is bulging;
you can't even
close the snap.
It would take hours
to go through
all the cards.
He has two.
Oh, there's another
bill in here.
Must be his emergency stash.
Hmm.
What is this?
Doesn't look like any
$100 bill I've ever seen.
- It's authentic.
- You're kidding.
Old Ben Franklin looks
like he's on steroids.
We call it the New Benjamin.
It was designed
to replace all
existing $100 bills.
Where did NCIS get this?
Found it on a dead body.
Something's very wrong here.
This new currency
hasn't been put
into circulation yet.
None of it
has ever
left our control.
Or been outside
a Treasury building.
Over a decade
of research and development
went into the New Benjamin's
security features.
Let me show you.
The changes include
color-shifting numbers
and Liberty Bell,
a 3-D ribbon
and raised printing.
It's counterfeit-proof.
When's it going to be
put into circulation?
Initially, the bills
were going to be released
in February 2011,
but there were production
problems and distribution
was delayed.
So what's the problem?
Well, um, because of all
the new security features,
it proved to be a very
difficult bill to produce.
Um, during the printing process,
there were little creases
in the notes.
Little creases?
It's kind of
a technical thing.
Sorry.
Um, much to our
embarrassment...
...uh, bills with
a face value of
$110 billion were printed.
We're not
exactly sure
how many of them
are flawed,
but estimates go, uh,
to, uh, 30%.
Wow. You'd get a big head slap
in our building
for that.
That's... that's a big number.
So heads rolled?
No, we-we
really don't
get into finger-pointing here
at the BEP, Agent DiNozzo.
Where are the bills now?
In vaults
in Fort Worth, Texas,
and here in Washington.
Sorry. I...
It's Senior.
I'll make it quick.
Let me check the serial number.
Hi, Dad.
No, I'm in the middle
of an investigation.
No!
That does not
work for me.
No! Take a cab!
The serial number
is from an early batch
that was shredded
and disposed of
a year and a half ago.
Obviously, it wasn't.
Secret Service Special Agent
Ashley Winter.
Heard NCIS
was in the building.
Would've appreciated
a call.
How much more
is missing, Donald?
Um, I-I don't know.
I-I just heard about this.
And, uh, but we're-we're
gonna get into it.
When we first found
the flaw,
we shredded millions
of dollars' worth
of the New Benjamins.
It's what we
routinely do with any
worn or damaged
U.S. currency.
I'll keep this.
It's property
of the Treasury Department.
No. No, I-I don't think so...
Ashley Winter.
No, it's evidence in an
NCIS death investigation.
Records show that Noel Huffner
never gained access
to the Bureau of Engraving
and Printing building.
And we have not been able
to connect him to anyone there.
So how'd he get the bill?
Hey, guys!
Look who I found
down in the lobby.
Dad, what are you
doing here?
Ziva, show me some love.
Oh!
Dad, I thought you
were taking a cab
from the airport
to the hotel.
No hotel.
I came to spend Christmas
with you. Gibbs.
Good to see you, A.D.
Nice to see you.
Happy holidays, Mr. DiNozzo.
Same to you, Tim.
I don't understand.
Where are you staying?
At your place.
No! No, no, no, no.
Because it's...
it's not big enough.
Oh, come on, Junior.
You've got room.
Doesn't he?
Um, I...
I would not know.
I've never been invited.
Is that true?
What's the matter with you?
You're gonna be spending
the holidays together.
It's so sweet!
No.
Yes, of course.
But not in...
because here's the thing.
It's a one-bedroom.
It's so small.
It's like a Habitrail.
But I'm gonna call
the Adams House.
I'm gonna get you a sweet suite,
my treat.
No, no, no, no, Junior,
I wouldn't hear of it.
I'll sleep on the couch
if I have to.
You do have a couch?
Happy holidays.
Adams House. Laurel speaking.
Come on, Tony.
Hello? Hello?
Okay, that'd be great.
So, you'll be joining us
Christmas Eve?
Oh.
Tony's started
this tradition
where we all watch
It's a Wonderful Life
together.
Abby, if you're
going to be there,
I wouldn't miss it.
Junior.
Dad.
I don't get it. Autopsy's done.
Usually Agent Gibbs
has been down here by now.
Methinks you have
just spoken of the devil,
Mr. Palmer.
What do we know?
Cause of death
was a broken neck.
Shattered the C-6
and C-5 vertebrae.
Almost severed
the spinal cord.
He didn't die
in that chair, Jethro.
It was definitely a homicide.
Anything else?
Well, although
it didn't kill him,
Mr. Huffner had
cirrhosis of the liver.
He was likely a
heavy drinker.
All right, here we are.
Junior... not what I expected.
Yeah, my girl,
there you go.
There's some treats.
That's my good girl.
You're getting fat.
My goldfish.
Her name is Kate.
How long have you lived here?
Almost 12 years.
You want to wash up
before we eat?
Sure.
Should we cook something here
or go out?
I don't really keep a lot
of food in the house, Dad.
We'll go out.
All right, Dad, you're
gonna stay in my room,
and I'll hit the couch.
That's your bed?
Yeah.
Not much room for play.
Well, when I come home,
Dad, I sleep alone.
You're serious?
Dad, this is my sanctuary.
Okay?
If I'm going to see a lady,
I will stay at her place.
That way,
I can leave when I want
and nobody overstays
their welcome.
What?
You're missing
so many things--
intimacy, commitment.
You know,
I'll see if we can
get a reservation
at the rooftop grill.
Hope it's not my fault.
Hey, this is
Anthony DiNozzo.
Can I get a table for
two up on the rooftop?
Abby... what are you doing?
Lifting prints.
This ornament has been
in my family since the 1890s.
It was my great-great-
grandmother's.
So I'm trying to identify
as many relatives that have
handled it as I can.
I already found my Great Uncle
Gooper and my Aunt Trixie.
Mm-hmm.
Ask her how she got a match.
I used to fingerprint all
my relatives at our reunions.
I started when I was
11 years old.
You got anything on
Huffner's computer or cell?
Uh, not really, but...
We have
something much,
much better.
Besides Noel Huffner's
fingerprint,
I also found someone else's
on this C-note,
and reliable old AFIS
got us a match.
You gonna give
me a name?
Second print belonged
to a Justin Cannady,
and it gets better, boss.
Not only did he
work at the Bureau
of Engraving and Printing;
he was fired
from there last year.
Huffner was working
with an inside man.
Tony... you all right?
No. I slept
on the couch last night.
I got a kink
in my neck and kinks
in my back-- it's killing me.
What'd you find out?
Justin Cannady
was not at
his apartment.
Secret Service had the place
locked down
and would not let us in.
We should have searched
the place ourselves
before we told Agent Winter.
She issued a BOLO
but couldn't stop us
from questioning
Cannady's neighbors.
No one had seen
him in weeks.
You able
to connect Cannady
to our dead Navy husband?
Not yet.
So you have just been lying down
on the job while we were gone.
Timmy, remote.
Check out
his credit score.
It's lower than McGee's
self-esteem in high school.
Cannady is broke.
Unemployment insurance
ran out last month,
car was repo'd,
he's two months behind
on his rent.
Gibbs.
Oh, my God.
Where did
that Susan B. Anthony dollar go?
She likes to roll.
Oh, Agent Winter,
what are you doing here?
I was summoned
to brief you.
Hmm.
Cannady worked
at the Bureau of Engraving
and Printing until last June.
Why'd he get fired?
Poor performance.
Tardiness and being
drunk on the job.
Cannady lost two fingers
in an accident.
Ouch.
He operated a shredding machine.
Assistant Director Linder
had to let him go.
Linder-- isn't that
the squirrelly guy
- that we talked to?
- Coworkers heard
from Cannady since?
No.
Is more money missing?
No way of telling.
You think Cannady killed
your Navy husband?
Your agents
turn up anything
at Cannady's apartment?
No.
They tore
that place apart.
I'd like to do the same
to Huffner's house.
No, that's not gonna
happen, Agent Winter.
That's on a
Navy base.
You handled
Cannady's apartment.
Now,
Special Agents DiNozzo and
McGee were just leaving.
It's always a pleasure.
I went to use
my credit cards at the
Navy Exchange this morning,
and they were
both declined
because my slug
of a husband drew
$5,000 against each
of the cards.
He forged
my signature.
What was he up to?
That's what we're trying
to find out, Commander.
Well, do you at least
know how he died?
Yeah, he was murdered.
We suspect
he was involved
in criminal activity
with a man named
Justin Cannady.
Do you know him?
Never seen him.
You aware that your husband
had a liver condition?
No, but I'm not surprised.
He drank too much,
and I always knew
where to find him.
Where was that?
Gillespie's Saloon
on Prescott Street.
So do you know
when I'm gonna be able
to get into my house again?
There are things
that I have to do.
We'll let you know
when we're finished.
Did you find anything
downstairs?
Done in the bedroom.
Yeah, well, you always
have to suspect the wife.
She was halfway
around the world.
She could have
hired someone.
Listen, I need you
to crack my back.
Go to a chiropractor.
I don't have time.
I need it now.
All right,
if I do it this once,
will you stop complaining?
No complaining.
You're a buddy.
Oh, that's good,
that's good.
Okay, let me
just relax.
Now just give me
a little bounce.
Oh-ho-ho, aah!
One more.
More.
Oh!
Whose is that?
It's mine.
Just put me down real slow.
Real slow.
Thank you. I'm a
little light-headed.
Hey, Dad.
Where do you keep
your roasting pan?
Dad, I don't have
a roasting pan.
I don't cook.
What are you doing?
I'm getting ready
for a traditional
DiNozzo Christmas dinner.
Takes days of prep.
Traditional dinner?
Listen, Dad,
can you hold
off, please?
'Cause I...
We'll talk about it tonight.
Okay?
You should appreciate
your father.
I never had family traditions.
Well, we haven't had them
for years.
Traditions kind of died
with my grandfather.
Senior was kind of
an absentee parent.
You know,
long-standing customs kind of...
disappeared.
Along with a certain
family signet ring.
It was always
passed on
to the next generation
on the Christmas
of the son's 21st birthday.
I never got it.
Senior claimed it was stolen.
"I was mugged, Junior."
But I think he pawned it
during the bad times.
Hey, come over here and help me
with this, will you?
Sure.
Thank you for that, by the way.
Much better.
Yeah.
All right, we're gonna lift
this right here.
All right, ready?
One, two, three.
Oh, look at that.
They don't open till 4:00.
Maybe he's setting up.
Let's check around back.
Hello.
NCIS Special Agents Gibbs
and David.
You got a minute?
NCIS?
What's this about?
I'd like to talk to you
about Noel Huffner.
Okay.
Um, I got to open
in a half an hour.
You mind if we talk inside?
Nah.
I recognize the grill.
It's a '53, right?
It was my old man's.
The original Gillespie,
he bought it new.
Huffner's wife
said he's a regular here.
Yeah.
And I've talked to her
a couple of times.
She calls here when he
won't answer his cell.
Problems in the marriage?
I think I'm gonna invoke
bartender/patron
confidentiality.
I don't want
to get a regular in trouble.
You're not gonna
get Huffner in trouble.
He's dead.
Oh.
I guess that's why
I haven't seen him in a while.
He's a young guy.
What happened?
Do you know him?
Yeah. Justin.
I don't think I ever heard
his last name before.
Justin and Huffner
know each other?
Oh, yeah.
The two of them
sit down there at
the end of the bar
just about every night,
like Cliff and Norm.
I haven't seen Justin
in a while, either.
Well, if Justin comes in,
would you give us a call?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, um...
You never told me how Noel died.
He was murdered.
What are you doing?
What's it look like?
Decorating the Christmas tree.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Big, full, great.
You moved my piano.
Well, I had to put the tree
in the window.
Oh, what...
what happened in here?
Is this how you're
going to react
to all the hard work
I did today?
I baked your favorite
Christmas cookies.
Snickerdoodles.
Used your mother's recipe.
I knew your staying
here was a mistake.
Look... this is my
apartment, okay?
This is my space.
Junior... chill.
Chill.
Get the Christmas spirit.
Tony?
I'll get it.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Look,
we can't let her know
that we're here.
I know you're home, Tony.
Ignore her.
Who is she?
She's the bloodhound from
across the hall. Shh.
Ooh, ooh.
Ooh, ooh. Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Have you closed
the deal on that?
Dad! Shh.
All right, listen,
something's come up at work.
I got to go.
Well, when will you be home?
I don't know.
Hikers found the body
just before sunset.
There's no I.D.
Duck, why'd the LEOs
think it was Cannady?
He's missing the appropriate
two digits.
How long has he been dead?
Oh, I'd venture the same
amount of time as Mr. Huffner.
Oh, great!
I got my maggots!
This is shaping up to
be one disgusting week.
Aw, hell.
Get the body into the van.
Don't need Agent Winter
snooping around.
Let's go, Mr. Palmer.
Chop-chop.
One, two, three.
Boss is gonna
head her off at the pass.
Hey, Winter.
Agent Gibbs.
What do we got?
I don't know.
May or may not be Cannady.
Oh. Huh.
Whoa, whoa,
I don't think
you're gonna make it down
that way in those heels.
No...
Come on, I'll show you a better way.
Look--
it's right there.
And she's clueless.
Agent Winter has no idea
what she's up against.
Nicely done.
Well, with Cannady dead,
we're looking for
another killer.
Noel Huffner had $400,000
of the new, uncirculated
$100 bills
at his house.
And all the serial numbers
came from a batch that was
supposedly shredded
on May 2, 2011.
And Justin Cannady was working
at the Bureau of Engraving
and Printing as a shredder.
It is safe to say
he was involved.
Right. So the
questions are:
How much more
might have been stolen,
and how'd they get it out
of such a heavily
secured building?
That a snickerdoodle?
Yes.
Where'd you get 'em?
Senior. He bakes.
Who knew?
Would you like one?
- Ziva?
-  No.
Uh, so you think the $10,000
that Huffner borrowed
from the credit cards
has anything to do with this?
What if Huffner bought
some of the New Benjamins
at a discount
from his bar buddy, Cannady?
You know, like,
$10,000 for $400,000?
Think about it--
Cannady couldn't spend
any of the new currency until
it was put into circulation.
But he was in debt
and needed money.
Maybe he got antsy
and decided to...
sell some of the uncirculated
cash to Huffner.
Well, that may all be true,
but why are they both dead?
What am I looking at?
Fibers, magnified
a thousand times.
These eensy-weensy
little buggers
were statically attracted
to the shrink-wrap
on the currency hidden
in Huffner's house.
What are the fibers?
Particles...
of shredded New Benjies.
The money was heavily
guarded in a vault
until some of it was
shredded for disposal.
Watch this.
Voilà.
The New Benjies
left the building...
in the trash.
Yeah, I know it's our first
Christmas as a married couple,
and I want it
to be special, but I...
Breena, I got to go.
Special Agent Winter, isn't it?
Is that the body I didn't
get to see last night?
Does Special Agent Gibbs
know that you're down here?
Have you
made a positive
identification yet?
Well, you must understand
how difficult it is
to lift a fingerprint
from a body
that has been
exposed to the elements
for so long a time.
First, you must
carefully remove
the dermis.
Then, using your own
gloved hands,
you spread the dermis
over a corresponding finger.
Roll it in the ink
and then on paper.
And have you been able...
I first used the process
when I was in India.
Yes, in the city of Allahabad.
Dr. Mallard,
cut the crap.
Tell me what you know.
If I find out you're impeding
a Secret Service investigation,
do you understand...
This is an
NCIS investigation,
and Dr. Mallard is doing exactly
what he needs to be doing.
I thought we were gonna work
with each other, Gibbs.
We are.
Tell her what
you know, Duck.
We have
a positive identification.
This is Justin Cannady.
The cause of death,
cervical fracture.
Identical to Mr. Huffner's,
I might add.
Anything else?
Yeah, just got a lead.
We need to talk
to Assistant Director Linder.
Hmm.
You're not doing it without me.
Wouldn't think of it.
It's very unlikely
that any of the currency
was removed from the vaults.
I've got $400,000
of your new bills
at NCIS that says
you're wrong.
I don't know, okay?
All bills that are removed
from the vaults are shredded,
compacted into bales
and disposed of.
Where?
That was a year and a half ago.
We have contracts with several
different landfills.
Okay, well, we'll narrow it
down for you, Donald.
Which one was used
on May 2 of last year.
Be assured we're gonna be
shaking up things
in this department.
Try the Adams County Landfill
in Virginia.
Thanks, Chris. Hi, Santa.
Hi, sweetheart.
Mwah.
Tony's out
in the field.
Did he know you were coming?
No, I'm, uh,
here to deliver presents.
Ah.
And this is for you,
my dear.
Thank you.
Even though I do not
celebrate Christmas,
I love the
holiday season,
and I'm very glad
you and Tony
are going to be together.
I'm not so sure that, uh,
Tony feels that way.
Things not going well?
I think I'm trying
to make up
for too many missed Christmases
all at once.
Well, maybe you're
trying too hard.
Well, Junior's the only
family I have left.
After his mother died,
it... it just hasn't
been the same.
He showed me a
picture of her.
She was really
beautiful.
Mm-hmm, inside and out.
She was the love
of my life, Ziva.
I've never been able
to fill up that void.
But God knows I've gotten
into a lot of trouble trying.
Timmy?
Stewie?
Hey, man.
How are you?
Good to see you.
You guys know each other?
Yeah, we went to
school together.
M.I.T.
M.I.T.?
And now you work... here.
Last I heard,
you were teaching
computational
evolutionary biology.
I was.
Burnt out, man,
but I found my calling, trash.
Crazy, huh?
You know you can learn
more about mankind
by what it throws away
than you can in any classroom?
What are you doing, Timmy?
I'm a federal agent, NCIS.
Shut up. No way.
Whoa!
You're packing a gun.
This was one crazy dude
in college.
Really knew how to have
a good time.
Shut up. No way.
Did he tell you he was
the school mascot?
No.
What was
the M.I.T. mascot?
Really doesn't matter.
Oh, yes, it does.
Stewie?
A beaver.
He was Tim the Beaver
our senior year.
Please tell me you dressed up
like a beaver.
Of course he did.
Little teeth, just...
Remember the...
Oh.
Yeah.
Listen, Stewart, we're
trying to track down
a batch of
shredded currency
that came from the Bureau
of Engraving and Printing
on May 2, 2011.
Let's see, May 2, 2011, uh,
that'd be in G sector,
and by now,
about 30 feet under.
Uh, we had a break-in
that night.
Police came to investigate,
shared a laugh.
What would anyone steal
from the dump?
I think we may have the answer.
Yeah, I know you're
a smart guy, Stewie,
but how do you remember
the exact date of the break-in?
Everybody remembers
where they were that day.
Don't you? It was the night
the Navy SEAL team
took out bin Laden.
Dad?
Junior?
Wow.
This looks fantastic.
What do you think, Kate?
I didn't even know
it could look like this.
Candles and everything.
You know, you were right.
This was a good idea.
Thank you.
Hey, listen.
Maybe you want to grab
some dinner?
Uh, I'll be right with you.
Didn't expect you back so soon.
Obviously.
Didn't mean for you to see that.
Oh.
It's forever etched
into my retinas.
Hi, Tony.
Hi.
Call me later.
I'll have to burn the bed now.
Aw, come on, Junior.
Don't make a big deal
out of this.
Well, you nearly pulled it off.
You know?
It was almost like old times.
Have to go just
a little too far.
Ah.
What can I say?
I'm me.
I'm not going to change.
I know.
I know you're not
going to change.
And I don't know
why I was smiling,
'cause there's nothing funny
about this.
Dad, this is my home.
I told you,
my rules, okay?
Uh-huh.
And you broke them.
It was a mistake
having you here for Christmas.
You want me to leave?
Aren't you gonna
open your cookies?
I thought you were not supposed
to open presents until...
Christmas morning.
Snickerdoodles don't count.
I'm worried.
About Tony and his father.
Did he say what happened?
No.
Just that it was complicated.
Where's DiNozzo?
He's on his way.
What did you find out
at the landfill?
They had a break-in.
Security cameras?
No.
Not much there worth protecting.
Boss, do you remember
that night?
May 2, 2011?
No.
Bet you do.
It's the night
Navy SEALs killed bin Laden.
So we raid Abbottabad,
and we kill the most
wanted man in the world.
Got to think Homeland
put the DC area
on high alert
and increased surveillance.
Yeah.
They have to be concerned
about retaliation.
I should get some credit.
I fired Justin last June.
The damage was done
by then, Linder.
And, as assistant director
of operations, you're going
to be held responsible.
Winter.
Hey, it's Gibbs.
Secret Service
is under Homeland now.
Let me guess, Agent Gibbs.
You need something.
We need to access
archival satellite surveillance
of the DC area.
What's going on?
I'll make some calls.
I can give you a ride
to the airport.
Ah, no, no, you're...
you're already late for work.
Sorry things didn't work out.
Me, too.
Bye, Junior.
Can you enhance it?
It's nighttime, Gibbs.
We can try.
Going in tighter and enhancing.
Sorry I'm late, boss.
Your dad?
Yeah, well, we hit
a little bump in the road.
Oh, no, but he can't miss
the Christmas Eve party.
Sorry, Abbs.
Where is he?
He is on his way
to the airport.
He's going back
to New York.
It's a little better.
Well, it looks like a pickup
truck, but because of the
lack of light
and angle, I can't get
a read on the license plate.
Uh, I don't need it.
Hey!
NCIS. Merry Christmas.
You're closing
early today, Gillespie.
I am?
We have a warrant to search
the premises and your residence.
What are you looking for?
Uncirculated
$100 Treasury notes.
Merry Christmas, gentlemen.
Drinks are on the house.
Wait, what
are you doing?
This photo was taken
at a Virginia landfill
the night
the money went missing.
Looks a lot like your truck.
Just your luck Big Brother
was watching that night.
The two figures--
you and Justin Cannady?
Or did Cannady do it alone
'cause he was broke
and tired of waiting?
He sell some of his share
to Huffner without telling you?
Is that why
you killed them?
You worried that they
were gonna blow it for you?
No, uh...
Hey!
Retired Marine?
Yeah, so?
You had access
to the base at Pax River.
We'll get the video,
and we'll place you there.
Once we find the money,
it will all fall into place.
Look, we can do this
the easy way
or the hard way, but we're not
leaving here without the money.
Oh, is she getting warmer,
Gillespie?
Oh...
that got
your attention.
There's a safe
in my office closet.
Stealing the money
your idea?
It sure as hell wasn't that
drunk Justin Cannady's idea.
Yeah, but you needed him
to pull it off. Ziva?
There's a safe
in the closet.
Come on.
Hey, you know,
we can wrap this up
and still have time
for the screening in MTAC.
I'm really not in the mood.
Come on, Tony,
it'll cheer you up.
Yeah, I left the DVD
in my apartment anyway.
So go get it.
♪
Not only were we able to recover
several million dollars
of stolen,
uncirculated currency,
but two murders were solved
in the process.
Are there any questions?
Yeah, I got one.
You get any help from NCIS?
Can you believe it?
She did not even mention us.
Ah, it's Christmas,
Ziva-- let it go.
Our gift to her.
Yes, the mulled cider
is good this year,
but it's not
quite the same.
I tried to remember
how Tony made it.
Maybe I left something out.
Probably the seven
pods of cardamom?
Don't even know
what that is, Tony.
Neither do I, to
tell you the truth.
Sorry I'm late.
I got distracted.
Even when he's not around,
Senior can have
an effect on me.
Look what I found
under the tree.
Oh, the family ring.
Mm-hmm.
It's beautiful.
That's why he was here.
He wanted to make amends,
and I blew it.
That's Abby.
May I see it?
Yeah. It's got
a diamond.
You know, the origin
of signet rings
dates back
to ancient Mesopotamia.
Royalty used them to
authenticate and seal documents.
Hope you didn't start
the movie yet.
Got something
for you, DiNozzo.
Thanks, Gibbs.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
Hey, Dad.
Thanks.
Merry Christmas.
I love you.
I love you, son.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==