♪
(brakes squeaking)
(flame crackles)
Here's your change, sir.
Thank you.
And your food.
Mmm... Mmm...
(door closes)
(gunshots)
(gunfire)
(grunts)
(pants)
♪ NCIS 10x09 ♪
Devil's Trifecta
Original air date on December 11, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
DiNozzo.
TONY: We'll take it
from here, boss.
Sketch and
shoot, McGee.
Relax. I told you
I was okay.
(siren chirps)
FORNELL: Rough day
at the office.
I was too tired to take it off.
Not too tired to shoot back.
He ruined
my favorite jacket.
I'd have shot my own mother.
Thanks for coming.
Didn't have a choice.
Shooter was Navy.
McGEE:
Meet Navy Seaman
Tyler Brown.
22 years old.
Just returned from
his first deployment
on the U.S.S.
Enterprise.
ZIVA:
His TDY was mess duty,
pending his next assignment,
and that is all we have.
You recognize him, Tobias?
Never seen him before
in my life.
ZIVA: Well, he must
have known you.
You receive
any threats lately?
Just from
my ex-wife.
But then, she lives
on my bad side.
DUCKY: Six shots,
right through the chest.
Nice shooting.
Remind me not to get
on your bad side.
Jethro, I think
we can safely say
that cause of death was...
One pissed-off FBI agent.
Can you think of anyone
you might have antagonized?
Is there anyone
I haven't?
I put 30 guys behind bars
in the past year.
12 of them are out already.
Gonna need a list.
I know the drill.
My gut tells me you're
barking up the wrong tree.
You see the shooter's car?
I'll bet you ten bucks
he's hopped up,
looking for some easy cash.
The constriction
in his pupils might suggest
that he was
on some sort of stimulant.
There you go.
Carjacking.
I was a target of opportunity.
TONY: I think you were
a little more than that.
Found this in
the shooter's car.
ZIVA: You were not
a target of opportunity.
You were targeted.
That's my
license plate.
♪
MAN:
Is this a bar?
What's a guy got to do
to get a drink
around here, huh?
Sober up. It's not even noon,
and you're hammered.
My parents are Hungarian,
all right?
It's aft...
After 8:00 in the Motherland.
BARTENDER: I know.
Now, behave yourself.
I got to talk
to these two guys from NCIS.
Look around--
you think you're the first
Navy cops I ever seen?
FBI. He's NCIS.
You know this guy?
Yeah.
He moonlights here
when he's off duty.
Is he in some kind of trouble?
He's dead.
That's trouble.
You don't seem
too broken up about it.
You gonna tell me what happened?
Seaman Brown tried to
shoot me; I shot back.
GIBBS:
He a bartender?
Bouncer.
BARTENDER:
Best I had.
Didn't mind kicking ass
when needed.
(laughs): Didn't mind?
The guy got off on it.
That's enough
out of you.
No.
How about a little more?
You care to elaborate?
(clattering) Hey, don't believe
a word he says.
All he does is annoy
my customers all day long.
WOMAN: Al!
I'll be back in two.
(chuckles):
Okay.
Hey. Talk.
Huh? Oh.
Like I said...
jerk-o-matic.
And you didn't
get it from me,
but I think he was dealing
speed on the side.
You ever see it?
Well, no, but, uh...
I hear things.
Don't go anywhere.
♪
What are you thinking?
Ducky did say he thought
the kid was on something.
I think we wait
for the blood work.
Then we run it down.
That's funny,
she looks just like
our ex-wife.
Well, this is
a coincidence,
the three of us running
into each other, like this.
Oh, I doubt that.
What are you doing here?
That's none of your business.
Excuse me.
(laughs)
Okay.
I'm working.
That what you call
pushing papers all day?
I am an auditor,
not a paper pusher.
After Emily
graduated eighth grade,
I went back to the IRS.
Fitting, isn't it?
A cheater going
after tax cheats.
Are you still
going on about that?
It's ancient history.
So, what are you doing here?
What else? An audit.
There were some discrepancies
with the bar's tax return.
So you're gonna pretend
you don't know anything
about what happened?
What happened?
Diane! I was...
Shh...
"Shh"?
Shh!
You two spring a leak
or something?
BARTENDER:
Oh.
I thought you'd left.
We just have a couple more
questions for both of you.
Okay. Just remember that our
conversation is... confidential.
Of course, Mrs. Fornell.
Mrs.--
Fornell?
But I spoke with the owner--
he appreciates the offer,
but he's not interested
in selling his bar.
Selling...
The bar?
FORNELL:
Didn't she say "audit"?
Yeah.
Do you know what
"confidential" means?
"obstruction of justice" means?
We got her settled
in Interrogation.
Good thing I had
my tetanus shot.
I almost lost a hand.
Uh,
she was quite, uh, vocal
about her displeasure.
Perhaps, uh,
the conference room...
would have been a more
suitable place to question her.
Oh... they stick
together, don't they?
I tried
small talk, but...
she wouldn't say
a word.
No. She needs
to cool off first.
You really
gonna hit your ex-wife
with an obstruction
of justice charge?
Yes. The manager said
she was interested
in buying the bar;
she never mentioned anything
about any audit.
Which means she lied
to a federal agent.
He also said
she introduced herself
as Diane Fornell.
Which means
she's using an alias.
Actually, she's using two.
Look what I found in her purse.
McGEE: And please, don't ever
make me spend time alone
with her again, ever.
She sucked you in, too.
FORNELL: But what's the game?
I didn't know then.
I sure as hell
don't know now.
Her presence at the bar
where Seaman Brown worked
might have simply
been a coincidence.
No way. And enough
with the girl power.
More likely
she finally hired
that hit man
she's been talking about
for years, to take me out.
(laughs):
No!
No.
But we should put
a pin in that.
Seaman Brown-- what
do we know about him?
Background confirms what
the annoying drunk guy told you.
Brown wasn't exactly model Navy.
He was reprimanded several times
for fighting with his shipmates
and for being
late for duty.
TONY:
He was actually in the process
of getting
a bad-conduct discharge.
But we didn't find a
thing in his background
that connects him
to Agent Fornell.
Other than the fact
that my ex-wife showed up
at his workplace today.
No putting it off
any longer.
Interrogation time.
I can't wait to see this.
Don't worry about it.
You're gonna have
a front-row seat.
How dare you!
Questioning me like
some common criminal!
(groans) Who do you
think you are?
When I get
through with you,
Agent Coif...
you're gonna be wishing
your parents hadn't
even been born.
Coif?
And you two!
(scoffs)
What, are you too afraid to come
in here and face me yourselves?
I won't dignify that
with a response!
You just did.
TONY: Okay, I don't want
to be here, either.
Will you please sit down!
(whispers): Will you
please just sit down?
(sighs)
(low grunt)
DIANE:
I have already told you,
I don't know
Seaman Brown.
She's lying--
her lip curled.
I saw it.
TONY: You also told
Agent Gibbs and Fornell you
were at the bar for a tax audit,
but you told the bar manager
you were interested
in buying the place.
It is a woman's prerogative
to change her mind.
Is it a woman's prerogative
to carry two fake I.D.'s?
You went through my purse?
No.
McGee did.
Now, uh...
does your husband
know that your...
walking around town
posing as Mrs. Fornell?
Victor is in Turks and Caicos
at a destination wedding
with my daughter.
What's the matter,
you didn't get invited?
Yes, I was invited.
I just needed a little...
time to myself.
Stop it!
You two!
I can hear you smirking
from in here.
Listen, you tell Agent...
uh, McGee
that when I catch
your frickin' scrawny ass...
Gibbs, the interrogation
is ov...
Right. Should've
seen that one coming.
Gibbs...
the interrogation is over.
Why?
DIANE:
Well, it took you long enough!
I'll bet she's a panther
in the sack.
Yes, sir.
I understand, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Idiot.
Satisfied?
I'm satisfied
I'm cleared to talk.
I am unsatisfied
that now I have
to talk to them.
"Cleared"?
Mrs. Sterling
was telling you the truth,
as least partly.
She did go
back to work
for the IRS,
just not as an auditor.
She's been promoted
to a GS-11 position
in Enforcement.
Which means...
It means that you two aren't
the only ones with a badge.
Wow.
My breakfast burrito
is about to say "hello."
The IRS Deputy Commissioner
called when he heard
that we had...
one of their agents.
Agents?
Wow.
"And the Lord wept."
DIANE: Yes, agent.
And I was undercover when
you two bumbled into the bar.
Undercover on what?
Big tax-fraud case.
Somebody's stealing
identities,
filing fake returns
and making off
with a boatload
in fraudulent refund checks.
Costs the IRS
billions each year.
We have traced several
identity thefts to the bar.
My plan was
to I.D. the thief
and follow him back
to the ringleader.
I was posing as a buyer
so I could interview
the employees on the DL.
You were posing as Mrs. Fornell.
Budget cuts.
A fake I.D.
is expensive.
I was improvising.
Improvising?!
Your improvising
almost got me killed!
You must have ruffled
the wrong feathers, Agent Fornell.
And those feathers
thought I was
part of your op
and put a hit out on me!
Sorry?
Sorry?!
VANCE: All right, calm down.
If there was a hit put out on you,
it means Agent Sterling
is getting close, which also
means she's in danger, too.
I want to see your files.
(laughs): No way!
It wasn't a request.
Oh, I'm so sorry,
let me rephrase that. Go...
VANCE:
I said calm down.
Everyone.
You'll have plenty of time
to review her files.
Since this case now spans
three federal agencies,
your bosses and
I have decided
that the three of you will be
working on this case together.
(whispers):
Here she comes.
Here I go.
Gibbs told us to stay put.
FORNELL: Better you should run
for the hills.
You know, I am not any happier
about this than you are,
so can we please make it
as painless as possible.
So says the Queen of Pain.
What is going on?
New assignment.
Special Agent... Sterling
will you bring
you up to speed.
TONY (laughing):
What...
Oh, that's-that's...
very cool.
DIANE: Chucky, would you
pull up the IRS mainframe,
directory: dsterling;
password: Tobias cheap.
As I told Frick and Frack already,
somebody is running
a major fraud operation
against the IRS,
stealing hundreds of identities,
submitting thousands
in fake tax returns.
DIANE: We've traced
the identity thefts...
To the Navy bar where Gibbs
and Fornell bumped into you?
And you think someone there was
lifting driver's license info.
McGEE:
Probably Seaman Brown.
As a bouncer,
he would've checked
every I.D. that
came through the door.
You must be very proud, Jethro.
Clearly Brown
is not the mastermind behind
this operation-- he doesn't
have the accounting chops.
We're looking for somebody else.
Did you run down
the addresses of
the fake tax returns?
Yeah, all P.O. boxes,
all dead ends.
They keep rotating them out
for new ones.
Where are the perps
cashing the refund checks?
Well, various storefronts
on the opposite side of town.
I've already run down
a whole bunch,
but I got a bunch more.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
GIBBS: Yeah.
Gibbs and I are gonna
double-check the P.O. boxes,
just in case you
missed something.
And me?
GIBBS: Check-cashing outlets.
Opposite side of town.
I'll be with you
in a minute.
This is not even close to
the "opposite side of town."
No, but I knew if I said that,
the boys would want to split up.
I'm not taking a break from my
husband just to spend it with my exes.
A break?
Are you and Victor
having difficulties?
(sighing):
Victor, no.
Me, yes.
I...
Did not mean to intrude.
Now, don't get me
wrong-- Victor,
he's a good man and he's...
he's a great role model for Emily,
but I just...
I don't know.
I'm starting to wonder if I made
a mistake getting married again.
How so?
Well, I...
I settled down so... early, and
I just went from marriage to marriage,
you know, and I never
went out and acted crazy,
like all my friends.
Mm. And now you wish to...
act... crazy?
Yeah.
I want to go out and
do something wild.
Just let loose for once.
Huh.
That's hard to do
if you're married.
To Victor.
MAN: Look, guy,
I'm gonna need
some kind of I.D., okay?
Next.
Or working for the IRS.
Hm.
Agent Sterling, IRS,
Criminal Investigations
Division.
Agent David, NCIS.
I'm not getting
a check-cashing vibe.
We're gonna need
some information.
ZIVA: These are
fraudulently
obtained IRS refund checks.
They were cashed here--
we need to know by whom.
Fraudulently obtained?
Hey, that's not my fault.
Well, as the owner,
it's your responsibility
to help us find out
whose fault it is.
All right. If it's
one thing I'm good at,
is throwing people
under the bus.
Uh...
yeah, I recognize
the billing code.
Oliver Lambert.
An accountant who
comes here once a week,
cashes checks for his clients.
Do you have his contact info?
Yeah.
I have his contact info,
records of transactions,
I've even got the guy's
shayna punim
on video, if you'd like.
Just give me a sec.
ABBY: Just like the man said--
once a week, like clockwork,
Lambert cashes about a dozen
refund checks and then splits.
Looks like we've
got our mastermind.
An accountant should
certainly have the chops
to scam the IRS.
He and Seaman Brown must've
been working together.
No word on Lambert's BOLO, boss.
He wasn't at his
home or office,
and his cell phone is off,
but we did get his computer.
ABBY: Have you checked race tracks?
'Cause I notice
every single time Lambert
shows up, he has the same
piece of paper folded up
in his back pocket.
It's a betting sheet.
He likes the horses.
I'll expand the BOLO,
but I don't think he's hanging around--
he just emptied his bank account.
Nah, he's running.
Must have found out
the Feds are after him.
I'm guessing
he already knew.
He's probably the one who tried
to have you killed, remember?
Speaking of which, Diane is
probably on his hit list, too.
It's getting late.
With Lambert on the loose,
she should probably...
sleep at your house tonight.
I'll talk to you later.
No, you're right,
she shouldn't be alone,
but since you
married her last,
I think that
means your place.
ABBY:
This is gonna be good.
FORNELL:
I've got no clean sheets.
My heater's broken.
I've got toxic black mold in my kitchen.
I'll let these two
figure it out,
since I know the one place
she's definitely not staying.
(sighs)
Oh, this is
ridiculous.
Why can't I just
stay at my place?
They can post an agent
outside my door.
'Cause the best way to protect you is
to make you hard to find.
Well, then trust me,
we're good,
because no one's
gonna come looking for me
this close to
where you shower.
Look, I'll take the couch;
you can have the bed.
I would rather stand;
I'll take the couch.
Whatever.
(sighs) You don't have to be
so rude about it.
Me? Being rude?
This coming from the woman
who spent
the entire car ride over here
telling me I had
the worst possible haircut
for my face.
I was trying to be helpful.
Oh, were you also being helpful
when you told me my elbows
weren't pointy enough?
What does that even mean?
Cut me slack, Chucky.
(groans) I almost had
my daughter's father killed,
my husband wants to leave me,
and now I find out
my own life might be in danger?
The rumor I heard was, you
were thinking of leaving Victor.
It's none of your business;
I don't want to talk about it.
Trust me, fine by me.
Oh, the thing is that Victor,
he used to tell me
every day I was the most
beautiful woman in the world,
and now he...
doesn't say that anymore.
So has he changed...
or have I?
What do you think?
Excuse me?
Well, it's a simple question.
You're an attractive man--
I-I want to know,
do you find me attractive?
Um...
you mean physically, or...?
I mean, when it
came to Jethro, you know,
who could blame me for that?
And he was still in love
with his dead wife,
and I was just another
in a string of failed marriages,
but then Tobias and...
and now maybe Victor...
You're worried something
might be wrong with you?
Yeah.
Look, you're... attractive.
At least on the outside.
(scoffs quietly)
I'll take it.
(relieved sigh)
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to unload
on you like that.
(sighs):
I just... you know,
I guess I...
what I really need...
To be alone?
No.
Yeah, well,
believe it or not, I...
I think I just need a hug.
I'm not hugging you.
Why not?
Uh, it's not gonna happen.
You come over here and hug me
right now, damn it!
No way.
What kind of man are you?
Here you have
a depressed,
miserable coworker
standing right in front of you,
you can't even give her
a simple hug?
(sighs)
Your parents failed.
(quiet sigh)
(sobs)
(Diane sobbing quietly)
(birds chirping)
(horn honking in distance)
(door opens)
FORNELL: Hey, Gibbs,
what's taking so long?
Come on, people!
Chop, chop!
Holy Fourth of July
weenie roast!
What the hell am I looking at?!
(moaning softly)
Mm?
Whoa! Boss, this is
not what it looks like.
What does it look like?
DIANE: W-We were talking
and, you know,
we fell asleep on the couch.
Intertwined like
horny rabbits!
What's it to you?
So what if something happened?
No, no, nothing happened.
We're not married anymore.
No, but you are!
Why are you...
GIBBS:
Enough! We need to all
put a pin in it.
Abby's got a lead
on an accountant.
Hey, boss. Abby found an e-mail
on the accountant's PC
about an overdue payment
on this rental house.
That's the search warrant.
Where's Agent Sterling?
We thought it was best for the op for
her to take a shower.
I mean head back to
NCIS to assist Abby.
I told you,
nothing happened.
Rental house?
Yeah, Lambert went out of his way
to hide his connection
to the place.
FORNELL:So, let's see
what's inside.
McGee...
you and I
take the back.
No. I'll go with you.
What was that all about?
I don't want to talk about it.
Come on, spill it.
(knocking)
NCIS! Open up, we got
a search warrant!
And an agent
keeping secrets!
Shut up and open it, Tony.
Relax, McGee.
(low groan)
Whew! It's colder in here
than it is outside.
Fishy.
(chuckles)
Right. Of course.
The accountant
was renting a home
for his frozen fish collection.
There's nobody home.
Nobody living,
at least.
FORNELL:
Is that the drunk guy
from the bar?
Okay... if you don't
tell me what happened
between you and Diane,
then I'm just gonna have
to believe the rumors.
Tony, how many times do I have
to tell you? Nothing happened.
Wait. What rumors?
The kind
that would make
a grown man blush, McGee.
Even our latest victim
turned a slight shade of pink
when he heard one.
And he's dead.
Oh, please
don't tell me everyone here
is talking about this.
We're working an IRS fraud case.
You sleeping alone
is more interesting.
Much less you sleeping with...
I didn't.
We didn't.
Look, we found
a house filled with nothing
but frozen fish.
That's not more
interesting to you?
No.
Diane and I
feel asleep on the couch,
talking, that's all.
Well, given Agent Gibb's and
Fornell's propensity for violence,
that's the story I would
stick to if I were you.
DUCKY:
All right, much as I find
your sexual escapades riveting,
the story that I'm
really interested in
belongs to
this man.
Go ahead, McCasanova,
change the subject.
His name is Viggo Kiln.
From what we can tell from the
files found at his home, he was
working with Seaman Brown
and the accountant.
TONY: Viggo provided
the assist, playing
the lovable barfly
chatting people up,
getting the details
about their lives
so that they could steal
their identities.
Once the accountant
had enough info,
he'd file a fake return,
then collect the refund check.
Yeah, well, it seems
our barfly's services
are no longer required.
We extracted two bullets
from his brain cavity.
Execution style.
Abby ran ballistics--
two .22-caliber low-loads.
She also
matched them
to a gun registered
to an Oliver Lambert.
The missing accountant.
Well, maybe the two
had a falling-out.
Maybe Lambert knew
we were on to him,
was looking to
tie up loose ends?
Well, neither of which explains
the presence of the frozen fish.
Do you have a theory
as to its significance?
DIANE: I think we have
a good working theory
on the fish-- I just want
to dig a little deeper
before we take it to the boys,
just in case we're wrong.
I think we have enough
to go to Gibbs.
Yeah, Gibbs maybe, but Fornell?
The man takes
too much pleasure
in proving me wrong.
The last thing
I want to do
is make him happy.
So...
do anything, um...
crazy lately?
Huh? What do you mean?
Well, you told me yesterday
you wanted to go out
and do something crazy,
so I was just wondering if...
you did.
DIANE:
Nailed it! I found a clue.
This is a shipping manifest
for a place called
Donggang in China.
You pull it up?
And 's right
on the border with...
North Korea-- that is
the third in a row.
Too many to be
a coincidence.
FORNELL:
And nobody likes those,
especially when
they involve North Korea
or couches.
GIBBS:
What do we got?
We were going over
the shipping manifests
we found in the fish house,
and we noticed a pattern.
All of the fish are being exported
to small fishing villages,
all on the borders of some
very interesting countries.
FORNELL:
Syria, North Korea and Iran.
The Axis of Evil 2.0.
Well, that
doesn't look good.
And what's with sending
fish to fishing villages?
Doesn't it usually work
the other way around?
Well, we're not sure
what that means.
I know a customs agent
I could talk to,
see if he'll issue a BOLO
on similar shipments.
That might
shed some light.
Tobias, go back to the FBI,
do the same thing.
Jethro, MTAC.
See if there's
any new intel on Syria,
North Korea or Iran.
Did she just give us orders?
Yeah.
But they're good ones.
I know!
Where'd everybody go?
To find out why frozen fish
are being sent to border towns
of our political adversaries.
That's weird.
But what's weirder
is that it's not just fish.
The official fish name
is Thunnus alalunga,
otherwise known
as albacore tuna.
And when I decided to
take a closer look...
Adson's retractor.
(whispers): That one.
Oh.
...I found something
very odd.
Forceps.
Is that a cell phone?
Yep.
There's a cell phone
inside the fish?
There is a
cell phone...
inside...
every fish.
Is there anything on them?
So far,
they're all unregistered,
but I noticed that their
IMEI numbers indicate
they all came from the
same manufacturing batch.
I was able to do a wideband
search of the batch number,
and I found an active cell
in the group.
Someone with a fish phone
made a phone call.
To...?
To... our missing accountant's
private voicemail.
I'm guessing from the length of
the call that they knew the password.
It may be him.
It's a good bet.
There was nothing useful
in the voice mail, but...
(beeping)
...I got the location
of the caller.
ZIVA:
No sign of Lambert.
Same here.
And I'm getting tired.
Didn't get enough sleep
last night, huh?
This is a wild-goose chase.
Guy made one
phone call from here.
He's long gone.
Well, you can always
go back to NCIS, wait for
Diane to come back from ICE.
But we should leave
no stone unturned.
Speaking of the
Spawn of Unholiness,
I did some checking with a
buddy of mine at the IRS--
know what I heard?
That's she's
not leaving Victor, it's Victor
thinking about leaving her?
How did you know that?
Can't say I'm surprised, either.
You ever notice how
she never gets sick?
Even germs don't like her.
But this Victor thing explains
something else that I heard,
something that I suspect
you don't know,
since you don't look nauseous.
I don't get nauseous.
We'll see about that.
Mm.
Ask yourself something.
What are the odds
of Diane being assigned a case
in your jurisdiction?
Pretty good. She was.
No. She wasn't.
She was originally
working a different jurisdiction
on this tax fraud thing.
When the identity theft
was traced to a Navy bar,
Diane asked to be transferred
to your jurisdiction.
That's right.
I can hear those stomach
acids gurgling from here.
Her father was Navy.
I worked for NCIS.
Diane, she's just
more familiar with the military.
You keep telling
yourself that.
Because you know
what I think?
I think she asked
for a transfer
because she was hoping
to run into you.
Looks like McGee has got
a little competition.
Boss, it's Lambert,
on your nine.
GIBBS: Okay,
here we go.
Let's move.
Oliver Lambert?
Yes?
NCIS.
FBI.
Need you to come with us.
FORNELL: Would you take your hands out
of your pockets, please, sir?
The money I took from the IRS
wasn't for me.
I'd love to hear about that;
I'd love to see your hands even more.
Put your hands
where we can see 'em.
I was just trying
to set things right.
Sudden moves are
not your friend.
But I'll...
tell you everything now.
I gave them
this week's payment,
but they're worried.
I... I think they
might try and kill me.
Hands!
Ducky confirmed Lambert died
of multiple stab wounds.
ZIVA: Fornell is still
taking statements,
but witnesses report
seeing Lambert in a car
with either a man, a woman
or nobody, depending on who you talk to.
Lambert said the money
he took wasn't for him.
TONY: Sounded like he was in the
hole to somebody for something.
McGEE:
One of his clients.
Abby found this thumb drive
in his wallet.
Looks like Lambert was gathering
evidence to cop a plea.
His files show that he embezzled
from one of his clients,
then blew the money
at the track--
and he had a statement
for the D.A.
It says that the client
threatened to kill him
if he didn't repay
the money he took,
then forced him
to steal from the IRS.
And then some.
Client must be a scary guy.
You got a name?
No. Lambert left it out.
Well, maybe he's holding it
for his plea bargain.
Okay. That was Diane;
she's on her way.
Her fish BOLO came back.
Customs found
another container
headed for Donggang, China.
More cell phones?
No.
This time they
found DVD's
and luxury soaps
inside the fish.
Client's a smuggler.
Put up maps.
GIBBS: There's U.N. sanctions
on all these countries.
Which means
no Western cell phones,
Dora DVD's
or lavender-scented bath soap.
And I thought the middle class
here was having a hard time.
Diane's contact thinks
the smuggler is using
local fishermen to get the goods
across sanctioned borders.
Apparently,
it is quite common.
GIBBS: Was Diane able
to trace the shipment?
It was a dead-end.
Shipper's info
was all fake.
Well, it's a good thing
you can't fake DNA.
Because I've got some.
So, I ran DNA on our tuna
to try to figure out
where it came from.
Sadly, for those of
us investigating fish-based crime,
there's no national database
to compare it to.
But...?
My fifth favorite word.
But... I sent Jimmy to
pick up albacore tuna
from every supermarket
between here and Alexandria,
and I got a familial match.
Our smuggle fish
definitely came
from the same catch
as our sample
from F&G Grocery.
And they buy their albacore
from a man named...
DIANE: Avis Boyle.
He owns a small
fish distributor that serves
the tristate area.
And according
to his tax return,
he was a client
of Oliver Lambert.
He's our smuggler.
Abby already briefed me.
First?
Let it go.
We have to figure out
our next move.
Our next move is
arresting Boyle.
For what?
That's right, Woodchuck.
You can't tie him
to Lambert's murder.
The books don't mention
Boyle by name.
And the fish DNA...
It's circumstantial.
Now,
the IRS has had their eye
on this guy for some time,
for undeclared earnings,
but they could never prove it.
But you got an idea.
And it's a good one.
Why do I feel
like I'm being set up?
Not you. Boyle.
So his accountant
was laundering his money.
But now the
accountant's dead.
Well, Boyle's
gonna need a new one.
No, forget it.
Can I finish?
We don't have a lot of time.
I've got to approach
Boyle before
he hires somebody else
to start doing his books.
I can talk the talk.
You can wire me and then bust
him when he incriminates himself.
It's a good plan,
and you know it.
You're not going in alone;
I'm coming with you.
You might regret that when you
find out where Boyle is today.
♪
(indistinct chatter)
Oh, I regret this.
FORNELL (over radio):
I am so glad
this is you and not me.
We're reading you
loud and clear, boss.
ZIVA:
And we're getting
a solid image from the camera
on Diane's brooch.
Which looks much better
on you than it did
on me, by the way.
McGEE:
Just be careful
not to knock it loose.
Oh, it's not going anywhere.
You spent more
than enough time
attaching it to my
ex-wife's... bosom.
Way too much time,
if you ask me.
I guess he didn't get
enough last night.
What?
No, I...
She's just...
Diane, the joke is over!
I'm just having
a little fun.
♪
So, shall we
find our man?
Do you remember how
you proposed to me?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Don't feel too bad;
I don't, either.
"Didn't get enough
last night."
That's what she said.
Which implies
that you did get something.
I didn't get anything;
there was nothing to get.
Will you two
just shut up?
DIANE:
Hey, isn't that our mark?
(tapping keyboard)
I see Boyle...
twelve o'clock.
You ready?
Yeah.
MAN: That was the most boring
best-man speech I've ever heard.
Oh, it was my nephew's wedding;
he told me to keep it clean.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
And you are?
(quietly): An accountant.
DIANE: Luckily for you, 'cause I heard
you might be looking for one.
BOYLE:
Uh, will you excuse me?
So, let's talk terms.
She's in.
BOYLE:
Uh, I'm sorry, I think
there's been a misunderstanding.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
No.
What you have, Ace,
is a large influx
of ill-gotten operating
gross revenues
that you're gonna have to shelter
from any Title 26 tax liabilities.
Unless you want to be
incredibly stupid
and go to jail.
Now you're listening, huh?
I used to work
with Lambert.
I did all that
jackass's grunt work.
And when I say all,
I mean all.
But he's gone
and I'm here.
So, what's it gonna be?
Oh. I see I'm not
talking to The Man,
which means you're just a
big waste of my time. See ya.
Uh...
Wait here.
(chuckles)
She's a natural.
She's just being herself.
(door opens)
Uh-oh.
We have a problem.
What is it?
(beeping)
ZIVA: The guy from
the check-cashing place.
Avis told me someone was making
a play to be my new accountant.
He didn't mention
it was an IRS special agent.
Walk.
(glass clinking)
GIBBS:
I'd like to propose a toast.
May you two always be as happy
as you are today.
WOMAN: Aw...
(lively chatter, applause)
GIBBS:
And while I'm at it,
I'd like to propose
something else,
this time to the lovely lady
with the lovely red hair.
WOMAN:
Aw...
I'm not much for words.
Most things are
better left unsaid.
It'd be a lot easier if I
could just pick you up
and we'd start running, and...
we'd never stop.
Maybe I'll
still do that.
But before I do...
(women gasping)
...I just want to ask you one thing.
Yes.
(women laughing)
I'll marry you.
(cheering, clapping)
(whistling, whooping)
Not so fast.
Let's go.
How come you didn't
just shoot him?
Ah, I figure... we've
ruined enough weddings.
Yeah.
DIANE:
We were wrong.
Boyle wasn't
the boss-- turns out
he was just one
of four distributors
that was involved
in the smuggling operation.
This is
the big guy.
Gordon Fremont.
He was running the entire op
out of his check-
cashing franchise.
Lot of cash
moving in and out.
Easy for him
to launder the money.
Was he the one that put the
hit out on the Fornells?
It's Sterling, remember?
I changed
my name before
the ink dried
on my divorce papers.
You never had
it so good!
Okay, you were a step up
from the last one,
but still subpar.
Hey!
VANCE: Don't make me
separate you three.
Truth is,
I'm proud of the way
you pulled this off.
DIANE:
At least I didn't kill them.
I've had root canals
that went better.
As a matter of fact,
we were discussing
the possibility of...
making the three of you
a permanent working group
for inter-agency-related
business.
That something you think
you might be interested in?
(dog barking in distance)
You coming down?
(sighs)
No.
I was gonna sneak out, actually.
But, you know, since
you caught me...
(laughs):
I could use a drink.
(liquid pouring)
That was a
sweet proposal.
I thought you said
you didn't remember it.
Yeah. Well...
I thought you didn't, either.
I certainly didn't remember
how sweet it was.
(dog barking in distance)
(sighs)
Uh, last time I was here,
I accused you of something.
I said, um...
that you never
loved me, and...
you didn't correct me.
But I think I was wrong.
(laughs softly)
Not that you're gonna
do anything about it
but stare at me right now.
Thanks for your help.
You got give Victor a break.
Excuse me?
Who told you that Victor
and I are having prob...
Oh, it was Chucky.
He's such a dead man.
(sighs)
Okay, what do I have to
give Victor a break for?
For being him...
and not somebody else.
You got to let it go, Diane.
I couldn't...
and I drove everybody away.
And...
the last thing
you want to be is me.
(whispers):
You're not so bad.
(laughs softly)
But I hear you.
Unfortunately, it might
be a little too late.
No, it's not.
(laughs)
How do you know
everything?
I don't.
I don't. I...
I just learned
how to listen.
Well, what about you?
Don't you think there's
somebody out there for you?
Or are you destined to spend
the rest of your days alone?
I'm not alone.
Captioning sponsored by
== sync, corrected by elderman ==