1
00:00:03,710 --> 00:00:06,080
我的天哪
Oh, my God!

2
00:00:15,860 --> 00:00:18,340
你居然亲她了  你个傻缺
Oh, you kissed her! You idiot!

3
00:00:18,340 --> 00:00:19,840
你...
You...

4
00:00:29,660 --> 00:00:30,850
不不不
No, no, no.

5
00:00:30,850 --> 00:00:32,720
我什么都没想干  啥都没想干
I wasn't doing anything. I wasn't. No, no, no.

6
00:00:32,720 --> 00:00:34,810
我啥都没想干  啥都没有
I wasn't doing anything, I wasn't doing anything, I...

7
00:00:34,810 --> 00:00:36,610
别想太空步溜走
Do not moonwalk away from me.

8
00:00:36,610 --> 00:00:38,210
站住  别走
Do not. You are not.

9
00:00:38,210 --> 00:00:40,170
你还真溜了  尼克
You're doing it. Nick?

10
00:00:40,620 --> 00:00:41,910
他真溜走了
He did.

11
00:00:53,220 --> 00:00:55,510
天嘞
Ugh, my God.

12
00:00:55,510 --> 00:00:56,550
我刚醒
Oh, I just woke up.

13
00:00:56,550 --> 00:00:58,920
我睡了好久好久
I've been sleeping for hours and hours.

14
00:00:58,920 --> 00:01:00,880
真棒  我也是
Nice. Me, too.

15
00:01:00,880 --> 00:01:03,130
让我瞧瞧
Let's see here.

16
00:01:03,700 --> 00:01:05,940
太美了  十封邮件
Oh, sweet. Ten e-mails.

17
00:01:09,530 --> 00:01:12,420
萨姆
Hey, Sam, um...

18
00:01:12,420 --> 00:01:13,430
我要告诉你件事
I have to tell you something.

19
00:01:13,430 --> 00:01:16,710
为啥你早上总是这么美
How do you always look so beautiful in the morning?

20
00:01:16,710 --> 00:01:18,310
我都不好意思看你了
Sometimes I can't even look at you.

21
00:01:18,310 --> 00:01:20,420
我都不...我得转过去了
I can't even-- I got to look away.

22
00:01:20,420 --> 00:01:21,710
我现在都不好意思看你
I can't even look at you right now.

23
00:01:21,710 --> 00:01:24,040
不行  还想看  不能看了
Wait, but I got to. Now I got to look away.

24
00:01:24,040 --> 00:01:26,350
可我忍不住  天啊
I just can't resist. Oh, geez.

25
00:01:27,510 --> 00:01:29,040
你想说啥来着
What were you gonna say?

26
00:01:31,060 --> 00:01:32,360
没什么
Nothing.

27
00:01:32,360 --> 00:01:33,760
没想说什么
It was nothing.

28
00:01:36,320 --> 00:01:37,040
杰茜
Jess?

29
00:01:37,040 --> 00:01:38,640
尼克亲我了
Nick kissed me.

30
00:01:39,430 --> 00:01:42,200
啥
Wha...?!

31
00:01:44,470 --> 00:01:47,700
杰茜驾到  第二季第十五集

32
00:01:51,420 --> 00:01:53,860
天啊  好吧
Oh, man. Okay.

33
00:01:53,860 --> 00:01:56,580
哥们儿昨晚滚到了最爽的床单
I had the best sex of my life last night.

34
00:01:56,580 --> 00:01:57,990
温斯顿  你回来太好了  我们得谈谈
Winston, I'm glad you're here. We need to talk.

35
00:01:57,990 --> 00:01:59,180
没错  黛西说哥超厉害
Yeah. Daisy said I was pretty good.

36
00:01:59,180 --> 00:02:01,310
听见了吗  超厉害
You hear that? Pretty good!

37
00:02:01,310 --> 00:02:02,380
这很重要
This is important.

38
00:02:02,380 --> 00:02:03,800
我甚至都没上手活
And I ain't even use my hands.

39
00:02:03,800 --> 00:02:04,910
你没上手活
You didn't use your hands?

40
00:02:04,910 --> 00:02:06,070
我前戏技巧比较多啦
Well, just I did a lot of side stuff.

41
00:02:06,070 --> 00:02:07,380
好了  温斯顿  你真是要弄死我
Okay, Winston, you're killing me.

42
00:02:07,380 --> 00:02:08,620
我非常需要跟你谈谈
I really need to talk to you,

43
00:02:08,620 --> 00:02:10,790
听完你的话  我都不想再见你了
and now after hearing that, I can barely look at you.

44
00:02:10,790 --> 00:02:12,480
我的爷们儿气概回来了  亲
Well, I got my mojo back, baby!

45
00:02:12,480 --> 00:02:14,640
我现在是真汉子
I'm the Mojo Man!

46
00:02:14,640 --> 00:02:17,280
真汉子  真汉子  这词儿真好听
Mojo Man, Mojo Man. I like the sound of that.

47
00:02:17,280 --> 00:02:18,800
你这事算是说不完了  是吧
Yeah, we're not gonna be getting to my thing, are we?

48
00:02:18,800 --> 00:02:20,490
真真真汉子
Mo-Mo-Mojo Man.

49
00:02:20,490 --> 00:02:21,710
我得告诉萨姆
I got to tell Sam.

50
00:02:21,710 --> 00:02:22,820
我不能告诉萨姆
I can't tell Sam!

51
00:02:22,820 --> 00:02:24,490
我没做错什么啊
I didn't even do anything wrong!

52
00:02:24,490 --> 00:02:25,540
是尼克亲的我
Nick kissed me!

53
00:02:25,540 --> 00:02:27,670
我又没亲他
I didn't even kiss him back!

54
00:02:27,670 --> 00:02:29,510
好吧  我也亲他了
Okay, fine! I kissed him back!

55
00:02:29,510 --> 00:02:30,770
你不就想让我承认么
Is that what you want me to say?

56
00:02:30,770 --> 00:02:32,480
我这一个小时
I literally haven't said a word

57
00:02:32,480 --> 00:02:33,400
一句话都没说
for, like, over an hour.

58
00:02:33,400 --> 00:02:35,150
现在他都不跟我说话了
And now he won't even talk to me,

59
00:02:35,150 --> 00:02:36,350
今早我看见他
'cause I saw him this morning

60
00:02:36,350 --> 00:02:38,450
他居然滑着慌张太空步溜走了
and he just panic moonwalked away from me.

61
00:02:38,450 --> 00:02:40,400
-什么  -他经常那么干
- He what? - He does that sometimes.

62
00:02:41,030 --> 00:02:43,760
天啊  恐怖主义啊
Man. Terrorism.

63
00:02:46,180 --> 00:02:47,980
然后  哈
And then... ha!

64
00:02:47,980 --> 00:02:49,850
尼克...他...
Nick just... He just...

65
00:02:49,850 --> 00:02:50,900
亲了你
Kisses you.

66
00:02:50,900 --> 00:02:52,190
大傻缺尼克·米勒
Stupid Nick Miller.

67
00:02:52,190 --> 00:02:53,160
那个吻怎么样  是...
How was it? Was it...?

68
00:02:53,160 --> 00:02:54,760
我就像斯佳丽·郝思嘉[《飘》女主人公]
I was like Scarlett O'Hara

69
00:02:54,760 --> 00:02:56,450
穿着我奇葩的睡裙
in my freaking curtain dress...

70
00:02:56,450 --> 00:02:57,410
他怎么做的
How did he do it?

71
00:02:57,410 --> 00:02:59,510
他就是直接把我搂过来
He just, like, grabbed me.

72
00:02:59,510 --> 00:03:01,200
-死死抓着我  -好爽
- And he just took me. - Oh, yeah.

73
00:03:01,200 --> 00:03:03,440
他是真汉子  我是真女人
I mean, he was a man and I was a woman.

74
00:03:03,440 --> 00:03:06,240
我们干柴烈火  浓情蜜意
It was firm, but tender.

75
00:03:06,240 --> 00:03:07,070
-爽翻了  -没错
- Oh, damn. - Yeah, I mean,

76
00:03:07,070 --> 00:03:08,890
有一瞬间我甚至洞穿了生死
I saw thorough space and time for a minute,

77
00:03:08,890 --> 00:03:10,720
但这不是重点
but that's not the point.

78
00:03:10,720 --> 00:03:11,660
天啊
Oh, man!

79
00:03:11,660 --> 00:03:12,660
你还好吗
Are you okay?

80
00:03:12,660 --> 00:03:14,270
我好想念做爱
I miss sex!

81
00:03:14,270 --> 00:03:18,100
这个月我一直跟老妈找的相亲对象约会
I've been on dates set up by my mother for the past month.

82
00:03:18,100 --> 00:03:19,970
你准备怎么办吧
I mean, what are you gonna do?

83
00:03:19,970 --> 00:03:21,700
你有没有...
I mean, do you...

84
00:03:21,700 --> 00:03:22,590
喜欢尼克
like Nick?

85
00:03:22,590 --> 00:03:24,950
啊呸
Ah! Bah!

86
00:03:24,950 --> 00:03:27,470
纳尼...
Nah! Neh?

87
00:03:27,470 --> 00:03:28,640
尼克
Nick?

88
00:03:29,750 --> 00:03:31,270
才不呢
No.

89
00:03:32,200 --> 00:03:33,780
我才不喜欢尼克
I don't like Nick.

90
00:03:33,780 --> 00:03:34,550
我喜欢萨姆
I like Sam,

91
00:03:34,550 --> 00:03:36,810
萨姆是那种不用你操心
'cause Sam's the kind of guy who fixes things

92
00:03:36,810 --> 00:03:38,360
把你照顾得超周到的人
that you didn't even know were broken.

93
00:03:38,360 --> 00:03:40,120
尼克则是那种
And Nick is the type of guy

94
00:03:40,120 --> 00:03:43,830
把东西糟践得...
who breaks things... that are...

95
00:03:43,830 --> 00:03:45,310
他糟践东西
He breaks things!

96
00:03:45,310 --> 00:03:46,470
-快瞧呀  -给我奶奶织的
- Look at that. - It's for my grandma.

97
00:03:46,470 --> 00:03:48,620
这真是  不
Wow, that's... oh, no.

98
00:03:48,620 --> 00:03:50,340
-不不不不不  -你干嘛  尼克
- No, no, no, no, no, no. - What are you-- Nick!

99
00:03:50,340 --> 00:03:51,350
-没事  我...  -尼克  尼克
- No, let me just... - Nick, Nick!

100
00:03:51,350 --> 00:03:52,920
-好了  没事了  -你干啥呢  尼克
- Okay, here, it's fine. - What are you... No!

101
00:03:52,920 --> 00:03:55,120
尼克  你干嘛
Nick, what are you...?

102
00:03:55,120 --> 00:03:57,010
这些应该是放在这的吧
I think those belong back on it.

103
00:03:57,720 --> 00:04:00,230
他可不能拆散我和萨姆
He is not getting in the way of me and Sam.

104
00:04:00,230 --> 00:04:02,070
他不能糟践我们俩
He is not ruining this.

105
00:04:02,070 --> 00:04:03,310
太恨他了
So mad at him.

106
00:04:03,310 --> 00:04:04,660
我都不能见他了
I can't even be around him.

107
00:04:04,660 --> 00:04:06,070
我能跟你待一天么
Can I just spend the day with you?

108
00:04:07,890 --> 00:04:09,580
这个嘛
Well, um...

109
00:04:09,580 --> 00:04:13,750
好吧  我之前没告诉你  但是...
Okay, I didn't tell you this before, actually, but, uh...

110
00:04:13,750 --> 00:04:14,770
希希今天要去
Cece is going to

111
00:04:14,770 --> 00:04:16,590
一个印度相亲大会
an Indian marriage convention today

112
00:04:16,590 --> 00:04:18,500
去找她的棕色老公
to find herself a brown husband.

113
00:04:18,500 --> 00:04:19,490
不过她不知道的是
Now, little does she know

114
00:04:19,490 --> 00:04:22,260
我也报名了这个相亲会
that I have signed up for the same convention.

115
00:04:22,260 --> 00:04:23,780
先生们  没有任何条款规定
Gentlemen, there is nothing that says

116
00:04:23,780 --> 00:04:25,630
白人男性不能报名
white men need not apply.

117
00:04:25,630 --> 00:04:27,550
你就像《飞越未来》里那个算命的
You look like the fortune teller in Big.

118
00:04:27,550 --> 00:04:28,860
等等  相亲会在公寓楼里吗
Wait a second, is it in the loft?

119
00:04:28,860 --> 00:04:30,250
是啊  尼克
Yes, Nick.

120
00:04:30,250 --> 00:04:33,290
西海岸首届印度单身男女的盛事
The West Coast's premiere Indian singles event,

121
00:04:33,290 --> 00:04:35,700
有三百名拉杰普特印度人齐聚一堂
where 300 eligible Rajput Indians get together

122
00:04:35,700 --> 00:04:37,970
来考察他们配对的可行性
to see if they should get arranged-married to each other,

123
00:04:37,970 --> 00:04:39,090
会在我们公寓楼
is in our loft.

124
00:04:39,090 --> 00:04:40,560
如果不在  我要跟你一起去
So if it's not, then I'm coming with.

125
00:04:40,560 --> 00:04:42,450
我要参加  小施  你有伴了
I'm in, Schmidty. You finally got company.

126
00:04:42,450 --> 00:04:43,480
我也去  走起
I'm coming. Let's do it. 

127
00:04:43,480 --> 00:04:44,940
真汉子也要去
The Mojo Man is in, too.

128
00:04:44,940 --> 00:04:46,570
真汉子  真汉子
Mojo Man, Mojo Man.

129
00:04:46,570 --> 00:04:47,940
好了  你俩谁也不许去
Okay, neither of you are coming.

130
00:04:47,940 --> 00:04:49,550
我已经研究了一周
I've been studying up for a full week.

131
00:04:49,550 --> 00:04:51,150
我已经掌握了印度语的日常会话
I can actually speak conversational Hindi.

132
00:04:51,150 --> 00:04:53,380
如果日常会话是指"你好"  "你好"
If that conversation is: "Hello." "Hello."

133
00:04:53,380 --> 00:04:55,080
"吃三角饺吗"  "请给个三角饺吧"
"Samosa?" "Yes, please, Samosa."

134
00:04:55,080 --> 00:04:56,420
"还要毛巾吗"  "你知道白人专用的
"More towels?" "Do you know where

135
00:04:56,420 --> 00:04:57,930
卫生间在哪吗"
the white person's toilet is?"

136
00:04:57,930 --> 00:04:59,550
除了这些  印度语非常难懂
After that, it gets very confusing.

137
00:04:59,550 --> 00:05:01,210
你穿这身能开车么
Can you drive in that dress?

138
00:05:01,210 --> 00:05:02,140
你说对了  我不能
You're right, I can't.

139
00:05:02,140 --> 00:05:03,370
好吧  你来开车  走起
All right, you're driving. Let's go.

140
00:05:03,370 --> 00:05:04,260
好嘞
Yeah!

141
00:05:09,740 --> 00:05:11,640
你好  我来报到
Hi, I'm-I'm checking in.

142
00:05:11,640 --> 00:05:13,080
我叫希西莉亚·帕里克
My name's Cecilia Parikh.

143
00:05:13,080 --> 00:05:13,740
这是我好朋友
This is my best friend.

144
00:05:13,740 --> 00:05:15,560
她只是来观摩的
She's just, she's just here to watch.

145
00:05:15,560 --> 00:05:16,740
所有人员必须参加相亲
All must participate.

146
00:05:16,740 --> 00:05:19,860
观摩者给我们惹过不少麻烦
We've had a lot of trouble with watchers.

147
00:05:22,480 --> 00:05:24,280
要么相亲  要么回家
You participate or you go home.

148
00:05:25,530 --> 00:05:28,050
好的  管它呢
All right, you know what? What the hell.

149
00:05:28,050 --> 00:05:29,910
你得填写一份问卷
You're going to have to fill out a questionnaire.

150
00:05:29,910 --> 00:05:32,270
包括个人信息  教育背景  个人履历
Information, education, resume.

151
00:05:33,070 --> 00:05:34,150
好的
Done.

152
00:05:34,150 --> 00:05:35,620
谢谢
Thank you.

153
00:05:38,460 --> 00:05:40,690
你们怎么也跑这儿来了
What the hell are you guys doing here?

154
00:05:40,690 --> 00:05:42,730
你看起来就像《爱情大师》里的角色
You look like a character from The Love Guru.

155
00:05:42,730 --> 00:05:43,880
谢谢夸奖哈
Aw, thank you.

156
00:05:44,900 --> 00:05:45,630
您好
Hello.

157
00:05:45,630 --> 00:05:47,520
我想和我两位朋友一起登记下
I'd like to check in with my two friends here.

158
00:05:47,520 --> 00:05:49,690
我们不是印度人  但你不能赶我们走
Look, we are not Indian, but you cannot turn us away,

159
00:05:49,690 --> 00:05:52,940
因为我无比激动地浏览了贵网站  库玛丽[印度童女神]
because I read the website vigorously, Kumari.

160
00:05:52,940 --> 00:05:53,940
-天呐  -那代表着"小姐"
- Oh, God. - That means "Miss."

161
00:05:53,940 --> 00:05:54,730
而我的朋友呢
My friend right there?

162
00:05:54,730 --> 00:05:56,820
他是瓦吉尔[印度指代理人]  代表着"律师"
Yeah, he's a vakeel. That means "Lawyer."

163
00:05:56,820 --> 00:05:58,350
我从卡吉尔学校辍学的
I dropped out of ka-heel school.

164
00:05:58,350 --> 00:05:59,670
是瓦吉尔  哥们
It's vakeel, man.

165
00:06:01,060 --> 00:06:01,910
你在这干神马
What are you doing here?

166
00:06:01,910 --> 00:06:04,050
没什么  我只是...
Oh, no. I just-- uh, yeah...

167
00:06:04,050 --> 00:06:05,720
哦
Oh!

168
00:06:06,430 --> 00:06:08,990
尼克  你在丢我的人
Nick, you're embarrassing me.

169
00:06:09,710 --> 00:06:11,810
尼克  你在干神马
Nick, what are you doing?

170
00:06:13,190 --> 00:06:15,330
尼克  尼克  尼克
Nick, Nick, Nick.

171
00:06:15,330 --> 00:06:16,420
尼尼尼尼克  你在干神马
N-N-N-Nick, what are you doing?

172
00:06:16,420 --> 00:06:18,180
别再太空步了  哥们
Stop moonwalking, man.

173
00:06:18,650 --> 00:06:20,620
你一上午都很奇怪
Man, you have been weird all morning.

174
00:06:20,620 --> 00:06:22,620
听着  我亲了杰茜
Hey, look, I kissed Jess.

175
00:06:25,270 --> 00:06:26,720
有什么就说什么吧
Say what you're gonna say.

176
00:06:26,720 --> 00:06:29,760
哦吼吼吼吼吼
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!

177
00:06:29,760 --> 00:06:31,720
喔哦
Whoo!

178
00:06:31,720 --> 00:06:32,980
我想这就是你想说的了
I thought that's what you were gonna say.

179
00:06:32,980 --> 00:06:34,090
我不想要个新室友
I don't want a new roommate.

180
00:06:34,090 --> 00:06:36,160
不要...  她不会搬出去的
Look, don't... She's not moving out.

181
00:06:36,160 --> 00:06:37,860
我没指她  天呐  当然不是她
I'm not talking about her. Hell no, not her!

182
00:06:37,860 --> 00:06:38,850
我是指你
I'm talking about you.

183
00:06:38,850 --> 00:06:40,200
这事要是抖出来
When this thing blows up in your face--

184
00:06:40,200 --> 00:06:41,820
而且一定会的  尼克
and it will blow up in your face, Nick--

185
00:06:41,820 --> 00:06:42,920
那时你才是该搬走的人
you're the one moving out.

186
00:06:42,920 --> 00:06:44,660
你认为我喜欢跟你住在一起吗
You think I like living with you?

187
00:06:44,660 --> 00:06:47,240
你床底有蜈蚣啊
You have centipedes living under your bed!

188
00:06:47,240 --> 00:06:49,300
-那不是  -你还给你的蛋蛋命名
- Those weren't centipedes. - You've named your testicles,

189
00:06:49,300 --> 00:06:50,440
叫它们莎伦
and they're both named Sharon.

190
00:06:50,440 --> 00:06:51,090
对  那又怎样
Yeah, so what?

191
00:06:51,090 --> 00:06:52,200
我真是不敢相信你会亲杰茜  哥们
I can't believe you kissed Jess! Man, 

192
00:06:52,200 --> 00:06:53,400
你到底在想什么
what were you thinking?

193
00:06:53,400 --> 00:06:55,470
我什么都没想
Look, man, I wasn't thinking anything.

194
00:06:56,480 --> 00:06:59,270
尼克  去道歉并把事情处理好  好吗
Nick, just apologize and make it right, all right?

195
00:07:00,670 --> 00:07:03,860
好的  我正打算这么做
All right. That's what I'm gonna do.

196
00:07:05,140 --> 00:07:07,050
哦  莎伦
Oh, Sharon!

197
00:07:07,050 --> 00:07:08,200
到  快到...
Get! Just... Get...?

198
00:07:08,200 --> 00:07:09,290
到这来
Get over here now.

199
00:07:09,290 --> 00:07:10,850
等下  怎么啦
Wait. What?

200
00:07:10,850 --> 00:07:12,900
你告诉我你已经释怀了
You told me you had moved on.

201
00:07:12,900 --> 00:07:15,880
只有无法释怀的人才会那样说
Only people who haven't moved on say things like that.

202
00:07:15,880 --> 00:07:18,130
我是松鼠  你是我的坚果
I'm a squirrel. You're my nut.

203
00:07:18,130 --> 00:07:18,670
冬天来了  
Winter's coming. 

204
00:07:18,670 --> 00:07:20,030
我要把你给吃了  姑娘
I'm gonna store you in my cheek, girl.

205
00:07:20,030 --> 00:07:21,590
快走开
Please leave.

206
00:07:21,590 --> 00:07:23,220
你没法和我在一起
You and I not being together 

207
00:07:23,220 --> 00:07:25,620
对此我很不理解
does not make sense to me.

208
00:07:25,620 --> 00:07:27,200
我想念你的身体
I miss your body

209
00:07:27,200 --> 00:07:28,560
还有我曾经对它做过的事
and the things I used to do to it.

210
00:07:28,560 --> 00:07:30,030
-施密特  -我是说滚床单
- Schmidt. - I'm talking about sex.

211
00:07:30,030 --> 00:07:33,250
今天我要找到
Today is about me finding someone

212
00:07:33,250 --> 00:07:34,430
合乎我的文化
within my own culture

213
00:07:34,430 --> 00:07:36,350
并且能和我共度一生的人
that I can build my life with.

214
00:07:36,350 --> 00:07:38,170
而不仅仅是滚床单
It's about more than sex.

215
00:07:38,170 --> 00:07:41,820
我们之间的滚床单意味深长
Our sex was about more than sex.

216
00:07:41,820 --> 00:07:44,190
既有历史感又有回忆感
It was about history and memory

217
00:07:44,190 --> 00:07:46,280
还有几千年殖民地的受虐感
and thousands of years of colonial suffering

218
00:07:46,280 --> 00:07:49,240
是一瞬间爆发的纯粹的激情
all being released in one moment of pure ecstasy.

219
00:07:49,240 --> 00:07:52,050
那为啥每次做完你总是大喊
Then why did the sex always end with you yelling,

220
00:07:52,050 --> 00:07:54,520
我擦  这竟然发生了
"Blammo, that happened"?

221
00:07:55,040 --> 00:07:56,100
我擦
Blammo.

222
00:07:57,520 --> 00:07:58,610
谢谢
Thank you.

223
00:08:01,120 --> 00:08:01,770
嗨
Hey.

224
00:08:01,770 --> 00:08:03,430
你居然能正常走路了
Oh, you can walk normally now, I see.

225
00:08:03,430 --> 00:08:05,720
很抱歉我亲了你
I'm sorry I kissed you.

226
00:08:05,720 --> 00:08:06,980
喔  好吧
Well, oh, wow.

227
00:08:06,980 --> 00:08:08,520
没想到你会这么说
That was unexpected.

228
00:08:08,520 --> 00:08:09,870
谢谢  尼克
Thanks, Nick.

229
00:08:09,870 --> 00:08:11,700
-那是个错误  -我感觉好些了
- You know what, it was a mistake. - I feel better.

230
00:08:11,700 --> 00:08:13,790
因为我觉得有些尴尬
'Cause, yeah, I was feeling awkward. 

231
00:08:13,790 --> 00:08:15,200
是的  你表现得有点怪
Yeah, right. You were acting a little bit weird,

232
00:08:15,200 --> 00:08:17,620
但说实话  我觉得这没有任何别的意思
but honestly, for me, it was, like, a nothing kiss.

233
00:08:17,620 --> 00:08:19,520
就好比亲了一个表妹
You know, it was like kissing a cousin.

234
00:08:19,520 --> 00:08:21,850
没有任何的男女私情
It was so nonsexual and nothing.

235
00:08:21,850 --> 00:08:25,060
我觉得还是有些含义的
Well... I think it meant something.

236
00:08:25,060 --> 00:08:27,230
对你来说  因为你亲了我
You know, to you, 'cause you kissed me.

237
00:08:28,870 --> 00:08:31,090
你可以承认那个吻对你有意义的  尼克
I think you can admit it meant something to you, Nick.

238
00:08:31,090 --> 00:08:33,180
不  我跟你说了  没任何别的意思
Oh, no, I-I'm telling you, it meant nothing to me.

239
00:08:33,180 --> 00:08:34,570
-我觉得有  -没有  没有
- I think it did. - No, no.

240
00:08:34,570 --> 00:08:36,450
我总会做一些没有任何含义的事
I do things I don't mean all the time.

241
00:08:36,450 --> 00:08:38,860
比如这样  你看  一瓶水
Like this. You see this? Bottle of water.

242
00:08:38,860 --> 00:08:39,650
我为什么要这样做  我也不知道
Why did I do that? I don't know.

243
00:08:39,650 --> 00:08:40,660
这没有任何意义
It doesn't mean anything.

244
00:08:40,660 --> 00:08:43,100
你可以承认那个吻对你有意义的 
I think you can admit that it meant something to you.

245
00:08:43,100 --> 00:08:45,380
杰茜卡  真没有
Hey, Jessica, it didn't. 

246
00:08:45,380 --> 00:08:47,870
我们只是在玩"铁杆美国人"
It was a drinking game, and I was finishing the game.

247
00:08:47,870 --> 00:08:49,950
对  但你是之后才亲我的
Yeah, but it happened after the game

248
00:08:49,950 --> 00:08:51,340
也就是说肯定代表着什么
when it meant something.

249
00:08:51,340 --> 00:08:53,890
-原来你很在乎啊  -什么
- Oh, so it meant something to you? - What?

250
00:08:53,890 --> 00:08:55,620
-你很在乎这件事啊  -没有...
- It meant something to you. - No, don't...

251
00:08:55,620 --> 00:08:57,760
如果你认为某个愚蠢糟糕的吻...
If you think some stupid, terrible kiss...

252
00:08:57,760 --> 00:08:59,680
-你现在就在想呢  -才没
- You're thinking about it right now! - No!

253
00:08:59,680 --> 00:09:01,900
-我要打给萨姆  -你要打给萨姆
- I'm calling Sam and... - Oh, you're calling Sam right now?

254
00:09:01,900 --> 00:09:03,640
他会马上过来  接我回去
He's gonna come here and pick me up,

255
00:09:03,640 --> 00:09:05,110
-然后我们要离开  -是吗
- and, uh, we're leaving. - Oh, you are?

256
00:09:05,110 --> 00:09:06,460
你为什么躲开  
Why are you running away? 

257
00:09:06,460 --> 00:09:08,660
因为这对你来说意味着什么吗
Because it meant something?

258
00:09:08,660 --> 00:09:10,650
我们哪也不去
We're not going anywhere.

259
00:09:11,700 --> 00:09:12,990
什么也不代表  尼克
Meant nothing, Nick!

260
00:09:13,470 --> 00:09:15,430
请看一下各位名牌上的数字
Please look at the numbers on your name tags

261
00:09:15,430 --> 00:09:17,860
然后走向对应数字的桌子
and go to the table with the corresponding numbers.

262
00:09:17,860 --> 00:09:19,150
这就是对你们的分组
These are your groupings.

263
00:09:19,150 --> 00:09:21,890
拥有相似履历和教育背景的人
People with similar resumes and education backgrounds 

264
00:09:21,890 --> 00:09:23,390
会被分到一组
have been grouped together.

265
00:09:23,390 --> 00:09:25,740
34  34  3...
Thirty four, thirty four, thir...

266
00:09:25,740 --> 00:09:27,590
34号桌
Table 34!

267
00:09:27,590 --> 00:09:29,210
我们共在一桌
We're at the same table!

268
00:09:29,210 --> 00:09:31,540
-点背到家了  -就当我疯了吧
- So this is rock bottom. - I mean, call me crazy,

269
00:09:31,540 --> 00:09:33,470
但我觉得今晚我们都会结婚
but I think we're all getting married tonight.

270
00:09:33,470 --> 00:09:35,340
-好吧  -好运桌  34号桌
- Yeah, um... - The money table right here, Table 34!

271
00:09:35,340 --> 00:09:37,410
嗨  打扰下  我觉得关于桌子的安排
Hi, excuse me, I think that there's been

272
00:09:37,410 --> 00:09:39,490
有些小问题
just a little bit of a mistake with the tables.

273
00:09:39,490 --> 00:09:41,100
30号以上都是没有高等学历的
Over 30, no advanced degrees,

274
00:09:41,100 --> 00:09:43,470
只有兼职工作的  尽在34号桌
part-time employment: Table 34.

275
00:09:43,470 --> 00:09:45,900
不是的  其实我是名专业模特
No, see, actually, I'm-I'm a professional model.

276
00:09:45,900 --> 00:09:47,080
我虽不出名
I'm not famous or anything,

277
00:09:47,080 --> 00:09:49,390
但我在李尔·韦恩[说唱歌手]的MV里出现过
but I was in Lil Wayne's last video.

278
00:09:49,390 --> 00:09:52,630
我就是那个他朝我扔草莓的女孩
I was the girl he was throwing strawberries at in slow motion.

279
00:09:54,940 --> 00:09:57,370
妥妥的34号桌
Definitely Table 34.

280
00:09:59,950 --> 00:10:01,210
抱歉
Excuse me?

281
00:10:01,210 --> 00:10:03,370
我没被分到桌子
Uh, I didn't get assigned a table.

282
00:10:03,370 --> 00:10:05,450
我很清楚这是由于...
Now, I know exactly what this is about...

283
00:10:05,450 --> 00:10:07,730
但是我确实有分位子给你
But I did assign you a seat.

284
00:10:08,300 --> 00:10:11,700
这一个  膝上首席座
This one. Lap number one.

285
00:10:11,700 --> 00:10:13,940
好吧  所以这和种族无关吗
Okay, so this is not a racial thing?

286
00:10:13,940 --> 00:10:15,650
目前  无关
Not yet, it isn't.

287
00:10:17,060 --> 00:10:19,290
我了解状况了
I see what's happening here.

288
00:10:19,290 --> 00:10:20,500
你感受到了我的男子汉魅力
You're feeling my mojo.

289
00:10:20,500 --> 00:10:24,320
你就像活蹦乱跳的小猫咪  我喜欢
You look like a jumpy cat, and I like that.

290
00:10:25,670 --> 00:10:27,350
我喜欢你的屁屁
I like that.

291
00:10:28,340 --> 00:10:31,050
好像超大号蓝莓
Like oversized blueberries.

292
00:10:32,760 --> 00:10:34,760
关闭魅力  关闭魅力
Mojo off. Mojo off.

293
00:10:34,880 --> 00:10:37,180
施密特  七号桌  七号桌
Schmidt, Table Seven, Table Seven.

294
00:10:37,180 --> 00:10:38,650
你来干嘛  你也在七号桌吗
What are you doing? You're at Table Seven,too?

295
00:10:38,650 --> 00:10:40,250
我在七号桌
I'm at Table Seven.

296
00:10:41,210 --> 00:10:41,740
怎么了
What?

297
00:10:41,740 --> 00:10:44,620
你这是被抬高身份  我觉得有点受辱了
Well, you should feel complimented. I feel slightly insulted.

298
00:10:44,620 --> 00:10:45,700
-什么  -无意冒犯
- What? - No offense.

299
00:10:45,700 --> 00:10:47,830
-你冒犯太多  -我只是说
- A lot of offense taken. - Well, I'm just saying...

300
00:10:47,830 --> 00:10:49,400
-很多  -杰茜
- A lot. - Jess!

301
00:10:50,800 --> 00:10:52,150
-你怎么样  -挺好的
- How are you?  - Okay.

302
00:10:52,150 --> 00:10:54,680
我登记了  他们给我分了桌子
Yeah, I checked in. Uh, they gave me my table.

303
00:10:54,680 --> 00:10:56,320
-不错  -真是个诡异的约会
- Okay. - This is a weird date.

304
00:10:56,320 --> 00:10:58,190
我一直以为在参加印度相亲大会之前
I always thought we'd go bowling before we went

305
00:10:58,190 --> 00:10:59,330
我们会先打保龄球的
to an Indian marriage convention.

306
00:10:59,330 --> 00:11:01,290
-你在几号桌  -一号桌吧
- What table are you at? - Table One, I think.

307
00:11:01,290 --> 00:11:02,420
一号桌
Table One?!

308
00:11:02,420 --> 00:11:04,520
感觉你好像什么拯救生命的大人物一样
It's almost like you save lives or something.

309
00:11:04,520 --> 00:11:06,990
等等  你确实是
Wait, you do.

310
00:11:06,990 --> 00:11:09,190
让我们先熟悉一下彼此
Let's start the icebreakers.

311
00:11:09,190 --> 00:11:11,870
这项活动能体现
This exercise shows how physically compatible

312
00:11:11,870 --> 00:11:13,160
两人肢体的协调程度
two people can be.

313
00:11:13,160 --> 00:11:16,160
{\an2}{\pos(70,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

314
00:11:13,160 --> 00:11:16,160
{\an2}{\pos(70,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

315
00:11:13,160 --> 00:11:16,160
{\an2}{\pos(60,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

316
00:11:13,160 --> 00:11:16,160
{\an2}{\pos(86,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

317
00:11:13,160 --> 00:11:16,160
{\an2}{\pos(101,267)}原创翻译  双语字幕

319
00:11:13,160 --> 00:11:16,160
{\an2}{\pos(240,267)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

320
00:11:16,160 --> 00:11:19,160
{\pos(190,268)}翻译： 施密咔  waterlike  口袋  end

322
00:11:19,160 --> 00:11:22,160
{\pos(190,268)}校对：想往D  爱是李    时间轴：扇子

324
00:11:22,160 --> 00:11:25,160
{\pos(190,268)}后期：鱼骨头     总监：爱是李

326
00:11:26,170 --> 00:11:28,370
-我的手  -怎么了
- My hand! - What?

327
00:11:28,370 --> 00:11:29,870
蠢男人
Stupid man.

328
00:11:31,050 --> 00:11:32,170
-漂亮  -那是
- Nice. - Yeah.

329
00:11:32,170 --> 00:11:34,460
准备好了吗 三  二  起
Ready? Three, two,ow.

330
00:11:34,460 --> 00:11:36,160
-不  不  我们  -抬高
- No, no. Let's... - Up?

331
00:11:36,160 --> 00:11:38,160
-不  你蹲下点  -我蹲下点
- No, you go down.  - All right. I go down?

332
00:11:38,840 --> 00:11:40,370
再近点就好了
Kind of just got to get in a little closer.

333
00:11:40,370 --> 00:11:42,140
好的  我试试
Okay, I'm trying.

334
00:11:42,140 --> 00:11:44,060
来真的
Seriously.

335
00:11:48,550 --> 00:11:49,280
笨蛋
Dummy.

336
00:11:49,280 --> 00:11:51,360
别再用你手指我  很讨厌哎
Stop pointing your finger at me. That's so annoying.

337
00:11:51,360 --> 00:11:53,870
你干嘛要喝我啤酒
Why are you drinking my beer?

338
00:11:53,870 --> 00:11:55,860
你要是再用手指那样指我  我就
You point that finger at me one more time, I'm...

339
00:11:55,860 --> 00:11:57,250
你为什么就是不承认那个吻对你有意义呢
Why don't you just admit that that kiss meant something to you?

340
00:11:57,250 --> 00:11:59,470
-没  没有  -我看得出来有意义  承认吧
- No, no! - I could tell it meant something, so admit it

341
00:11:59,470 --> 00:12:00,660
否则我就整天画圈圈  整天画圈圈
or I'll do this all day. I'll do it all day.

342
00:12:00,660 --> 00:12:02,780
下一个挑战  只用报纸和胶带
Next challenge: make a table

343
00:12:02,780 --> 00:12:05,810
做一个桌子
out of nothing but newspaper and tape.

344
00:12:05,810 --> 00:12:09,240
女士向左看  男士向右
Women look to your left, men to the right.

345
00:12:09,240 --> 00:12:10,810
这就是你们的搭档
These are your partners.

346
00:12:10,810 --> 00:12:11,620
开什么国际玩笑啊
You got to be kidding me.

347
00:12:11,620 --> 00:12:13,950
第一个能承受住电话本的桌子胜出
First table that can hold a phone book wins.

348
00:12:13,950 --> 00:12:15,390
好吧  我们得做一个桌子
All right, so we have to make a table.

349
00:12:15,390 --> 00:12:16,160
行
Okay.

350
00:12:16,160 --> 00:12:17,730
-给我胶带  -不给
- Give me the tape. - No.

351
00:12:19,690 --> 00:12:22,230
我来告诉你什么不是报纸做的
I'll tell you what's not made out of newspaper,

352
00:12:22,230 --> 00:12:24,780
那就是你紧致的小屁屁
that tight little ass of yours.

353
00:12:24,780 --> 00:12:26,430
杰茜  你享受和我接吻
Jess, you liked kissing me!

354
00:12:26,440 --> 00:12:27,940
说出来也没什么啊
It's fine to say that.

355
00:12:27,940 --> 00:12:30,050
-不  我没有  -我又没有跪下来
- No, I didn't. - I'm not on my knee asking you

356
00:12:30,050 --> 00:12:30,970
求婚  那是个美好的吻
to marry me; it was a nice kiss.

357
00:12:30,970 --> 00:12:33,140
你就像只狗  我嘴里
You were like a dog and my mouth

358
00:12:33,140 --> 00:12:35,720
就像有一碗狗奶
was like a bowl full of dog... milk!

359
00:12:35,720 --> 00:12:37,630
那是个童话般的吻好不好
It was like a damn fairy tale, that kiss!

360
00:12:37,630 --> 00:12:38,780
那是你一生中最好的吻
It was the best kiss of your life.

361
00:12:38,780 --> 00:12:40,760
-你开玩笑的吧  尼克  -而且你也有责任
- Are you serious, Nick? - And you have to take

362
00:12:40,760 --> 00:12:42,810
因为你穿着那件柔软的粉色睡袍
a little responsibility, tarting around in that

363
00:12:42,810 --> 00:12:44,220
花枝招展的乱晃
little soft pink robe,

364
00:12:44,220 --> 00:12:45,730
-还期望不被吻  -花枝招展的乱晃
- not expecting to get kissed. - Tarting around?

365
00:12:45,730 --> 00:12:47,940
我是个男人  杰茜卡
I'm a man, Jessica!

366
00:12:47,940 --> 00:12:49,580
-那又怎样  -粉色睡袍是我的兴奋点
- What? - Pink robes are my catnip.

367
00:12:49,580 --> 00:12:51,550
已经有一对胜出了
And we have a winning couple!

368
00:12:51,550 --> 00:12:53,150
我们不是一对
We are not a couple!

369
00:12:53,760 --> 00:12:55,730
-我们不是一对  -而且这是个很差的桌子
- We're not a couple. - And this is a very bad table.

370
00:12:55,730 --> 00:12:57,930
-很糟糕的桌子  -大家都别鼓掌了
- Terrible table. - And stop clapping, everybody.

371
00:12:57,930 --> 00:12:59,290
-这太糟糕了  -看  它什么都放不了
- This is awful. - Look. It won't hold anything.

372
00:12:59,290 --> 00:13:01,190
准备笑吧
Be prepared to laugh!

373
00:13:02,450 --> 00:13:03,860
不  我的意思是  这是  像
No, I mean, this is, like...

374
00:13:03,860 --> 00:13:05,570
我来  我来
I got it, I got it.

375
00:13:05,570 --> 00:13:06,790
拿来  放地上  只要  好
Here, put it down. Just-- okay.

376
00:13:06,790 --> 00:13:08,770
很不牢的桌子
Very weak table.

377
00:13:09,940 --> 00:13:11,340
烂啊
Break!

378
00:13:12,870 --> 00:13:14,340
这是个很牢固的桌子
It's a strong table.

379
00:13:14,340 --> 00:13:17,270
牢固的桌子  牢靠的一对
Strong table, strong couple.

380
00:13:17,270 --> 00:13:18,570
上来  跳跳  对
Come on. Jump up, yeah.

381
00:13:18,570 --> 00:13:19,620
跳起来  跳起来  跳起来
Jump up! Jump up! Jump up!

382
00:13:19,620 --> 00:13:21,010
再来
Come on.

383
00:13:21,010 --> 00:13:22,800
-这回来真的  伙计  -来吧
- It's real, man. - Come on.

384
00:13:23,250 --> 00:13:24,570
真是令人刮目相看的桌子
That's an impressive table!

385
00:13:26,680 --> 00:13:29,700
祝贺你赢得了制作桌子的比赛  宝贝
Congratulations on winning the table-building competition, baby.

386
00:13:29,700 --> 00:13:31,070
是  但它代表不了什么
Yeah, it didn't mean anything.

387
00:13:31,070 --> 00:13:32,410
我没说那代表了什么
I didn't think it meant anything.

388
00:13:32,410 --> 00:13:34,870
是  不  只是  尼克让我抓狂
Yeah, no, just-- Nick just drives me crazy.

389
00:13:34,870 --> 00:13:37,080
-就像  你知道吗  -是  我从没
- It's like... you know? - Yeah, I mean, I never...

390
00:13:37,080 --> 00:13:39,030
这就是  就是我想说的
Well, yeah, that's just... That's what I was saying.

391
00:13:39,030 --> 00:13:40,650
你是不是有事瞒着我
Is there something I should know here?

392
00:13:40,650 --> 00:13:41,950
没有  因为
No. 'Cause...

393
00:13:41,950 --> 00:13:43,510
男士们  请换位
Men, switch seats!

394
00:13:43,510 --> 00:13:44,940
不  萨姆  别去
No. Sam, stop.

395
00:13:44,940 --> 00:13:46,520
因为  别走  我想和你谈谈
'Cause... No, I want to talk to you.

396
00:13:46,520 --> 00:13:48,560
-萨姆  我  -你喜欢陆上曲棍球吗
- Sam, I  - Do you like field hockey?

397
00:13:48,560 --> 00:13:51,160
我  喜欢喜欢
I... Yeah. Yeah.

398
00:13:52,720 --> 00:13:55,260
-你好  -很抱歉  小可爱  过  
- Hi!  - I'm so sorry, sweetie. Pass.

399
00:13:55,260 --> 00:13:57,070
你是什么时候决定成为一名模特的
So, when did you decide to become a model?

400
00:13:57,070 --> 00:13:59,500
我还真没注意过
Oh. Didn't really think about it at all.

401
00:13:59,500 --> 00:14:02,150
有人说要给我钱让我打扮漂亮点  所以
Someone just said they'd pay me for being pretty, so...

402
00:14:02,150 --> 00:14:03,430
我喜欢你的帽子
I like your hat.

403
00:14:03,430 --> 00:14:06,380
这是我最爱的颜色
It's my favorite color.

404
00:14:08,860 --> 00:14:11,510
-我什么都没说  -闭嘴  闭嘴  闭嘴
- I didn't say anything. - Shut up, shut up, shut up.

405
00:14:11,510 --> 00:14:12,610
那你想要几个孩子
So how many children do you want?

406
00:14:12,610 --> 00:14:14,120
我得尽快开始
Well, I have to start soon, 

407
00:14:14,120 --> 00:14:16,520
所以  能生几个生几个
so I guess I'll just jump right in.

408
00:14:16,520 --> 00:14:18,670
那么你是会斟酌你每一项决定
So, do you think through any of your decisions

409
00:14:18,670 --> 00:14:20,400
还是随心所欲
or do you always just do whatever you want?

410
00:14:20,400 --> 00:14:22,250
M·奈特·沙马兰
M. Night Shyamalan.

411
00:14:20,400 --> 00:14:22,250
{\an8}M·奈特·沙马兰  《第六感》的导演  印度人

412
00:14:22,250 --> 00:14:24,280
我给你个戏剧性的结局  闭嘴
I got a twist ending for you: shut up.

413
00:14:24,280 --> 00:14:25,240
七号桌  你想怎样
What do you want, Table Seven? 

414
00:14:25,250 --> 00:14:26,500
施密特  去和你的女孩说话
Schmidt, just talk to your girl.

415
00:14:26,500 --> 00:14:27,540
-你好  -你最好小心点  朋友
- Hi!  - You better watch it, buddy.

416
00:14:27,540 --> 00:14:29,980
因为我会  我会在这里亲手碎尸
'Cause I will, I will Cal-cut-a-bitch up in here.

417
00:14:29,980 --> 00:14:32,070
-我会亲手碎尸  -施密特
- I will Cal-cut-a-bitch. - Schmidt!

418
00:14:32,070 --> 00:14:34,050
别担心  本·阿弗莱克  我还没有那么饥渴
Don't worry, Ben Affleck. I'm not desperate.

419
00:14:34,050 --> 00:14:35,310
我不会和六号桌以下的人交往
I don't date below Table Six.

420
00:14:35,310 --> 00:14:36,920
时间到  交换位子
Time's up. Switch places.

421
00:14:38,380 --> 00:14:39,540
萨姆
Sam

422
00:14:40,680 --> 00:14:42,170
那可不好  他过分了
That was not nice. He crossed a line.

423
00:14:42,170 --> 00:14:43,990
施密特  你说过你不会打扰我的
Schmidt, you said you would leave me alone.

424
00:14:43,990 --> 00:14:45,890
-你说过你不会  -他过分鸟
- You said you would leave... - He crossed a line.

425
00:14:45,890 --> 00:14:47,800
你说过你不会打扰我的
You said you would leave me alone.

426
00:14:51,200 --> 00:14:52,980
在这里遇见你真有趣
Funny seeing you here.

427
00:14:56,480 --> 00:14:57,650
你该走了
You have to go.

428
00:14:57,650 --> 00:14:59,350
是的  你该去那边了
Yeah, you have to go over there.

429
00:14:59,350 --> 00:15:00,820
好了  拜拜
Okay. Bye-bye.

430
00:15:00,820 --> 00:15:01,730
现在就去  你好
Go now. Hi.

431
00:15:02,390 --> 00:15:06,160
萨姆  我确实有事瞒着你
Sam, I do have something to tell you.

432
00:15:07,610 --> 00:15:09,380
你知道我们为什么在三十四号桌吗
You know why we're at Table 34?

433
00:15:09,380 --> 00:15:13,180
因为我们生活不幸  却拥有模特的良好外形
'Cause we're both bad at life, but we have model good looks.

434
00:15:13,180 --> 00:15:16,070
是因为我们从不透彻地思考问题
It's 'cause we don't think things through.

435
00:15:16,070 --> 00:15:18,510
你吻杰茜的时候就没有
You didn't think it through when you kissed Jess.

436
00:15:18,510 --> 00:15:21,590
她告诉我了  我们总是冲动做决定
She told me. It's like we just make these impulsive decisions,

437
00:15:21,590 --> 00:15:24,800
结果总会伤害别人
and all we end up doing is hurting other people.

438
00:15:26,580 --> 00:15:28,180
真想不到
I can't believe this.

439
00:15:28,180 --> 00:15:30,440
别  别  萨姆
No. No, Sam...

440
00:15:31,490 --> 00:15:32,900
萨姆   等等
Sam? Wait.

441
00:15:32,900 --> 00:15:34,110
萨姆  等等
Sam, wait.

442
00:15:34,530 --> 00:15:35,520
真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.

443
00:15:35,520 --> 00:15:37,170
我说过我会认真对待这段感情
I said I wanted to commit to this.

444
00:15:37,170 --> 00:15:38,610
还以为你清楚什么叫认真对待
I thought you understood what that meant.

445
00:15:38,610 --> 00:15:40,120
我很清楚  我有认真对待
I do. I did.

446
00:15:40,120 --> 00:15:41,900
等等  萨姆  听我说
Hey, hey. Sam, listen.

447
00:15:41,900 --> 00:15:43,560
-你又怎么了  -萨姆  听我说
- What?  - Sam, hear me out.

448
00:15:43,560 --> 00:15:45,020
是我亲她的
I kissed her, okay?

449
00:15:45,020 --> 00:15:46,280
她没有回吻
She didn't kiss me.

450
00:15:47,160 --> 00:15:49,280
这对她没任何意义
It didn't mean anything to her.

451
00:15:49,280 --> 00:15:50,130
谢谢
Thank you.

452
00:15:52,420 --> 00:15:53,810
我勒个去
Oh, my God!

453
00:15:53,810 --> 00:15:55,030
不好意思  尼克  哥有练过
I'm sorry, Nick. It's the training.

454
00:15:55,030 --> 00:15:57,940
他很难受  你差点杀了他
He's in such terrible shape! You could've killed him.

455
00:15:57,940 --> 00:15:59,210
我会揍死你的  小崽子
I'm gonna kick your ass, man.

456
00:15:59,210 --> 00:16:00,520
杰茜  可能这对你不算什么
Jess, it may not have meant something

457
00:16:00,520 --> 00:16:02,170
可这对我很重要
to you, but it meant something to me.

458
00:16:02,170 --> 00:16:04,780
这里还有谁是医生吗
Is there another doctor in the house?!

459
00:16:04,780 --> 00:16:06,260
这群人里肯定有
With this crowd, I'm sure.

460
00:16:06,260 --> 00:16:09,380
我接受不了  那...
I'm done. So...

461
00:16:10,150 --> 00:16:11,820
再见了  杰茜
Good-bye, Jess.

462
00:16:11,820 --> 00:16:14,520
不要  萨姆
No. Sam.

463
00:16:15,970 --> 00:16:18,560
用冰敷  24小时
Ice it, 24 hours.

464
00:16:18,560 --> 00:16:20,240
保持抬高
And keep it elevated.

465
00:16:22,420 --> 00:16:24,130
-他连离场都那么帅  -天哪
- He even exits cool. - Oh, God.

466
00:16:27,310 --> 00:16:29,860
安努  我给你找到伴了
Anu? I got something for you.

467
00:16:29,860 --> 00:16:31,490
这位是弗雷迪
Now, this is Freddy.

468
00:16:31,490 --> 00:16:33,580
你看看  他的体格
As you can see, he has the exact

469
00:16:33,580 --> 00:16:35,180
跟我完全一样  是不
same build as me, all right?

470
00:16:35,180 --> 00:16:38,290
他还是单身  是不  弗雷迪
And he is totally available. Ain't that right, Freddy?

471
00:16:38,290 --> 00:16:41,570
这才是真正的相亲
That is what I call an arranged bang.

472
00:16:42,480 --> 00:16:47,050
弗雷迪  你怕被囚禁在狭小空间吗
Freddy, are you scared of being confined in small spaces?

473
00:16:49,250 --> 00:16:52,030
你太适合了
Oh, you'll do just fine.

474
00:16:53,620 --> 00:16:56,460
记着  不论你在哪儿
Now, just remember, wherever you are,

475
00:16:56,460 --> 00:16:58,150
真汉子就在你身边
the Mojo Man is there.

476
00:17:07,140 --> 00:17:08,880
你真该死  施密特
Damn it, Schmidt.

477
00:17:12,320 --> 00:17:13,740
我要用麦
I'm taking this.

478
00:17:13,740 --> 00:17:17,750
不好意思  打扰了  闭嘴
Excuse me. Excuse me! Hold up!

479
00:17:17,750 --> 00:17:18,930
知道吗  今天刚来这里的时候
You know, when I came here today,

480
00:17:18,930 --> 00:17:21,220
我还觉得印度是个很棒的国家
I thought India was a pretty cool country.

481
00:17:21,610 --> 00:17:22,780
你们显然都很聪明
You guys are obviously smart.

482
00:17:22,780 --> 00:17:24,290
你们看着巴士车顶  想着
You l-looked at the roof of a bus and you said,

483
00:17:24,290 --> 00:17:27,760
"这不只是车顶  还有座位呢"
"That's not just a roof, that's more seating."

484
00:17:28,100 --> 00:17:31,090
凯尔·潘是个天才  谢谢你们创造出他
Kal Penn, he's a genius. Thank you for him.

485
00:17:28,100 --> 00:17:31,090
{\an8}凯尔·潘  著名印度籍演员及政治家

486
00:17:31,890 --> 00:17:33,370
可我不知道
But what I didn't know

487
00:17:33,370 --> 00:17:35,940
你们整国人都是瞎了眼的白痴
is that you're a country full of blind idiots.

488
00:17:35,940 --> 00:17:37,240
-我的天哪  -因为在你们之中
- Oh, God. - Because in your midst

489
00:17:37,240 --> 00:17:38,580
有一个棕皮肤天使
walks a brown angel.

490
00:17:39,930 --> 00:17:42,220
那个女人  就在那里
That woman. Right there.

491
00:17:43,600 --> 00:17:44,560
我可能是个傻瓜
I may be an idiot,

492
00:17:44,560 --> 00:17:47,210
但没傻到连失去了都不知道珍惜
but I'm smart enough to know what I lost.

493
00:17:48,390 --> 00:17:50,630
你们本可以拥有这一切
You people could've had it all.

494
00:17:50,630 --> 00:17:54,600
可你们把她晾在那  跟尼克一张桌子
And you shoved her over there at a table with Nick.

495
00:17:54,600 --> 00:17:56,820
赶紧特么去追她  印度阿三
Get your crap together, India.

496
00:17:56,820 --> 00:17:58,530
施密特
Schmidt...

497
00:17:59,110 --> 00:18:00,650
不玩儿了
out!

498
00:18:05,230 --> 00:18:07,570
你好  我在那里没看到你
Hello. I didn't see you over here.

499
00:18:08,520 --> 00:18:09,490
我想...
I would love to...

500
00:18:10,720 --> 00:18:12,240
抱歉我之前没看到你
Sorry I didn't see you earlier.

501
00:18:12,240 --> 00:18:13,400
好吧  他们都...  好吧
Okay. They're all-- okay.

502
00:18:13,400 --> 00:18:15,080
你们别一下子扎堆跑过去啊
You don't all have to run over there at once.

503
00:18:15,080 --> 00:18:17,210
她也没那么好啦  大伙儿
I mean, she... she's not that great, you guys.

504
00:18:17,210 --> 00:18:19,440
她挺老的
I mean, she's kind of old.

505
00:18:19,440 --> 00:18:21,450
你得看她的乳晕  一个像直升机停机坪
You should see her areolas-- one's like a helicopter pad,

506
00:18:21,450 --> 00:18:23,660
另一个像...像
the other one's like a, you know, like...

507
00:18:23,660 --> 00:18:24,730
蜱虫叮咬的疤
like a tick bite.

508
00:18:24,730 --> 00:18:26,780
很恶心的  很奇怪
It's freaky. Very disorienting.

509
00:18:28,710 --> 00:18:30,360
我这样你会不会感觉好点
Is this making you feel better at all?

510
00:18:41,290 --> 00:18:44,300
我只想一个人听泰勒·斯威夫特
I just wanted to listen to Taylor Swift alone!

511
00:18:46,320 --> 00:18:47,110
这动作如何
How's that?

512
00:18:47,110 --> 00:18:50,330
你被甩的时候  总会绞尽脑汁想
You know when you get dumped and you're, like, racking your brain

513
00:18:50,330 --> 00:18:52,420
自己到底做错了什么
for what was it that I did wrong?

514
00:18:52,420 --> 00:18:54,540
这次情况特殊
Well, this is a really unique situation

515
00:18:54,540 --> 00:18:57,100
我不用再想了
in that I don't have to do that.

516
00:18:57,100 --> 00:18:58,600
那是怎么回事
Well, what happened?

517
00:18:59,460 --> 00:19:02,220
对不起  我知道  我知道这是我的错
I'm sorry. I know what-- I know that it's my fault.

518
00:19:02,220 --> 00:19:03,940
我没想到事情会...
I didn't mean it like...

519
00:19:05,500 --> 00:19:06,710
杰茜  能让我说句
Jess, can I say something

520
00:19:06,710 --> 00:19:09,220
-对情况毫无帮助的话吗  -不行
- that'll potentially not help this situation? - No.

521
00:19:09,220 --> 00:19:11,640
我从来没试过当小三
I've never been a home-wrecker.

522
00:19:12,430 --> 00:19:14,520
感觉真爽
And I liked it.

523
00:19:14,520 --> 00:19:17,970
萨姆竟然受到我的威胁
I mean, Sam was threatened by me.

524
00:19:18,560 --> 00:19:20,470
我把这当做胜利了
I mean, I see that as a victory.

525
00:19:23,030 --> 00:19:27,020
可...更重要的是
But in-in more important...

526
00:19:27,020 --> 00:19:31,570
这...这是个巨大的损失
uh, ways, a huge, huge, devastating loss.

527
00:19:31,570 --> 00:19:33,360
对你而言
For you.

528
00:19:34,040 --> 00:19:34,700
我该叫希希来吗
Should I call Cece?

529
00:19:34,700 --> 00:19:36,150
感觉这是希希的管辖范围
This feels like Cece territory.

530
00:19:36,150 --> 00:19:37,350
尼克不该出场
This isn't Nick territory.

531
00:19:37,350 --> 00:19:39,800
这...
This is, uh...

532
00:19:41,620 --> 00:19:43,970
听着  杰茜
Look, Jess...

533
00:19:45,260 --> 00:19:47,530
对不起  真的
I'm sorry, okay,

534
00:19:47,530 --> 00:19:49,190
对不起  我吻了你
that I kissed you.

535
00:19:49,190 --> 00:19:50,550
我不该亲你的
But I shouldn't have done it,

536
00:19:50,550 --> 00:19:52,210
这显然是个错误
because it was obviously a mistake,

537
00:19:52,210 --> 00:19:54,210
现在又把你惹哭了
and now you're crying and...

538
00:19:54,710 --> 00:19:56,450
我不会再犯了
I won't do it again.

539
00:19:58,140 --> 00:19:59,930
好吧
Well...

540
00:19:59,930 --> 00:20:04,670
可能一开始就出现问题了
maybe it was a little bit broken to begin with.

541
00:20:04,670 --> 00:20:06,190
-怎么了  -他...
- What happened? - He just...

542
00:20:06,770 --> 00:20:09,950
早上起床的时候总爱玩碰拳
He always wanted to fist bump in the morning.

543
00:20:09,950 --> 00:20:12,810
-你不喜欢吗  -讨厌死了  怎么了
- And you didn't like that?  - I hated it. What are...what...

544
00:20:12,810 --> 00:20:14,790
-我觉得你原谅我了  -我没有
- I feel like you're forgiving me. - No.

545
00:20:14,790 --> 00:20:17,640
-说这句话之前  你已经原谅我了  -没有
- I felt like before I said that you were though. - Nope. Nope.

546
00:20:17,640 --> 00:20:20,440
你现在又想起你该生我气  没吗  好吧
Now you remembered you're still mad at me. No? Okay.

547
00:20:20,440 --> 00:20:22,250
-好了  晚安  尼克  -晚安  杰茜  
- All right, good night, Nick. Night. - Okay, good night, Jess.

548
00:20:22,250 --> 00:20:23,410
杰茜  等等
Hey, Jess.

549
00:20:24,940 --> 00:20:26,150
太早了吗
Too soon?

550
00:20:26,150 --> 00:20:27,410
是的  太早了
Yeah, too soon!

551
00:20:27,410 --> 00:20:30,420
好吧  那晚安啦  真的很对不起
Well, hey, good night. And I'm sorry about everything.

552
00:20:30,420 --> 00:20:31,270
好吧
Okay.

553
00:20:39,000 --> 00:20:40,170
好吧
Okay, yeah.

554
00:20:40,170 --> 00:20:41,710
-这有点  -是啊  真有点
- That was... - Yeah. That was...

555
00:20:41,710 --> 00:20:43,170
-有点尴尬  -很尴尬
- a little bit weird. - So weird.

556
00:20:43,170 --> 00:20:44,050
以后别这样了
Let's not ever do that again.

557
00:20:44,050 --> 00:20:45,690
-是啊  -别这样了  好的
- Yeah. - Do it again. Okay.

558
00:20:45,690 --> 00:20:48,510
-晚安  米勒  -晚安
- Good night. Night, Miller!  - Good night.

559
00:20:48,510 --> 00:20:50,080
晚安  警官
Good night, Sergeant.

560
00:20:52,040 --> 00:20:54,470
太好了  一切回归正常了
I'm glad everything's back to normal around here.

561
00:20:58,740 --> 00:20:59,630
谢谢你说的那番话
Thank you for what you said up there.

562
00:20:59,630 --> 00:21:01,450
-我拿到了很多电话号码  -很好
- You know, I got a lot of phone numbers. - Good.

563
00:21:02,990 --> 00:21:04,210
我应该会去很多约会
I think I'm gonna go on a lot of dates.

564
00:21:04,210 --> 00:21:06,210
-这是好事  很好  -是啊
- I think that's a great thing. Good. - Yeah.

565
00:21:08,360 --> 00:21:09,870
计划不变  我还得跟印度佬结婚
The plan hasn't changed. I am still marrying an Indian guy.

566
00:21:09,870 --> 00:21:11,150
-没事  没问题  -没问题吗
- No, yeah, that's fine. - Okay?

567
00:21:11,150 --> 00:21:12,950
可你跟裹头巾的犹太人回家了  说说而已
But you went home with a Jew in a turban, so I'm just saying.

568
00:21:12,950 --> 00:21:14,060
快把衣服脱了  
Just take this off.  

569
00:21:14,060 --> 00:21:15,800
快  快脱
Come on. Let's go.

570
00:21:16,670 --> 00:21:18,460
老天  我想死这了
God, I have missed this.

571
00:21:21,280 --> 00:21:22,880
戴头巾吗  戴吗
Turban on? Turban off?

572
00:21:22,880 --> 00:21:25,120
我会恨死自己说出这话  可...
I'm gonna hate myself for saying this, but...

573
00:21:25,120 --> 00:21:27,880
-戴上头巾  -那就戴头巾吧
- Turban on. - Turban on it is.

574
00:21:32,030 --> 00:21:33,710
举起手  好像在坐飞毯
Take it up. That magic carpet ride.

575
00:21:33,710 --> 00:21:35,090
-像吗  不像吗  -闭嘴  爽
- Yeah? No? - Shut up! Whoo!

