Should have responded
to your recall earlier.
You made the right choice.
Chance to bury Division?
I'm in.
It's what we do.
Welcome to the winning side.
Ops, I got visual
on target.
Okay, Nikki, be careful.
We don't know what her contact
is armed with.
Relax.
I have to warn her.
I have to warn Amanda.
No.
If she finds out
I didn't warn her,
she will trigger
my kill chip,
and I will die right here.
That's not gonna happen.
She's going down.
You're getting free.
I'm sorry.
I already did.
I had to.
Nikki, look out!
It's a trap!
Well, that worked out.
Birkhoff.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because he
didn't trust you.
Sonya.
I no longer
require your services.
No!
Sonya!
Agh.
Just tell her.
I can't breathe, Nikki.
Nerd?
Are you ever not armed?
Seriously?
Why are you shadowing me?
I had to make sure
nobody else was.
Okay.
You said you felt
like you were being watched
for, like, a month now.
Yeah, but I haven't spotted
anyone till now.
There's a good reason
for it.
Trust me.
Sonya is the mole.
What?
She needs your help.
About three weeks ago,
Amanda's cleaner grabbed her
coming out of her apartment.
They reactivated
her kill chip.
Now if she doesn't update them
every two hours,
she's considered compromised.
She couldn't take ten minutes
to ask for help?
We can remove her chip
in medical.
No, no, no,
there's a second mole.
Someone whose sole job
it is to watch her,
make sure she stays
in line.
She has access to you,
to us.
Yeah, Amanda wants her
to focus on personal dirt.
She doesn't care
about the missions.
She's playing
the long game.
She wants to see me suffer.
You did the right thing
telling me.
But we--we gotta tell
the others.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I told Sonya that--
Listen,
I'll keep it quiet.
Trust me, I promise.
Okay.
In the meantime,
make sure Sonya plays along.
Most wanted.
That's what I like to hear.
How do you know
she isn't playing you?
Do I detect a hint
of jealousy, Anne?
No.
Suspicion.
Why do you trust Sonya?
She has an explosive
in her brainstem
that I have on speed dial.
Who needs trust?
As long as you know
when to use it.
Let's check
the weather then.
Partially cloudy
but still a balmy 78.
You see?
Wailea Beach?
If our friend
on the inside
senses Sonya
is flirting with betrayal,
the forecast
on this weather site changes,
and I retire Sonya.
This must be what it felt like
to be Nikita.
On the run
from place to place,
launching her war
from a laptop
with a mole inside Division.
She lives
inside stronger walls now.
But in a way,
she's weaker than ever.
Even the strongest walls
can come crashing down.
All you need to find is
a single crack on the surface.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
It's a nice day.
I took a walk.
Yeah.
It's a little warm to wear
that jacket, huh?
Not really.
Were you following me?
- Should I be?
- No.
I--I just--
lately I've been feeling
like someone's
been watching me.
We all have.
We're letting
Amanda's mind games get to us.
Or maybe you just took
too many of these.
Sobelex, huh?
I thought I saw the signs
on you a few days ago.
Give it back,
Michael.
Why?
They're not yours.
They're Division's.
It's an experimental painkiller
designed for combat use,
not recommended
for ex-drug addicts.
I was only taking it
for my shoulder.
I wanted to help out.
Help?
This doesn't just put
your life in danger, Alex.
This puts my life
in danger.
Nikita's.
And anyone who relies on you
to shoot straight
and back them up
in the field.
I do.
- It's Nikita.
- Okay, look, Michael.
Look, you're right, okay?
I'll stop, I'll stop.
Just please don't tell Nikita.
Please.
Hey.
I'm on my way.
We're needed
back at the office.
- Thank you.
- Don't.
I made the decision
to talk to you before Nikita
because this would hurt her
more than anyone,
on account of everything
she's gone through for you.
So you are gonna be
the one that tells her.
And in the meantime,
you're gonna clean up,
and you're not going
back out into the field
until that happens.
What did Nikita want?
Looks like we're both
gonna find out.
All right, people,
we need to up our game.
Let's close the net.
Now we know
that she was in Luxembourg
three weeks back
and Andalusia six days ago.
We need to figure out
where she's going next.
Let's go!
Sonya, where's the list
of her confiscated inventory?
Almost done.
We need it now.
Bring it into briefing.
Yes, sir.
That should buy us
some time.
You call that believable?
"Okay, people,
we need to up our game."
Birkhoff, calm down.
It sounded fake.
We should be doing this
in Ryan's office anyway.
Then I couldn't be here.
Your fake inventory, sir.
Are you sure
there's a second mole?
No, but I can't take
the risk.
Let's start going over
our options.
Surgery, remove the chip.
We lost our best surgeon
in Amanda's attack on medical.
Surgery takes
six hours minimum.
And I have to check in
every two.
Which rules out a trip
to an outside hospital as well.
Why can't someone else
check in for you?
The second mole would see
and alert Amanda.
What about deactivation?
Three hours.
Laparoscopic procedure.
Portable equipment.
Still gotta buy
the extra hour.
Wait, didn't Amanda
deactivate your kill chip once?
How'd that work?
She electrocuted me.
I was clinically deceased
for 32 seconds.
It fooled the chip.
I'm not getting killed
to save my life.
I have to get back
to my station.
Wait, there is another way.
We kill the threat
at its source.
We kill Amanda.
How?
She relies on you for intel.
We set a trap.
End this for good.
No, no, no, no, no.
That means leaving
her kill chip active.
This is about
how we deactivate it.
But this could be the only w--
No!
No, we're not risking
her life any further.
It's not your life,
Seymour.
It's mine.
Everyone in here
is trying to save me,
and all I've done
is jeopardize your lives
by not asking
for help sooner.
Besides, I want revenge
for what she's done to me.
Let's bait the bitch.
I knew I liked her.
♪ Nikita 3x06 ♪
Intersection
Original air date on January 18, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Top secret
Birkhoff device.
Not interested.
Better step it up, honey,
or it's die time.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah.
Yes, I did.
What do you think?
It's nice.
Nice?
Ahem.
This is
a hydraulic battering ram
with spike deployment.
We've got N.O.S. booster,
onboard radar,
oil slick.
See those headlights
right there?
They launch
laser-guided missiles.
Really?
No, but how cool would that be
if they did?
That's why we all
gotta get on board
and convince Ryan
it's worth spending the cash.
Michael, spare me
the Psych 101, okay?
Well, she's all you ever
talk about at home, here.
It's always about Amanda.
I'm getting sick of this--
Awkward.
We were just leaving.
Yeah, we were.
See, this is exactly
what I'm talking about.
We can't get
a moment alone in here.
Is this what's wrong,
or is there something else
bothering you?
Why does there need
to be something else?
Because lately it feels like
you're holding back,
you're suppressing something.
No, no, no.
The only one
who's holding back is you.
You are holding us back.
Once we got rid of Percy,
we were supposed
to be done with this place,
but now with your obsession--
What? No! No!
Yes, yes,
with your obsession,
you are blind to the problem
in front of you.
What?
Are we done yet?
The camera stopped
ten seconds ago.
I just didn't want you
to break character.
Are we sure
this is gonna work?
You and me fighting,
Amanda catnip.
Okay, I will compress
and upload the video to her,
and then I will tell her that
Michael has gone off to the pub
to drown his sorrows
in drink.
No, send the video,
let it marinate,
and then on your next update,
let her know where Michael
will be drinking.
And we're positive
Amanda's gonna show up?
I don't know,
could be she sends Anne.
She sends Anne,
we follow her to Amanda.
Either way,
we have to plant the bait,
so let's get started.
We're on a schedule, go.
Hey, guys,
I just wanted to say
how much it means to me--
Hey, Nerd,
can we do this later?
You have
another mole to I.D.
Ryan and Alex are waiting,
phase two.
- Right, cool.
- Great.
You're awesome.
What?
Let's not fight like that.
- Ohh.
Phase two, whac-a-mole.
All right, people.
Everybody listen up.
We've got our first lead
on Amanda.
With your help,
we can finish this.
Alex is gonna bring you
up to speed.
Based on our intel,
we believe Amanda
has a safe house
within a 2-mile radius
of Hofgarten.
I want everyone
to pool their resources
and do whatever you can
to close the circle
even further.
Okay, stations
2, 5, 6, 8, 10, and 13.
That many people spiked
at the mention of Amanda?
Yeah, now let's narrow it down
even further.
See who reacts
to Sonya reacting.
Go.
And then there were four.
Better get going
and prep the next phase.
On it.
Ops, we're a go.
Is this what's wrong,
or is there something else
bothering you?
Okay, why does there need
to be something else?
Because lately it feels
like you're holding back.
Do you see what I see?
I see
why you forbid relationships
when you were running
Division.
Nikita is perceptive.
Michael is hiding something.
And I have an idea
what it might be.
Well, it's all
coming together
or falling apart.
Contact the Watchman.
Tell him I have
another assignment for him.
I don't understand
how he gets so close
to take these pictures.
We all have our specialty.
You have your knife.
The Watchman has his eye.
I find the cracks
on the surface.
Anything yet?
She should have responded
by now.
What if she knows?
She doesn't.
Wait.
Dealtown Shoe Outlet?
Amanda encodes her orders
on regular websites
using steganography.
Why would Amanda have Sonya
watching the two of you?
She must have had
someone following us.
Us?
Both of you?
We ran into each other
this morning.
Michael, stop.
Nikita, a couple weeks ago,
I started using again.
What?
Michael found out
and confronted me.
She was supposed
to tell you.
She was supposed to?
But it wasn't
the right time.
This thing with Sonya--
Wait, using what?
Sobelex for my arm.
It helped me retrieve
the cryptograph, okay?
No, if I had told you,
you would have had me benched.
You're damn right
I would have.
Nikita--
No, you I understand
even less.
A member of our team
is unstable,
and you don't warn me,
you don't warn Ryan?
I wanted to avoid
this type of overreaction.
Overreaction?
She is an addict, Michael.
All right.
Guys, guys, stop.
Listen to yourselves.
Okay, this is
what Amanda wants,
the lies, the blame.
Fracture.
Birkhoff's right, we set out
to fake a fight for Amanda,
and here we are
in a real one.
Well, this was my fault,
so I'll stand down.
No.
We are going to adjust,
and we are going to work
with what we have.
We have confirmation
that Amanda is tailing us.
We've suspected it
for weeks.
I didn't see anyone,
and I was looking.
If you were surveilled,
it had to be
at extremely long range.
Or extremely close.
Amanda has another rogue
on her side.
Oh, sit.
The Watchman.
Who's the Watchman?
He's a Division legend
and now our ticket
to Amanda.
She thinks something's going on
between the two of you.
Let's give the lady
what she wants.
Excellent work
on the last batch of photos.
Exactly the kind of intel
I was looking for.
Doesn't come cheap.
Stay with Michael and Alex.
Don't worry
about Nikita for now.
Whatever's happening
between the two of them
is more important.
I'll begin as soon
as the money hits my account.
Already on its way.
This was taken
from a park cam earlier today.
Here's me and Alex,
and here's the Watchman.
How can you be sure
that's him?
Because we had Birkhoff
run his facial recog program
through all
the surrounding cameras.
He was able to track
everyone from the coffee cart
about 12 blocks.
This guy vanished in one.
Vanished?
That's his specialty.
The Watchman was Division's
close surveillance expert.
He was able to change
his appearance
at a moment's notice,
he made it a habit.
His job was
to surveil a target
without making them aware
they were even being followed.
Only Percy and Amanda
knew his name
and what he really
looked like.
- What's in his file?
- Never had one.
His other job was
to investigate Division agents.
He did routine checks
on everyone,
observed them
in their cover lives
and made sure
they didn't break any rules.
Which is why he only
reported to Percy and Amanda.
He's about to write
his last report.
I'm still not sure
about this.
You want Michael and I
to pretend
to rendezvous
in some nightclub.
Sonya will feed
the address to Amanda.
This is a photo op.
Wherever you go,
the Watchman will follow,
and I will follow him.
When he makes contact
with Amanda,
we trace his communications
and zero her location.
Now what
about the second mole?
They're still in play.
Birkhoff's got that
under control.
Okay, people, look alive.
What are we doing
down here?
What's with
all the questions?
So Halon system went off,
covered the tower,
fried eight of the nodes.
- Did it malfunction?
- No.
Our fire prevention system
suddenly became self-aware
and decided to attack us
with whipped cream.
That's a joke.
Anyway, people, the point
is we're in the middle
of the hunt for Amanda.
We need to be up and running
at full capacity.
So I want each of you
to choose two nodes
and rebuild them
from the ground up.
What?
That'll take hours.
Then you better stop whining
and get to work.
'Cause none of you are leaving
until the job's done.
Enjoy.
Malfunction,
my ass.
This looks like sabotage.
What do you think, Baker?
Another present from
our friendly neighborhood mole?
I think
you should just stop talking.
We've got a lot
of work to do.
I don't want to be stuck
down here all night
with you
and your conspiracy theories.
Excuse me.
♪
You guys are supposed
to be having an affair,
not on the most
awkward date ever.
Well, it is awkward.
I'm on a date with
my best friend's boyfriend,
and her voice
is in my head.
Fiance.
Now pretend you like each other.
You know what,
why don't we start
with pretend
you know each other.
♪
- So what do we talk about?
- I don't know.
I've never cheated
on anyone before.
Me neither.
Well, as long as we're here,
we might as well talk
about your recovery.
There's a detox treatment,
it's called buprenorphine.
Bupawhat?
It makes it easier
to come off the stronger stuff.
It also eases the pain.
That's just the first step.
What's the second?
You need to talk to someone.
I'm pretty sure
that if I told a shrink
about the secret government
agency I work with,
they would have me
committed.
Nikita, any news
on our shapeshifting friend?
Well, he came here
for a show,
and you guys
are giving him nothing.
We need him
to accomplish his mission,
force him to exit.
What do you have in mind?
Kiss her.
Are you joking?
Michael, jokes are funny.
We're on a mission.
Okay, be a good, little spy,
and kiss her.
♪
It's okay.
Just when I thought
this couldn't get
any more uncomfortable.
She ratchets it
to a whole new level.
♪
Gotcha.
Birkhoff,
do you have an image?
Yeah, but it's not
gonna do much good.
He's gonna change up his look
to screw
with my street cam algorithms.
I'm gonna have
to do this manual.
Call it out.
Get ready to adjust
your image for tan raincoat.
I lost him.
12th and Bennett.
Probably went out the front.
Got him.
He just hopped in a cab
off Bennett.
Following him now.
Birkhoff, you got him?
I'm on the leader.
Go.
Go, go, go.
Okay, he's at 69th,
just off Amsterdam Ave.
523 69th Street,
Apartment One.
Got it.
He's transmitting directly
to an I.P. address
in Quebec City.
Pulling the coordinates now.
He's all yours.
Oh, yeah.
Hey.
Ready for your close-up?
Birkhoff, got some trash
for pickup.
You guys should be set.
Wish I was going with you.
You should be here.
Birkhoff's gonna need someone
to watch his back
when he starts
the deactivation.
Who watches the Watchman?
Did you kick him
in the peeping Toms?
Yeah.
Speaking of, there are
a lot more photos on this
than we actually thought.
Eww. What?
Well, he's got
a couple shots
of you proposing to me
in Tribeca.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
After I took ten showers,
I was thinking it might
actually be a nice keepsake.
Can you give this to Ryan?
Yes, absolutely.
Hey.
I know it's been
a rough day,
but we'll talk
about your relapse
when I get back, okay?
- Be careful.
- Okay.
It's a two-hour flight
to Quebec City.
You can change
on the plane.
Michael, do you think
I'm obsessed?
What?
With getting Amanda.
That was our fake fight.
I'm having trouble
keeping track.
Yeah, Amanda
knows how to hurt us
more than anyone else.
I know that I won't be able
to breathe easy
until she's gone.
I just have this feeling
that something's gonna happen.
Something.
To Sonya?
Hey.
Nikita, we can't control
the future.
What's important is,
whatever happens,
we face it together.
That's all
that matters to me.
Let's finish this.
We can't wait.
We can't wait any longer.
We've got to start
this thing now.
Nikita and Michael
aren't in position yet.
They're an hour outside
Amanda's location.
Deactivation takes
three hours.
Let's get this thing going.
Okay, we haven't I.D.'ed
the second mole yet.
We can't wait for that.
What if the mole
has a check-in time?
We don't know.
We don't even know
if the mole is real.
All I know,
the kill chip is active.
I need to make it
the other way.
Where do you want
to do this?
Sublevel 12.
Whoa,
Amanda's old torture room?
Yeah, nobody goes down there.
We won't be bothered.
How long will our suspects
be occupied?
Four hours, tops.
Do it.
If anyone leaves,
I'll deal with them.
I've got your back.
Okay, I'm freaking out.
Why are you
not freaking out?
I don't see
how that would help.
I'm focusing on the plan.
There's gotta be another way
we can do this
that doesn't involve
risking your life.
We've already narrowed down
the list of suspects to four.
They're under surveillance.
So you can finally disable
this damn thing in my head.
How can you be so sure
this is gonna work?
I'm about to let you poke
at my brain with a needle.
Apparently I trust you.
Okay, come on.
Make yourself comfortable.
Okay, just lean forward.
Just like that.
Looks scary.
Actually,
it's a very, uh...
A simple procedure.
Okay.
Now just relax.
Just...
stay calm.
Take deep breaths.
Okay, now this is just
a local anesthetic.
A slight pinch.
Gonna need you to hold
very still.
Whatever you say,
Dr. Birkhoff.
I'm supposed to keep
asking you questions
to make sure your brain's
functioning properly.
I think the sarcasm quadrant
is working just fine.
Ask away.
Are you serious?
Anything to distract me.
Okay.
Um...
What are you gonna be
for Halloween this year?
A princess.
Oh, a princess, huh?
Leia?
Zelda.
I knew
you were gonna be Zelda.
Well,
then why'd you say Leia?
Because it distracted you.
Didn't it?
Hard part's over.
Agh, damn it!
Stupid cart.
That looks serious.
- I'm gonna go to medical.
- Right.
Server room.
Yes, this is Alex.
Is Baker there?
I've got a question.
You just missed him.
He's headed to medical.
Accidentally cut himself.
Did Baker come by here?
I don't see anything.
Movement, second left.
Ah.
Now I can't get
a clear shot.
We're gonna have to go inside,
up close and personal.
We can't risk breach until
Sonya's chip is deactivated.
Birkhoff,
how is she?
47% and climbing.
You always did like
the recruits, didn't you?
Your friend Marcel
contacted Ari.
He's willing to meet,
but only if you're there.
- Where?
- Serbia.
I've got a Netjet waiting
for you at the local airport.
I hate Serbia.
But at least I'll get
some work done on the plane.
Lost?
Cut myself.
Going to medical.
You're about 12 floors off.
What does Amanda have on you?
What does she have?
She has my loyalty.
She's always had it.
You're the traitor here,
and traitors die.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
What the hell's
going on out there?
It was Baker
in the server room
with the candlestick.
Baker, really?
Dude had skills.
I never liked him.
Guy was a douche bag.
You should call Nikki,
tell her the good news.
Is it green for Amanda?
We're at 72%.
So the mole is down,
but the chip is active?
- Correct.
- Where are we at?
- 72%.
- Minutes, Alex.
Nikita.
B, how many minutes?
Eh, five, six?
Five or six.
Is it five, or is it six?
Nikita, look.
She's out of pocket.
Change of plan.
She's on the move.
We're on the move.
Damn it.
- You're too close.
- We can't lose her.
That's strange.
The weather inside Division
hasn't changed at all.
That's good, right?
I mean, there's been
no refresh in the data,
no update at all.
It's done.
It's done?
Seymour?
You're safe.
Nikita, chip is down.
We're green to strike.
It's Nikita.
How did she--
Birkhoff!
What are you doing?
They're shooting at us.
Wait!
Grenade!
Anne, stop.
Do not kill her.
Michael.
Are you okay?
My arm's stuck.
Anne!
Nikita, just go.
No, the tank's gonna blow.
I know, I want you to live.
Just go, please.
I love you.
Damn it, just go!
Aghh!
Michael.
We gotta go,
it's gonna blow.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==