1
00:00:00,760 --> 00:00:02,954
Well it's a pleasure
to be here, ladies.

2
00:00:03,008 --> 00:00:04,575
I didn't think
anybody really cared

3
00:00:04,577 --> 00:00:06,611
about my time
on the city council.

4
00:00:06,613 --> 00:00:09,280
Oh, we do. I mean,
you are such an inspiration.

5
00:00:09,282 --> 00:00:11,315
Still going strong
at 82.

6
00:00:13,652 --> 00:00:15,419
How old is that handkerchief?

7
00:00:15,421 --> 00:00:17,171
Well, it's not a handkerchief.
It's a receipt.

8
00:00:17,173 --> 00:00:18,656
[Groans]

9
00:00:18,658 --> 00:00:21,959
Paula Horke was Pawnee's
first female city councilor

10
00:00:21,961 --> 00:00:24,545
40 years ago, and she was
a huge inspiration to me.

11
00:00:24,547 --> 00:00:26,597
Women have come a long way
in Pawnee,

12
00:00:26,599 --> 00:00:28,549
but we still have
quite a ways to go.

13
00:00:28,551 --> 00:00:30,968
I mean, technically,
I'm not allowed to reserve

14
00:00:30,970 --> 00:00:34,472
this conference room without my
husband or father's signature.

15
00:00:34,474 --> 00:00:37,608
Government was a real
boys' club back in the '70s.

16
00:00:37,610 --> 00:00:39,193
They smoked their cigars,

17
00:00:39,195 --> 00:00:40,511
they snapped my bra,

18
00:00:40,513 --> 00:00:42,363
wore mirrors on their shoes

19
00:00:42,365 --> 00:00:43,397
to look up my skirt.

20
00:00:43,399 --> 00:00:44,899
Well, I am happy
to report

21
00:00:44,901 --> 00:00:47,318
that it is now a pervert-free
people's club.

22
00:00:47,320 --> 00:00:49,320
Well,
except for Councilman Dexhart,

23
00:00:49,322 --> 00:00:50,905
who's a self-described pervert.

24
00:00:50,907 --> 00:00:53,374
Yeah, and didn't Milton
try to kiss you?

25
00:00:53,376 --> 00:00:55,076
Well, yeah,
things aren't perfect.

26
00:00:55,078 --> 00:00:58,246
All the other councilmen
used to keep a calendar

27
00:00:58,248 --> 00:00:59,513
of my menstrual cycle.

28
00:00:59,515 --> 00:01:01,031
Are you kidding me?

29
00:01:01,033 --> 00:01:03,751
That is horrible.
They don't do that to me.

30
00:01:03,753 --> 00:01:05,136
Do they do that to me?

31
00:01:05,138 --> 00:01:07,338
I once tried
to start a commission

32
00:01:07,340 --> 00:01:10,007
to try to get more jobs
for women in city government,

33
00:01:10,009 --> 00:01:11,475
and they dismissed me,

34
00:01:11,477 --> 00:01:13,844
saying that it was because it
was just my time of the month.

35
00:01:13,846 --> 00:01:16,347
Admittedly,
they were right.

36
00:01:16,349 --> 00:01:17,982
Because of the calendar.

37
00:01:17,984 --> 00:01:19,684
Manpigs.
All of them.

38
00:01:19,686 --> 00:01:21,769
You know what, I'm gonna get
that commission going,

39
00:01:21,771 --> 00:01:24,238
because this inequality
has gone on long enough.

40
00:01:24,240 --> 00:01:26,223
You know what, I think
men are better than women.

41
00:01:26,225 --> 00:01:27,608
She's kidding.

42
00:01:27,610 --> 00:01:29,777
No, I'm not.
They provide for us,

43
00:01:29,779 --> 00:01:32,380
and we must obey them
because they are our masters.

44
00:01:32,382 --> 00:01:33,881
April, stop it.

45
00:01:33,883 --> 00:01:37,668
Leslie, you'll never land a
beau with that domineering tone.

46
00:01:37,670 --> 00:01:39,220
We must always walk
behind the men.

47
00:01:39,722 --> 00:01:40,537
Sheugh.

48
00:01:40,539 --> 00:01:44,258
[Triumphant music]

49
00:01:44,260 --> 00:01:49,016
<font color="#ff8c00">Sync & corrections by Alice</font>
<font color="#ff8c00">www.addic7ed.com</font>

50
00:02:00,725 --> 00:02:03,277
Both: Moustache!
Dumb-dumb!

51
00:02:03,279 --> 00:02:04,695
Moustache!
Dumb-dumb!

52
00:02:04,697 --> 00:02:05,896
- Hello.
- I just came

53
00:02:05,898 --> 00:02:08,249
to drop off some
of the employee--

54
00:02:08,251 --> 00:02:10,001
What is happening?

55
00:02:10,003 --> 00:02:11,719
The girls are on break,

56
00:02:11,721 --> 00:02:13,404
and their sitter
had to go out of town

57
00:02:13,406 --> 00:02:15,339
for the day,
so I'm watching them

58
00:02:15,341 --> 00:02:16,340
while Diane works.

59
00:02:16,342 --> 00:02:18,292
I borrowed some markers
from Leslie

60
00:02:18,294 --> 00:02:20,211
and some stickers
from Leslie

61
00:02:20,213 --> 00:02:24,548
and a Lite-Brite
which I got from Andy.

62
00:02:24,550 --> 00:02:25,883
Girls, this is Ann.

63
00:02:25,885 --> 00:02:29,303
Talk to Ann.
She's terrific.

64
00:02:29,305 --> 00:02:31,389
Hey, dudettes.

65
00:02:31,391 --> 00:02:34,392
You stoked about the weekend?
No.

66
00:02:34,394 --> 00:02:37,928
Oh, look at this pwetty,
pwetty wittle beads.

67
00:02:37,930 --> 00:02:39,563
They're not infants.

68
00:02:39,565 --> 00:02:41,932
I don't know.
I'm weird with kids.

69
00:02:41,934 --> 00:02:46,120
So you guys like Coldplay?

70
00:02:46,122 --> 00:02:47,271
You're weird.

71
00:02:47,273 --> 00:02:49,106
You're...

72
00:02:50,742 --> 00:02:53,160
Well, hey, girls.

73
00:02:53,162 --> 00:02:54,161
No.

74
00:02:54,163 --> 00:02:56,247
Okay.
Thanks.

75
00:02:56,249 --> 00:03:00,251
An equal gender
employment commission.

76
00:03:00,253 --> 00:03:02,970
Leslie, I don't think
this is a good idea.

77
00:03:02,972 --> 00:03:04,889
I think it's a fantastic idea.

78
00:03:04,891 --> 00:03:06,123
Oh.
[Laughs]

79
00:03:06,125 --> 00:03:07,624
I didn't know where you
were going with that.

80
00:03:07,626 --> 00:03:10,127
The lack of women
in this government is criminal.

81
00:03:10,129 --> 00:03:11,795
I'm gonna
ask each department

82
00:03:11,797 --> 00:03:14,231
to send two people
to a meeting today.

83
00:03:14,233 --> 00:03:15,766
- Yeah!
- And!

84
00:03:15,768 --> 00:03:18,402
And--and I can ask
Shauna Malwae-Tweep

85
00:03:18,404 --> 00:03:19,854
to write an article
about it

86
00:03:19,856 --> 00:03:20,855
for the <i>Pawnee Journal.</i>

87
00:03:20,857 --> 00:03:22,639
She's my special friend.

88
00:03:22,641 --> 00:03:24,024
That's what you're
calling her now.

89
00:03:24,026 --> 00:03:25,826
I don't know
what to call her.

90
00:03:25,828 --> 00:03:28,446
I don't entirely understand
the behavior of young people.

91
00:03:28,448 --> 00:03:31,866
Recently, we engaged in
something called a "group hang."

92
00:03:31,868 --> 00:03:34,201
It was like a date, but there
were seven other people there.

93
00:03:34,203 --> 00:03:36,120
It was very confusing.

94
00:03:36,122 --> 00:03:38,456
I'm not really sure
what our label is.

95
00:03:38,458 --> 00:03:40,791
Labels can be bad,
but they can also be good.

96
00:03:40,793 --> 00:03:43,294
"Warning: Toxic bleach"
is a good label.

97
00:03:43,296 --> 00:03:47,181
Shauna Malwae-Tweep
has amazing dimples.

98
00:03:47,183 --> 00:03:49,433
- So the commission?
- Yes, right, the commission.

99
00:03:49,435 --> 00:03:51,404
- I'm gonna get that going right now.
- Great.

100
00:03:53,106 --> 00:03:55,189
Okay, I know this text
you sent me was a lie

101
00:03:55,191 --> 00:03:58,109
and Michael Stipe
is not actually here, correct?

102
00:03:58,111 --> 00:03:59,777
Correct.
That was a lie.

103
00:03:59,779 --> 00:04:00,895
Yeah, no,
I knew it was.

104
00:04:00,897 --> 00:04:03,197
I just couldn't
live with myself

105
00:04:03,199 --> 00:04:04,231
if it had been true.

106
00:04:04,233 --> 00:04:05,566
And that's
why I sent it.

107
00:04:05,568 --> 00:04:06,817
Where's free Skittles?

108
00:04:06,819 --> 00:04:07,902
Here you go, buddy.

109
00:04:07,904 --> 00:04:09,236
- [Laughs]
- Aw!

110
00:04:09,238 --> 00:04:10,287
He gets his thing?

111
00:04:10,289 --> 00:04:15,578
[Skittles clattering]

112
00:04:17,580 --> 00:04:18,862
Listen, I need you two

113
00:04:18,864 --> 00:04:21,916
to teach me everything
you know about basketball.

114
00:04:21,918 --> 00:04:23,818
Rent-A-Swag
is doing really well.

115
00:04:23,820 --> 00:04:27,171
I'm on track to turn a profit
in my third month.

116
00:04:27,173 --> 00:04:29,256
One problem: All the kids
that shop in the store

117
00:04:29,258 --> 00:04:31,041
are basketball crazy.

118
00:04:31,043 --> 00:04:32,092
It's all they talk about.

119
00:04:32,094 --> 00:04:33,594
I need to be able
to schmooze them,

120
00:04:33,596 --> 00:04:35,546
and I can't keep referring
to basketball players

121
00:04:35,548 --> 00:04:38,098
as "Khloe Kardashian's husband
and his friends."

122
00:04:38,100 --> 00:04:40,100
You're just the men
to help me out.

123
00:04:40,102 --> 00:04:42,520
One jock,
one geek who loves stats.

124
00:04:42,522 --> 00:04:43,737
I'll give you a few minutes

125
00:04:43,739 --> 00:04:45,356
to cancel the rest
of your plans for the day.

126
00:04:45,358 --> 00:04:47,691
No need. My only plan
was to buy Skittles.

127
00:04:48,944 --> 00:04:50,327
- [Exhales]
- Wow, Chris.

128
00:04:50,329 --> 00:04:54,865
Your gender equality commission
is a real sausage fest.

129
00:04:54,867 --> 00:04:56,233
Oh, my God.
You're kidding me.

130
00:04:56,235 --> 00:04:58,569
I just assumed
that some of the departments

131
00:04:58,571 --> 00:04:59,920
would send women.

132
00:04:59,922 --> 00:05:02,289
Oh, my God.

133
00:05:02,291 --> 00:05:03,374
I am part
of the problem.

134
00:05:03,376 --> 00:05:05,042
Excuse me, everyone.

135
00:05:05,044 --> 00:05:06,877
Did anyone notice
that there are no women

136
00:05:06,879 --> 00:05:08,596
on the Gender Equality Commission?

137
00:05:08,598 --> 00:05:11,015
Oh, there's a lady
right next to you.

138
00:05:11,017 --> 00:05:12,516
Oh, wait, no.

139
00:05:12,518 --> 00:05:14,385
It's just a very beautiful man.

140
00:05:14,387 --> 00:05:15,586
Yes, okay,
we are gonna need

141
00:05:15,588 --> 00:05:17,521
to rebalance this commission.

142
00:05:17,523 --> 00:05:19,723
Listen, you did a great job
setting it up

143
00:05:19,725 --> 00:05:21,392
and getting the snacks ready,

144
00:05:21,394 --> 00:05:22,926
but we'll take it
from here.

145
00:05:22,928 --> 00:05:24,979
Well, Councilman Milton,
I did put the snacks together,

146
00:05:24,981 --> 00:05:26,397
and they are delicious,
I must say,

147
00:05:26,399 --> 00:05:27,431
but that is not the point.

148
00:05:27,433 --> 00:05:30,284
Round of applause
for the girl.

149
00:05:30,286 --> 00:05:32,236
She has to leave
to get more snacks.

150
00:05:32,238 --> 00:05:33,737
No, I don't!
This is my commission!

151
00:05:33,739 --> 00:05:36,491
Ouch.
Why so ornery?

152
00:05:37,493 --> 00:05:39,778
It's not the 7th yet.

153
00:05:42,780 --> 00:05:44,415
Hm.

154
00:05:44,417 --> 00:05:46,083
Your shoes
are red now.

155
00:05:46,085 --> 00:05:47,968
- Yay.
- Hooray.

156
00:05:47,970 --> 00:05:49,920
- [Giggles]
- Hey!

157
00:05:49,922 --> 00:05:51,589
Both: Mommy!

158
00:05:51,591 --> 00:05:52,723
You survived, huh?

159
00:05:52,725 --> 00:05:54,227
Indeed, I did.

160
00:05:56,429 --> 00:05:57,845
How were they?
Really?

161
00:05:58,047 --> 00:05:59,730
Couldn't have
been better.

162
00:05:59,732 --> 00:06:01,932
We had a wonderful time.
Well, that's good.

163
00:06:01,934 --> 00:06:05,019
'Cause my sitter's
still out of town,

164
00:06:05,021 --> 00:06:07,488
so I really hate
to ask you this,

165
00:06:07,490 --> 00:06:10,724
but is there any way you
could take them again tomorrow?

166
00:06:10,726 --> 00:06:12,359
Of course.
I'd be delighted.

167
00:06:12,361 --> 00:06:14,194
You're a lifesaver.
Thank you.

168
00:06:14,196 --> 00:06:15,863
Girls, you wanna
spend another day with Ron?

169
00:06:15,865 --> 00:06:17,114
Both: Yeah!

170
00:06:25,006 --> 00:06:28,759
I believe one problem
with hiring women

171
00:06:28,761 --> 00:06:31,378
is that they're frail
and breakable.

172
00:06:31,380 --> 00:06:34,515
Is it possible you're thinking
about light bulbs?

173
00:06:34,517 --> 00:06:35,633
- Or your hip?
- Mm.

174
00:06:35,635 --> 00:06:38,269
If I were 300 years older, Councilman.

175
00:06:38,271 --> 00:06:41,355
Incoherent ramblings aside,
I've done some research,

176
00:06:41,357 --> 00:06:44,858
and the female employment rate
in government is abysmal.

177
00:06:44,860 --> 00:06:47,127
The number one offender:
Sanitation.

178
00:06:47,129 --> 00:06:48,779
All right!

179
00:06:48,781 --> 00:06:51,014
No, no, no,
stop celebrating.

180
00:06:51,016 --> 00:06:53,350
Why are there no female garbage
collectors, Steve?

181
00:06:53,352 --> 00:06:55,486
I don't know.
We hire women for other things.

182
00:06:55,488 --> 00:06:57,521
You have one woman,
and she's a secretary.

183
00:06:57,523 --> 00:06:59,856
And she's the best secretary we got,

184
00:06:59,858 --> 00:07:00,991
except for Dan.

185
00:07:00,993 --> 00:07:02,376
- Dan's awesome.
- Dan.

186
00:07:02,378 --> 00:07:04,044
Garbage collectors
make good wages,

187
00:07:04,046 --> 00:07:05,496
they have good benefits,

188
00:07:05,498 --> 00:07:08,699
and they are the smelly glue
that keeps this city together.

189
00:07:08,701 --> 00:07:09,700
You need
to hire more women.

190
00:07:09,702 --> 00:07:11,385
Not that many women apply,

191
00:07:11,387 --> 00:07:14,755
plus it's a very physically
demanding job.

192
00:07:14,757 --> 00:07:17,508
Your average woman
can't handle it.

193
00:07:17,510 --> 00:07:19,210
Oh, no?

194
00:07:20,212 --> 00:07:21,712
Okay,
so I took extensive notes

195
00:07:21,714 --> 00:07:23,230
on ways
to maximize our efficiency,

196
00:07:23,232 --> 00:07:25,265
because we can't be just
as good as the men.

197
00:07:25,267 --> 00:07:26,567
We have to be better.

198
00:07:26,569 --> 00:07:28,152
Yeah, you're totally right.
Let's rock this.

199
00:07:28,154 --> 00:07:29,770
April, I love you,

200
00:07:29,772 --> 00:07:31,238
but I don't
need your sarcasm right now.

201
00:07:31,240 --> 00:07:33,073
I'm serious.
Let's get rolling.

202
00:07:33,075 --> 00:07:34,525
I wanna get
into some garbage.

203
00:07:34,527 --> 00:07:35,609
[Knocks on metal]

204
00:07:35,611 --> 00:07:37,945
What? I love garbage.

205
00:07:37,947 --> 00:07:40,280
You ever found a dead body
in the trash?

206
00:07:40,282 --> 00:07:41,582
Or body parts?

207
00:07:41,584 --> 00:07:42,733
Like, a torso
or a head?

208
00:07:42,735 --> 00:07:44,118
Please say head.

209
00:07:44,120 --> 00:07:46,403
Hey, Dewey.
Leslie brought binders.

210
00:07:46,405 --> 00:07:47,738
[Laughter]

211
00:07:47,740 --> 00:07:48,789
What do they say?

212
00:07:48,791 --> 00:07:50,507
"Pick up garbage.
Put in truck"?

213
00:07:50,509 --> 00:07:52,042
[Chuckling]
Actually, yeah.

214
00:07:52,044 --> 00:07:53,577
That's what's in the binder
on every page

215
00:07:53,579 --> 00:07:55,045
because I believe
in being thorough.

216
00:07:55,047 --> 00:07:56,880
- All right.
- Okay.

217
00:07:56,882 --> 00:07:58,349
Let's do it,
trash people!

218
00:07:58,351 --> 00:07:59,683
Whoo!

219
00:05:15,185 --> 00:05:16,885
Let's feed the beast!

220
00:08:05,288 --> 00:08:06,472
Here you are.

221
00:08:06,474 --> 00:08:08,691
I had to search the directory
for quite a while.

222
00:08:08,693 --> 00:08:11,443
I thought your last name
was Hanson for some reason.

223
00:08:11,445 --> 00:08:13,998
No, it's Perkins.
Always has been.

224
00:08:15,600 --> 00:08:17,016
You seem more
like a Hanson.

225
00:08:17,318 --> 00:08:19,568
Anyway, I have
the girls again today,

226
00:08:19,570 --> 00:08:21,186
and they're asking
to play with you.

227
00:08:21,188 --> 00:08:22,855
Really?
I thought they hated me.

228
00:08:22,857 --> 00:08:24,123
No, the opposite.

229
00:08:24,125 --> 00:08:25,491
I don't know
what you did to 'em,

230
00:08:25,493 --> 00:08:27,409
but it worked
like gangbusters.

231
00:08:27,411 --> 00:08:28,577
Or they do hate me,

232
00:08:28,579 --> 00:08:30,830
and you're just desperate
and tired.

233
00:08:30,832 --> 00:08:32,531
Either way,
can you help me?

234
00:08:32,533 --> 00:08:34,283
I'm out of activities,
and they're playing

235
00:08:34,285 --> 00:08:35,718
with my land mine.

236
00:08:35,720 --> 00:08:37,136
[Giggling]

237
00:08:37,138 --> 00:08:39,638
This thing's cool.
What are these things?

238
00:08:41,258 --> 00:08:43,926
Let's play
a word association game.

239
00:08:43,928 --> 00:08:46,095
I'll say a word,
and then you say the first thing

240
00:08:46,097 --> 00:08:47,146
that pops
into your mind.

241
00:08:47,148 --> 00:08:49,381
- Okay.
- You.

242
00:08:49,383 --> 00:08:50,983
- Reporter.
- Me.

243
00:08:50,985 --> 00:08:52,935
- City manager.
- Us.

244
00:08:52,937 --> 00:08:56,555
Ooh! Magazine.

245
00:08:56,557 --> 00:08:58,440
- [Sighs]
- Oh!

246
00:08:58,442 --> 00:08:59,608
According to Leslie's binder,

247
00:08:59,610 --> 00:09:01,560
she and April are making
even better time

248
00:09:01,562 --> 00:09:03,061
than the guys do
on a normal day.

249
00:09:03,063 --> 00:09:04,196
Wow, that's weird.

250
00:09:04,198 --> 00:09:06,115
You know, with us
being women and all,

251
00:09:06,117 --> 00:09:08,000
you'd think our boobs
would get in the way.

252
00:09:08,002 --> 00:09:09,668
Is that accurate
Mr. Phlegner?

253
00:09:09,670 --> 00:09:12,070
Is Councilwoman Knope ahead
of the regular schedule for this route?

254
00:09:12,072 --> 00:09:14,907
Whatever.
No comment.

255
00:09:15,409 --> 00:09:16,876
- Tough stuff.
- Are you posing?

256
00:09:16,878 --> 00:09:18,794
I don't have a photographer
with me.

257
00:09:18,796 --> 00:09:20,129
Google Earth...

258
00:09:20,131 --> 00:09:21,547
Always taking pics.

259
00:09:21,549 --> 00:09:22,631
Let's move it out!

260
00:09:22,633 --> 00:09:24,416
All right, let's start
with the basics.

261
00:09:24,418 --> 00:09:26,018
Uh, why don't you just
play some one-on-one,

262
00:09:26,020 --> 00:09:27,019
see if you can score?

263
00:09:27,021 --> 00:09:28,521
Andy, guard him.

264
00:09:29,523 --> 00:09:31,056
Eh, he's too big.
I can't see over him.

265
00:09:31,058 --> 00:09:32,191
It's not fair.

266
00:09:32,193 --> 00:09:33,392
I feel like everyone
should be the same size.

267
00:09:33,394 --> 00:09:35,060
Okay, you have
to create space.

268
00:09:35,062 --> 00:09:36,929
You gotta just
dribble around him.

269
00:09:36,931 --> 00:09:38,364
- There you go.
- Now what?

270
00:09:38,366 --> 00:09:40,432
Shoot!
Shoot the ball.

271
00:09:40,834 --> 00:09:42,117
Did I do basketball?

272
00:09:42,319 --> 00:09:43,903
Kind of.

273
00:09:43,905 --> 00:09:45,307
Try it again.

274
00:09:52,244 --> 00:09:53,581
Tommy for the dunk!

275
00:09:57,550 --> 00:10:01,720
[Sighs]
[Screams]

276
00:10:01,722 --> 00:10:03,389
My screen!

277
00:10:04,557 --> 00:10:07,309
But it was actually
a blood-hungry witch

278
00:10:07,311 --> 00:10:09,795
who was wearing
their mom's face like a mask!

279
00:10:09,797 --> 00:10:11,296
[Shrieking]

280
00:10:11,298 --> 00:10:12,781
[Laughs]

281
00:10:12,783 --> 00:10:14,116
What is wrong
with you, woman?

282
00:10:14,118 --> 00:10:16,969
Sorry. I thought kids
liked ghost stories.

283
00:10:16,971 --> 00:10:19,021
Hey, girls! Did you wanna
look through my nurse kit?

284
00:10:19,023 --> 00:10:22,107
Both: Yeah!
- Ooh, check it out, bandages!

285
00:10:22,109 --> 00:10:23,242
We can wrap up the dolls,

286
00:10:23,244 --> 00:10:24,610
and pretend they just
had surgery.

287
00:10:24,612 --> 00:10:25,611
- Yeah!
- Awesome!

288
00:10:25,613 --> 00:10:27,029
Yeah, or we can
use this hammer

289
00:10:27,031 --> 00:10:28,146
and test reflexes.

290
00:10:28,148 --> 00:10:29,748
- Yeah!
- Here, Zoe, watch.

291
00:10:29,750 --> 00:10:31,650
- [Chuckles]
- Do me! Do me!

292
00:10:31,652 --> 00:10:33,619
- [Chuckles]
- Do Princess Junebug now!

293
00:10:33,621 --> 00:10:34,753
Okay.
You know what, Ron?

294
00:10:34,755 --> 00:10:35,821
I can watch them
for a little while,

295
00:10:35,823 --> 00:10:37,990
if you wanna...

296
00:10:37,992 --> 00:10:39,508
Take a break.

297
00:10:42,879 --> 00:10:45,163
This is
Stacy Knoblauch's house.

298
00:10:45,165 --> 00:10:46,215
I went to high school
with her,

299
00:10:46,217 --> 00:10:47,833
and she was super mean
to me,

300
00:10:47,835 --> 00:10:51,169
and now I know
that she dyes her hair.

301
00:10:51,171 --> 00:10:53,840
I knew that wench
wasn't naturally blonde.

302
00:10:54,842 --> 00:10:56,225
Oh, my God!

303
00:10:56,227 --> 00:10:59,612
She has to use
prescription-strength deodorant.

304
00:11:00,614 --> 00:11:02,815
This is the best day
of my life.

305
00:11:02,817 --> 00:11:04,900
Hey, ladies, someone
just called in a pickup.

306
00:11:04,902 --> 00:11:06,485
We have
to make an unscheduled stop.

307
00:11:06,487 --> 00:11:07,820
Hope you
can handle it.

308
00:11:07,822 --> 00:11:09,605
- It's not in the binders.
- A new challenge?

309
00:11:09,607 --> 00:11:11,023
Bring it on, Stevie boy.

310
00:11:11,025 --> 00:11:13,742
Whoo!
April, let's finish up!

311
00:11:13,744 --> 00:11:15,627
We have some stereotypes
to overcome.

312
00:11:15,629 --> 00:11:17,746
And some privacy
to violate!

313
00:11:17,748 --> 00:11:18,747
- Yeah!
- Whoo!

314
00:11:18,749 --> 00:11:20,532
[Bangs on truck]
Wait, no.

315
00:11:22,585 --> 00:11:24,803
- Oh!
- Yes!

316
00:11:24,805 --> 00:11:26,505
- Nothin' but net.
- Nice!

317
00:11:26,507 --> 00:11:28,507
You are officially a baller.

318
00:11:28,509 --> 00:11:30,042
I've been a baller
since birth, son.

319
00:11:30,044 --> 00:11:31,760
Now, I'm an athlete.

320
00:11:31,762 --> 00:11:34,229
Hey! You little chumps
wanna play some ball?

321
00:11:34,231 --> 00:11:36,065
- Sure.
- Let's do this.

322
00:11:36,067 --> 00:11:38,503
Watch out.
Tommy from half court.

323
00:11:41,105 --> 00:11:43,522
This could really only
go poorly.

324
00:11:52,916 --> 00:11:54,583
- He won't get out of my way!
- Tom--

325
00:11:59,339 --> 00:12:01,056
Oh, my God!

326
00:12:05,762 --> 00:12:07,096
- Yeah!
- Yes!

327
00:12:12,052 --> 00:12:13,135
Tom, what the hell
are you doing?

328
00:12:13,137 --> 00:12:14,603
I'm pivoting.
Ben told me to pivot.

329
00:12:14,605 --> 00:12:16,088
I told you you
<i>can</i> pivot,

330
00:12:16,090 --> 00:12:17,756
not that you
can <i>only</i> pivot.

331
00:12:17,758 --> 00:12:19,525
Stop pivoting!

332
00:12:19,527 --> 00:12:21,193
All right,
that's illegal.

333
00:12:21,195 --> 00:12:22,928
I may not know much,
but you can't just

334
00:12:22,930 --> 00:12:24,446
steal the ball
from another player.

335
00:12:24,448 --> 00:12:25,931
Hey, aren't you the guy
who owns Rent-A-Swag?

336
00:12:25,933 --> 00:12:29,034
- Yeah! Tom Haverford.
- You suck at basketball, man.

337
00:12:29,036 --> 00:12:31,436
Well, you suck
at being polite, sir.

338
00:12:31,438 --> 00:12:33,739
This has been fun, but we
have an actual game tomorrow

339
00:12:33,741 --> 00:12:36,108
against guys
who can actually play.

340
00:12:36,110 --> 00:12:37,576
Let's go.

341
00:12:37,578 --> 00:12:39,080
Andy Dwyer
for the dunk!

342
00:12:41,882 --> 00:12:43,999
Aw, that wall's so close.

343
00:12:44,001 --> 00:12:47,302
Doctors, the operation
is now complete.

344
00:12:47,304 --> 00:12:49,388
Doctor Zoe, could you
please use the reflex hammer

345
00:12:49,390 --> 00:12:50,622
to see if she's okay?

346
00:12:50,624 --> 00:12:53,926
This is the most fun
I have ever had with kids.

347
00:12:53,928 --> 00:12:55,177
They even said they
wanted to be doctors

348
00:12:55,179 --> 00:12:56,294
when they grow up.

349
00:12:56,296 --> 00:12:58,764
Hot tip for you baby-sitters
out there.

350
00:12:58,766 --> 00:13:01,483
Let your kids play
with medical tools all the time.

351
00:13:01,485 --> 00:13:02,801
- We have a problem.
- What?

352
00:13:02,803 --> 00:13:03,936
Oh, my God.

353
00:13:03,938 --> 00:13:05,971
Girls! This
is not a negotiation.

354
00:13:06,273 --> 00:13:08,407
- Unlock the door immediately.
- No!

355
00:13:08,409 --> 00:13:09,691
We're doing surgery!

356
00:13:09,693 --> 00:13:11,460
Only doctors
are allowed in here.

357
00:13:11,462 --> 00:13:13,078
Okay.

358
00:13:13,080 --> 00:13:14,646
Stand back, ladies!

359
00:13:14,648 --> 00:13:16,331
Ron, no, no, no, no!
That's dangerous!

360
00:13:16,333 --> 00:13:17,916
Somebody in here's
gotta have keys, right?

361
00:13:17,918 --> 00:13:19,084
I have keys.
Wha--

362
00:13:19,086 --> 00:13:20,169
Jerry.

363
00:13:20,171 --> 00:13:21,486
I never thought
I would say this,

364
00:13:21,488 --> 00:13:23,005
but I am so glad
you're here.

365
00:13:23,007 --> 00:13:25,207
Well, it's gotta be one
of these, right?

366
00:13:25,209 --> 00:13:27,292
[Clears throat]

367
00:13:27,294 --> 00:13:29,595
- Oh, no.
- Ladies, no, no, no, no, no!

368
00:13:29,597 --> 00:13:31,329
The patient
needs a haircut.

369
00:13:31,331 --> 00:13:32,764
Her hair is infected.

370
00:13:32,766 --> 00:13:33,849
- Hurry, Jerry!
- Okay, I'm trying.

371
00:13:33,851 --> 00:13:35,167
- It's not this one.
- No.

372
00:13:35,169 --> 00:13:37,335
Okay, I'm not good
under pressure like this.

373
00:13:37,337 --> 00:13:39,104
Zoe, stop it, please!

374
00:13:39,106 --> 00:13:42,024
- No!
- Zoe, put the scissors down.

375
00:13:42,026 --> 00:13:44,977
Oh!
[Groans]

376
00:13:44,979 --> 00:13:46,395
- [Gasps]
Both: No!

377
00:13:46,397 --> 00:13:49,114
[Giggling]

378
00:13:50,366 --> 00:13:51,733
Bakery called this in.

379
00:13:51,735 --> 00:13:53,819
Needs to go
on that truck right there.

380
00:13:53,821 --> 00:13:55,537
Ah, easy,
breezy, beautiful.

381
00:13:55,539 --> 00:13:57,456
That's the Covergirl slogan.
I didn't mean to say that.

382
00:13:57,458 --> 00:13:59,625
Okay, here we go!
On three!

383
00:13:59,627 --> 00:14:01,493
- Okay.
- One, two,

384
00:14:01,495 --> 00:14:03,695
three, move it.

385
00:14:03,697 --> 00:14:05,714
[Groans]

386
00:14:05,716 --> 00:14:07,365
On four, five, six,
here we go!

387
00:14:07,367 --> 00:14:08,696
[Sighs]

388
00:14:08,697 --> 00:14:09,468
- You need a hand?

389
00:14:09,470 --> 00:14:10,636
No, no,
we don't need a hand.

390
00:14:10,638 --> 00:14:13,088
What, you think Joan of Arc
needed a hand?

391
00:14:13,090 --> 00:14:14,640
- Doing what?
- Let me tell you something.

392
00:14:14,642 --> 00:14:15,891
We are not leaving

393
00:14:15,893 --> 00:14:19,211
until this symbolic feminist
obstacle is loaded

394
00:14:19,213 --> 00:14:21,096
onto that truck
of women's advancement,

395
00:14:21,098 --> 00:14:23,098
and you can put that
on the record, Shauna.

396
00:14:23,100 --> 00:14:25,267
Well, you ladies clearly
have everything in hand.

397
00:14:25,269 --> 00:14:26,818
Dewey and I
are gonna head back to base.

398
00:14:26,820 --> 00:14:27,936
Hope we didn't throw you
off schedule.

399
00:14:27,938 --> 00:14:30,222
- Not at all.
- Have fun!

400
00:14:30,224 --> 00:14:33,358
Hey, Shauna, maybe not
put this part on the record.

401
00:14:33,360 --> 00:14:35,060
You know, leave the earlier part
on the record,

402
00:14:35,062 --> 00:14:37,029
but if we can't get this fridge
onto the truck

403
00:14:37,031 --> 00:14:38,230
then maybe not
put that on the record,

404
00:14:38,232 --> 00:14:39,831
and then just
destroy the record altogether.

405
00:14:39,833 --> 00:14:41,200
Okay, guys,
I'm gonna go ahead

406
00:14:41,202 --> 00:14:43,401
and decide what's on
and off the record on my own.

407
00:14:43,403 --> 00:14:45,237
- Cool?
- Uhhuh.

408
00:14:45,739 --> 00:14:47,206
The whole city is watching.

409
00:14:47,208 --> 00:14:49,675
If I can't move that fridge
onto that truck,

410
00:14:49,677 --> 00:14:52,961
then feminism is over
in this town.

411
00:14:52,963 --> 00:14:54,680
[Groans]

412
00:14:59,219 --> 00:15:01,420
I don't know why I thought
sneaking up on it would work.

413
00:15:04,011 --> 00:15:05,610
This is the one.
This is-- Oh!

414
00:15:05,611 --> 00:15:07,944
Why do you
have so many keys?

415
00:15:07,946 --> 00:15:10,113
We did surgery
just like you taught us!

416
00:15:10,115 --> 00:15:11,331
Okay, you know what?

417
00:15:11,333 --> 00:15:13,200
Why don't you girls
clean up all this hair,

418
00:15:13,202 --> 00:15:14,417
and I'm gonna talk
to Ron.

419
00:15:14,419 --> 00:15:16,586
- Let's cut off our toes!
- No, let's not.

420
00:15:16,588 --> 00:15:18,939
I'm gonna take
this bag, too.

421
00:15:18,941 --> 00:15:20,207
You need
to fix this.

422
00:15:20,559 --> 00:15:22,375
It's not that bad.
Nobody got hurt.

423
00:15:22,377 --> 00:15:24,144
It's extremely bad!

424
00:15:24,146 --> 00:15:26,246
I love this woman,
and I just wanna show her

425
00:15:26,248 --> 00:15:28,215
that I'm capable
of watching her children

426
00:15:28,217 --> 00:15:30,934
without something
horrible happening.

427
00:15:30,936 --> 00:15:32,252
What?

428
00:15:32,254 --> 00:15:34,354
Did you just
say you love Diane?

429
00:15:34,356 --> 00:15:35,922
No.
I did not.

430
00:15:35,924 --> 00:15:38,441
Yes, you did!
That is so <i>cute!</i>

431
00:15:38,443 --> 00:15:39,726
For God's sake, Hanson,

432
00:15:39,728 --> 00:15:41,594
will you please focus
on the larger problem?

433
00:15:41,596 --> 00:15:43,263
[Mimicking kissing sounds]

434
00:15:43,265 --> 00:15:46,432
Both: Ron loves Mommy!

435
00:15:46,434 --> 00:15:48,735
Ron loves Mommy!

436
00:15:48,737 --> 00:15:51,454
Girls, girls, I don't know
what you think you heard,

437
00:15:51,456 --> 00:15:53,790
but please
don't tell your mother

438
00:15:53,792 --> 00:15:55,358
what you incorrectly
think you heard.

439
00:15:55,360 --> 00:15:57,460
- Ron loves--
all: Mommy!

440
00:15:57,462 --> 00:15:59,412
Ron loves Mommy!

441
00:15:59,414 --> 00:16:00,580
I love nothing!

442
00:16:00,582 --> 00:16:01,993
[Snickers]

443
00:16:03,785 --> 00:16:05,635
I'm gonna have to start
writing this up soon.

444
00:16:05,637 --> 00:16:07,387
Kinda sucks. I thought
maybe we'd be done in time

445
00:16:07,389 --> 00:16:08,555
- to grab a drink.
- Oh!

446
00:16:08,557 --> 00:16:10,140
Have you been
to Bistro d'Amour?

447
00:16:10,142 --> 00:16:11,975
- It's really romantic.
- Ooh.

448
00:16:11,977 --> 00:16:13,843
Yeah, it was just
gonna be you and me,

449
00:16:13,845 --> 00:16:15,395
my sister,
a few people from work,

450
00:16:15,397 --> 00:16:16,513
and my ex-boyfriend.

451
00:16:16,515 --> 00:16:19,015
[Laughs]
That's really confusing.

452
00:16:19,017 --> 00:16:20,367
I have a request.

453
00:16:20,369 --> 00:16:21,651
Could you
please make sure

454
00:16:21,653 --> 00:16:24,321
that my involvement in this
stays off the record?

455
00:16:24,323 --> 00:16:26,356
I wouldn't want anyone thinking
that you're biased

456
00:16:26,358 --> 00:16:28,658
because we're something.

457
00:16:28,660 --> 00:16:30,110
You don't have
to worry about that.

458
00:16:30,112 --> 00:16:31,278
I'm gonna
include a disclaimer

459
00:16:31,280 --> 00:16:34,080
describing the nature
of our relationship.

460
00:16:34,082 --> 00:16:35,982
I guess I'll have to wait
for tomorrow's paper

461
00:16:35,984 --> 00:16:37,834
to find out our status.

462
00:16:37,836 --> 00:16:39,252
Why did I have
to fall for somebody

463
00:16:39,254 --> 00:16:40,620
from the old media?

464
00:16:41,789 --> 00:16:44,441
Maybe we should just
eat the refrigerator.

465
00:16:44,443 --> 00:16:46,209
We start chewing now,
we can finish

466
00:16:46,211 --> 00:16:47,544
before the sun
comes up.

467
00:16:47,546 --> 00:16:49,546
We have
to solve this problem,

468
00:16:49,548 --> 00:16:51,181
or they are going to point
to this forever

469
00:16:51,183 --> 00:16:52,799
as a reason
to not hire women.

470
00:16:53,301 --> 00:16:54,634
I should never
have taken the bait.

471
00:16:54,636 --> 00:16:59,189
It was just such tasty,
righteously-flavored bait.

472
00:16:59,191 --> 00:17:01,691
[Sighs]
You here to move the fridge?

473
00:17:01,693 --> 00:17:03,393
- Are you a ghost?
- Yes, we are.

474
00:17:03,395 --> 00:17:05,545
Why you think
you can lift it?

475
00:17:05,547 --> 00:17:07,397
You are two little canaries.

476
00:17:07,399 --> 00:17:09,783
Those garbagemen
couldn't even lift it.

477
00:17:09,785 --> 00:17:12,068
They are
like giant bears.

478
00:17:12,070 --> 00:17:13,370
Hold on.
What do you mean?

479
00:17:13,372 --> 00:17:15,455
Bears are bigger
than canaries, yes?

480
00:17:15,457 --> 00:17:17,073
So if bears
can't lift the--

481
00:17:17,075 --> 00:17:19,192
No, I understand animal sizes.

482
00:17:19,194 --> 00:17:20,877
What do you mean
they couldn't lift it?

483
00:17:20,879 --> 00:17:23,163
They tried three days ago,

484
00:17:23,165 --> 00:17:24,798
and it does not budge.

485
00:17:24,800 --> 00:17:26,833
They say they're gonna
come back with more guys,

486
00:17:26,835 --> 00:17:28,635
but they come back
with canaries.

487
00:17:28,637 --> 00:17:30,639
Fly away,
little canaries.

488
00:17:33,141 --> 00:17:36,142
Those Sanitation goons
set us up.

489
00:17:36,144 --> 00:17:37,543
You know what?
Let's just go.

490
00:17:37,545 --> 00:17:38,645
What?
No!

491
00:17:38,647 --> 00:17:39,712
We can't let them
beat us.

492
00:17:39,714 --> 00:17:40,764
Just call it a tie.

493
00:17:40,766 --> 00:17:42,215
Nobody can lift it.

494
00:17:42,217 --> 00:17:44,184
No, Leslie,
we do not want to tie.

495
00:17:44,186 --> 00:17:45,518
We want to win.

496
00:17:45,520 --> 00:17:47,070
Those guys suck, okay?

497
00:17:47,072 --> 00:17:48,321
We have
to prove them wrong.

498
00:17:48,323 --> 00:17:50,407
Look, all we have to do
is get some PCP.

499
00:17:50,409 --> 00:17:52,359
You can move anything
on angel dust.

500
00:17:52,361 --> 00:17:54,361
My cousin Hesen, he beat off
five cops on that stuff.

501
00:17:54,363 --> 00:17:55,695
Okay, hold on.
Sir!

502
00:17:55,697 --> 00:17:57,614
Does this refrigerator
still work?

503
00:17:57,616 --> 00:18:00,066
Works okay.
We got a new one.

504
00:18:00,068 --> 00:18:01,751
We don't need it.

505
00:18:03,404 --> 00:18:04,621
So what if those kids

506
00:18:04,623 --> 00:18:05,872
think you're the lamest guy
in the world?

507
00:18:05,874 --> 00:18:08,508
That's not who you want shopping
at Rent-A-Swag anyways, Tom.

508
00:18:08,510 --> 00:18:10,543
That's exactly who I want
shopping at Rent-A-Swag.

509
00:18:10,545 --> 00:18:12,578
Oh, well, then,
that sucks.

510
00:18:12,580 --> 00:18:15,099
Look, I wanna
show you something.

511
00:18:18,803 --> 00:18:20,637
Okay, this is Kevin Durant
and Russell Westbrook

512
00:18:20,639 --> 00:18:22,105
after a bad loss.

513
00:18:22,107 --> 00:18:23,523
Even the greats
get beat,

514
00:18:23,525 --> 00:18:25,308
but they get back
out there the next day,

515
00:18:25,310 --> 00:18:26,976
and they fight.

516
00:18:26,978 --> 00:18:28,978
So let's hit the gym again
tomorrow.

517
00:18:28,980 --> 00:18:31,597
Guys, I think I just
dribbled up an idea.

518
00:18:31,599 --> 00:18:33,533
No, double dribbled it.

519
00:18:33,535 --> 00:18:36,437
Yeah, you have learned nothing
about basketball.

520
00:18:37,439 --> 00:18:38,938
You're a good friend, Ben.

521
00:18:38,940 --> 00:18:39,989
Oh, thanks.

522
00:18:40,491 --> 00:18:41,658
Can I borrow $1,500?

523
00:18:41,660 --> 00:18:44,744
You're not allowed
to ask what it's for.

524
00:18:44,746 --> 00:18:46,079
Fireworks.

525
00:18:46,081 --> 00:18:48,415
First of all,
everyone is fine.

526
00:18:48,417 --> 00:18:51,584
No one got hurt,
but there was an incident.

527
00:18:51,586 --> 00:18:53,788
Oh, my God.
What happened?

528
00:18:55,790 --> 00:18:58,124
[Exhales]
Diane, this is all my fault.

529
00:18:58,126 --> 00:18:59,959
I let them go
into my nurse's bag.

530
00:18:59,961 --> 00:19:01,794
[Laughs]

531
00:19:01,796 --> 00:19:03,263
[Chuckles]

532
00:19:03,265 --> 00:19:05,231
Well, who has been
having fun with scissors?

533
00:19:05,233 --> 00:19:06,232
Us!

534
00:19:06,234 --> 00:19:08,068
Ann taught us
how to be doctors!

535
00:19:08,070 --> 00:19:10,136
- Yay!
- You're not mad?

536
00:19:10,138 --> 00:19:11,804
No, it's fine.
They're kids.

537
00:19:11,806 --> 00:19:13,606
Once, Zoe put Ivy
in the dryer, so...

538
00:19:13,608 --> 00:19:15,442
I'm still incredibly sorry.

539
00:19:15,444 --> 00:19:16,943
I feel like
I let you down.

540
00:19:16,945 --> 00:19:20,613
It is so sweet to me
how much you care.

541
00:19:20,615 --> 00:19:22,832
This is why I love you.

542
00:19:22,834 --> 00:19:23,983
Oh.

543
00:19:23,985 --> 00:19:27,320
Well, I love you, too.

544
00:19:27,322 --> 00:19:28,488
[Laughs]

545
00:19:28,490 --> 00:19:29,923
That's my cue.

546
00:19:29,925 --> 00:19:31,324
All right, girls,
good hang.

547
00:19:31,326 --> 00:19:32,792
Both: Bye, Ann!
- Thanks, Ann.

548
00:19:32,794 --> 00:19:33,826
Oh.

549
00:19:34,528 --> 00:19:35,545
Hey, Leslie!

550
00:19:35,547 --> 00:19:37,547
Shauna just
sent me the disclaimer

551
00:19:37,549 --> 00:19:39,665
that she's gonna use
before she prints the article.

552
00:19:39,667 --> 00:19:40,934
"City manager Chris Traeger

553
00:19:40,936 --> 00:19:42,635
"was present
for this event,

554
00:19:42,637 --> 00:19:45,338
and has a personal relationship
with the author."

555
00:19:45,340 --> 00:19:46,689
Okay, that's
pretty good, right?

556
00:19:46,691 --> 00:19:47,774
"Personal relationship."

557
00:19:47,776 --> 00:19:49,893
It's not romantic.

558
00:19:49,895 --> 00:19:51,844
But it is descriptive.
No, it's not even descriptive.

559
00:19:51,846 --> 00:19:53,196
I know you're not used
to this,

560
00:19:53,198 --> 00:19:55,815
but maybe you should just try
to keep it chill

561
00:19:55,817 --> 00:19:57,150
and see what happens.

562
00:19:57,152 --> 00:19:58,568
Great advice.

563
00:19:58,570 --> 00:19:59,869
Impossible to follow,

564
00:19:59,871 --> 00:20:01,687
but great advice.

565
00:20:01,689 --> 00:20:03,523
So do you think
the soup kitchen

566
00:20:03,525 --> 00:20:04,624
could use that fridge?

567
00:20:04,626 --> 00:20:06,692
I mean, April and I
were gonna haul it

568
00:20:06,694 --> 00:20:09,195
onto the truck effortlessly,
but if you need it...

569
00:20:09,197 --> 00:20:10,914
Absolutely.
This is a godsend.

570
00:20:10,916 --> 00:20:12,665
Thank you
for thinking of us.

571
00:20:12,667 --> 00:20:13,800
Grab a side, ladies.

572
00:20:13,802 --> 00:20:16,085
I think all of us
can get it on the truck.

573
00:20:16,087 --> 00:20:18,221
Not only did we
complete the garbage route

574
00:20:18,223 --> 00:20:20,140
and move an unmovable fridge,

575
00:20:20,142 --> 00:20:21,508
but the Sanitation department

576
00:20:21,510 --> 00:20:24,544
hired three new
female trash-haulers.

577
00:20:24,546 --> 00:20:26,312
And, best of all,

578
00:20:26,314 --> 00:20:27,564
April gave me this present

579
00:20:27,566 --> 00:20:29,901
to commemorate
our feminist victory.

580
00:20:33,020 --> 00:20:34,655
And it's trash.

581
00:20:35,157 --> 00:20:36,823
It's filled
with trash.

582
00:20:36,825 --> 00:20:38,525
Maybe there's something
on the bottom here.

583
00:20:38,527 --> 00:20:40,160
Let me see--
No, just trash.

584
00:20:41,039 --> 00:20:44,257
This is Brandon Turnbill
for <i>Kids' 46 News.</i>

585
00:20:44,541 --> 00:20:47,927
I'm here with the star
of today's win, Josh Diamond.

586
00:20:47,945 --> 00:20:49,729
What was the key
to the victory, Josh?

587
00:20:49,763 --> 00:20:51,197
Well, uh, everything just
came together for us,

588
00:20:51,231 --> 00:20:52,481
and we came out
on top,

589
00:20:52,533 --> 00:20:54,033
and we're gonna try
to keep it going next week

590
00:20:54,067 --> 00:20:55,384
against Snerling.

591
00:20:55,435 --> 00:20:56,835
Thanks, tiny reporter.

592
00:20:56,854 --> 00:20:58,855
It was a huge win
for Josh and the boys,

593
00:20:58,889 --> 00:21:00,189
and after a huge win,

594
00:21:00,224 --> 00:21:04,060
be sure to visit Rent-A-Swag
on Durham Avenue

595
00:21:04,111 --> 00:21:06,928
for all your post-game press
conference fashion rental needs.

596
00:21:07,111 --> 00:21:08,228
We've got everything:

597
00:21:08,411 --> 00:21:10,128
Dope suits,
pocket squares,

598
00:21:10,311 --> 00:21:12,328
Gingham shirts,
glasses with no lenses,

599
00:21:12,811 --> 00:21:14,428
Tiny cardigans,
Fedoras...

600
00:21:14,911 --> 00:21:16,000
Look at this watch!

601
00:21:16,001 --> 00:21:17,535
Whatever swag you need,

602
00:21:17,553 --> 00:21:19,670
You can rent
at Rent-A-Swag.

603
00:21:19,704 --> 00:21:21,039
Now, that's basketball.

604
00:21:21,040 --> 00:21:24,039
<font color="#ff8c00">Sync & corrections by Alice</font>
<font color="#ff8c00">www.addic7ed.com</font>

1
00:00:00,760 --> 00:00:02,954
女士們 我很高興能來這裏

2
00:00:03,008 --> 00:00:04,575
沒想到會有人關注

3
00:00:04,577 --> 00:00:06,611
我曾經在議會裏的表現

4
00:00:06,613 --> 00:00:09,280
我們都關注 你簡直是個楷模

5
00:00:09,282 --> 00:00:11,315
82歲還老當益壯

6
00:00:13,652 --> 00:00:15,419
你那手帕用多少年了

7
00:00:15,421 --> 00:00:17,171
這不是手帕 是收據

8
00:00:18,658 --> 00:00:22,559
40年前 Paula Horke是Pawnee第一位女市議員

9
00:00:22,561 --> 00:00:24,545
她給了我很大的鼓舞

10
00:00:24,547 --> 00:00:26,597
女性在Pawnee的革命之路走了一大半

11
00:00:26,599 --> 00:00:28,549
但還有一大半要走

12
00:00:28,551 --> 00:00:31,468
理論上說 我連訂這件會議室

13
00:00:31,470 --> 00:00:34,472
都需要我父親或丈夫的簽名

14
00:00:34,474 --> 00:00:37,608
70年代的政府就是個男人俱樂部

15
00:00:37,610 --> 00:00:39,193
他們抽雪茄

16
00:00:39,195 --> 00:00:40,511
解開我胸罩

17
00:00:40,513 --> 00:00:42,363
在鞋上裝鏡子

18
00:00:42,365 --> 00:00:43,397
好偷看我裙底

19
00:00:43,399 --> 00:00:44,899
我能很高興地告訴你

20
00:00:44,901 --> 00:00:47,318
現在的政府是沒有變態 人人盡歡的地方

21
00:00:47,320 --> 00:00:49,320
除了議員Dexhart之外

22
00:00:49,322 --> 00:00:50,905
他都自認是變態

23
00:00:50,907 --> 00:00:53,374
對啊 Milton不是也試過想親你

24
00:00:53,376 --> 00:00:55,076
對 世事無完美

25
00:00:55,078 --> 00:00:59,513
以前所有的議員都會記錄我的月經週期

26
00:00:59,515 --> 00:01:01,031
真的嗎

27
00:01:01,033 --> 00:01:03,751
真可怕 他們沒對我這麼幹過

28
00:01:03,753 --> 00:01:05,136
他們也對我這麼幹嗎

29
00:01:05,138 --> 00:01:07,338
我曾想建立一個委員會

30
00:01:07,340 --> 00:01:10,007
讓政府雇用更多的女性

31
00:01:10,009 --> 00:01:11,475
結果被他們駁回了

32
00:01:11,477 --> 00:01:13,844
說我是姨媽來了

33
00:01:13,846 --> 00:01:16,347
誠然姨媽的部分是對的

34
00:01:16,349 --> 00:01:17,982
有日曆為證

35
00:01:17,984 --> 00:01:19,684
他們都是豬

36
00:01:19,686 --> 00:01:21,769
你猜怎麼著 我要把這委員會建起來

37
00:01:21,771 --> 00:01:24,238
不平等存在太久了

38
00:01:24,240 --> 00:01:26,223
我覺得男人比女人強

39
00:01:26,225 --> 00:01:27,608
她在開玩笑

40
00:01:27,610 --> 00:01:29,777
我沒有 他們給我們提供物質生活

41
00:01:29,779 --> 00:01:32,380
我們必須服從他們 因為他們是主人

42
00:01:32,382 --> 00:01:33,881
April 停下來

43
00:01:33,883 --> 00:01:37,668
Leslie 你說話這麼專橫可釣不了金龜婿

44
00:01:37,670 --> 00:01:39,220
我們必須走在男人後面

45
00:01:42,969 --> 00:01:44,258
<font color="#2894FF">第五季第十集：垃圾部門的女人</font>

46
00:01:44,560 --> 00:01:45,816
<font color="#2894FF">翻譯 Matt</font>

47
00:02:00,725 --> 00:02:04,695
鬍子 鬍子

48
00:02:04,697 --> 00:02:08,249
- 你好啊
- 我只是來送些雇員

49
00:02:08,251 --> 00:02:10,001
發生了什麼事

50
00:02:10,003 --> 00:02:11,719
女孩們放假了

51
00:02:11,721 --> 00:02:13,404
保姆今天要出門

52
00:02:13,406 --> 00:02:15,339
所以Diane在工作的時候

53
00:02:15,341 --> 00:02:16,340
我來照看她們

54
00:02:16,342 --> 00:02:18,292
我從Leslie那借了些記號筆

55
00:02:18,294 --> 00:02:20,211
和一些貼紙

56
00:02:20,213 --> 00:02:24,548
還有從Andy那拿來的點陣畫圖

57
00:02:24,550 --> 00:02:25,883
女孩們 這是Ann

58
00:02:25,885 --> 00:02:29,303
跟Ann聊聊 她人很好哦

59
00:02:29,305 --> 00:02:31,389
嘿 姐妹們

60
00:02:31,391 --> 00:02:34,392
週末噢是不是high爆了 不對

61
00:02:34,394 --> 00:02:37,928
哇 看這串珠子好漂漂哦

62
00:02:37,930 --> 00:02:39,563
她們不是嬰兒

63
00:02:39,565 --> 00:02:41,932
我不知道怎麼跟小孩相處

64
00:02:41,934 --> 00:02:46,120
那你們喜歡Coldplay不

65
00:02:46,122 --> 00:02:47,271
你很古怪

66
00:02:47,273 --> 00:02:49,106
你才

67
00:02:50,742 --> 00:02:53,160
哇你們好啊

68
00:02:53,162 --> 00:02:54,161
不要

69
00:02:54,163 --> 00:02:56,247
好吧

70
00:02:56,249 --> 00:03:00,251
一個性別平等就業委員會

71
00:03:00,253 --> 00:03:02,970
Leslie 我不覺得這是個好主意

72
00:03:02,972 --> 00:03:04,889
我覺得這是個超棒的主意

73
00:03:04,891 --> 00:03:06,123
噢

74
00:03:06,125 --> 00:03:07,624
還以為你要說什麼呢

75
00:03:07,626 --> 00:03:10,127
這政府太缺乏女性了

76
00:03:10,129 --> 00:03:11,795
我會叫每個部門

77
00:03:11,797 --> 00:03:14,231
今天派兩個人來開會

78
00:03:14,233 --> 00:03:15,766
還有

79
00:03:15,768 --> 00:03:18,402
我可以叫Shauna Malwae-Tweep

80
00:03:18,404 --> 00:03:20,855
在Pawnee Journal上對此寫一篇報導

81
00:03:20,857 --> 00:03:22,639
她是我很特別的朋友

82
00:03:22,641 --> 00:03:24,024
你現在這樣叫她拉

83
00:03:24,026 --> 00:03:25,826
我不知道該怎麼稱呼她

84
00:03:25,828 --> 00:03:28,446
我不太瞭解年輕人的做法

85
00:03:28,448 --> 00:03:31,866
最近 我們參加了一個叫群聚的活動

86
00:03:31,868 --> 00:03:34,201
有點像約會 但旁邊還有7個人

87
00:03:34,203 --> 00:03:36,120
非常令人疑惑

88
00:03:36,122 --> 00:03:38,456
我不太清楚我們屬於哪類關係

89
00:03:38,458 --> 00:03:40,791
標籤有時是不好 但有時又很好

90
00:03:40,793 --> 00:03:43,294
警告 有毒漂白劑 就是個好標籤

91
00:03:43,296 --> 00:03:47,181
Shauna Malwae-Tweep酒窩很好看

92
00:03:47,183 --> 00:03:49,433
- 那委員會如何
- 對 委員會

93
00:03:49,435 --> 00:03:51,404
- 我馬上著手
- 好極了

94
00:03:53,106 --> 00:03:55,189
好吧 我就知道這短信是騙我的

95
00:03:55,191 --> 00:03:58,109
Michael Stipe不在這是吧
（R.E.M.樂隊）

96
00:03:58,111 --> 00:03:59,777
沒錯 那是騙人的

97
00:03:59,779 --> 00:04:00,895
我就知道

98
00:04:00,897 --> 00:04:04,231
我只是怕萬一是真的我會含恨終生

99
00:04:04,233 --> 00:04:05,566
所以我才這麼做

100
00:04:05,568 --> 00:04:06,817
免費的彩虹糖在哪

101
00:04:06,819 --> 00:04:07,902
那給你

102
00:04:09,238 --> 00:04:10,287
他就拿到他想要的了

103
00:04:17,580 --> 00:04:18,862
聽著 我要你們

104
00:04:18,864 --> 00:04:21,916
把所有籃球知識教給我

105
00:04:21,918 --> 00:04:23,818
氣場出租生意很好

106
00:04:23,820 --> 00:04:27,171
應該第三個月就盈利

107
00:04:27,173 --> 00:04:29,256
只有一個問題 來店裏的小孩

108
00:04:29,258 --> 00:04:31,041
都超愛籃球

109
00:04:31,043 --> 00:04:32,092
一天到晚都在說籃球

110
00:04:32,094 --> 00:04:33,594
我得能跟他們閒聊

111
00:04:33,596 --> 00:04:35,546
又不能總把籃球運動員叫成

112
00:04:35,548 --> 00:04:38,098
Khloe Kardashian的老公和他的朋友

113
00:04:38,100 --> 00:04:40,100
你們是我的最佳選擇

114
00:04:40,102 --> 00:04:42,520
一個運動少年 一個喜歡統計的書呆子

115
00:04:42,522 --> 00:04:43,737
我給你們幾分鐘

116
00:04:43,739 --> 00:04:45,356
把今天的其他活動都取消了

117
00:04:45,358 --> 00:04:47,691
不用了 我的唯一計畫就是去買彩虹糖

118
00:04:48,944 --> 00:04:50,327
哇Chris

119
00:04:50,329 --> 00:04:54,865
你的性別平等委員會全是男的

120
00:04:54,867 --> 00:04:56,233
天啊怎麼搞的

121
00:04:56,235 --> 00:04:59,920
我只是想說有些部門會讓女性來

122
00:04:59,922 --> 00:05:02,289
天啊

123
00:05:02,291 --> 00:05:03,374
我就是問題的一部分

124
00:05:03,376 --> 00:05:05,042
不好意思各位

125
00:05:05,044 --> 00:05:06,877
你們注意到沒

126
00:05:06,879 --> 00:05:08,596
性別平等委員會裏面沒有女人

127
00:05:08,598 --> 00:05:11,015
你旁邊不就是一女的

128
00:05:11,017 --> 00:05:12,516
噢等下不對

129
00:05:12,518 --> 00:05:14,385
只是一個很漂亮的男人

130
00:05:14,387 --> 00:05:17,521
好了 我們要重新調整這個委員會

131
00:05:17,523 --> 00:05:19,723
聽著 你初期工作做得不錯

132
00:05:19,725 --> 00:05:21,392
還準備了零食

133
00:05:21,394 --> 00:05:22,926
但接下來就由我們接手

134
00:05:22,928 --> 00:05:24,979
議員Milton 是我準備的零食

135
00:05:24,981 --> 00:05:26,397
它們也確實很好吃

136
00:05:26,399 --> 00:05:27,431
但重點不在這

137
00:05:27,433 --> 00:05:30,284
大家為這女的鼓掌

138
00:05:30,286 --> 00:05:32,236
她要離開了 去拿更多零食

139
00:05:32,238 --> 00:05:33,737
我才不走 這是我的委員會

140
00:05:33,739 --> 00:05:36,491
脾氣怎麼這麼暴躁

141
00:05:37,493 --> 00:05:39,778
又還沒到7號

142
00:05:44,417 --> 00:05:46,083
你的鞋子變紅色了

143
00:05:46,085 --> 00:05:47,968
- 嘢
- 萬歲

144
00:05:47,970 --> 00:05:49,920
嘿

145
00:05:49,922 --> 00:05:51,589
媽咪

146
00:05:51,591 --> 00:05:52,723
你活下來了

147
00:05:52,725 --> 00:05:54,227
沒錯

148
00:05:56,429 --> 00:05:57,845
她們表現如何 說真的

149
00:05:58,047 --> 00:05:59,730
不能再好

150
00:05:59,732 --> 00:06:01,932
- 我們過得很愉快
- 噢很好啊

151
00:06:01,934 --> 00:06:05,019
因為我的保姆還沒回來

152
00:06:05,021 --> 00:06:07,488
雖然我很不想這樣做

153
00:06:07,490 --> 00:06:10,724
但你明天還能照看她們嗎

154
00:06:10,726 --> 00:06:12,359
當然 我很高興

155
00:06:12,361 --> 00:06:14,194
你救了我一命 謝謝

156
00:06:14,196 --> 00:06:15,863
孩子們 想再和Ron玩一天嗎

157
00:06:15,865 --> 00:06:17,114
嘢

158
00:06:25,006 --> 00:06:28,759
我覺得雇用女人的問題之一

159
00:06:28,761 --> 00:06:31,378
就是她們太脆弱了

160
00:06:31,380 --> 00:06:34,515
你是在想著電燈泡吧

161
00:06:34,517 --> 00:06:35,633
或者你的腰

162
00:06:35,635 --> 00:06:38,269
嗯 如果我再老300歲的話

163
00:06:38,271 --> 00:06:41,355
就別胡說八道了 我做了些調查

164
00:06:41,357 --> 00:06:44,858
這政府的女性雇用率糟透了

165
00:06:44,860 --> 00:06:47,127
首要問題部門是衛生部

166
00:06:47,129 --> 00:06:48,779
嘢

167
00:06:48,781 --> 00:06:51,014
不不 別慶祝

168
00:06:51,016 --> 00:06:53,350
為什麼沒有女性收垃圾人員呢Steve

169
00:06:53,352 --> 00:06:55,486
不知道 我們雇用女人幹別的事情

170
00:06:55,488 --> 00:06:57,521
你們只請了一個女的 做秘書

171
00:06:57,523 --> 00:06:59,856
而她是我們最好的秘書

172
00:06:59,858 --> 00:07:00,991
除了Dan之外

173
00:07:00,993 --> 00:07:02,376
Dan最好了

174
00:07:02,378 --> 00:07:04,044
垃圾收集員工資好

175
00:07:04,046 --> 00:07:05,496
福利好

176
00:07:05,498 --> 00:07:08,699
而且是維護城市的重要人員

177
00:07:08,701 --> 00:07:09,700
你們要請多點女人

178
00:07:09,702 --> 00:07:11,385
沒多少女人申請

179
00:07:11,387 --> 00:07:14,755
而且這職位需要體力

180
00:07:14,757 --> 00:07:17,508
你們一般女性做不來

181
00:07:17,510 --> 00:07:19,210
喔真的嗎

182
00:07:20,212 --> 00:07:21,712
好了 我記了很多筆記

183
00:07:21,714 --> 00:07:23,230
好讓我們能最高效工作

184
00:07:23,232 --> 00:07:25,265
因為我們不止要和男人一樣好

185
00:07:25,267 --> 00:07:26,567
我們要做得比他們更好

186
00:07:26,569 --> 00:07:28,152
你說的沒錯 來吧

187
00:07:28,154 --> 00:07:29,770
April 我愛你

188
00:07:29,772 --> 00:07:31,238
但現在不要來諷刺我

189
00:07:31,240 --> 00:07:33,073
我是認真的 來幹吧

190
00:07:33,075 --> 00:07:34,525
我想跳進垃圾堆裏

191
00:07:35,611 --> 00:07:37,945
幹嘛 我喜歡垃圾

192
00:07:37,947 --> 00:07:40,280
你在垃圾裏發現過屍體沒

193
00:07:40,282 --> 00:07:41,582
或者屍體的一部分

194
00:07:41,584 --> 00:07:42,733
像四肢啊 或者頭

195
00:07:42,735 --> 00:07:44,118
拜託告訴我出現過頭

196
00:07:44,120 --> 00:07:46,403
嘿Dewey Leslie帶文件夾過來了

197
00:07:47,740 --> 00:07:48,789
寫著什麼呢

198
00:07:48,791 --> 00:07:50,507
撿起垃圾 放進貨車

199
00:07:50,509 --> 00:07:52,042
沒錯

200
00:07:52,044 --> 00:07:53,577
那文件夾裏每一頁都這麼寫的

201
00:07:53,579 --> 00:07:55,045
因為我堅信做事要徹底

202
00:07:55,047 --> 00:07:56,880
好吧

203
00:07:56,882 --> 00:07:58,349
動起來 垃圾人士

204
00:07:59,400 --> 00:08:01,000
來把這車喂飽

205
00:08:05,288 --> 00:08:06,472
你在這呢

206
00:08:06,474 --> 00:08:08,691
我在地址錄裏面找了好一陣

207
00:08:08,693 --> 00:08:11,443
不知為何以為你姓Hanson

208
00:08:11,445 --> 00:08:13,998
不 從來都是Perkins 

209
00:08:15,600 --> 00:08:17,016
你看起來更像個Hanson

210
00:08:17,318 --> 00:08:19,568
不管怎樣 我今天又要看小孩

211
00:08:19,570 --> 00:08:21,186
她們說想和你玩

212
00:08:21,188 --> 00:08:22,855
真的嗎 我以為她們討厭我

213
00:08:22,857 --> 00:08:24,123
沒有 正相反

214
00:08:24,125 --> 00:08:25,491
我都不知道你施了什麼魔法

215
00:08:25,493 --> 00:08:27,409
非常有效

216
00:08:27,411 --> 00:08:28,577
或者她們確實討厭我

217
00:08:28,579 --> 00:08:30,830
而你是又絕望又累

218
00:08:30,832 --> 00:08:32,531
那你要不要幫我

219
00:08:32,533 --> 00:08:34,283
我想不出活動了

220
00:08:34,285 --> 00:08:35,718
她們在玩我的地雷

221
00:08:37,138 --> 00:08:39,638
這東西好酷 是什麼啊

222
00:08:41,258 --> 00:08:43,926
我們來玩字詞聯想遊戲

223
00:08:43,928 --> 00:08:46,095
我說一個詞 你說出腦裏

224
00:08:46,097 --> 00:08:47,146
想到的第一個詞

225
00:08:47,148 --> 00:08:49,381
- 好
- 你

226
00:08:49,383 --> 00:08:50,983
- 記者
- 我

227
00:08:50,985 --> 00:08:52,935
- 市執行長
- 我們

228
00:08:52,937 --> 00:08:56,555
噢 雜誌

229
00:08:58,442 --> 00:08:59,608
根據Leslie的文件夾

230
00:08:59,610 --> 00:09:03,061
她和April比正常情況下男的幹活更快

231
00:09:03,063 --> 00:09:04,196
哇 那就怪了

232
00:09:04,198 --> 00:09:06,115
我們還是女人呢

233
00:09:06,117 --> 00:09:08,000
還以為我們的胸部會是個問題呢

234
00:09:08,002 --> 00:09:09,668
她們說得對嗎 Phlegner先生

235
00:09:09,670 --> 00:09:12,070
Knope議員做得比這路線的正常時間表要快

236
00:09:12,072 --> 00:09:14,907
隨便拉 不評論

237
00:09:15,409 --> 00:09:16,876
- 挺棘手的
- 你是在擺姿勢嗎

238
00:09:16,878 --> 00:09:18,794
我沒帶攝影師

239
00:09:18,796 --> 00:09:20,129
Google地球

240
00:09:20,131 --> 00:09:21,547
永遠都在拍照

241
00:09:21,549 --> 00:09:22,631
走吧

242
00:09:22,633 --> 00:09:24,416
好了 先從基本開始

243
00:09:24,418 --> 00:09:26,018
來打一對一好了

244
00:09:26,020 --> 00:09:27,019
看你能不能進球

245
00:09:27,021 --> 00:09:28,521
Andy 防好

246
00:09:29,523 --> 00:09:31,056
呃 他身軀龐大 我都看不見前面

247
00:09:31,058 --> 00:09:32,191
不公平

248
00:09:32,193 --> 00:09:33,392
我覺得大家都應該一樣大

249
00:09:33,394 --> 00:09:35,060
你要製造空間

250
00:09:35,062 --> 00:09:36,929
你要繞著他帶球

251
00:09:36,931 --> 00:09:38,364
- 這就對了
- 然後呢

252
00:09:38,366 --> 00:09:40,432
投球

253
00:09:40,834 --> 00:09:42,117
我剛才是在打籃球嗎

254
00:09:42,319 --> 00:09:43,903
有點像

255
00:09:43,905 --> 00:09:45,307
再試試

256
00:09:52,244 --> 00:09:53,581
Tommy扣球

257
00:10:01,722 --> 00:10:03,389
我的螢幕

258
00:10:04,557 --> 00:10:07,309
但它其實是嗜血的巫婆

259
00:10:07,311 --> 00:10:09,795
拿她們媽媽的臉皮當面具戴著

260
00:10:12,783 --> 00:10:14,116
你是有什麼毛病

261
00:10:14,118 --> 00:10:16,969
對不起 我以為小孩子喜歡鬼故事

262
00:10:16,971 --> 00:10:19,021
嘿 你們想不想看我的護士裝備

263
00:10:19,023 --> 00:10:22,107
- 好嘢
- 噢看這個 繃帶

264
00:10:22,109 --> 00:10:23,242
我們可以把娃娃卷起來

265
00:10:23,244 --> 00:10:24,610
假裝它們剛做完手術

266
00:10:24,612 --> 00:10:25,611
嘢 好棒

267
00:10:25,613 --> 00:10:27,029
或者我們可以用這小錘子

268
00:10:27,031 --> 00:10:28,146
來測試反射

269
00:10:28,148 --> 00:10:29,748
- 嘢
- 來 Zoe 看著

270
00:10:29,750 --> 00:10:31,650
該我了

271
00:10:31,652 --> 00:10:33,619
給六月蟲公主試試

272
00:10:33,621 --> 00:10:34,753
好 喂Ron

273
00:10:34,755 --> 00:10:35,821
我可以照看她們一陣子

274
00:10:35,823 --> 00:10:37,990
如果你想

275
00:10:37,992 --> 00:10:39,508
休息一下的話

276
00:10:42,879 --> 00:10:45,163
這裏是Stacy Knoblauch的房子

277
00:10:45,165 --> 00:10:46,215
我們高中同校

278
00:10:46,217 --> 00:10:47,833
她對我很惡毒

279
00:10:47,835 --> 00:10:51,169
而現在我知道她的頭髮是染的

280
00:10:51,171 --> 00:10:53,840
就知道她不是天然金髮

281
00:10:54,842 --> 00:10:56,225
天啊

282
00:10:56,227 --> 00:10:59,612
她還要用醫用強度的除臭劑

283
00:11:00,614 --> 00:11:02,815
這真是我生命中最美好的一天

284
00:11:02,817 --> 00:11:04,900
女士們 剛有人打電話要我們收東西

285
00:11:04,902 --> 00:11:06,485
我們要多走一站

286
00:11:06,487 --> 00:11:07,820
希望你們沒問題

287
00:11:07,822 --> 00:11:09,605
- 你文件夾裏沒記錄的哦
- 新的挑戰嗎

288
00:11:09,607 --> 00:11:11,023
來吧 Stevie小朋友

289
00:11:11,025 --> 00:11:13,742
April 來吧

290
00:11:13,744 --> 00:11:15,627
我們要打破對女人的刻板印象

291
00:11:15,629 --> 00:11:17,746
還要去侵犯些隱私

292
00:11:18,749 --> 00:11:20,532
等等 不對

293
00:11:24,805 --> 00:11:26,505
不錯嘛

294
00:11:26,507 --> 00:11:28,507
你正式變為成功球員了

295
00:11:28,509 --> 00:11:30,042
哥從來都成功

296
00:11:30,044 --> 00:11:31,760
現在 我是名運動員了

297
00:11:31,762 --> 00:11:34,229
嘿 你們幾個小孩想打球不

298
00:11:34,231 --> 00:11:36,065
- 好啊
- 來吧

299
00:11:36,067 --> 00:11:38,503
看招 Tommy從半場來

300
00:11:41,105 --> 00:11:43,522
這只能往壞發展

301
00:11:52,916 --> 00:11:54,583
- 他不肯讓開
- Tom--

302
00:11:59,339 --> 00:12:01,056
天啊

303
00:12:12,052 --> 00:12:13,135
Tom你在幹嘛啊

304
00:12:13,137 --> 00:12:14,603
我在旋轉 Ben叫我旋轉

305
00:12:14,605 --> 00:12:16,088
我說你可以旋轉

306
00:12:16,090 --> 00:12:17,756
不是叫你只旋轉

307
00:12:17,758 --> 00:12:19,525
別轉了

308
00:12:19,527 --> 00:12:21,193
好了 剛才是犯規吧

309
00:12:21,195 --> 00:12:22,928
我是不太懂 但你不能

310
00:12:22,930 --> 00:12:24,446
從別人那偷球吧

311
00:12:24,448 --> 00:12:25,931
嘿 你不是氣場出租的店主嗎

312
00:12:25,933 --> 00:12:29,034
- 對 Tom Haverford
- 你球技很爛啊同學

313
00:12:29,036 --> 00:12:31,436
你也很沒禮貌 先生

314
00:12:31,438 --> 00:12:33,739
玩玩還挺有趣 但我們明天有真的比賽

315
00:12:33,741 --> 00:12:36,108
要和真的會打的人對決

316
00:12:36,110 --> 00:12:37,576
走吧

317
00:12:37,578 --> 00:12:39,080
Andy Dwyer來扣球

318
00:12:41,882 --> 00:12:43,999
啊 那堵牆好靠近

319
00:12:44,001 --> 00:12:47,302
醫生 手術完成

320
00:12:47,304 --> 00:12:49,388
醫生Zoe 你用反射錘

321
00:12:49,390 --> 00:12:50,622
看看她是否一切正常

322
00:12:50,624 --> 00:12:53,926
我和小孩子玩得最開心就是今天了

323
00:12:53,928 --> 00:12:56,294
她們還說長大了想當醫生

324
00:12:56,296 --> 00:12:58,764
給你們這些保姆一點建議

325
00:12:58,766 --> 00:13:01,483
讓你的小孩玩醫學用品

326
00:13:01,485 --> 00:13:02,801
- 出問題了
- 什麼

327
00:13:02,803 --> 00:13:03,936
天啊

328
00:13:03,938 --> 00:13:05,971
女孩們 我不是開玩笑的

329
00:13:06,273 --> 00:13:08,407
- 馬上把門打開
- 不要

330
00:13:08,409 --> 00:13:09,691
我們在做手術

331
00:13:09,693 --> 00:13:11,460
只有醫生才能進來

332
00:13:11,462 --> 00:13:13,078
好吧

333
00:13:13,080 --> 00:13:14,646
站後點

334
00:13:14,648 --> 00:13:16,331
Ron 不要 好危險

335
00:13:16,333 --> 00:13:17,916
總有人有鑰匙吧

336
00:13:17,918 --> 00:13:19,084
我有鑰匙

337
00:13:19,086 --> 00:13:20,169
Jerry

338
00:13:20,171 --> 00:13:21,486
從沒想過我會這麼說

339
00:13:21,488 --> 00:13:23,005
但我很慶倖你在這

340
00:13:23,007 --> 00:13:25,207
就在這一大串裏面

341
00:13:27,294 --> 00:13:29,595
噢 不要啊

342
00:13:29,597 --> 00:13:31,329
病人要剪頭髮

343
00:13:31,331 --> 00:13:32,764
她的頭髮被感染了

344
00:13:32,766 --> 00:13:33,849
- 快點啊Jerry
- 我在努力了

345
00:13:33,851 --> 00:13:35,167
不是這把

346
00:13:35,169 --> 00:13:37,335
我不擅長在重壓下做事

347
00:13:37,337 --> 00:13:39,104
Zoe 停下來 拜託

348
00:13:39,106 --> 00:13:42,024
- 不要啊
- Zoe 把剪刀放下

349
00:13:50,366 --> 00:13:51,733
麵包房通知我們的

350
00:13:51,735 --> 00:13:53,819
要搬上那輛貨車

351
00:13:53,821 --> 00:13:55,537
啊 簡單輕鬆又漂亮

352
00:13:55,539 --> 00:13:57,456
那是封面女郎彩妝的廣告語 我不是故意的

353
00:13:57,458 --> 00:13:59,625
好了 來 數三聲

354
00:13:59,627 --> 00:14:01,493
一 二

355
00:14:01,495 --> 00:14:03,695
三 用力

356
00:14:05,716 --> 00:14:07,365
四 五 六 用力

357
00:14:08,697 --> 00:14:09,468
要幫忙嗎

358
00:14:09,470 --> 00:14:10,636
不需要

359
00:14:10,638 --> 00:14:13,088
你覺得聖女貞德會需要幫忙嗎

360
00:14:13,090 --> 00:14:14,640
- 看哪方面了（need a hand雙關）
- 我告訴你

361
00:14:14,642 --> 00:14:17,291
在這個象徵女權主義阻礙物的冰箱

362
00:14:17,293 --> 00:14:19,211
被搬上那女性進步之車之前

363
00:14:19,213 --> 00:14:21,096
我們是不會走的

364
00:14:21,098 --> 00:14:23,098
你可以把這段記錄下來 Shauna

365
00:14:23,100 --> 00:14:25,267
女士們顯然很有把握

366
00:14:25,269 --> 00:14:26,818
Dewey和我就先回總部了

367
00:14:26,820 --> 00:14:27,936
希望我們沒耽誤你的時間表

368
00:14:27,938 --> 00:14:30,222
- 一點不會
- 玩開心點

369
00:14:30,224 --> 00:14:33,358
嘿Shauna 也許別把這部分放進去

370
00:14:33,360 --> 00:14:35,060
把前面那段寫好

371
00:14:35,062 --> 00:14:37,029
但如果我們不能把冰箱移到車上

372
00:14:37,031 --> 00:14:38,230
就別寫這段了

373
00:14:38,232 --> 00:14:39,831
然後再把整篇都丟了

374
00:14:39,833 --> 00:14:43,401
好了 我會自行決定要寫什麼

375
00:14:43,403 --> 00:14:45,237
好嗎

376
00:14:45,739 --> 00:14:47,206
整個城市都在觀望

377
00:14:47,208 --> 00:14:49,675
如果我不能把冰箱移到車上

378
00:14:49,677 --> 00:14:52,961
那這城市的女權主義算毀了

379
00:14:59,219 --> 00:15:01,420
我怎會以為偷襲它會有用

380
00:15:04,011 --> 00:15:05,610
就是這把了

381
00:15:05,611 --> 00:15:07,944
你怎麼會有這麼多鑰匙

382
00:15:07,946 --> 00:15:10,113
我們像你教的那樣做手術了

383
00:15:10,115 --> 00:15:11,331
好了 你知道嗎

384
00:15:11,333 --> 00:15:13,200
你們何不把這些頭髮清理下

385
00:15:13,202 --> 00:15:14,417
我和Ron聊一下

386
00:15:14,419 --> 00:15:16,586
- 我們來把腳趾剪了吧
- 不 不要

387
00:15:16,588 --> 00:15:18,939
這包我也要拿走

388
00:15:18,941 --> 00:15:20,207
你要搞定它

389
00:15:20,559 --> 00:15:22,375
也沒很糟糕 沒人受傷

390
00:15:22,377 --> 00:15:24,144
這超級無敵糟糕

391
00:15:24,146 --> 00:15:26,246
我愛這女人 我想讓她看看

392
00:15:26,248 --> 00:15:28,215
我能照看她的小孩

393
00:15:28,217 --> 00:15:30,934
而不讓壞事發生

394
00:15:30,936 --> 00:15:32,252
什麼

395
00:15:32,254 --> 00:15:34,354
你剛才說你愛Diane嗎

396
00:15:34,356 --> 00:15:35,922
我沒有

397
00:15:35,924 --> 00:15:38,441
你有 好可愛啊

398
00:15:38,443 --> 00:15:39,726
天啊 Hanson

399
00:15:39,728 --> 00:15:41,594
就不能關注下更大的問題

400
00:15:43,265 --> 00:15:48,735
Ron愛媽咪

401
00:15:48,737 --> 00:15:51,454
女孩們 我不管你們以為自己聽到了啥

402
00:15:51,456 --> 00:15:53,790
但別把你們聽錯的資訊

403
00:15:53,792 --> 00:15:55,358
告訴你們的媽媽

404
00:15:55,360 --> 00:15:57,460
- Ron愛
- 媽咪

405
00:15:57,462 --> 00:15:59,412
Ron愛媽咪

406
00:15:59,414 --> 00:16:00,580
我什麼都不愛

407
00:16:03,785 --> 00:16:05,635
我快要開始寫稿了

408
00:16:05,637 --> 00:16:07,387
真不爽 還以為能按時完成

409
00:16:07,389 --> 00:16:08,555
- 然後去喝杯酒
- 噢

410
00:16:08,557 --> 00:16:10,140
你去過d'Amour小餐館沒

411
00:16:10,142 --> 00:16:11,975
- 好浪漫的
- 噢

412
00:16:11,977 --> 00:16:13,843
對啊 就只有我們兩個人

413
00:16:13,845 --> 00:16:15,395
我姐姐 幾個同事

414
00:16:15,397 --> 00:16:16,513
和我前男友

415
00:16:16,515 --> 00:16:19,015
真讓人迷惑

416
00:16:19,017 --> 00:16:20,367
我有個請求

417
00:16:20,369 --> 00:16:21,651
你能確保

418
00:16:21,653 --> 00:16:24,321
不記錄我的參與過程嗎

419
00:16:24,323 --> 00:16:26,956
我不想讓別人以為因為我們的關係

420
00:16:26,958 --> 00:16:28,658
讓你有所偏袒

421
00:16:28,660 --> 00:16:30,110
你不用擔心

422
00:16:30,112 --> 00:16:31,278
我會加上一條免責聲明

423
00:16:31,280 --> 00:16:34,080
用來描述我們的關係

424
00:16:34,082 --> 00:16:35,982
我想我要等看明天的報紙

425
00:16:35,984 --> 00:16:37,834
才知道我們走到哪一步了

426
00:16:37,836 --> 00:16:39,252
為什麼我要喜歡一個

427
00:16:39,254 --> 00:16:40,620
在舊媒體工作的人

428
00:16:41,789 --> 00:16:44,441
也許我們應該把這冰箱吃了

429
00:16:44,443 --> 00:16:47,544
現在開始嚼，天亮前該能嚼完

430
00:16:47,546 --> 00:16:49,546
我們一定要解決這問題

431
00:16:49,548 --> 00:16:51,181
不然他們永遠都會把這

432
00:16:51,183 --> 00:16:52,799
當作不雇用女人的藉口

433
00:16:53,301 --> 00:16:54,634
我不該上鉤的

434
00:16:54,636 --> 00:16:59,189
但那誘餌實在是太美味了

435
00:16:59,191 --> 00:17:01,691
你來移冰箱嗎

436
00:17:01,693 --> 00:17:03,393
- 你是鬼嗎
- 我們是來移冰箱的

437
00:17:03,395 --> 00:17:05,545
你怎想你能移

438
00:17:05,547 --> 00:17:07,397
你們就是兩金絲雀

439
00:17:07,399 --> 00:17:09,783
那些收垃圾的都移不動

440
00:17:09,785 --> 00:17:12,068
他們就像大熊一樣

441
00:17:12,070 --> 00:17:13,370
等等 你什麼意思

442
00:17:13,372 --> 00:17:15,455
熊比金絲雀大 是吧

443
00:17:15,457 --> 00:17:17,073
那如果熊都移不動

444
00:17:17,075 --> 00:17:19,192
不 我知道動物大小

445
00:17:19,194 --> 00:17:20,877
你說他們也移不動是什麼意思

446
00:17:20,879 --> 00:17:23,163
他們三天前試過了

447
00:17:23,165 --> 00:17:24,798
動都沒動

448
00:17:24,800 --> 00:17:26,833
他們說會帶更多人過來

449
00:17:26,835 --> 00:17:28,635
結果帶了金絲雀來

450
00:17:28,637 --> 00:17:30,639
飛走吧 小金絲雀

451
00:17:33,141 --> 00:17:36,142
衛生部的賤人坑我們

452
00:17:36,144 --> 00:17:37,543
我說我們乾脆走吧

453
00:17:37,545 --> 00:17:38,645
什麼 不行

454
00:17:38,647 --> 00:17:39,712
我們不能被他們打敗

455
00:17:39,714 --> 00:17:40,764
就當平手吧

456
00:17:40,766 --> 00:17:42,215
沒人能搬得動

457
00:17:42,217 --> 00:17:44,184
不行Leslie 我們不想平手

458
00:17:44,186 --> 00:17:45,518
我們想贏

459
00:17:45,520 --> 00:17:47,070
那些男的賤死了

460
00:17:47,072 --> 00:17:48,321
我們必須證明他們是錯的

461
00:17:48,323 --> 00:17:50,407
我們要做的就是搞點迷幻藥

462
00:17:50,409 --> 00:17:52,359
嗑點天使粉你什麼都能移

463
00:17:52,361 --> 00:17:54,361
我的表弟Hesen嗑藥之後撂倒了5個員警

464
00:17:54,363 --> 00:17:55,695
好吧 等等 先生

465
00:17:55,697 --> 00:17:57,614
這冰箱還能用嗎

466
00:17:57,616 --> 00:18:00,066
能用 我們買了個新的

467
00:18:00,068 --> 00:18:01,751
不需要了

468
00:18:03,404 --> 00:18:04,621
就算那些小孩

469
00:18:04,623 --> 00:18:05,872
覺得你弱爆了又如何

470
00:18:05,874 --> 00:18:08,508
你也不想讓他們來租衣服啊Tom

471
00:18:08,510 --> 00:18:10,543
我就是想讓他們這族群來租

472
00:18:10,545 --> 00:18:12,578
那真是糟透了

473
00:18:12,580 --> 00:18:15,099
我想讓你看點東西

474
00:18:18,803 --> 00:18:20,637
這是Kevin Durant和Russell Westbrook

475
00:18:20,639 --> 00:18:22,105
在一次大敗之後

476
00:18:22,107 --> 00:18:23,523
就算是厲害的人也會被打敗

477
00:18:23,525 --> 00:18:25,308
但他們第二天就會站起來

478
00:18:25,310 --> 00:18:26,976
重新戰鬥

479
00:18:26,978 --> 00:18:28,978
我們明天再去練練吧

480
00:18:28,980 --> 00:18:31,597
同學們 我剛想出了個很好的主意
（dribble up：運球推進）

481
00:18:31,599 --> 00:18:33,533
不對 是雙重好主意
（double dribble：兩次運球，犯規行為= =）

482
00:18:33,535 --> 00:18:36,437
嗯 你一點都不懂籃球

483
00:18:37,439 --> 00:18:38,938
你是個好朋友 Ben

484
00:18:38,940 --> 00:18:39,989
謝謝

485
00:18:40,491 --> 00:18:41,658
我能借1500不

486
00:18:41,660 --> 00:18:44,744
你不能問為什麼

487
00:18:44,746 --> 00:18:46,079
煙花

488
00:18:46,081 --> 00:18:48,415
首先 大家都沒事

489
00:18:48,417 --> 00:18:51,584
沒人受傷了 但發生了點事故

490
00:18:51,586 --> 00:18:53,788
天啊發生了什麼

491
00:18:55,790 --> 00:18:58,124
Diane 都是我的錯

492
00:18:58,126 --> 00:18:59,959
我讓她們翻我的護士包

493
00:19:03,265 --> 00:19:05,231
誰在玩剪刀玩這麼high啊

494
00:19:05,233 --> 00:19:06,232
我們

495
00:19:06,234 --> 00:19:08,068
Ann教我們怎麼做醫生

496
00:19:08,070 --> 00:19:10,136
- 嘢
- 你不生氣嗎

497
00:19:10,138 --> 00:19:11,804
沒事 她們是小孩子

498
00:19:11,806 --> 00:19:13,606
有一次 Zoe把Ivy放烘乾機裏 所以

499
00:19:13,608 --> 00:19:15,442
我還是很抱歉

500
00:19:15,444 --> 00:19:16,943
我覺得讓你失望了

501
00:19:16,945 --> 00:19:20,613
我很高興你這麼在乎

502
00:19:20,615 --> 00:19:22,832
所以我才愛你

503
00:19:22,834 --> 00:19:23,983
噢

504
00:19:23,985 --> 00:19:27,320
我也愛你

505
00:19:28,490 --> 00:19:29,923
我該走了

506
00:19:29,925 --> 00:19:31,324
好了孩子們 我玩得很開心

507
00:19:31,326 --> 00:19:32,792
Ann 再見

508
00:19:34,528 --> 00:19:35,545
嘿 Leslie

509
00:19:35,547 --> 00:19:37,547
Shauna在發稿前

510
00:19:37,549 --> 00:19:39,665
把要用的聲明發過來

511
00:19:39,667 --> 00:19:40,934
市執行長Chris Traeger

512
00:19:40,936 --> 00:19:42,635
也參加了此次活動

513
00:19:42,637 --> 00:19:45,338
並且他和作者有私人關係

514
00:19:45,340 --> 00:19:46,689
還不錯嘛

515
00:19:46,691 --> 00:19:47,774
私人關係

516
00:19:47,776 --> 00:19:49,893
並不浪漫

517
00:19:49,895 --> 00:19:51,844
但也能說清楚 不對 也沒說清楚

518
00:19:51,846 --> 00:19:53,196
我知道你不習慣這樣

519
00:19:53,198 --> 00:19:55,815
但也許你該試試保持冷靜

520
00:19:55,817 --> 00:19:57,150
看會怎麼發展

521
00:19:57,152 --> 00:19:58,568
好建議

522
00:19:58,570 --> 00:19:59,869
不可能實現

523
00:19:59,871 --> 00:20:01,687
但是好建議

524
00:20:01,689 --> 00:20:03,523
你覺得流動廚房

525
00:20:03,525 --> 00:20:04,624
能用上這冰箱嗎

526
00:20:04,626 --> 00:20:07,692
April和我能毫不費力把它拖上車

527
00:20:07,694 --> 00:20:09,195
但如果你需要的話

528
00:20:09,197 --> 00:20:10,914
當然 這是上帝的禮物

529
00:20:10,916 --> 00:20:12,665
謝謝你能想起我們

530
00:20:12,667 --> 00:20:13,800
一人拉一邊 女士們

531
00:20:13,802 --> 00:20:16,085
我想大家一起能把它拉上車

532
00:20:16,087 --> 00:20:18,221
我們不僅完成了收垃圾的人物

533
00:20:18,223 --> 00:20:20,140
移動了不可能移動的冰箱

534
00:20:20,142 --> 00:20:24,544
衛生部還雇用了三個新的女性垃圾收集員

535
00:20:24,546 --> 00:20:26,312
然後 最好的事

536
00:20:26,314 --> 00:20:27,564
April給了我這份禮物

537
00:20:27,566 --> 00:20:29,901
來慶祝我們女權主義的勝利

538
00:20:33,020 --> 00:20:34,655
是垃圾

539
00:20:35,157 --> 00:20:36,823
裏面全是垃圾

540
00:20:36,825 --> 00:20:38,525
也許底部有東西

541
00:20:38,527 --> 00:20:40,160
我看看 不 全是垃圾

542
00:20:41,039 --> 00:20:44,257
這裏是Kids' 46 News節目的Brandon Turnbill

543
00:20:44,541 --> 00:20:47,927
我身旁的是今天勝出隊的明星Josh Diamond

544
00:20:47,945 --> 00:20:49,729
制勝關鍵是什麼呢Josh

545
00:20:49,763 --> 00:20:51,197
一切都很順利

546
00:20:51,231 --> 00:20:52,481
結果我們贏了

547
00:20:52,533 --> 00:20:55,384
下周我們會繼續努力對抗Snerling的

548
00:20:55,435 --> 00:20:56,835
謝謝 細小的記者

549
00:20:56,854 --> 00:20:58,855
今天是Josh和夥伴們的大勝

550
00:20:58,889 --> 00:21:00,189
而在大勝之後

551
00:21:00,224 --> 00:21:04,060
記得要去Durham大道的氣場出租看看

552
00:21:04,111 --> 00:21:06,928
供你們賽後記者會服飾租借需求

553
00:21:07,111 --> 00:21:08,228
我們什麼都有

554
00:21:08,411 --> 00:21:10,128
好西裝 裝飾手帕

555
00:21:10,311 --> 00:21:12,328
格子襯衫 沒鏡片的眼鏡

556
00:21:12,811 --> 00:21:14,428
小件羊毛衫 淺頂軟呢帽

557
00:21:14,911 --> 00:21:16,000
看看這手錶

558
00:21:16,001 --> 00:21:17,535
無論想要什麼風格

559
00:21:17,553 --> 00:21:19,670
都能在氣場出租找到

560
00:21:19,704 --> 00:21:21,039
這才叫籃球

561
00:21:21,040 --> 00:21:24,039
<font color="#2894FF">翻譯 Matt</font>

