Mr. Hotate, hi.
Thank you for coming.
Would you like some water?
Water?
Like fire water?
That's racist,
and I do not appreciate it.
No, no, no, no, no.
I-I didn't mean it like that.
I just meant, you know--
I'm just messing
with you.
- Oh, my God!
- [Laughs]
He's funny.
This guy's funny.
- He does that sometimes.
- But seriously.
I'll have a whiskey.
Ken Hotate is the leader
of the Wamapoke people,
and we are trying
to get them involved
in our Pawnee Commons project.
Ken and I
get along great.
But historically,
Pawnee's relationship
with the Wamapoke
has been more...
Murder-y.
What about--and I'm just
spit-balling here--
a large neon advertisement
for the Wamapoke casino?
We have a new slogan
that I'm quite proud of:
"Our slots
are downright filthy."
I think it's a slam-dunk idea.
I think we're done here.
I don't--
I don't think we are.
I don't know if we could
put that in a public park.
In that case,
the playground will be great.
Why don't we retire
to my longhouse
and smoke the ceremonial
peace pipe to celebrate?
[Chuckles]
- Is he joking?
- I don't know.
[Triumphant music]
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Mr. Best Man
and Bachelor boy.
Ann Perkins,
Maid of Honor,
are you ready
for the bachelorette party?
Uh, more than ready.
We've got dancing,
Jell-o shots,
private karaoke,
and anything
that can be penis-shaped
will be penis-shaped.
- Ohhh!
- What?
As Leslie's maid of honor,
I really need her
bachelorette party to go well.
Which is why I'm stress-eating
gummy penises.
What are you losers doing
for your bachelor party?
I told Ben he could do
whatever he wants.
Sky is the limit.
We have Haverford,
Swanson, Dwyer--
Jerry forced his way
in there somehow--
things are bound
to get crazy.
The game is
Settlers of Catan.
The object is be the first
to build a civilization
on this fictional island.
I can't believe
this is what you want to do
for your bachelor party.
Look, guys,
we don't have to play this game
if you don't want to.
I mean,
I'm nationally ranked,
so it isn't even
really fair.
Ben, this is your night.
We do what you want to do.
Come on, let's play.
[Pounds on table]
I'm not a big bachelor party
kind of guy,
so when the guys asked me
what my perfect night would be,
I told them the truth--
beer and board games.
They thought I was kidding.
I was not kidding.
Is this gonna be one of
those cool bachelorette parties
where things get out of control
and we murder someone,
and then we all have to take
a blood oath
to never reveal our secret?
No.
Then I might have
to leave early.
What the hell?
Well, well, well.
Don't you ladies look nice...
For once?
Just kidding.
I've actually always been
attracted to this one.
Jamm, what the hell
are you doing?
We're laying
the groundwork
for Pawnee's
newest restaurant.
"Future home
of Paunch Burger.
Start drooling, fatties"?
Look, the deal was
that both of us
had three months to get
our proposals together,
and then we put it
up for a vote.
- We still have two weeks left.
- Yeah, that's true.
However, here's the problem.
Turns out, I don't care.
You can't stop this train.
Make all the ruckus
you want.
By the time
this all gets cleared up,
the people will be frothing
at the mouth
for that beef.
Aw, sweet!
A new Paunch Burger.
Their burgers will kill you!
They're full of wasps!
Yeah, but they taste
real good.
Yes, they do, sir.
Once again,
open invitation.
I'm still technically married,
but my wife knows the deal.
Ugh.
Oh, I'm sorry,
what's this?
Seven contiguous segments,
giving me longest road
and a sweet-ass ten points
for the win.
Oh, booyah!
Okay.
All right.
Guys, come on over here.
Gather round.
I want to propose a toast.
To our new Lord of Catan,
Ben Wyatt,
a great friend
and a wonderful man.
May you and Leslie find
eternal happiness together.
- Hey.
- Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
Thanks, you guys.
Thanks for indulging me.
Hey, you want
to stick around?
I got a bunch
of Homeland episodes
burning a hole
in my DVR.
No!
I'm sorry.
On principle,
I cannot stand idly by
and watch a bachelor party
peter out like this.
Now, I know you said
no strippers
'cause they make you sad.
Correct.
Then let's go get a drink
at Essence.
It's the hot new bar
in Eagleton.
Things Magazine said
it's the next big thing.
But, Tom,
this is Ben's night.
Oh, believe me,
if the group's happy, I'm happy.
- I'd go.
- If you guys spot me.
It sounds expensive.
Just so you know,
it's not your typical bar.
They specialize
in molecular mixology.
It's kind of like
an experimental new way
to consume alcohol.
Son, there's no wrong way
[Hip-hop music]
Here's your Bud light.
- I ordered a beer.
- That is a beer.
And here's
your Nimbus Martini.
May I go ahead and chisel
your aromasphere?
Please!
This is the wrong way
to consume alcohol.
Whoa,
that's a pretty stiff cloud.
- Who ordered the Scotch?
- Right here.
Hold out your hands,
please.
What's happening?
Oh, this is
a sort of play on Scotch.
It's a whiskey-infused lotion.
Can I ask
if this entire establishment
is a practical joke
of some kind?
If you don't like the Scotch,
they have a vodka
that's served in the form
of a flash of light.
Hey.
Having fun?
Well, four years of work
down the drain,
and I have a penis
on my head.
Jamm is stealing this lot
right out from under us.
My dream is dead, Ann.
Mine too.
This is
why I prefer nightmares.
You are sad drinking
right now,
and I need you
to be happy drinking.
Like when we watch
Grease together.
I know, Ann, but everything's
gonna disappear.
April's mini-dog park,
the Li'l Sebastian fountain,
even the Wamapoke playground.
Yet another piece
of Wamapoke land
plowed over
by the white man.
Just try to forget
about it.
I mean, there's nothing
you can do to stop them tonight.
For almost 200 years,
Pawnee repeatedly built
factories, restaurants,
and other stuff
on land held sacred
by the Wamapoke people.
So we passed a law
saying that
if any sacred Wamapoke artifact
is found
on a development site,
all construction
must immediately stop.
It would be terrible
if that were to happen
on this future
Paunch Burger site.
[Chuckles wickedly]
Oh, this is bad.
I should not have done this.
[Doorbell]
Oh, I wonder
who that is.
[Women cheer]
Well, if it isn't Babe Lincoln!
- Imagine that.
- Hello, ladies.
I'm Abraham Lincoln.
Who's the lucky Mary Todd?
Right here.
Ah, ah, ah, me first.
Me first.
Oh, okay.
All right,
tear it up, 16!
Emancipate them abs.
[Women cheering]
Come on, Ann, not now.
Come on, Leslie,
just loosen up.
I know for a fact
this is a sex dream
you've had.
Looks like it's time
for the Gettysburg undressed!
[Women cheering]
Okay.
And we're gonna have
to stop now.
I'm sorry,
I'm just not in the mood
for historical nudity.
Please, Mr. president,
put your pants back on.
Ann, can I speak
with you privately?
Is your name Glenn?
- Yeah.
- I sat behind you
in middle school band.
Do you still play
the clarinet?
Yeah.
How have you been, man?
[Space age music]
Man, if I ever have
a bachelor party,
I am definitely
coming back here.
You never had one before
you were married to Wendy?
No, it was
a green card wedding.
I did watch
the three-way sex scene
from Wild Things
a few times
the night before,
but it didn't really count.
I never had
a bachelor party either.
Me and April, we got married
with no warning.
[Laughs]
I didn't even have time
to take a shower
before my wedding.
[Laughs]
Or after.
For, like,
a week and a half.
Tammy One forbade me
from any kind
of celebration,
and Tammy Two thwarted me
by calling in
a bomb threat
to the steakhouse.
I didn't have one either!
Yeah, really,
it's a funny story.
So two weeks
before I married Gayle,
I had
an emergency appendectomy.
Boop! That's me hitting
the snooze button.
Don't talk again
for another ten minutes.
New idea!
Tonight, everyone
gets the bachelor party
they never had.
One activity per bachelor.
Welcome
to Tom's bachelor party,
held in a white airplane hangar
from the ice planet Hoth,
replete with dangling,
beautiful aerialists.
To Tom Haverford.
To Tom Haverford!
[All cheering]
Hey, hey--
and to my bride, Rihanna.
We truly did find love
in a hopeless place.
Waiter, a round
of light-flash shots
for me and my friends!
- Ohhh!
- Whoo!
Okay, so what happened?
Well, I buried a bunch
of Wamapoke artifacts
in the dirt
so that people
would find them
and have to stop developing
at the site.
You know, when I say it out
loud, it doesn't sound so bad.
- No, that's bad.
- Yeah, that's pretty uncool.
- Shut up, Glenn.
- I'm sorry, guys.
Councilman Jamm
was being sneaky,
and then I tried
to sneaky him back,
and it turned to crummy,
and I have to undo it.
I need your help.
- You don't mean--
- I do.
No.
I'm not doing that.
[Grunts]
You guys, the penis hats
cut your digging time
in half.
I'm serious.
Don't be afraid.
Use the penises.
Bachelorette party.
Whoo.
Perkins does it again.
You know, I met Gayle
right here at Sherm's.
- Mm-mm.
- She was slender.
Blonde hair, big breasts,
long legs.
Ugh,
not my type at all.
And what was it, exactly,
that led to you two
hitting it off?
Was she ill,
or did your father
witness her father
committing a crime?
- Or was she temporarily blind--
- You know what?
All that matters
is that you got married,
and you're happy.
So as all-time best man,
I suggest we raise a cone
to Jerry Gergich.
Jerry Gergich.
All: Jerry!
- Thank you.
- Gergich.
- Aw, jeez.
No worries, Gary.
Oh, thanks, Sherm.
[Chuckling]
How did you have that
ready so fast?
I always make
a backup cone.
He drops it
about half the time.
Andy,
you're next.
Any activity in the world.
What would you do?
Well, mine's impossible.
[Chuckles]
I want to see
a Colts game.
I want to see the Colts
beat the Patriots 49 to nothing,
then I yell at Tom Brady
and make him cry,
then I hook up
with Dave Matthews,
and we play golden tee
for ten hours.
♪ A-la-la baby
that's a very specific
dream, son.
Hey, Jim, Chris Traeger.
I need a favor.
I'm dead.
I am dead.
And this is what heaven
is like.
I knew it.
Oh, this is
where they play the games!
You're up, Andy.
Hey, guys!
Guys, come on over here.
Andy, I want you to meet
Indianapolis Colts owner
Jim Irsay.
Andy,
good to meet you, my friend.
Thank you.
I love your team, sir.
I love them
like they're my own children.
You're big enough
to play football yourself,
it looks like to me.
I can't tell
if you're joking,
but I hope you're not.
This whole place
is yours.
Jim Irsay and I
became friends
while volunteering to mentor
Indianapolis teens.
I gave them tours
of the state house.
Jim gave them Colts tickets
and autographed jerseys.
They preferred Jim.
Reggie Wayne.
I can't look at you,
[Laughing] Oh.
I got married in your jersey.
That's no joke.
That's weird.
But I respect that.
I'm a big fan,
Mr. Luck.
Okay, guy, settle down.
- Okay.
- Uh, Mr. Andrew Luck,
it's every groom's dream
to catch a touchdown pass
thrown by you.
Could you do me the honor?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Keep the spiral tight.
- I'll try.
- Okay.
[Panting]
[All cheering]
Touchdown, Dwyer!
[Laughter and applause]
- Andy!
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
- See ya!
[Salt-n-Pepa's shoop]
♪ Hey, yeah
♪ I wanna shoop, baby
♪ shoop, shoop-ba-doop
♪ uh, here I go
here I go ♪
♪ here I go again
♪ girls
what's my weakness? ♪
- ♪ men
- ♪ Okay then
♪ uh
ooh, let's call Ann real quick.
Rub it in.
[Line rings]
Hello?
- Ann Perkins!
[All shouting]
We're having
the time of our lives,
and I'm calling you
to rub it in!
- Whoo!
- Boom!
- Really.
- We went to an insane bar,
played football
with the Colts.
- With the Colts!
- The Colts!
Football!
Now we're going
to a steakhouse.
What are you doing?
Uh, well, we're surrounded
by hot guys.
- We're surrounded by hot guys.
- Boom!
Oh, Donna just ripped off
a stripper's underwear
with her teeth.
- Whoo!
- Ann, who are you lying to?
- Shh.
- No!
Can I take a break?
My hands are tired.
Uhuh.
We paid for an hour.
You gonna dig
for an hour.
Gentlemen, welcome
to the Steak House of St. Elmo.
- Whoo!
- Yes!
Tonight we eat
something's flesh!
I want meat!
Jerry, are you sure
this is our table?
There's only four settings.
Excuse me, sir.
This is not your table.
Well, I thought you said
the Gergich party.
No, no, I said
the Gingrich party.
[Gasps]
Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry.
Damn it, Jerry.
But you know what?
Gingrich, Gergich.
I wonder if we're related.
I don't think so, Jerry.
[Chuckles]
Okay.
One rare porterhouse,
one rare sirloin,
and a rasher of bacon.
- Oh.
- It's the lord's work
you're doing, John.
I'd like
four more glasses
of Lagavulin
in liquid form.
That's not something
you really need to specify.
You'd be surprised.
So, bachelor boy,
how's it going
with Diane?
Hmm.
I'm gonna be very candid
with you all.
I like her.
- Whoa!
- Wow!
[Laughter]
Okay, okay, okay.
[Clears throat]
There are so many things
that I could say about Ron,
but I think
that the best man's speech
should represent the groom.
So I will just say...
To Ron.
- Oh, to Ron!
- To Ron!
To Ron.
Just perfect.
Perfect, Chris.
Here you are, sir.
And I thought you might
also like to know
that your meal has already
been taken care of
- by Mr. Hibbert.
- W-what?
- Oh!
- Hey!
- Oh, whoa!
What's up, Jell-o shot?
- Hey, man.
- How's it going?
Roy Hibbert.
Entertainment 720 reunion.
Hey, Tom.
I am not paying
for that guy.
He owes me a lot of money.
It's true.
[Birds chirping]
[Yawns]
Coffee?
Yes, please.
Take extra cream, 30 sugars.
I can't believe I tried
to exploit the Wamapoke
for my own personal gain.
Well, we got
most of the artifacts,
and even if we didn't,
they probably won't find them.
Yeah, and if they do,
you'll just go to jail.
But you can make wine
in your toilet
and fight people,
which is a super-cool way
to live.
Oh, my God.
Tweep.
I tweeped.
I called Tweep.
Look, I'm telling the truth
here, lady.
We haven't found
any American Indian artifacts.
Or regular Indian.
Japanese, Muslim,
Jewish,
none of those weird countries.
- Weird countries?
- Shauna Malwae-Tweep.
Wow, I'm so glad
that you're here.
[Chuckles]
What's going on? Nothing?
Found something!
There's other stuff too.
Arrowheads, more pottery.
I also found some weird-looking
gummy candy.
All right, shut it down.
This is a P.R. nightmare.
We can't do anything
until the Indian Affairs
Commission weighs in.
This is
[Bleep] bull[Bleep].
Okay.
Lesie, Ken Hotate
is right over there,
you need to talk to him
before the meeting
and come clean.
[Groans]
He's gonna be so mad.
The zodiac killer
never confessed.
Why do I have to?
Leslie, I want the Pawnee
Commons as bad as you do.
Actually,
that's not true.
You want everything
a thousand times more than I do.
But we do not want
to win this way.
Oh, April, I wish you weren't
right, but you are.
You have turned
into a very beautiful, wise,
and fertile
government employee.
Stop.
It's kind of weird
when she just starts
raining compliments
on you, huh?
Don't try to bond
with me.
Can't win.
- [Groaning]
- [Laughing]
Hey, guys,
I had these T-shirts made.
They're not exactly
a summary of the party
- we ended up having.
- Whoa.
But they're a good memento.
Madness indeed.
I love this!
Usually you can only get
board game t-shirts in XXL.
I just remembered.
We left Jerry back at
the gas station in Martinsville.
I'll go get him.
Ah, that guy's the best.
[Engine turns over]
I feel bad he didn't get
to have his moment last night.
Hey, you know what
we should do for him?
Yeah, get him a pet snake,
but I keep it.
What?
In 1921,
several Wamapoke families
were removed
from their homes
so that Pawnee could install
a bumper car track.
In 1951,
Pawnee made it illegal
for people to,
"Dance or smell
like a native American."
Why are you telling me
all this?
Well, I want to raise the bar
of awfulness
so that when I confess
something to you,
you have perspective.
Those artifacts found
at lot 48
were placed there
by me.
I wanted to delay construction
on the Paunch Burger
and buy some more time
for my park project.
[Sighs]
That is not great.
It sucks.
I'm very, very sorry.
I have great respect
for the Wamapoke culture.
And this isn't even
about the Pawnee Commons.
I just hope that you
can forgive me, Ken.
[Sighs]
Hey!
Hey, guys.
What are you doing here?
Congratulations. You have won
the award for Best Nan.
Full disclosure--
I voted for Ryan Gosling,
but you came in
a close second.
Now,
you've never been married,
so you didn't get
your own bachelor party.
But let's look ahead.
The year is 2018.
America is thriving
under president Nick Cannon,
and tomorrow,
Chris Traeger's getting married.
Who's the lucky lady?
Maybe she's an upbeat gal
who's nuts about fitness.
Maybe she owns
a juice bar in Snerling.
Maybe it's April.
Maybe I die.
Skydiving explosion.
Pbbbt.
And then you go marry April.
And it makes me sad,
but if she's gonna be
with somebody,
I'd like it to be you.
Strange, but sweet.
Only I didn't really die.
I was faking it.
And I come back.
I spy on you
from my red Corvette.
And I'm planning
to kick your ass,
but I see how happy
you make her,
and I have to walk away.
I have to.
And I do, slowly.
In a rainstorm.
Okay, this isn't really
in the spirit
of what we're trying to do.
But as time goes by,
it eats away at me.
You're out living it up
with my wife.
And I'm alone.
In a cave.
Training.
Anyone else
want to chime in?
I thought
you were my friend.
I thought you were my friend!
Okay, what we're trying
to say is
that you are a great guy,
and someday,
you're gonna meet somebody
who's into all the same stuff
that you are.
You know, the old Chris
would've loved
this super-fit
health goddess
you guys
are talking about.
But our great adventure
reminded me
that now I just want someone
that values
the important things
in life--
friendships, passion,
happiness.
And dimples
are a plus.
- [Chuckles]
- Aw, that's sweet.
I forgive you, bro.
You take care of April.
After careful examination,
we have determined that
these Wamapoke artifacts
could not have originated
in lot 48.
Boom.
Knew it.
There's something else.
I would like to go
on record and say that--
Hold on, Ms. Knope.
Please.
I would like to go
on record.
Speaking as a citizen
of Pawnee,
I do not like the way
you went back on your deal
with Councilwoman Knope.
It reminds me of what
the settlers of Pawnee did
to my ancestors,
taking their land
without permission.
He really plays white people
like a fiddle.
[Chuckles]
Wow.
It's amazing to watch.
You and Leslie
had a deal.
If that deal
is not restored,
well, I believe
there are six Paunch Burgers
in the Wamapoke casino.
Perhaps it's time
that we revisited
those contracts.
Is that a threat?
Why, yes, I--
I thought that was obvious.
Take the sign down.
We'll wait
until everything's official.
In the spirit
of fair play,
I suggest we put on these
authentic Wamapoke headdresses
and dance
around the table.
Absolutely not.
That sounds
highly offensive.
Does it, white man?
No.
It's not offensive.
- So let's do it.
- You first.
So clearly,
this is not offensive.
It is offensive.
- I am very sorry.
- Take it off.
Hey, Wyatt.
Oh, hey, Shauna.
So I was chasing
this story,
but it seems like
a dead end.
Then I heard about your crazy
rotating bachelor party.
Would you mind
if I wrote about it?
Sure.
But is that really news?
To me it is.
A group of good friends
having fun,
doing nice things
for each other.
I mean, that's what's important
in life,
and I want to write
about it.
Hey, Chris.
Ben Wyatt.
And Shauna Malwae-Tweep.
Hey,
Shauna's doing a story
on our group bachelor party.
She said she wanted
to write stories
about good people doing
nice things for each other.
So I figured you two might have
a lot to talk about.
You may be right
about that.
Do you have a second
right now?
I have thousands
of seconds.
Would you like
to have lunch?
Are you a vegetarian?
A vegan?
A pescatarian?
Not that it matters.
- Um, I like burgers.
- Perfect.
Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh!
Three, ten, bullock!
Give it to me.
How great a day was today?
[Panting]
Oh, God, I could die.
Greatest day of my life.
I met Andrew Luck today.
I met Reggie Wayne today.
And I met Jim Irsay.
I'm standing
on the field.
Lucas Oil Stadium.
And I'm playing football
with my friends.
ALL: Cheering.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com