You are being watched.
The government
has a secret system--
a machine that spies on you
every hour of every day.
I designed the machine
to detect acts of terror,
but it sees everything...
Violent crimes
involving ordinary people.
The government considers
these people irrelevant.
We don't.
Hunted by the authorities,
we work in secret.
You will never find us.
But victim or perpetrator,
if your number's up,
we'll find you.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Hi, mom.
Hi, dad.
If you're watching this,
you'll know I'm in trouble.
I've always tried to
be good, keep the rules.
Now I'm gonna break them
in a big way.
Just hold him still.
Bear, afliggen!
Sit.
Well, that was a big help.
So, you said we had
another number?
Yes.
Abby Monroe, 26.
Honor student at school,
degree in engineering.
She's worked for the last year
at a military charity,
Homes For Our Returning Heroes,
maybe because
her younger brother
was killed in Afghanistan
18 months ago.
She quit the charity
a week ago.
She's now working as a temp
in a city planning office.
Any threats?
Not that I can see,
but some anomalies.
She dumped her phone
five days ago
and moved out of her apartment.
In fact, the only way
I could trace her
was through the temp agency.
She's hiding from someone.
I'd better get eyes on her.
It's your turn to dry him.
She could be in
imminent danger, Finch.
Mr. Reese,
he's your dog.
You'll manage.
- Detective.
Dinner was fun.
What about doing it again?
I'm free tonight,
as it happens.
Sorry.
Got a case I'm looking at.
Him, actually.
Davidson.
The Internal Affairs cop
went missing last winter.
Did you know him?
Know him?
I had some run-ins with him.
What's your interest?
I got a tip, anonymous.
Said a cop killed him.
Whoa.
Well, maybe he was mixed up
in some HR business.
Maybe an HR cop took him out.
I heard of one group out of
the 51st was offing dealers
and selling their supply.
You got any names?
Most of them are behind bars
or dead, but not all of them.
Will you excuse us?
Detective Carter,
we need to talk.
I'll catch up with you later.
So, with HR degraded
to the point of irrelevance,
my team is shifting priorities
back to the man in the suit.
He's still out there.
Do you still want to catch him?
- Yes, of course.
- Good.
We have some new information,
including who he's working for.
Now, the bureau has been
tracking the emergence
of private intelligence
networks,
like the CIA or MI6,
but for profit.
We think the biggest of these
has Chinese backing.
They've got technology,
serious resources,
and they've been
buying up talent.
For instance,
we think Mark Snow,
the CIA agent
who contacted you,
may also have been recruited,
possibly by the man
in the suit.
- Really? Snow?
- Makes sense.
I mean, Snow was sent to
find this man by the CIA.
He catches him, and then
the man in the suit flips him.
Gets snow to be his asset.
Listen, Carter, I want to
read you into this,
but it's classified,
so I've been authorized
to offer you
a temporary assignment
to the bureau.
And I know, with your skills,
it'll soon become permanent.
Sooner you're on board,
sooner I can fill you in.
So, please, think about it.
I will.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Carter.
Hello, Detective.
I need to find our friend.
We have a big problem.
You'll find him at the
department of city planning.
So he just downloaded
the file and walked out?
Yeah.
Didn't anyone try to stop her?
Apparently nobody noticed.
Detective Carter.
Uh, what do we got?
- You heard the 10-31 too,
Detective?
Yep.
So, what is it?
Uh, like we were telling
Marshal Jennings here--
Marshal Jennings, huh?
The manager called it in
'cause one of his staff,
a girl by the name
of Abby Monroe,
downloaded a file illegally.
And walked out with it
two hours ago.
No one noticed till too late.
Well, does anyone know
what's on the file?
Well, we keep plans here
for some important buildings,
but all she walked out with
were some engineering drawings
for the 1400 block of Hanover
near Wall Street.
It's got
an electrical sub-station,
lawyers' offices, and the HQ
of an investment bank.
Nothing like a critical
infrastructure target.
So, does anyone know where
this Abby Monroe lives?
We ran a check.
The address she gave us
is fake.
The phone number
is a pay phone.
Hey,
solid background check there.
What can I say?
I mean, she seemed like
a sweet kid.
Kind of disappointing to find
she was a flake.
Kids. You never know.
Right, Detective?
Right.
Anyway, good job,
following up so quickly.
Gentlemen.
Thank you, Marshal.
Uh, look, if you come up
with anything else,
give me a call.
John. John!
Are you out of your mind?
Impersonating
a law enforcement officer?
Marshal Jennings?
You took his star?
He wasn't using it anymore.
It's great, Carter.
Just flash a badge,
and people tell you everything.
You gotta stop, John.
Donnelly's back, and he's hot
for the man in the suit.
He has a new theory.
Yeah, that I'm working
for China or something.
We heard.
We also heard his offer.
Maybe a transfer to the FBI
would be good for you.
Do you listen to
all of my conversations?
More or less.
You're looking nice, Carter.
Maybe this Cal Beecher
would be good for you too.
Long as he treats you right.
He messes with you,
he'll be hearing from me.
Okay. All right, look.
We're gonna have to set
some boundaries here.
Well, sure.
Things get heavy
with you and Cal,
we'll tune out right away.
Never mind.
Um, what's the deal
with Abby Monroe?
I was checking to see
she wasn't in trouble.
Looks like I'm a bit late.
Carter, can you get me footage
from that camera
from about two hours ago?
And that camera too?
Thank you.
There's Abby.
Were you able to trace
the owner of the motorcycle,
Detective?
No, because it was stolen
from a second-hand showroom
in Queens four days ago.
I got the camera tapes
out of the robbery squad.
I see the perp
is a single male.
You looking at the footage now?
Yes. Why?
No reason.
Blew the locks with det cord.
Ignored the alarms,
'cause he knew he'd be
less than 30 seconds.
He broke the key case
with his bare hand.
Chose his machine.
Whoa.
That's impressive.
What is-- what--
what is going on here?
Don't tell me you can see
what's on my computer too.
What did I say
about setting boundaries?
That's a prosthetic hand.
High-end prosthetic,
use of det cord to gain entry
into a building.
My guess, ex-military.
Might explain
his connection to Abby.
The question is,
what are they doing?
I don't think you're
gonna like the answer.
Comp stat just flagged
my license plate inquiry.
The same motorcycle was seen
on a traffic light camera
near a robbery
at a construction site
in New Jersey three nights ago.
What was stolen?
Explosives.
Semtex.
20 pounds of it,
and blasting caps.
Let's see, theft of explosives,
theft of engineering plans
for a block on Wall Street.
This guy could be
the next Timothy McVeigh,
and your girl
is working with him.
He may have manipulated her
into getting involved.
She's still involved.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna have to do my job.
I'm gonna have to put
her name out on an APB.
We've got to find her first.
Hey, Olson,
you worked at the 55.
You know a Narco detective
named Cal Beecher?
Oh, yeah, sure do.
We used to call him
18-karat Cal.
Better suits, better cars,
better girls
than the rest of us.
Maybe he just had better taste.
Or maybe he was on the take.
Did you hear me say that?
Don't know.
What are you saying?
Look, he was
undercover narcotics.
A lot of buy-and-busts,
a lot of money hanging around.
Anyway, why you want to know?
Ah, I just been
seeing him around.
Yeah. He's been hanging around
Detective Carter.
Bees like honey, Fusco.
Yeah.
I'm just saying, but the way
Abby went off the grid,
cut all ties,
she's planning something,
Finch.
You think our honor student
wants to blow up Wall Street?
Well, her boyfriend might.
He isn't the first vet
to try something extreme.
We are an odd bunch, Finch.
You are odd, Mr. Reese.
You're also wrong.
If Abby were involved
with domestic terrorism,
which would be
a relevant crime,
the machine would have
given her number
to-- to whoever
now runs that end of things
at the government, not to us.
Whether she's the target
or the source of the threat,
the issues must be personal.
Fine, but what leads
do we have left, Finch?
We have two.
First, the pay phone number
that she gave the temp agency.
It's a street corner in Queens.
The agency must have been able
to contact her there
at one point.
It might give you a clue
as to where she's living.
Okay.
And the second lead?
The one stable point
in her life for the last year--
The charity,
Homes For Our Returning Heroes.
I'll check that one out.
Good.
You need to get out more.
You're in a good mood,
Mr. Reese.
I am.
I woke up this morning
and felt--
it took me a while to put
my finger on it,
but I felt happy.
Must be this job.
Well, I'm glad.
Sorry, Bear.
Not now.
Abby tapped into
that pay phone.
I think I've found
where our Bonnie and Clyde
have been laying low.
Josh Monroe,
Abby's little brother.
I'm an old friend
of Abby's family,
and as I was visiting New York,
they asked if I'd try to
find out where Abby is
and why she left her job here.
She never told them?
Well, I'm sorry,
but I had to fire her.
- Fire her? What on earth for?
- Stealing.
At first, it was just
petty cash, and I let it go,
thinking it was simple
carelessness, but then I found
she was sneaking
into the charity's accounts,
trying to move money around--
significant amounts.
Mr. Chapple,
that really doesn't sound
like the Abby I know.
Well, unfortunately, it's true.
We give low-cost loans to
veterans in financial trouble.
Any hint of a scandal,
and our donations would
just dry right up.
Abby had to go.
Hi, mom.
Hi, dad.
If you're watching this,
you'll know I'm in trouble.
I don't think you've really been
mad at me since I was eight,
that time I tied Josh
to his skateboard
and pushed him down the hill
in front of our house
to see how fast he would go.
Since then, I've always tried to
be good, keep the rules.
Now I'm gonna break them
in a big way.
Why? Well, it's complicated
and it's simple.
I'm doing it because
it's right,
and I know Josh
would agree with me.
He was my little brother,
but I always looked up to him,
and I know
that he would be proud of me,
just like I hope you are
when you know the truth.
I love you, and I hope
you never have to see this.
Any idea
why she started stealing?
I believe the trouble started
when she met a former Marine.
Uh, they'd talk
when he came by the offices.
Somehow, he must have made
an impression on Abby,
'cause, just about that time,
she started stealing.
I don't understand.
Why did this Marine come here?
I'm sorry.
We have a strict
confidentiality agreement
with all
of our loan recipients.
Suffice it to say,
it was not a pleasant visit.
Could you at least
tell me his name?
Corporal Shayn Coleman,
explosives ordinance
disposal expert.
Lost his right arm
defusing an IED in Afghanistan
three years ago.
He's our motorcycle thief.
I tracked down Shayn's parents
in his hometown in Ohio.
They haven't seen him
in more than two months.
Did they know
he was in trouble?
They said he'd had
his home foreclosed on,
and his fiancee dumped him.
Must be why
he went to Chapple--
to ask for another loan.
However it happened,
this is more than enough
to tip someone over the edge.
He's our guy.
I'm adding his name to the APB.
Do what you have to do,
Detective.
Finch, are you still there?
Yes.
I'm watching Philip Chapple
meet with two armed men.
What are they like?
Like you, to be honest--
low-key and vaguely menacing.
I suspect he's telling them
to follow me
via the GPS transponder
he slipped into my pocket
as I was leaving.
And where is
the transponder now?
It's on a laundry van
with Jersey plates.
Nice work, Finch.
Obviously, Chapple
will take any opportunity
to track Abby down.
What she's planning
must connect to him too.
When the charity closes,
I'll go back in,
see what I can find.
When I said
you need to get out more,
I didn't mean that.
Let me take care of it.
No such thing as
a risk-free life, Mr. Reese,
and Abby is still our priority.
You wait for her.
So, I'll go back in,
see what exactly
Chapple's hiding.
I'm inside,
but the alarm
has been tampered with.
That's because they could be
waiting for you, Harold.
Ah!
What was that?
Finch, get out now.
Who the hell are you?
Who I am is not important,
Mr. Coleman.
How do you know my name?
What are you doing here?
The same thing as you,
I expect,
and since you woke
the whole building,
we better hurry.
I'm on my way to you.
Please, just walk away now,
Finch.
Shh!
- Who are you?
- It's okay.
- Let go of me!
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
Finch, get out now.
Don't risk it.
I've got Abby.
Just get out of there.
Nearly done, Mr. Reese.
Please don't do that.
Then get off of me.
Let me go.
Please, no guns.
Finch, talk to me.
What's happening?
The situation
is evolving, Mr. Reese.
There they go!
Stop right there!
Get on, or they'll kill you!
Get on!
Finch, are you okay?
Aside from riding on a
motorcycle illegally, I'm fine!
I'll be in touch!
Well done.
Hello, Abby.
I'm John.
Okay, you should leave now,
because my boyfriend's
gonna be here any minute.
Your boyfriend, Shayn?
I don't know how
you know that, but yes,
and he's a Marine,
so you do not want to meet him.
Actually,
I do want to meet him,
but first things first.
What does that message
to your mom and dad mean?
What?
You broke into my room
and went through my stuff?
Get out, or I'm--
What?
You'll call the police?
I know about the building plans
and the explosives.
I knew it.
You work for Chapple.
No, but I'm interested
to know why you and Shayn
are going after him.
Because Chapple's a liar
and a thief,
and I'm not saying another word
until you tell me who you are.
I'm here to stop you from
getting into even more trouble.
Not what I asked.
Who are you?
I find it hard to answer that,
even to myself.
I was a soldier once,
like your brother Josh.
But I was lucky.
I made it out.
- Mr, Reese?
- Yes, Finch. What's happening?
I've explained to Shayn
that we're trying to help him.
Did he believe you?
No, especially when I told him
that you have Abby.
Things are a little tense.
Let me talk to him.
Who is this?
You know, Abby keeps
asking me the same thing.
It's really not important.
If you hurt her,
you will be sorry.
The same goes for you
and my friend.
We should meet.
Once you leave with Shayn,
I can't protect you anymore.
I never asked you to
protect me in the first place.
Whatever you're planning,
I know why, Abby.
You couldn't save your brother,
so you're trying to save Shayn.
I understand that, truly.
I'd feel the same way.
Tell me,
what did Chapple do to you?
Nothing I can't handle,
but he nearly destroyed Shayn.
- By lending him money?
- Yes.
Chapple made him a loan.
The interest rates
tripled in a year.
No one could keep up
those payments.
Millions of people
lost their homes.
They don't go around
stealing explosives.
Shayn should move on.
He lost his home
and his fiancee.
He even introduced some of
his buddies to Chapple,
one of whom shot himself
on the porch of the house
he no longer owned.
Should he move on from that?
Look, I went through
Chapple's files.
I saw what he was doing.
There are hundreds,
hundreds of soldiers
who lost their homes.
What are you gonna do, Abby?
The right thing.
Can I go now?
I assume you
put a tracker on him.
Rather a clever one,
if I do say so myself.
His prosthetic arm is controlled
by myoelectric sensors
by way of a wireless link,
so I cloned the link
and reprogrammed it
to attempt a forced pair with
every cell phone they pass.
Leaving a nice GPS trail.
Well done, Finch.
Especially on the back
of a speeding motorcycle,
which was exhilarating,
by the way.
I might have to get myself one.
Working late?
Uh, yeah. Um...
It's always something,
you know?
Yeah.
Is something wrong, Carter?
Donnelly made me
an offer today.
What, I got competition?
From that guy?
No, not that sort of offer.
He, um, invited me
to join the FBI.
Could be a good move.
I mean, yeah,
small fish in a big pond,
but think of the prospects,
Carter, and the money.
You should do it.
But what about my kid?
I mean,
it-- it'll probably mean
I have to move out of New York.
You mean I'd never
see you again?
It's Cal.
No problem.
I'll see you then.
Uh, now what were we
talking about?
About never seeing me again.
Right.
It's Cal.
Cal, Alonzo Quinn.
Can we meet?
Tyrell Park.
Say, 30 minutes?
No problem.
I'm hoping you can
help me out, Cal.
Any way I can,
Mr. Quinn.
The Mayor has seen this
crime spike in Crown Heights--
drug busts, uh, burglaries,
even homicides.
He wants me to find out
what's happening.
I told him I got a godson
who's got his ear to the ground.
So, do you?
Crown Heights, yeah.
We think it's a Russian,
Peter Yogorov.
Used to work Brighton Beach
till Elias kicked him out.
We believe he's pulling strings
from the inside,
working to take over
the Heights.
Boo.
What are you doing here,
Simmons?
I'm keeping an eye on you,
you slippery little mutt.
What are you doing?
None of your business.
You're following Cal Beecher.
You're checking him out
for Carter?
No, I've been wondering
who else you've been
flapping your gums to.
About you burying Davidson?
Not Beecher.
Not yet.
You crossed a line when you
made that call to Carter,
pointing her towards me
in the Davidson murder.
What line is that?
The line where I don't
give a crap anymore.
So watch your back.
You know how many times
I've heard that?
And here I am,
beautiful as ever.
Go home, Fusco.
What are you doing here,
Simmons?
I said, go home.
There's our cell phone trail.
It looks like Abby and Shayn
are heading
for the 1400 block of Hanover.
Question is, what's there?
I've listed every
business name on the block,
cross-checking against the
download of Chapple's computer.
Bingo. An investment bank,
Merton Watts.
Maybe he has an account there.
Not according
to his computer records.
- Then a safe deposit box?
- What would he keep in it?
According to his accounts,
Chapple's not rich.
Abby said hundreds
of the loans he made
were foreclosed on.
If he's getting kickbacks
from the banks--
You may be right.
Merton Watts has first lien
on any properties
Chapple loans money on.
That means they handle
all foreclosure sales.
And split the profits
with Chapple,
which he keeps in his
safe deposit box at the bank.
That's what Abby and Shayn
are after.
Why is she doing this?
For Shayn?
Yes.
And for her brother.
She still feels a debt.
The dead have a power
like that, as you know.
So, how are they
going to do this?
Semtex and building plans.
They'll find a soft entry point
and blast their way
into the vault.
I like these kids.
I'd like them to live.
Please try to get to them
before Chapple's thugs do.
System's back up.
They get anything
from the safe?
The box code and the keys.
But there's no way they can
get into the vault
at the bank, is there?
What do you think?
Police band says
they stole explosives
and engineering plans.
Well, get down there.
Deal with them.
You have to pay
for another man.
It's a big area to cover.
Whatever you need.
Just finish it.
Carter, I need to see you
immediately.
Can I have your phone?
What's going on, Donnelly?
I'm sorry, but I think the
organization our man works for
has some sophisticated
capabilities.
Like wire-tapping cops?
Has something happened?
I think we got our break.
The man in the suit was involved
in a robbery at a charity
on the Upper East Side.
How do you know that?
Now, before I can let you in,
I have to know
if you'll accept the temporary
assignment to the bureau.
Okay, yes.
Good.
You won't regret it.
So, we've been tracking
this man for ten months.
Every time we get close,
he slips right out
from under us,
as if he has
some guardian angel.
All I've looked for since then
is a lead, any lead,
and then I realized, the phone.
He's in constant communication
with his handlers.
I thought of that.
Cross-checked crime scenes
he was reported at
with cell tower logs of IMEIs.
- Came up with nothing.
- Exactly. Nothing.
Our engineers at Quantico
analyzed the cell tower traffic
from that night he gave us
the slip downtown.
Under the wireless
and radio noise,
they found short bursts
of a cloned IMEI
with a unique signature.
I tasked an FBI computer cluster
to search for that signature.
24 hours ago,
the cluster came online.
It spotted another burst
of cloned imeis
at the exact time
and location of the robbery.
It's him.
I've got SWAT teams
standing by.
If he uses that phone,
we'll have him.
Abby, this is far enough.
I'll handle this from here.
I'll meet you back
at the apartment.
No.
No, together or nothing.
You've risked enough, Abby.
This isn't your fight
right now.
This is my fight.
You're my fight.
I wouldn't do that.
Or that.
Now, the truth...
or I take you
to the cops myself.
I know you're here
to steal Chapple's money.
What then?
We want to give it back to
the people he stole it from.
How?
We haven't thought
that far ahead.
You haven't thought
very far at all.
Now, why not go to the cops
or a lawyer?
Abby did.
She went to the DA,
but Chapple got there first,
spread his poison.
The DA even threatened
to prosecute her
for theft and slander.
When I got to my apartment,
one of Chapple's mercenaries
was there.
He beat me up.
He said if I said another word,
he would come back
and put a bullet in my head.
I assume the bank's
through there?
We blow that wall,
we're underneath it.
John, this has gone far enough.
Has it, Finch?
Yes. Stop them.
I can deal with Chapple.
Chapple hurt them, Finch.
They tried the law.
The law wasn't interested.
What have they got left?
Besides, I've always
had a thing
about people who screw
with veterans.
John, it's far too risky.
What did you say, Harold?
No such thing
as a risk-free life.
Let's do it.
Wait for the subway.
Now.
This is where
the safe deposit boxes are.
We realized
we couldn't get to them
from inside the bank,
so we decided
to bring them to us.
You're gonna blow the roof.
We got something here.
John, what's your situation?
Ten more minutes.
I'm seeing
what I can only describe
as interference
on our phone link.
Is it Root?
No, it's
a broad spectrum sweep,
heavy-duty computer power.
Root's more subtle than that.
It must be our FBI friend.
Stay off the line
and please get out now.
If Shayn and Abby won't come,
leave them.
I don't leave people,
and they're bringing down
a very bad man.
Now, isn't that what
your experiment's all about?
My experiment
is about stopping people
from getting killed,
not robbing banks.
Five minutes and we're out.
In three, two, one.
Let's go.
There, 158.
His account's in a bank
in Venezuela.
- Is this what you need?
- Is it ever.
There's more than
$30 million here.
His charity stole $30 million.
Then let's go,
back the way we came.
Get down!
- You okay?
- Karma at last.
It's those thugs
Chapple hired, isn't it?
The bank opens in 30 minutes.
We've got to get out
before then.
Hang tight.
911 call.
Possible underground explosion
near Wall Street.
We're tracking IMEI bursts
in the same area. It's him.
Now, we hook up a
SWAT en route.
- Are you with us?
- Uh, yeah, of course.
I just need to make
a phone call.
All right, make it quick.
Hi, mom, can you make sure
Taylor gets to school?
Mom?
You been drinking, Carter?
Tell Harold, Donnelly is
headed to Wall Street.
He says John is there.
He's tracking the phones.
Okay, mom. Yes.
Thank you. I love you.
Hey, it's Fusco.
Wherever wonderboy is, I hope
it's not near Wall Street,
because that's where
Donnelly's heading.
That's exactly where John is.
Merton Watts Investment Bank,
Hanover Street.
Yeah, plus Carter
said something
about him being up
on your phones.
Just as I feared.
Anything you can do
to run interference for us
at the bank, Detective,
I would be most grateful.
I take it
you know this gentleman?
Peter Yogorov, enforcer
for the Russian mob.
Least he used to be until
Elias took out his old man.
Seems like something
that might be to our advantage.
To hit back at Elias?
To build
another revenue stream.
Yogorov's at MCC,
awaiting trial
with his little brother Lazlo.
DA's got him dead to rights
on a dozen different counts.
Maybe we can do something
about that.
You need something
on the District Attorney?
Let me handle that.
By going all spartan
on our emissaries,
Elias has made it clear--
that relationship is over.
We need new friends.
You want me to talk
to the Russians?
Open negotiations?
They have all the right pieces,
but with us behind them,
cash flow would no longer
be an issue.
Understood, boss.
Just heard something
interesting.
Looks like
that pain-in-the-ass Donnelly
finally caught up
with the man in the suit.
Not even 7:00 AM,
and already a perfect day.
The bank's about to open, John.
Where are you?
Mr. Reese,
what's happening?
I hate to say this, Finch,
but we're in a bit
of a pickle here.
Get upstairs to the foyer.
I have IDs and passes
for all of you.
Cover us.
What are you looking for?
Clothes.
You need to get changed.
We're gonna dress up
like bankers.
We're gonna climb up there
and walk right out
the front door.
Come on.
Base just picked up another
burst of comms from the target.
- Same location?
- Yes, sir.
So, you can track him, but you
can't hear what he's saying?
Do you know who
he's talking to?
Not yet.
Give me the gun.
You take Abby.
You've done enough.
I'm the one
who got us into this mess.
We all got ourselves
into this mess.
We're all going to
get ourselves out.
Now, when you get up
to the foyer, look for Harold.
I'll be right behind you.
Now.
Looks like nothing's
going on inside.
No, the signal's still active,
and the 911 call
said the explosion was
underground, remember?
He's in there.
All right, one team
in front with me,
second team, around the back.
We move in 30.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I'm a client here at the bank.
I need to get into
the vault now.
Hello.
Here. Take these.
My name is Harold Wren.
I own an insurance company.
You are my associates.
We have an appointment here.
Where's John?
FBI!
Everybody back against the wall!
- Stay where you are!
- Don't move!
- Hands up!
- See your hands!
Foyer's secure.
Check every ID.
No one leaves.
Half your men here,
half with me.
Yes, sir.
Let's go!
Hands where we can see them!
You! Don't move!
- See your ID, please?
- John, can you hear me?
Shayn and Abby are safe.
FBI are in the bank.
Get out now.
We got company.
Lose the weapons
and get the hell out.
John, can you hear me?
You must get out now.
Blew out the damn floor.
Alpha, this is Delta.
Vault level is secure.
I'm not gonna make it, Harold.
Sorry I screwed up.
But I meant
what I said yesterday.
So, thanks, Harold.
It was fun.
John?
ID?
Harold Wren,
Universal Heritage Insurance.
My associates.
Why are you in the bank?
We have a meeting
with the vice president
of Corporate Strategy.
ID.
Did you get what you wanted?
All the money Chapple stole.
More than $30 million.
Can you do anything
with the accounts?
Yes.
I'll empty them,
deposit every last cent
into the accounts of reputable
military charities.
Would that do?
Then I have to
get you out of here
and out of this state.
As long as we're together.
Check the top level.
Check down back.
Don't worry.
I got you covered.
What about John?
♪ It's just a shot away ♪
♪ it's just a shot away ♪
♪ baby ♪
We finally got you.
♪ It's just a shot away ♪
♪ it's just a shot away ♪
Sir, there's a problem.
Step back.
♪ It's just a shot away ♪
♪ it's just a shot away ♪
♪ yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Well, do you recognize him?
Uh...
no.
♪ Gimme, gimme shelter ♪
Cuff 'em all.
♪ Or I'm gonna fade away ♪
♪ war, children ♪
♪ it's just a shot away ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com