You are being watched.
The government
has a secret system...
A machine that spies on you
every hour of every day.
I designed the machine
to detect acts of terror,
but it sees everything...
Violent crimes
involving ordinary people.
The government considers
these people irrelevant.
We don't.
Hunted by the authorities,
we work in secret.
You will never find us.
But victim or perpetrator,
if your number's up,
we'll find you.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/
[Female voice]
911. What is your emergency?
This is
subway train operator 4827.
There's been an accident.
I couldn't stop the train
in time,
and I hit a kid.
I think
he might have been pushed.
Open.
I want 'em held in isolation.
No contact:
Not with their lawyers,
not with each other,
not with anybody.
This is a matter
of national security.
They're terrorists?
They look more like
investment bankers to me.
Well, warden,
three of them may be.
But one of them is
the most dangerous criminal
I've ever pursued.
I can hold them for 72 hours
without charging them,
and I fully intend to.
Then you have 72 hours.
This is Rikers, not Guantanamo.
You don't plan on asking them
any questions?
Don't worry, Carter.
We've got the DNA evidence
from new Rochelle,
we got the blood
from the burned car,
and, thanks to you,
fingerprints.
He's ours.
[Buzzer echoes]
[Overlapping murmuring]
[Metallic jingling]
[Buzzer]
[Metal clangs]
[Cell phone buzzing]
How did I know
the federal government would be
no match for you?
As I suspect
it might be compromising for you
to be found with a phone,
I'll be brief.
The matter is in hand, John.
We'll get you out of there.
I took too many risks.
It's my fault.
I'll handle it.
Listen to me.
I made preparations
for a scenario like this.
In 72 hours,
you will walk free.
What if
another number comes up?
Unfortunately,
as I told you,
they never stop coming.
I'll have
to manage as best I can.
I sincerely hope
our next conversation is
under better circumstances.
[Overlapping murmuring]
I'll be in touch.
My name is Mr. Swift.
I'm your substitute teacher.
Ms. Benthem received
a last-minute opportunity
to attend an all-expenses-paid
teaching seminar in Maui.
I see
in Ms. Benthem's lesson plan
that today we're doing...
Addition.
That can't be right.
It's busywork, punishment.
We're supposed
to add all the numbers
from one to a hundred.
You know,
in the late 18th century,
there was a math prodigy
named Carl Friedrich Gauss
who was faced
with the same tedious problem
that you are.
He figured a way around it.
One to a hundred.
Who'd like to take a crack
at working out Gauss' equation?
Anybody?
Mr. Phipps?
Uh...
I got to be honest, "Mr. Swifty,"
you lost me at "Friedrich."
[Laughter]
I'll give you a hint.
[Class bell rings]
[Overlapping murmuring]
[Cell phone rings]
- Fusco.
- Good morning, Detective.
I trust
that you received my email?
And the entire roll call
for Brooklyn science.
I need you
to tell me everything you can
about Caleb Phipps.
Couple run-ins with the NYPD.
Typical kid stuff.
- Nothing exceptional.
- I'll say.
2.6 gpa
and test scores that
sit squarely in the mid-range.
He spent my whole class doodling
in his notebook.
Hey, you still there?
Please continue.
One thing did come up.
Caleb had an older brother Ryan,
killed two years ago
in a subway accident.
Kid was drunk.
Slipped on the tracks
and got clipped.
Sounds awful.
Any further details?
I'll pull the incident report.
Now Caleb lives alone
with his mom.
She's an administrative
assistant in Kensington.
Hey, Caleb.
You going
to that party saturday?
Uh, no, that's
not my kind of thing.
Oh.
Besides,
I'm heading out of town.
Taking a trip.
[Overlapping murmuring]
They never seem
to stop texting.
Beginning to feel like
I'm on another planet.
Get used to it.
Their planet's gonna be running
ours in about ten years.
High schools
are different nowadays.
Gang fights, drug searches,
and pregnancies.
This kid could be
into anything.
[Cell phone
camera shutter clicks]
You weren't exaggerating
about the drug problem.
Kids ain't
what they used to be.
Be careful in there, pal.
I-I won't even ask.
Probably best.
Besides, we have
more urgent matters to discuss.
Our friend in Rikers.
I have the situation in hand.
I don't want you crossing
some kind of line to do...
This?
Already deleted them
from the network too.
That line
you're talking about,
I crossed it a long time ago.
Now we have
to deal with the DNA sample.
FBI keeps it in a secure lab
here in New York.
I know what to do.
But I'm gonna need
a couple things from you.
[Over P.A.]
This is principal Lawton,
reminding you
that the Brooklyn school
of science & humanities
closes promptly at 5:00 P.M.
Thank you.
Mr. Swift.
[Door shuts]
A word, please.
It has come to my attention
that you tried
to show Ms. Benthem's students
how to get around
one of her assignments.
Well, the assignment
seemed a bit remedial.
- I was hoping to teach...
- Teaching is Ms. Benthem's job.
Your job is to ensure
that her students
do the work
that she prepared.
Don't sweat Lawton.
She thinks schools
would run better
if they just got rid
of the students and teachers.
Chris Beckner,
computer science.
Harold Swift.
- Nice to meet an idealist.
- No, no, not me.
Throw all this stuff online,
I say.
Let me teach in my boxers.
Run wild, man.
[School bell rings]
I believe I will.
[Cell phone chime]
Yes, Detective Fusco?
Do you have some
new information for me?
Yeah, as a matter of fact,
I do.
I took a look at the report
of his brother's death.
- Caleb was the only witness.
- He was there?
His brother died
right in front of him?
Yeah, but something's
not right.
I looked at every incident
report that night.
The transit cop called
for a backup, to dispatch,
and then canceled the request.
Why would a policeman rescind
a request for backup?
That's what I'm trying
to figure out.
I'm waiting on the transcripts
to find out why.
Maybe it's time
I go meet Caleb's mom
and find out
what his home life is like.
Interesting.
Caleb's latest
national aptitude test score
is exactly 50%.
A statistically
improbable score.
Unless you try to get it.
You see, Caleb knew the answer
to every question.
But he chose only
to fill in every other one.
I don't get it.
He tanked on purpose?
Why would you want to hide
the fact you're a genius?
Why, indeed?
Caleb, a word?
I couldn't help but notice this.
No offense, Mr. Swift,
but now you're going
through the garbage?
[School bell rings]
[Murmuring fades]
Pi.
Can any of you tell me
what it means?
I'll settle for
an intelligent question here.
My friend has a question,
Mr. Swift.
"What is any of this good for,
and when would we ever use it?"
[Laughter]
Let me show you.
Pi.
The ratio of the circumference
of a circle
to its diameter.
And this is just the beginning.
It keeps on going.
Forever.
Without ever repeating.
Which means that contained
within this string of decimals
is every single other number.
Your birth date, combination
to your locker,
your social security number.
It's all in there somewhere.
And if you convert
these decimals into letters,
you would have every word
that ever existed
in every possible combination.
The first syllable you spoke
as a baby,
the name of your latest crush,
your entire life story
from beginning to end.
Everything we ever say or do...
All of the world's infinite
possibilities rest
within this one simple circle.
Now what you do
with that information...
What it's good for...
Well, that would be up to you.
[Knock on door]
NYPD, ma'am.
We're investigating
a string of burglaries
in the area.
Talking
to residents about things
they might have seen or heard.
Mind if I come in
and ask you a few questions?
I'm running a little late.
So you, uh, you live alone?
With my son Caleb.
We don't have a lot of room,
so Caleb takes the couch.
[Cell phone rings]
Uh, that's work.
Just give me a sec.
So you and your son see
anything suspicious lately?
Any strange comings and goings?
Anyone who stands out?
Nothing I can think of.
Cops come a few times a year.
It's domestic stuff mostly.
Some families have it rough,
you know?
Yeah, I know
exactly what you mean.
Thanks for your time.
[Door opens]
[Static, voices]
Yes, Detective?
I planted that webcam for you.
Met Caleb's mom.
[Sighs]
Late for work, rolling
out the door with the shakes.
My guess is
she's hitting the bottle.
No wonder Caleb doesn't care
about his grades.
Anything new on our two dealers?
Diego Velasquez
and Ronnie Samms.
Used to deal for a guy
by the name of Lorenzo.
Type of guy
you don't wanna cross.
But now they're working
for some new up-and-comer
that narcotics
hasn't been able to identify.
I tell you, that school's
a real minefield.
Okay.
[Door slams]
Gonna keep your mouth shut,
right, chief?
Yeah, sure.
[Sighs]
Except to say this.
The next time you decide
you want to deal E
to a kid who's clearly never
bought in his entire life,
do it
in the locker room downstairs,
because this jumpy fool
is a neon sign shouting
"drugs ahoy"... Chief.
That's enough!
Unless you want to settle this
in the principal's office.
Are you okay?
I don't need your help... okay?
"Hacker" used to refer
to industrious coders
who pushed the boundaries
of modern computing.
Then that word
became misappropriated
by those who pushed
the boundaries so far
that they ended up
with jail time.
Like Kevin Mitnick,
back in the 1980s.
He was just trying
to see how stuff worked.
Mitnick was looking
for flaws in the system.
And he did so
by breaking the law.
But he proved people were
the flaw, not the code.
Now they're paying him millions
for the same thing that got him
locked up in the first place.
[Laughter]
Perhaps the most notorious
hacker of them all
was the one that got away.
Back when Uncle Sam was trying
to maintain IriTrip
on the budding Internet...
Or Arpanet,
as it was known then...
This hacker, this coder,
hacked into the system
and laid its secrets bare,
ensuring that the Internet
would become an open forum.
Plus that hacker made his mark
without ever getting busted.
True.
Whoever it was,
that person's still out there.
[School bell rings]
[Cell phone buzzes]
Hey, I'm checking
on the boy genius.
Not you, the other one.
Turns out
he's quite the little coder.
He's been coding
a massive program.
In longhand, he doesn't
have a computer at home.
Then he writes it
into a computer in the lab.
If the partial code
I've discovered
is a snapshot of his work...
What he's creating...
Could be groundbreaking.
Detective Fusco,
can you do something for me?
I need you
to follow Diego and Ronnie.
Caleb had a run-in
with them today
that might lead to trouble.
- Is there a history there?
- Hard to tell.
But Caleb seemed
to take an outsized interest
in their drug dealing.
If someone's pulling
their strings,
I'd like to know who.
Finch, whoever this drug
dealer is, he's careful.
[Cell phone chimes]
Detective, how goes
phase one of your plan?
I got
the package you sent over,
but if I'm gonna wade
in this pool,
I need the right specs.
Yeah.
Sending them to you now.
Our friend in Rikers
is counting on you.
- Okay.
- Knock 'em dead, Detective.
They won't know
what hit 'em.
[Mellow club music]
Wow.
Hi, I'd like to have...
The first one, on me.
How are you doing?
Thanks, but, um, I'm looking
for something a little more...
Specific.
Detective Fusco,
our Young man is on the move.
Give you a ride home?
Car is right down there.
I'd like that.
I have to admit,
you kind of threw me at first.
Asking all those questions
about my background,
my health.
I couldn't tell whether
we were flirtin'
or fillin' out
my medical history.
I'm a practical girl.
I like to know
what I'm getting into.
[Giggles]
So are we... Getting
into anything tonight?
I am.
Ooh, I don't know
what happened, but...
I didn't even have
that much to drink.
Yeah.
[Clicks tongue]
Open wide, big fella.
I've been following
this drug money all night.
Diego and Ronnie
handed a bagful of it
to a homeless guy,
who I followed
till he dumped it off
at a money transfer place.
The worker there wired it
to another money hub
across town,
where I hoofed it over there
just in time
to see some other guy
pick up the cash
and drop it in a P.O. box
right here in crown heights.
Our mysterious drug lord
is laundering his money,
making it untraceable.
Well, not untraceable enough.
Whoever comes in
for this cash is our guy.
Where are you anyway?
I'm looking at you.
Thought you were following
the kid.
I am.
- Here you go, sir.
- Thanks.
Well, I'll be damned.
Our mystery drug lord
is Caleb.
Graded your quizzes.
Some of you have been
paying attention.
Caleb, I expected better.
Pssh.
[Cell phone rings]
- What did the kid do now?
- Caleb just got a message.
He's supposed
to meet his supplier at 2:00.
We have to follow him.
Tricky little bastard,
keeping his identity a secret.
He's better
than most dealers twice his age.
I'll be sure and tell him
how impressed you are
with his criminal aptitude.
[Class bell rings]
Beckman just broke
into Caleb's account, Detective.
He copying a file
named 17-6-21
onto a thumb drive.
Whatever Caleb's making...
His teacher's interest in it...
Is far from academic.
[Overlapping murmuring]
Oh, Mr. Phipps!
Look, I'm kind of
on my way somewhere.
I just wanted
to return something of yours.
You dropped this yesterday.
You really got to stop going
through the trash, Mr. Swift.
You know, I used
to do a little coding myself.
That's an elegant string
you have.
But it occurs
to me that if you want
to implement multi-threading,
you'd do better
to use atomic variables.
Just a thought.
Wait, that...
That works.
Yes, that's why
I suggested it.
Uh, thanks.
I hope you have your service
weapon with you, Detective.
Yeah, I got you
a machine gun too.
Very funny, Detective.
Let's try not to lose him.
Yo, Roman.
You here?
[Moaning]
Oh, jeez.
[Triggers clicking]
Whoa.
That's what
you came for, right?
So tell me...
Why would a kid like you
do something so stupid
like dealing at a school
in my neighborhood?
That's Lorenzo, all right,
Diego and Ronnie's old boss.
What's the plan?
Crap.
You know, before he had
his little accident here...
Roman was telling me
how you're just trying
to score some bank
to take a big trip.
That true?
Yeah.
You pay back
every dime you made
selling to my customers,
I'll let you leave town intact.
Be back here tomorrow
night, 8:00 P.M.,
or I'll come find you.
How do you expect me
to score that kind of cash
in a day?
Relax.
All right, I'll...
Rob a bank or something.
I like you.
You got brass.
But you don't show
tomorrow night...
Break a lot more than your legs.
Kid's got it tough.
But picking a fight
with a drug dealer?
A dumb move for a genius.
Why would a Young man
with such potential
risk it all just
to get some easy drug money?
I don't think
it's about the money.
I think it's about the brother.
[Paper rustling]
Dispatch transcripts
from the night Ryan Phipps died.
Now the transit cop who filed
the report called for backup...
Because Caleb initially reported
that two youths got
into a shoving match with Ryan,
pushed him onto the tracks.
But the officer canceled
the backup call
and filed
an accident report instead.
Why would Caleb
change his story?
Maybe he knew the killers.
Maybe he was thinking about
taking care of them himself.
Diego and Ronnie?
He's manipulating
those morons.
Got 'em running drugs for him,
and they don't even know it.
What's Beckner so absorbed in?
That's Caleb's work.
[Line rings]
Howard, it's Chris.
Can you still meet up tonight?
I think you'll be impressed
with what you see.
Great. I'll see you there.
- Change of plans, Detective.
- Let me guess.
You need me to keep an eye
on little Einstein,
myself, tonight.
Keep me posted.
[Static, voices]
So, Mr. venture capital
firm partner...
Junior partner.
Long way from the corner office.
Still have
to watch my step.
- Pick my projects carefully.
- I get it.
When you see this...
Well, then, let's...
Let's just see it, Chris,
so I can get back
to my wife and kids.
[Sighs]
[Computer trilling]
What the hell was that?
The library of congress.
What?
235 terabytes on...
On one thumb drive?
The Internet's choking
on streaming video.
They're gonna need
a new compression algorithm
to continue growing.
And I've got it.
All I need is an investment
from a firm like yours
to help me get it
off the ground.
So... here's the thing,
Chris.
I remember your code
from back in college.
You were a medium talent
at best.
There is no way that
that Chris Beckner
designed something
this extraordinary.
Unlike our old friends, I
didn't peak in college.
So no one else knows
about this project?
Programmers? Developers?
No other entanglements?
I can guarantee it.
Well, let's hope so.
Because I would hate for anyone
to come between you
and what I believe is going
to be a very large check.
[Beep]
Finally tracked down
that transit cop, Murphy.
The one who was first
on the scene
when Caleb's brother died.
Left a message for him
to come down to the eighth
after his shift.
Speaking of which,
where's the kid now?
He's moving money around,
large amounts.
Getting the cash
to pay off Lorenzo?
No, he set up
some kind of a trust,
and he's pouring
all his money into it.
Maybe he's thinking
about taking that trip
he's always talking about.
[Cell phone buzzing]
Beckner just texted Caleb.
He wants
to meet at 8:00 tonight.
The same time he's supposed
to meet Lorenzo.
And quantum physics
notwithstanding,
he can't be
in two places at once.
Unless I'm right,
and this kid's got a plan,
time's running out
on two fronts.
Maybe skipping town's
the best thing for him.
Then we could focus some on
getting your pal out of lockup.
Mr. Reese can take care
of himself, Detective.
And right now,
he's in very capable hands.
Detective Carter,
time is ticking away fast
for our friend in Rikers.
Don't worry.
I know what to do.
[Over computer]
Here you go.
Mm. Sorry, honey.
I'll be better tomorrow.
I promise.
Yeah.
Everything's gonna
be better tomorrow, ma.
Detective Fusco.
I just want to remind you
that I need your help tonight.
Caleb has two appointments,
and we have no idea which one
he intends to keep.
I'll be there.
You wanted to speak with me?
Yeah, have a seat,
officer Murphy.
Like I said, I'm, uh...
Working on a cold case.
Commuter got pushed.
Looking for related cases,
this popped up.
Ryan Phipps.
Says here you were first
on the scene?
Yeah, that's right.
Kid was six months shy
of his 18th birthday.
Coming home
with his little brother Caleb.
Ryan was horsing around,
drinking a little bit.
Slipped on the tracks
and got clipped.
Yeah, yeah, I remember.
It was a rough one.
Because it was a kid?
Or because you didn't report
the whole story?
I know about the kids
who pushed Ryan on the tracks.
I'm no Detective, Detective.
I'm just a lowly transit cop.
I seen a lot of things
in my time.
And I made a lot
of decisions I regret.
This is not one of those times.
You may regret it
when Caleb becomes a killer.
What are you talking about?
You think revenge is gonna
make Caleb feel better
about seeing his brother die?
You're a long ways off,
Detective.
Then give me some directions.
You know, I did to the kid
what you're doing
to me right now.
When I asked him
for descriptions
of the other kids...
Kept changing it up.
There were no other kids.
[Quietly]
No.
Just two brothers drinking.
Bored.
Waiting for a train
to go home.
So they dare each other
to, uh... cross the tracks.
You know, how many times
you can cross back and forth
before a train comes?
Well, Ryan doesn't want to lose
to his little brother.
One kid makes it,
the other kid doesn't.
I don't know
who got the better deal.
So I told him I'd leave all that
out of the report,
write it up as an accident,
and for him
to keep it to himself.
So no matter what he had
to tell his mom...
Or the cops,
or God himself...
Nothing was gonna bring
his brother back.
What can I tell you?
Some things you can't fix.
[Cell phone rings]
[Beep]
Hey, I just talked
to Murphy.
The brother's death
was an accident,
but it sounds like
Caleb blames himself for it.
Well, that's a problem,
Detective,
because I lost Caleb.
He got on a city bus, and it
left before I could catch up.
You're kidding me.
May I remind you that of the
many things I'm equipped to do,
pursuit would not be chief
among them.
Our only option now
is to wait for Caleb
at the two places
he's likeliest to turn up.
I'll stake out beckner
at the High School.
You keep an eye out
for our aggrieved drug dealer.
Get everyone,
and hunt that kid down!
[Line dials]
Our boy is a no-show,
and Lorenzo wants his head.
You worry about the kid.
I'll take care of Lorenzo.
[Panting] He's
not here either, Detective.
I may be too late.
Swift,
what are you doing here?
I was gonna ask you the same.
- I-I left some papers on...
- Stop it!
I saw you break
into Caleb's account
and copy his files.
Is that what you're willing
to stoop to?
Stealing the work of a student
and passing it off as your own?
I am not gonna stand here
and be accused of plagiarism
by some substitute teacher.
Besides, why would I copy work
off of a "C"-grade student?
Because Caleb
is anything but average.
And you know it.
That's why you took his work
to your friend.
Caleb... Approached
me a few months ago
about this project
he was working on.
I was skeptical,
but when I... saw his code
I couldn't believe my eyes,
so I decided to help him.
- By cutting him out of it.
- No.
All he wanted was
some money up front
for this trip that he wants
to take.
Said he didn't even want
any credit.
Why on earth
would you agree to that?
I didn't.
Read it for yourself.
Caleb gets all the credit.
It was just easier for me to...
Pitch the idea
with him myself...
Get some capital...
And then reveal
the true brain behind it.
He offered me half
if I put the other half
in a trust that he set up
for his mom.
But I'm giving him
the whole thing.
All the money from 17-6-21.
17-6-21?
It's the name
he gave the program.
He said it was some kind
of dedication.
Look, I am telling you,
six months from now,
Caleb is going
to be the richest 18-year-old
in the country.
No.
No, he won't.
Dispatch?
Officer Murphy,
regarding the subway fatality.
on the backup request.
10-5, officer.
Cancel backup request?
Affirmative.
This seat taken?
What are you doing here?
You're so smart, Caleb.
Ask me something you don't know.
The thing
about being reckless...
Taking chances...
Is that you make
a lot of mistakes,
cause a lot of grief.
Gonna start lecturing me
on mistakes?
How I need to live and learn?
Move on?
That's really inspiring,
Mr. Swift.
I'd stand up on my desk
and clap for you.
But... No.
Your mistakes, like mine,
are part of who you are now.
You can't move on from that.
Believe me.
I've made a sizable number.
But... Sometimes your
mistakes can surprise you.
My biggest mistake,
for instance...
Brought me here.
At exactly this moment...
When you might need some help.
17 years, 6 months
and 21 days into your life.
The age
at which your brother died.
The age you've chosen
to end your life too.
17-6-21.
So, you see... Maybe you
and I are connected.
Two reckless people.
Yeah? Then what's the use?
We're just gonna keep
breaking things...
Over and over.
Why not save everyone the grief?
The thing about the world is
that it doesn't have
any extra pieces.
It's like pi.
It contains everything.
You remove a single piece...
No circle.
Your recklessness,
your mistakes,
are the reason why,
when they say
"you can't change the world,"
you won't listen.
The world is better off
with both of us in it, Caleb,
- rather than the alternative.
- Yeah? You sure about that?
Yes, and your mom is
better off with you in it.
If you think
money can replace you...
You haven't seen
the whole equation.
Take it
from someone who thought
that leaving would make it
easier on everyone...
And then learned otherwise.
[Subway train rumbling]
[Rumbling fades]
[Dramatic music]
♪
Say it to me again.
Slowly.
According to the lab results,
none of the DNA we took
from these four men
matches any of the DNA
in our database.
They're clean, sir.
All four of 'em.
I want every one of
those samples sent to Quantico,
reviewed through codis,
and inspected for tampering.
They got to it.
I don't know how,
but those bastards got to it.
Go.
One more thing.
Get me Carter.
You really ought to be
more careful with your code.
Thanks.
I grew up during
the Cold War...
When computer networks
were just a gleam
in the eye
of the department of defense.
Things seemed
more black and white then.
Arpanet was the new frontier.
Till a kid
with a homemade computer
turned the whole thing
inside out.
All I'm saying is...
It's a new era now,
and things are about
to get really weird.
So you should keep your code
close to your vest.
And pick your friends wisely.
Pi.
The first 3,000 digits.
My number's in there somewhere.
You're smart,
you'll figure it out.
Wait, uh, the hacker.
The one who got away?
How'd you know he did that
with a homemade computer?
I've read all that research.
No one's ever mentioned that.
I must have heard it
somewhere.
Detective Carter?
Has our friend in Rikers
been released?
Almost. I'm going
to meet him now.
[Keys jingling]
Your DNA wasn't a match for
whoever they're looking for.
We'll be processing you out
momentarily.
[Gate buzzes]
Stop right there.
These men have
all been classified
as "unlawful combatants"
by the AUMF.
Until we can establish
that they're not a threat
to national security,
they're not going anywhere.
[Paper rustles]
Put him back.
Just the person
I wanted to see.
What is going on?
I thought the evidence
cleared these guys.
The DNA, the fingerprints,
it's all too neat.
I've been burned too many times
trying to bring this man
to justice.
There's only one person
that I know I can trust anymore:
You.
You've been chasing him
from the beginning.
And we've only got one shot left
at him, Detective.
If he walks out of here,
we're never gonna see him again.
I know you were
a senior interrogator in Iraq.
It's time to put
those military skills to use.
I want you to interrogate
every last one of these men.
Find out who they are,
what they know.
Start with him.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/