1
00:00:02,140 --> 00:00:03,530
你被监视着
You are being watched.

2
00:00:04,580 --> 00:00:06,480
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--

3
00:00:06,890 --> 00:00:10,420
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.

5
00:00:10,020 --> 00:00:10,180
{\pos(180,210)}联系系统管理员

6
00:00:10,350 --> 00:00:10,520
{\pos(180,210)}联系系统管理员

7
00:00:10,690 --> 00:00:10,850
{\pos(180,210)}联系系统管理员

8
00:00:11,020 --> 00:00:11,270
{\pos(180,210)}联系系统管理员

9
00:00:11,340 --> 00:00:13,660
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror

10
00:00:13,520 --> 00:00:13,650
身份不明

11
00:00:13,650 --> 00:00:13,770
身份不明

12
00:00:13,770 --> 00:00:15,090
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--

13
00:00:13,940 --> 00:00:14,110
身份不明

14
00:00:14,270 --> 00:00:14,440
身份不明

15
00:00:14,610 --> 00:00:14,770
身份不明

16
00:00:15,500 --> 00:00:18,110
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.

17
00:00:18,950 --> 00:00:21,620
政府以为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.

18
00:00:21,820 --> 00:00:22,700
关键执行人

19
00:00:21,940 --> 00:00:22,780
我们不
We don't.

20
00:00:22,070 --> 00:00:22,360
失踪

21
00:00:22,530 --> 00:00:22,700
失踪

22
00:00:22,700 --> 00:00:23,320
关键执行人

23
00:00:22,860 --> 00:00:23,030
失踪

24
00:00:23,200 --> 00:00:23,360
失踪

25
00:00:23,320 --> 00:00:23,660
关键执行人

26
00:00:24,070 --> 00:00:27,910
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.

27
00:00:24,620 --> 00:00:24,910
状态：纽约警局任职

28
00:00:25,070 --> 00:00:25,580
状态：纽约警局任职

29
00:00:25,580 --> 00:00:25,990
状态：纽约警局任职

30
00:00:25,990 --> 00:00:26,160
状态：纽约警局任职

31
00:00:26,990 --> 00:00:27,290
状态：纽约警局任职

32
00:00:27,450 --> 00:00:28,540
状态：纽约警局任职

33
00:00:28,600 --> 00:00:29,930
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.

34
00:00:30,320 --> 00:00:32,400
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,

35
00:00:32,580 --> 00:00:35,460
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.

36
00:00:35,000 --> 00:00:38,420
{\pos(195,180)}疑犯追踪

37
00:00:35,000 --> 00:00:38,420
{\pos(190,196)}第二季 第十集

38
00:00:39,180 --> 00:00:40,250
妈  爸
Hi, mom. Hi, dad.

39
00:00:41,420 --> 00:00:43,400
要是你们看到这个  就说明我现在有麻烦了
If you're watching this, you'll know I'm in trouble.

40
00:00:44,710 --> 00:00:46,060
我一直都很乖
I've always tried to be good,

41
00:00:47,670 --> 00:00:49,120
循规蹈矩
keep the rules.

42
00:00:50,840 --> 00:00:52,770
这次我要干件彻底逆转的大事
Now I'm gonna break them in a big way.

43
00:00:54,000 --> 00:00:58,000
<font color="#00ff00">-=耐卡影音论坛=-
www.ncar.cc/bbs
欣赏更多精彩美剧</font>

51
00:01:06,000 --> 00:01:10,000
<font color="#ffff00">字幕源自Internet</font>

53
00:01:12,570 --> 00:01:13,500
安抚住他
Just hold him still.

54
00:01:14,260 --> 00:01:16,650
小熊  趴下  坐好
Bear, afliggen! Sit.

55
00:01:16,790 --> 00:01:18,210
可真是帮了大忙了
Well, that was a big help.

56
00:01:18,460 --> 00:01:19,870
你说我们又有新号码了
So, you said we had another number?

57
00:01:20,030 --> 00:01:22,560
是的  艾比·门罗  26岁
Yes. Abby Monroe, 26.

58
00:01:22,560 --> 00:01:25,200
学校里的优秀学生  有工程学学位
Honor student at school, degree in engineering.

59
00:01:25,320 --> 00:01:27,830
去年在一家军人慈善组织工作
She's worked for the last year at a military charity,

60
00:01:27,830 --> 00:01:29,740
名叫"归国英雄之家"
Homes For Our Returning Heroes,

61
00:01:30,400 --> 00:01:31,830
也许是因为她弟弟
Maybe because her younger brother

62
00:01:31,830 --> 00:01:34,310
一年半前在阿富汗牺牲
was killed in Afghanistan 18 months ago.

63
00:01:36,700 --> 00:01:38,830
她上周从那家慈善组织辞职了
She quit the charity a week ago.

64
00:01:39,250 --> 00:01:42,650
现在在一家城市规划办公室做短期工
She's now working as a temp in a city planning office.

65
00:01:43,100 --> 00:01:43,950
发现威胁了吗
Any threats?

66
00:01:44,090 --> 00:01:46,740
没发现  不过有些异常
Not that I can see, but some anomalies.

67
00:01:47,040 --> 00:01:48,640
她五天前弃用了电话
She dumped her phone five days ago

68
00:01:48,640 --> 00:01:49,840
搬出了公寓
and moved out of her apartment.

69
00:01:49,840 --> 00:01:51,580
其实  我现在追踪她
In fact, the only way I could trace her

70
00:01:51,720 --> 00:01:53,640
只能靠短期工中介
was through the temp agency.

71
00:01:53,910 --> 00:01:55,200
她在躲什么人
She's hiding from someone.

72
00:01:56,290 --> 00:01:57,650
我最好盯紧她
I'd better get eyes on her.

73
00:01:58,540 --> 00:01:59,970
现在轮到你来吹干
It's your turn to dry him.

74
00:02:00,340 --> 00:02:02,500
她随时可能有危险啊  芬奇
She could be in imminent danger, Finch.

75
00:02:02,660 --> 00:02:04,020
里瑟先生  这是你的狗
Mr. Reese, he's your dog.

76
00:02:04,020 --> 00:02:04,790
你搞定呗
You'll manage.

77
00:02:14,890 --> 00:02:17,340
-你好警探  -你好警探
- Detective. - Detective.

78
00:02:18,110 --> 00:02:21,140
上次晚餐挺好玩的  我们再约一次如何
Dinner was fun. What about doing it again?

79
00:02:23,280 --> 00:02:25,280
我今晚有空  真巧
I'm free tonight, as it happens.

80
00:02:26,110 --> 00:02:29,270
抱歉  我有个案子要跟
Sorry. Got a case I'm looking at.

81
00:02:30,610 --> 00:02:33,410
其实就是他  戴维森
Him, actually. Davidson.

82
00:02:32,640 --> 00:02:34,950
{\an8}失踪
伊恩·戴维森警探

83
00:02:33,410 --> 00:02:35,500
去年冬天失踪的内务部警察
The Internal Affairs cop went missing last winter.

84
00:02:35,500 --> 00:02:36,160
你认识他吗
Did you know him?

85
00:02:36,750 --> 00:02:38,980
岂止认识  我还跟他有过节
Know him? I had some run-ins with him.

86
00:02:39,260 --> 00:02:40,280
有什么发现
What's your interest?

87
00:02:40,280 --> 00:02:42,620
有条线报  匿名的
I got a tip, anonymous.

88
00:02:43,190 --> 00:02:44,730
说他被个警察谋杀了
Said a cop killed him.

89
00:02:47,070 --> 00:02:49,280
也许他牵扯进了HR的生意中
Well, maybe he was mixed up in some HR business.

90
00:02:49,830 --> 00:02:51,690
也许HR的警察把他弄掉了
Maybe an HR cop took him out.

91
00:02:51,810 --> 00:02:55,400
我听说51街有个组织在清理贩货人
I heard of one group out of the 51st was offing dealers

92
00:02:55,400 --> 00:02:56,470
并且在清货
and selling their supply.

93
00:02:56,900 --> 00:02:58,280
知道名字吗
You got any names?

94
00:02:58,570 --> 00:03:01,050
大部分不是跑路了就是死掉了  不过也不是全部
Most of them are behind bars or dead, but not all of them.

95
00:03:02,710 --> 00:03:04,000
能打扰一下吗
Will you excuse us?

96
00:03:04,000 --> 00:03:05,610
卡特警探  我们得谈谈
Detective Carter, we need to talk.

97
00:03:08,250 --> 00:03:09,540
晚点聊
I'll catch up with you later.

98
00:03:11,650 --> 00:03:14,430
HR一案现在只剩下些枝节在处理了
So, with HR degraded to the point of irrelevance,

99
00:03:14,430 --> 00:03:17,130
所以我们的工作重心现在转移到西装男身上
my team is shifting priorities back to the man in the suit.

100
00:03:17,380 --> 00:03:19,210
他还逍遥在外  你还想抓到他吧
He's still out there. Do you still want to catch him?

101
00:03:19,330 --> 00:03:20,720
想  当然
Yes, of course.

102
00:03:21,320 --> 00:03:22,160
好
Good.

103
00:03:23,860 --> 00:03:25,150
我们有些新发现
We have some new information,

104
00:03:25,550 --> 00:03:27,240
发现了他为之工作的人
including who he's working for.

105
00:03:27,380 --> 00:03:29,870
局里一直在追查
Now, the Bureau has been tracking the emergence

106
00:03:29,870 --> 00:03:31,610
私人情报网
of private intelligence networks,

107
00:03:31,610 --> 00:03:34,330
就像中情局和军情六处那种  不过是营利性质的
like the CIA or MI6, but for profit.

108
00:03:34,450 --> 00:03:37,070
我们认为其中最大的一个有中国背景
We think the biggest of these has Chinese backing.

109
00:03:37,320 --> 00:03:39,870
他们有技术  有资源
They've got technology, serious resources,

110
00:03:39,990 --> 00:03:41,570
并一直在持续买进
and they've been buying up tant.

111
00:03:41,680 --> 00:03:43,400
比如  我们认为马克·斯诺
For instance, we think Mark Snow,

112
00:03:43,400 --> 00:03:44,970
那名联系你的中情局特工
the CIA agent who contacted you,

113
00:03:44,970 --> 00:03:46,340
可能被招募了
may also have been recruited,

114
00:03:46,480 --> 00:03:48,430
可能就是被西装男招募
possibly by the man in the suit.

115
00:03:48,830 --> 00:03:51,590
-真的吗  斯诺  -讲得通
- Really? Snow? - Makes sense.

116
00:03:51,700 --> 00:03:54,020
斯诺被中情局派来追他
I mean, Snow was sent to find this man by the CIA.

117
00:03:54,020 --> 00:03:56,380
他抓到了  然后西装男策反了他
He catches him, and then the man in the suit flips him.

118
00:03:56,490 --> 00:03:57,840
让斯诺成为了他的情报提供者
Gets Snow to be his asset.

119
00:03:58,620 --> 00:04:00,770
卡特  我想你介入
Listen, Carter, I want to read you into this,

120
00:04:00,940 --> 00:04:02,280
但这是机密
but it's classified,

121
00:04:02,440 --> 00:04:03,910
所以上边允许我招募你
so I've been authorized to offer you

122
00:04:03,910 --> 00:04:05,620
到局里做临时雇员
a temporary assignment to the Bureau.

123
00:04:06,750 --> 00:04:08,510
我知道  凭你的能力
And I know, with your skills,

124
00:04:08,770 --> 00:04:10,040
很快就会升为永久雇员
it'll soon become permanent.

125
00:04:10,730 --> 00:04:12,940
你一加入  我就能让你介入本案
Sooner you're on board, sooner I can fill you in.

126
00:04:12,940 --> 00:04:14,410
所以  请考虑一下
So, please, think about it.

127
00:04:14,600 --> 00:04:16,380
我会的  谢谢你
I will. Thank you.

128
00:04:20,210 --> 00:04:21,010
谢了
Thanks.

129
00:04:25,790 --> 00:04:26,500
卡特
Carter.

130
00:04:26,500 --> 00:04:27,180
你好  警探
Hello, Detective.

131
00:04:27,330 --> 00:04:28,910
我得找到那位朋友
I need to find our friend.

132
00:04:29,360 --> 00:04:30,610
我们有大麻烦了
We have a big problem.

133
00:04:31,430 --> 00:04:33,710
你去城市规划局找他吧
You'll find him at the Department of City Planning.

134
00:04:49,400 --> 00:04:51,140
那她下载完文件就走了
So she just downloaded the file and walked out?

135
00:04:51,140 --> 00:04:51,730
是的
Yeah.

136
00:04:53,700 --> 00:04:55,200
你们没一个人拦住她
Didn't anyone try to stop her?

137
00:04:55,340 --> 00:04:57,060
看来当时没人知道啊
Apparently nobody noticed.

138
00:04:57,260 --> 00:04:59,740
我是卡特警探  什么情况
Detective Carter. Uh, what do we got?

139
00:04:59,960 --> 00:05:02,030
你也收到报告了  警探
You heard the 10-31 too, Detective?

140
00:05:02,460 --> 00:05:04,310
是啊  怎么样了
Yep. So, what is it?

141
00:05:04,430 --> 00:05:06,630
我们刚刚告诉了这位詹宁斯法警
Like we were telling Marshal Jennings here--

142
00:05:06,630 --> 00:05:07,780
詹宁斯法警啊
Marshal Jennings, huh?

143
00:05:08,620 --> 00:05:10,720
经理报告说他的一位职员
The manager called it in 'cause one of his staff,

144
00:05:10,720 --> 00:05:12,190
叫艾比·门罗的姑娘
a girl by the name of Abby Monroe,

145
00:05:12,190 --> 00:05:13,990
非法下载了一份文件
downloaded a file illegally.

146
00:05:13,990 --> 00:05:15,720
两小时前离开了
And walked out with it two hours ago.

147
00:05:15,720 --> 00:05:17,070
等有人发现已经晚了
No one noticed till too late.

148
00:05:17,320 --> 00:05:18,970
有人知道文件里是什么内容吗
Well, does anyone know what's on the file?

149
00:05:18,970 --> 00:05:21,090
我们存了一些重要建筑物的规划
Well, we keep plans here for some important buildings,

150
00:05:21,090 --> 00:05:23,380
不过她拿走的只是
but all she walked out with were some engineering drawings

151
00:05:23,380 --> 00:05:26,220
华尔街附近汉诺威街1400的工程样图
for the 1400 block of Hanover near Wall Street.

152
00:05:26,340 --> 00:05:27,530
那里有配电站
It's got an elerical sub-station,

153
00:05:27,680 --> 00:05:30,780
律师事务所  还有家投行总部
lawyers' offices, and the HQ of an investment bank.

154
00:05:30,920 --> 00:05:33,130
没什么关键性基础设施目标
Nothing like a critical infrastructure target.

155
00:05:33,130 --> 00:05:35,460
有没有人知道艾比·门罗住在哪里
So, does anyone know where this Abby Monroe lives?

156
00:05:35,460 --> 00:05:36,360
我们查了
We ran a check.

157
00:05:36,450 --> 00:05:38,010
她给的地址是假的
The address she gave us is fake.

158
00:05:38,370 --> 00:05:39,570
电话号码是投币式公用电话
The phone number is a pay phone.

159
00:05:41,940 --> 00:05:43,330
这里的背景调查可真靠谱
Hey, solid background check there.

160
00:05:43,460 --> 00:05:44,370
怎么说呢
What can I say?

161
00:05:44,500 --> 00:05:45,980
她看起来是个乖巧的孩子
I mean, she seemed like a sweet kid.

162
00:05:46,480 --> 00:05:48,530
居然是装的  真令人失望
Kind of disappointing to find she was a flake.

163
00:05:49,250 --> 00:05:52,760
孩子嘛  说不准的  是吧警探
Kids. You never know. Right, Detective?

164
00:05:52,760 --> 00:05:53,490
是啊
Right.

165
00:05:53,990 --> 00:05:56,690
总之  干得不错  跟进及时
Anyway, good job, following up so quickly.

166
00:05:57,480 --> 00:05:58,290
失陪了各位
Gentlemen.

167
00:05:59,220 --> 00:06:00,040
谢谢你  法警
Thank you, Marshal.

168
00:06:00,690 --> 00:06:02,920
如果有其他发现
Look, if you come up with anything else,

169
00:06:02,920 --> 00:06:03,680
给我电话
give me a call.

170
00:06:05,440 --> 00:06:06,800
约翰  约翰
John. John!

171
00:06:07,130 --> 00:06:08,440
你脑子进水了吗
Are you out of your mind?

172
00:06:08,440 --> 00:06:10,580
居然冒充执法人员
Impersonating a law enforcement officer?

173
00:06:11,260 --> 00:06:13,430
詹宁斯法警  你拿了他的徽章
Marshal Jennings? You took his star?

174
00:06:13,750 --> 00:06:15,430
他反正也不用了
He wasn't using it anymore.

175
00:06:15,930 --> 00:06:16,860
很好用啊  卡特
It's great, Carter.

176
00:06:16,860 --> 00:06:19,220
把徽章一亮  人们就知无不言了
Just flash a badge, and people tell you everything.

177
00:06:19,220 --> 00:06:20,280
你别再作了  约翰
You gotta stop, John.

178
00:06:20,280 --> 00:06:22,970
唐纳利又来了  一心要抓西装男
Donnelly's back, and he's hot for the man in the suit.

179
00:06:23,480 --> 00:06:24,650
他有了新的想法
He has a new theory.

180
00:06:24,880 --> 00:06:26,720
是啊  我在为中国工作之类的
Yeah, that I'm working for China or something.

181
00:06:27,210 --> 00:06:28,000
我们听到了
We heard.

182
00:06:28,640 --> 00:06:30,100
我们还听到他的招募了
We also heard his offer.

183
00:06:31,020 --> 00:06:33,640
也许调到联调局对你有好处
Maybe a transfer to the FBI would be good for you.

184
00:06:35,350 --> 00:06:37,590
你们俩监听我的全部谈话吗
Do you listen to all of my conversations?

185
00:06:38,270 --> 00:06:39,140
多多少少吧
More or less.

186
00:06:39,140 --> 00:06:40,150
你气色不错  卡特
You're looking nice, Carter.

187
00:06:40,590 --> 00:06:42,630
看来这位卡尔·比彻对你也有好处
Maybe this Cal Beecher would be good for you too.

188
00:06:42,770 --> 00:06:43,900
他对你好就行了
Long as he treats you right.

189
00:06:44,040 --> 00:06:45,640
他敢惹你生气  我去找他算账
He messes with you, he'll be hearing from me.

190
00:06:45,640 --> 00:06:46,720
好吧  行了  听着
Okay. All right, look.

191
00:06:46,970 --> 00:06:49,010
我们得讨论下界线问题了
We're gonna have to set some boundaries here.

192
00:06:49,330 --> 00:06:50,350
当然
Well, sure.

193
00:06:50,610 --> 00:06:52,080
你和卡尔进展到某种程度时
Things get heavy with you and Cal,

194
00:06:52,080 --> 00:06:53,080
我们会闭上眼睛不看
we'll tune out right away.

195
00:06:54,540 --> 00:06:55,340
当我没说
Never mind.

196
00:06:56,310 --> 00:06:57,790
艾比·门罗是怎么回事
What's the deal with Abby Monroe?

197
00:06:57,990 --> 00:06:59,900
我想查查她是不是麻烦了
I was checking to see she wasn't in trouble.

198
00:07:00,300 --> 00:07:01,470
看来晚了一步
Looks like I'm a bit late.

199
00:07:01,910 --> 00:07:03,860
卡特  你能不能帮我拿到那个摄像头
Carter, can you get me footage from that camera

200
00:07:03,860 --> 00:07:04,760
两小时前的录像
from about two hours ago?

201
00:07:05,520 --> 00:07:06,780
还有那个摄像头
And that camera too?

202
00:07:07,230 --> 00:07:07,930
谢了
Thank you.

203
00:07:12,290 --> 00:07:13,170
这是艾比
There's Abby.

204
00:07:17,180 --> 00:07:17,960
你能否查到
Were you able to trace

205
00:07:17,960 --> 00:07:20,010
那辆摩托车的主人  警探
the owner of the motorcycle, Detective?

206
00:07:20,460 --> 00:07:21,770
不能  因为这辆车是
No, because it was stolen

207
00:07:21,770 --> 00:07:24,370
四天前从皇后区一家二手车陈列室被偷走的
from a second-hand showroom in Queens four days ago.

208
00:07:24,530 --> 00:07:26,830
我从抢劫组拿到了监控录像
I got the camera tapes out of the Robbery Squad.

209
00:07:26,970 --> 00:07:29,410
我看到一开始有个单身男子
I see the perp is a single male.

210
00:07:29,880 --> 00:07:31,250
你现在在看录像吗
You looking at the footage now?

211
00:07:31,250 --> 00:07:32,290
是的  怎么了
Yes. Why?

212
00:07:32,710 --> 00:07:33,560
随便问问
No reason.

213
00:07:34,660 --> 00:07:36,440
用炸药引信炸开了锁
Blew the locks with det cord.

214
00:07:36,610 --> 00:07:38,030
没理会警报
Ignored the alarms,

215
00:07:38,030 --> 00:07:40,290
因为他清楚自己能在30秒内脱身
'cause he knew he'd be less than 30 seconds.

216
00:07:42,300 --> 00:07:44,760
他赤手空拳打开了钥匙框
He broke the key case with his bare hand.

217
00:07:46,360 --> 00:07:47,740
选好了工具
Chose his machine.

218
00:07:52,010 --> 00:07:53,060
令人惊叹
That's impressive.

219
00:07:56,780 --> 00:07:59,470
怎么  怎  怎么回事
What is--what-- what is going on here?

220
00:08:00,390 --> 00:08:02,920
别告诉我你们俩还能看到我的电脑
Don't tell me you can see what's on my computer too.

221
00:08:03,550 --> 00:08:06,400
我是怎么说界限问题来着
What did I say about setting boundaries?

222
00:08:12,930 --> 00:08:14,220
那是假手
That's a prosthetic hand.

223
00:08:14,590 --> 00:08:15,920
高档假体
High-end prosthetic,

224
00:08:16,080 --> 00:08:18,520
用炸药引信进入
use of det cord to gain entry into a building.

225
00:08:18,780 --> 00:08:21,530
依我看  是退役军人
My guess, ex-military.

226
00:08:21,530 --> 00:08:23,170
所以才会跟艾比认识
Might explain his connection to Abby.

227
00:08:23,170 --> 00:08:24,580
问题是  他们在干什么
The question is, what are they doing?

228
00:08:24,780 --> 00:08:26,510
我想答案你不会喜欢
I don't think you're gonna like the answer.

229
00:08:26,670 --> 00:08:29,500
调度站刚刚回应了我的车牌协查要求
Comp stat just flagged my license plate inquiry.

230
00:08:29,620 --> 00:08:30,550
那辆摩托车
The same motorcycle was seen

231
00:08:30,550 --> 00:08:32,930
被交通灯摄像头拍到出现在
on a traffic light camera near a robbery

232
00:08:32,930 --> 00:08:35,550
三天前新泽西一起建筑工地抢劫中
at a construction site in New Jersey three nights ago.

233
00:08:35,670 --> 00:08:36,550
抢走了什么
What was stolen?

234
00:08:36,550 --> 00:08:39,170
爆炸物  塞姆汀塑胶炸药
Explosives. Semtex.

235
00:08:39,350 --> 00:08:41,520
足有九公斤  还有爆破雷管
20 pounds of it, and blasting caps.

236
00:08:41,670 --> 00:08:43,110
这么一看  偷爆炸物
Let's see, theft of explosives,

237
00:08:43,110 --> 00:08:46,890
偷华尔街上一栋建筑物的工程平面图
theft of engineering plans for a block on Wall Street.

238
00:08:47,760 --> 00:08:49,540
这家伙就是下一个蒂莫西·麦克维
This guy could be the next Timothy Mcveigh,

239
00:08:47,760 --> 00:08:49,540
{\an8}曾在1995年的俄克拉荷马州制造过一起导致168人丧生的爆炸案

240
00:08:49,540 --> 00:08:51,120
而那位姑娘跟他一起
and your girl is working with him.

241
00:08:51,120 --> 00:08:53,050
他也许是拐骗她牵涉其中的
He may have manipulated her into getting involved.

242
00:08:53,150 --> 00:08:54,590
那她也是牵涉其中了
She's still involved.

243
00:08:54,750 --> 00:08:58,540
抱歉  我得履行我的职责
I'm sorry. I'm gonna have to do my job.

244
00:08:59,200 --> 00:09:01,340
我得把她的名字发布到全境通告上
I'm gonna have to put her name out on an APB.

245
00:09:06,280 --> 00:09:07,580
我们得先找到她
We've got to find her first.

246
00:09:22,360 --> 00:09:24,060
奥尔森  你在55区工作过
Hey, Olson, you worked at the 55.

247
00:09:24,190 --> 00:09:26,390
你认不认识一个叫卡尔·比彻的缉毒警探
You know a narco detective named Cal Beecher?

248
00:09:26,510 --> 00:09:27,340
当然认识
Oh, yeah, sure do.

249
00:09:27,530 --> 00:09:29,480
我们以前都叫他纯金卡尔
We used to call him 18-karat Cal.

250
00:09:29,480 --> 00:09:30,650
衣服好  车子好
Better suits, better cars,

251
00:09:30,650 --> 00:09:32,020
女友好  全都好过我们
better girls than the rest of us.

252
00:09:32,130 --> 00:09:33,580
也许他只是品味好
Maybe he just had better taste.

253
00:09:33,930 --> 00:09:35,100
也许他是受贿
Or maybe he was on the take.

254
00:09:35,260 --> 00:09:36,270
你听我说过吗
Did you hear me say that?

255
00:09:36,450 --> 00:09:37,670
不知道  你说什么了
Don't know. What are you saying?

256
00:09:38,070 --> 00:09:40,460
他曾是卧底缉毒警
Look, he was undercover narcotics.

257
00:09:40,570 --> 00:09:42,700
来来回回  一笔钱进进出出
A lot of buy-and-busts, a lot of money hanging around.

258
00:09:44,060 --> 00:09:45,190
不过  你打听这个干嘛
Anyway, why you want to know?

259
00:09:45,480 --> 00:09:47,060
就是最近老见着他
I just been seeing him around.

260
00:09:47,060 --> 00:09:48,530
是啊  他在和卡特警探约会
Yeah. He's been hanging around Detective Carter.

261
00:09:48,650 --> 00:09:50,620
人家会招蜂引蝶啊  弗斯科
Bees like honey, Fusco.

262
00:09:51,130 --> 00:09:52,150
是啊
Yeah.

263
00:09:56,160 --> 00:09:58,930
我只是说  像艾比这样
I'm just saying, but the way Abby

264
00:09:58,930 --> 00:10:00,460
奋不顾身  舍弃一切
went off the grid, cut all ties,

265
00:10:00,730 --> 00:10:02,470
她肯定有所计划  芬奇
she's planning something, Finch.

266
00:10:02,470 --> 00:10:05,120
你觉得这位优秀学生想要炸掉华尔街吗
You think our honor student wants to blow up Wall Street?

267
00:10:05,120 --> 00:10:06,130
可能她男朋友想
Well, her boyfriend might.

268
00:10:06,250 --> 00:10:08,430
他可不是第一个想尝试极端手段的
He isn't the first vet to try something extreme.

269
00:10:09,100 --> 00:10:10,910
我们这对儿就挺古怪啊  芬奇
We are an odd bunch, Finch.

270
00:10:11,030 --> 00:10:13,850
你才古怪呢  里瑟先生  而且你错了
You are odd, Mr. Reese. You're also wrong.

271
00:10:14,050 --> 00:10:16,820
如果艾比牵涉的是境内恐怖主义
If Abby were involved with domestic terrorism,

272
00:10:17,570 --> 00:10:19,190
这属于相关信息
which would be a relevant crime,

273
00:10:19,300 --> 00:10:21,010
机器会把她的号码
The machine would have given her number

274
00:10:21,570 --> 00:10:24,320
给  给到现在政府中负责这事的人
to--to whoever now runs that end of things at the government,

275
00:10:24,320 --> 00:10:25,100
而不会给我们
not to us.

276
00:10:26,460 --> 00:10:29,290
无论她是威胁的目标  还是威胁的来源
Whether she's the target or the source of the threat,

277
00:10:29,390 --> 00:10:30,730
原因肯定是个人性质的
The issues must be personal.

278
00:10:30,850 --> 00:10:33,260
好吧  那我们还有什么线索  芬奇
Fine, but what leads do we have left, Finch?

279
00:10:33,260 --> 00:10:33,950
有两条
We have two.

280
00:10:34,310 --> 00:10:36,890
第一  她给短期工中介的投币式公用电话号码
First, the pay phone number that she gave the temp agency.

281
00:10:37,240 --> 00:10:39,440
在皇后区的一个街角
It's a street corner in Queens.

282
00:10:39,640 --> 00:10:41,200
中介之前必须
The agency must have been able

283
00:10:41,200 --> 00:10:42,750
得通过那个电话联系上她
to contact her there at one point.

284
00:10:42,750 --> 00:10:44,490
也许可以找到线索她住在哪里
It might give you a clue as to where she's living.

285
00:10:44,600 --> 00:10:47,020
好  那第二个呢
Okay. And the second lead?

286
00:10:47,120 --> 00:10:49,340
她去年工作的那个地方
The one stable point in her life for the last year--

287
00:10:49,420 --> 00:10:51,740
那个慈善组织  "归国英雄之家"
the charity, Homes For Our Returning Heroes.

288
00:10:51,740 --> 00:10:52,600
我去查这个
I'll check that one out.

289
00:10:53,470 --> 00:10:55,750
好  你应该多出去
Good. You need to get out more.

290
00:10:56,220 --> 00:10:57,810
你心情可真好  里瑟先生
You're in a good mood, Mr. Reese.

291
00:10:57,810 --> 00:10:58,310
是好
I am.

292
00:10:58,440 --> 00:10:59,990
我早上一觉醒来  感觉
I woke up this morning and felt--

293
00:10:59,990 --> 00:11:01,280
我再三斟酌才能把这话说出来
it took me a while to put my finger on it,

294
00:11:01,280 --> 00:11:02,270
我感觉很幸福
but I felt happy.

295
00:11:03,000 --> 00:11:03,920
肯定是因为这份工作
Must be this job.

296
00:11:05,550 --> 00:11:06,430
我很开心
Well, I'm glad.

297
00:11:08,330 --> 00:11:09,360
抱歉  小熊  这次不行
Sorry, Bear. Not now.

298
00:11:27,730 --> 00:11:29,450
艾比接入了这个公用电话
Abby tapped into that pay phone.

299
00:11:30,950 --> 00:11:32,080
{\an8}维多利亚公寓
日租  周租  月租

300
00:11:31,920 --> 00:11:32,520
我想我找到
I think I've found

301
00:11:32,520 --> 00:11:34,440
这对雌雄大盗之前的藏身之处了
where our Bonnie and Clyde have been laying low.

302
00:12:15,400 --> 00:12:18,330
乔什·门罗  艾比的弟弟
Josh Monroe, Abby's little brother.

303
00:12:28,730 --> 00:12:30,450
我是艾比家的老朋友
I'm an old friend of Abby's family,

304
00:12:30,450 --> 00:12:32,260
我来纽约
And as I was visiting New York,

305
00:12:32,620 --> 00:12:34,410
他们拜托我找找艾比住在哪里
they asked if I'd try to find out where Abby is

306
00:12:34,410 --> 00:12:36,200
为什么要辞职
and why she left her job here.

307
00:12:36,470 --> 00:12:37,560
她没告诉家里吗
She never told them?

308
00:12:38,790 --> 00:12:40,570
抱歉  但我不得不解雇她
Well, I'm sorry, but I had to fire her.

309
00:12:40,890 --> 00:12:44,150
-解雇她  到底为什么呢  -偷东西
- Fire her? What on earth for? - Stealing.

310
00:12:44,540 --> 00:12:46,690
一开始  只是些现金  我就没多追究
At first, it was just petty cash, and I let it go,

311
00:12:47,050 --> 00:12:49,840
以为只是单纯的粗心大意  但后来我发现
thinking it was simple carelessness, but then I found

312
00:12:49,840 --> 00:12:52,100
她偷偷潜入我们慈善组织的账户
she was sneaking into the Charity's accounts,

313
00:12:52,450 --> 00:12:55,550
想转钱出去  一大笔钱
trying to move money around-- significant amounts.

314
00:12:56,060 --> 00:12:56,920
查普先生
Mr. Chapple,

315
00:12:58,300 --> 00:13:00,620
这不像我认识的艾比
that really doesn't sound like the Abby I know.

316
00:13:00,740 --> 00:13:01,880
很遗憾  这是事实
Well, unfortunately, it's true.

317
00:13:02,210 --> 00:13:05,630
我们向有经济问题的退役老兵发放低息贷款
We give low-cost loans to veterans in financial trouble.

318
00:13:05,630 --> 00:13:06,970
有一点点丑闻
Any hint of a scandal,

319
00:13:06,970 --> 00:13:08,640
捐款者就会抽身走人
and our donations would just dry right up.

320
00:13:09,810 --> 00:13:10,690
艾比必须离开
Abby had to go.

321
00:13:12,620 --> 00:13:14,240
妈  爸
Hi, mom. Hi, dad.

322
00:13:15,280 --> 00:13:17,820
要是你们看到这个  就说明我现在有麻烦了
If you're watching this, you'll know I'm in trouble.

323
00:13:18,530 --> 00:13:23,050
你们上次对我发火  还是在我八岁的时候
I don't think you've really been mad at me since I was eight,

324
00:13:23,830 --> 00:13:26,450
那时我把乔什绑在滑板上
that time I tied Josh to his skateboard

325
00:13:26,450 --> 00:13:28,350
把他从山上推下滑到我们家门口
and pushed him down the hill in front of our house

326
00:13:28,350 --> 00:13:29,640
想看他能有多快
to see how fast he would go.

327
00:13:32,000 --> 00:13:36,010
那以后  我一直都很乖  循规蹈矩
Since then, I've always tried to be good, keep the rules.

328
00:13:36,470 --> 00:13:38,110
这次我要干件彻底逆转的大事
Now I'm gonna break them in a big way.

329
00:13:39,720 --> 00:13:44,010
为什么  原因既复杂又简单
Why? Well, it's complicated and it's simple.

330
00:13:45,500 --> 00:13:47,110
因为我在做正确的事
I'm doing it because it's right,

331
00:13:47,110 --> 00:13:50,630
我知道乔什也会同意的
and I know Josh would agree with me.

332
00:13:52,400 --> 00:13:54,780
他是我弟弟  但我一直敬佩他
He was my little brother, but I always looked up to him,

333
00:13:54,780 --> 00:13:58,450
我知道他会为我骄傲的
and I know that he would be proud of me,

334
00:13:59,720 --> 00:14:02,630
我希望你们了解真相后也会如此
just like I hope you are when you know the truth.

335
00:14:04,470 --> 00:14:08,900
我爱你们  真希望你们不用看到这个
I love you, and I hope you never have to see this.

336
00:14:11,560 --> 00:14:14,090
知道她为什么要偷东西吗
Any idea why she started stealing?

337
00:14:14,900 --> 00:14:17,860
应该是在她认识某个退役的海军陆战队员之后
I believe the trouble started when she met a former marine.

338
00:14:18,080 --> 00:14:20,550
他来公司时他们俩聊过
Uh, they'd talk when he came by the offices.

339
00:14:20,690 --> 00:14:24,580
他不知怎么的  反正让艾比印象深刻
Somehow, he must have made an impression on Abby,

340
00:14:24,580 --> 00:14:27,380
因为从那以后她就开始偷东西了
'cause, just about that time, she started stealing.

341
00:14:27,940 --> 00:14:30,210
我不明白  陆战队员怎么会来这呢
I don't understand. Why did this marine come here?

342
00:14:30,590 --> 00:14:31,220
不好意思
I'm sorry.

343
00:14:31,220 --> 00:14:33,190
我们与贷款用户签有
We have a strict confidentiality agreement

344
00:14:33,190 --> 00:14:34,570
严格的保密协议
with all of our loan recipients.

345
00:14:34,710 --> 00:14:38,420
简而言之  不是很愉快
Suffice it to say, it was not a pleasant visit.

346
00:14:38,810 --> 00:14:40,830
至少告诉我他叫什么
Could you at least tell me his name?

347
00:14:42,690 --> 00:14:44,340
尚恩·科尔曼下士
Corporal Shayn Coleman,

348
00:14:44,560 --> 00:14:46,880
爆炸物处理专家
explosives ordinance disposal expert.

349
00:14:46,880 --> 00:14:48,010
他的右臂三年前
Lost his right arm

350
00:14:48,010 --> 00:14:50,780
在阿富汗拆除简易爆炸装置时失去了
defusing an IED in Afghanistan three years ago.

351
00:14:51,150 --> 00:14:52,640
他就是偷摩托车的人
He's our motorcycle thief.

352
00:14:52,890 --> 00:14:56,240
我问了尚恩在俄亥俄老家的父母
I tracked down Shayn's parents in his hometown in Ohio.

353
00:14:56,240 --> 00:14:59,030
他们两个多月没见到他了
They haven't seen him in more than two months.

354
00:14:59,130 --> 00:15:00,410
他们知道他有麻烦了吗
Did they know he was in trouble?

355
00:15:00,550 --> 00:15:03,390
他们说他家的赎回权被取消了
They said he'd had his home foreclosed on,

356
00:15:03,390 --> 00:15:04,940
他未婚妻甩了她
and his fiancee dumped him.

357
00:15:05,140 --> 00:15:06,700
他肯定是为此去找查普的
Must be why he went to Chapple--

358
00:15:06,960 --> 00:15:08,510
希望能再次贷款
to ask for another loan.

359
00:15:08,640 --> 00:15:11,240
不知道发生了什么事  反正是足以
However it happened, this is more than enough

360
00:15:11,240 --> 00:15:12,820
把人推向不归路了
to tip someone over the edge.

361
00:15:12,930 --> 00:15:15,990
他是我们要找的人  我得发布全境通告
He's our guy. I'm adding his name to the APB.

362
00:15:16,790 --> 00:15:18,430
做你该做的事  警探
Do what you have to do, Detective.

363
00:15:21,160 --> 00:15:23,060
芬奇  你还在吗
Finch, are you still there?

364
00:15:23,540 --> 00:15:24,620
是的
Yes.

365
00:15:26,150 --> 00:15:29,370
我看到菲利普·查普在和两个携带武器的人碰面
I'm watching Philip Chapple meet with two armed men.

366
00:15:29,720 --> 00:15:30,650
他们长什么样
What are they like?

367
00:15:31,000 --> 00:15:34,340
坦白说  像你  低调而危险
Like you, to be honest-- low-key and vaguely menacing.

368
00:15:34,540 --> 00:15:36,340
我估计他是在告诉他们追踪
I suspect he's telling them to follow me

369
00:15:36,340 --> 00:15:38,230
我身上的GPS信号
via the GPS transponder

370
00:15:38,230 --> 00:15:40,450
我离开时他放进我口袋里的
he slipped into my pocket as I was leaving.

371
00:15:40,750 --> 00:15:42,530
发射器现在在哪呢
And where is the transponder now?

372
00:15:42,740 --> 00:15:45,150
在一辆新泽西牌照的洗衣车上
It's on a laundry van with Jersey plates.

373
00:15:45,530 --> 00:15:46,800
干得好  芬奇
Nice work, Finch.

374
00:15:46,800 --> 00:15:51,120
很明显  查普不会放过追踪艾比的任何机会
Obviously, Chapple will take any opportunity to track Abby down.

375
00:15:51,490 --> 00:15:54,020
她的计划肯定与他有关
What she's planning must connect to him too.

376
00:15:54,220 --> 00:15:55,840
等慈善组织关门后  我再潜进去
When the charity closes, I'll go back in,

377
00:15:55,840 --> 00:15:56,880
看看能发现什么
see what I can find.

378
00:15:57,230 --> 00:15:58,730
我说你该多出去
When I said you need to get out more,

379
00:15:58,730 --> 00:15:59,510
可不是这个意思
I didn't mean that.

380
00:15:59,670 --> 00:16:01,040
我来搞定
Let me take care of it.

381
00:16:01,280 --> 00:16:03,990
没有无风险的人生  里瑟先生
No such thing as a risk-free life, Mr. Reese,

382
00:16:04,150 --> 00:16:05,730
艾比是我们要优先考虑的
and Abby is still our priority.

383
00:16:05,730 --> 00:16:06,450
你在那等她
You wait for her.

384
00:16:07,060 --> 00:16:08,270
我回去
So, I'll go back in,

385
00:16:08,270 --> 00:16:09,840
看看查普究竟在隐藏什么
see what exactly Chapple's hiding.

386
00:16:20,980 --> 00:16:21,820
我进来了
I'm inside,

387
00:16:23,190 --> 00:16:27,710
不过报警装置已经被破坏了
but the alarm has been tampered with.

388
00:16:27,710 --> 00:16:30,130
因为他们在恭候你了  哈罗德
That's because they could be waiting for you, Harold.

389
00:16:31,180 --> 00:16:33,320
怎么了  芬奇  快离开
What was that? Finch, get out now.

390
00:16:35,500 --> 00:16:36,510
你是谁
Who the hell are you?

391
00:16:36,690 --> 00:16:38,640
我是谁并不重要  科尔曼先生
Who I am is not important, Mr. Coleman.

392
00:16:38,790 --> 00:16:41,150
你怎么知道我的名字  你在这做什么
How do you know my name? What are you doing here?

393
00:16:41,250 --> 00:16:42,820
我估计是和你一样
The same thing as you, I expect,

394
00:16:42,820 --> 00:16:44,240
不过你已经惊动了全楼
and since you woke the whole building,

395
00:16:44,240 --> 00:16:45,290
我们得快点
we better hurry.

396
00:16:48,340 --> 00:16:49,170
我去找你
I'm on my way to you.

397
00:16:49,170 --> 00:16:50,600
拜托  只管离开  芬奇
Please, just walk away now, Finch.

398
00:16:55,070 --> 00:16:56,160
你是谁
Who are you?

399
00:16:56,160 --> 00:16:57,120
放开我
let go of me!

400
00:16:57,260 --> 00:16:58,560
别害怕  我不会伤害你的
It's okay. I'm not gonna hurt you.

401
00:17:11,730 --> 00:17:12,620
芬奇  马上离开
Finch, get out now.

402
00:17:12,940 --> 00:17:14,410
别冒险  我找到艾比了
Don't risk it. I've got Abby.

403
00:17:14,410 --> 00:17:15,230
赶紧离开
Just get out of there.

404
00:17:15,350 --> 00:17:16,870
马上就好  里瑟先生
Nearly done, Mr. Reese.

405
00:17:19,370 --> 00:17:20,550
拜托别这样
Please don't do that.

406
00:17:20,820 --> 00:17:23,390
那就放开我  让我走
Then get off of me. Let me go.

407
00:17:39,780 --> 00:17:40,810
拜托  别动枪
Please, no guns.

408
00:17:49,590 --> 00:17:52,040
芬奇  说话  怎么了
Finch, talk to me. What's happening?

409
00:17:52,180 --> 00:17:54,350
事态在发展  里瑟先生
The situation is evolving, Mr. Reese.

410
00:17:57,570 --> 00:17:58,300
他们在那儿
There they go!

411
00:17:59,400 --> 00:18:00,600
站住
Stop right there!

412
00:18:06,360 --> 00:18:07,260
上来  他们会杀了你
Get on, or they'll kill you!

413
00:18:07,260 --> 00:18:07,970
上来
Get on!

414
00:18:16,210 --> 00:18:17,140
芬奇  你没事吧
Finch, are you okay?

415
00:18:17,240 --> 00:18:20,080
除了坐在一辆非法摩托车上外  我还好
Aside from riding on a motorcycle illegally, I'm fine!

416
00:18:20,080 --> 00:18:20,860
保持联系
I'll be in touch!

417
00:18:22,630 --> 00:18:23,510
干得好
Well done.

418
00:18:26,610 --> 00:18:27,510
你好  艾比
Hello, Abby.

419
00:18:29,350 --> 00:18:30,500
我叫约翰
I'm John.

420
00:18:44,600 --> 00:18:46,880
好了  你该离开了
Okay, you should leave now,

421
00:18:46,880 --> 00:18:48,980
我男朋友随时会回来的
because my boyfriend's gonna be here any minute.

422
00:18:49,610 --> 00:18:50,900
你男朋友  尚恩
Your boyfriend, Shayn?

423
00:18:52,560 --> 00:18:54,370
我不知道你怎么知道的  不过没错
I don't know how you know that, but yes,

424
00:18:55,020 --> 00:18:57,590
他是陆战队员  你可不会想见他
and he's a marine, so you do not want to meet him.

425
00:18:57,710 --> 00:18:59,270
实际上  我正想见他
Actually, I do want to meet him,

426
00:18:59,580 --> 00:19:00,540
不过一件件来
But first things first.

427
00:19:00,720 --> 00:19:02,610
你留给你父母的视频是什么意思
What does that message to your mom and dad mean?

428
00:19:02,740 --> 00:19:03,510
什么
What?

429
00:19:04,070 --> 00:19:06,020
你闯进我家翻了我的东西
You broke into my room and went through my stuff?

430
00:19:06,020 --> 00:19:08,620
出去  否则我
Get out, or I'm--

431
00:19:08,960 --> 00:19:11,160
怎么  你要报警吗
What? You'll call the police?

432
00:19:12,110 --> 00:19:14,900
我知道建筑设计图和爆炸物的事
I know about the building plans and the explosives.

433
00:19:14,900 --> 00:19:17,220
我就知道  你是查普的人
I knew it. You work for Chapple.

434
00:19:17,400 --> 00:19:20,420
不  不过我很好奇为什么你和尚恩
No, but I'm interested to know why you and Shayn

435
00:19:20,420 --> 00:19:21,330
要追查他
are going after him.

436
00:19:22,520 --> 00:19:25,290
因为查普是个骗子  盗贼
Because Chapple's a liar and a thief,

437
00:19:25,890 --> 00:19:27,140
我不会再多说一句话了
and I'm not saying another word

438
00:19:27,140 --> 00:19:28,670
除非你告诉我你是谁
until you tell me who you are.

439
00:19:30,280 --> 00:19:33,630
我是来阻止你陷入更多麻烦的人
I'm here to stop you from getting into even more trouble.

440
00:19:33,910 --> 00:19:35,110
不是我要的答案
Not what I asked.

441
00:19:35,290 --> 00:19:36,370
你是谁
Who are you?

442
00:19:39,100 --> 00:19:40,510
这有点难回答
I find it hard to answer that,

443
00:19:40,940 --> 00:19:42,020
我自己也说不好
even to myself.

444
00:19:45,850 --> 00:19:48,640
我当过兵  和你弟弟乔什一样
I was a soldier once, like your brother Josh.

445
00:19:49,480 --> 00:19:50,970
不过我很幸运  活着回来了
But I was lucky. I made it out.

446
00:19:53,310 --> 00:19:55,950
-里瑟先生  -在  芬奇  怎么了
- Mr. Reese? - Yes, Finch. What's happening?

447
00:19:56,120 --> 00:19:58,830
我跟尚恩说咱们是想帮助他
I've explained to Shayn that we're trying to help him.

448
00:19:58,830 --> 00:20:00,090
他相信你了吗
Did he believe you?

449
00:20:00,420 --> 00:20:03,760
没有  尤其是我告诉他你抓了艾比后
No, especially when I told him that you have Abby.

450
00:20:04,080 --> 00:20:06,220
形势有点紧张
Things are a little tense.

451
00:20:06,370 --> 00:20:07,730
让我跟他说
Let me talk to him.

452
00:20:14,220 --> 00:20:15,260
你是谁
Who is this?

453
00:20:15,270 --> 00:20:17,820
艾比也在问我同样的问题
You know, Abby keeps asking me the same thing.

454
00:20:17,820 --> 00:20:19,340
这真的不重要
It's really not important.

455
00:20:19,340 --> 00:20:21,570
敢伤害她  你会后悔的
If you hurt her, you will be sorry.

456
00:20:21,630 --> 00:20:23,970
你那边也是一样
The same goes for you and my friend.

457
00:20:25,880 --> 00:20:27,190
我们该碰个面
We should meet.

458
00:20:32,730 --> 00:20:36,050
你跟尚恩离开  我就没法保护你了
Once you leave with Shayn, I can't protect you anymore.

459
00:20:36,050 --> 00:20:38,610
我一开始就没要你保护
I never asked you to protect me in the first place.

460
00:20:38,610 --> 00:20:41,130
不管你在计划什么  我知道原因  艾比
Whatever you're planning, I know why, Abby.

461
00:20:41,240 --> 00:20:42,650
你没能救你弟弟
You couldn't save your brother,

462
00:20:42,650 --> 00:20:44,440
所以想要救尚恩
so you're trying to save Shayn.

463
00:20:46,720 --> 00:20:48,830
我理解  真的
I understand that, truly.

464
00:20:49,450 --> 00:20:51,040
我也这么想过
I'd feel the same way.

465
00:20:52,020 --> 00:20:55,040
告诉我  查普怎么你了
Tell me, what did Chapple do to you?

466
00:20:55,060 --> 00:20:58,600
对我没什么  可他几乎毁了尚恩
Nothing I can't handle, but he nearly destroyed Shayn.

467
00:20:58,600 --> 00:21:00,790
-贷款的事  -对
- By lending him money? - Yes.

468
00:21:01,060 --> 00:21:02,530
查普贷款给他
Chapple made him a loan.

469
00:21:02,530 --> 00:21:04,690
利息一年滚了三倍
The interest rates tripled in a year.

470
00:21:04,690 --> 00:21:06,870
没人能付得起
No one could keep up those payments.

471
00:21:06,880 --> 00:21:09,110
失去房子的人成百上千万
Millions of people lost their homes.

472
00:21:09,140 --> 00:21:11,710
人家也没去偷爆炸物
They don't go around stealing explosives.

473
00:21:11,710 --> 00:21:13,210
尚恩得放手
Shayn should move on.

474
00:21:13,210 --> 00:21:15,890
他失去了孩子  失去了未婚妻
He lost his home and his fiancee.

475
00:21:16,210 --> 00:21:18,700
他还曾把自己的朋友介绍给查普
He even introduced some of his buddies to Chapple,

476
00:21:18,700 --> 00:21:20,540
结果其中一个饮弹自尽
one of whom shot himself

477
00:21:20,540 --> 00:21:22,740
就在失去的房子门口
on the porch of the house he no longer owned.

478
00:21:22,740 --> 00:21:24,720
让他这么放手不理吗
Should he move on from that?

479
00:21:25,280 --> 00:21:27,270
我查过查普的文件
Look, I went through Chapple's files.

480
00:21:27,270 --> 00:21:28,720
发现了他的所作所为
I saw what he was doing.

481
00:21:28,720 --> 00:21:30,350
有成百上千
There are hundreds,

482
00:21:30,670 --> 00:21:33,400
成千上万的士兵失去了家园
hundreds of soldiers who lost their homes.

483
00:21:46,070 --> 00:21:47,690
你要做什么  艾比
What are you gonna do, Abby?

484
00:21:47,900 --> 00:21:49,170
做正确的事
The right thing.

485
00:21:50,900 --> 00:21:52,210
我能走了吗
Can I go now?

486
00:22:01,870 --> 00:22:04,180
我猜给他安追踪器了吧
I assume you put a tracker on him.

487
00:22:05,230 --> 00:22:08,040
恕我自夸  远不止此
Rather a clever one, if I do say so myself.

488
00:22:09,070 --> 00:22:12,040
他的假肢由肌电感应器控制
His prosthetic arm is controlled by myoelectric sensors

489
00:22:12,040 --> 00:22:14,320
无线连接
by way of a wireless link,

490
00:22:14,430 --> 00:22:18,670
我克隆连接  二次编程
so I cloned the link and reprogrammed it

491
00:22:18,680 --> 00:22:22,110
只要路过手机就会强制配对
to attempt a forced pair with every cell phone they pass.

492
00:22:22,110 --> 00:22:24,470
GPS轨迹清晰无误
leaving a nice GPS trail.

493
00:22:25,590 --> 00:22:26,970
干得漂亮  芬奇
Well done, Finch.

494
00:22:27,150 --> 00:22:29,270
而且是在狂飚的摩托车后座上完成的
Especially on the back of a speeding motorcycle,

495
00:22:29,280 --> 00:22:32,010
对了  感觉好刺激
which was exhilarating, by the way.

496
00:22:32,440 --> 00:22:34,080
我想自己弄一个
I might have to get myself one.

497
00:22:42,680 --> 00:22:43,790
加班啊
Working late?

498
00:22:44,960 --> 00:22:46,890
是啊
Yeah.

499
00:22:48,030 --> 00:22:50,060
总是有事做
It's always something, you know?

500
00:22:51,380 --> 00:22:54,370
是啊  有什么事吗  卡特
Yeah. Is something wrong, Carter?

501
00:22:55,710 --> 00:22:57,470
唐纳利今天请我过去
Donnelly made me an offer today.

502
00:22:57,470 --> 00:22:59,930
什么  我有情敌了  那家伙吗
What, I got competition? From that guy?

503
00:22:59,930 --> 00:23:01,500
不  不是那意思
No, not that sort of offer.

504
00:23:01,500 --> 00:23:06,360
他  邀请我加入联调局
He, um, invited me to join the FBI.

505
00:23:07,760 --> 00:23:09,060
兴许是好事
Could be a good move.

506
00:23:09,600 --> 00:23:11,510
我是说  虽说宁为鸡头不为凤尾
I mean, yeah, small fish in a big pond,

507
00:23:11,510 --> 00:23:14,220
不过想想职业前途  卡特  还有收入
but think of the prospects, Carter, and the money.

508
00:23:14,220 --> 00:23:15,290
你应该去
You should do it.

509
00:23:16,090 --> 00:23:17,440
可我的孩子呢
But what about my kid?

510
00:23:17,440 --> 00:23:19,800
我是说  恐怕得
I mean, it--it'll probably mean

511
00:23:19,800 --> 00:23:22,440
从纽约搬走
I have to move out of New York.

512
00:23:22,720 --> 00:23:24,420
你是说我们再也见不到面了吗
You mean I'd never see you again?

513
00:23:28,500 --> 00:23:29,520
卡尔
It's Cal.

514
00:23:32,690 --> 00:23:35,050
没问题  不见不散
No problem. I'll see you then.

515
00:23:37,460 --> 00:23:39,380
我们说到哪儿了
Now what were we talking about?

516
00:23:39,530 --> 00:23:41,530
再也见不到面了
About never seeing me again.

517
00:23:42,100 --> 00:23:43,090
对
Right.

518
00:23:45,270 --> 00:23:49,210
{\an7}比彻  卡尔文
警探  缉毒组

519
00:23:45,690 --> 00:23:46,590
是卡尔
It's cal.

520
00:23:46,590 --> 00:23:49,210
卡尔  我是阿伦佐·奎恩  能见见吗
Cal, Alonzo Quinn. Can we meet?

521
00:23:47,980 --> 00:23:49,990
{\an9}奎恩  阿伦佐
HR头目

522
00:23:49,210 --> 00:23:49,990
{\an7}比彻  卡尔文
从属关系不明

523
00:23:49,210 --> 00:23:51,290
泰瑞尔公园  半小时后吧
Tyrell Park. Say, 30 minutes?

524
00:23:51,290 --> 00:23:52,380
没问题
No problem.

525
00:23:58,790 --> 00:24:00,280
希望你帮个忙  卡尔
I'm hoping you can help me out, Cal.

526
00:24:00,280 --> 00:24:01,950
您尽管说  奎恩先生
Any way I can, Mr. Quinn.

527
00:24:02,320 --> 00:24:06,390
市长发现皇冠高地犯罪率暴增
The mayor has seen this crime spike in Crown Heights--

528
00:24:06,890 --> 00:24:10,220
涉毒  抢劫  还有命案
drug busts, uh, burglaries, even homicides.

529
00:24:10,220 --> 00:24:11,730
他想让我查查到底怎么回事
He wants me to find out what's happening.

530
00:24:11,730 --> 00:24:14,350
我回复说我教子有些路子
I told him I got a godson who's got his ear to the ground.

531
00:24:14,680 --> 00:24:15,910
怎么样
So, do you?

532
00:24:16,620 --> 00:24:18,410
皇冠高地  成
Crown Heights, yeah.

533
00:24:18,540 --> 00:24:20,930
应该是一俄国佬  彼得·约格洛夫
We think it's a Russian, Peter Yogorov.

534
00:24:20,930 --> 00:24:23,890
曾在布莱顿海滩干  最后被以利亚踢开了
Used to work Brighton Beach till Elias kicked him out.

535
00:24:24,110 --> 00:24:26,290
我们认为他是幕后主使
We believe he's pulling strings from the inside,

536
00:24:26,290 --> 00:24:28,190
想拿下高地那里
working to take over the Heights.

537
00:24:32,810 --> 00:24:33,990
你在干嘛  西蒙斯
What are you doing here, Simmons?

538
00:24:33,990 --> 00:24:36,890
你在监视你  你个老狐狸
I'm keeping an eye on you, you slippery little mutt.

539
00:24:37,340 --> 00:24:38,360
你在干嘛
What are you doing?

540
00:24:38,360 --> 00:24:39,620
关你屁事
None of your business.

541
00:24:41,590 --> 00:24:43,460
你在跟踪卡尔·比彻
You're following Cal Beecher.

542
00:24:43,460 --> 00:24:45,320
在帮卡特查他
You're checking him out for Carter?

543
00:24:45,320 --> 00:24:48,090
不  我就是想知道
No, I've been wondering

544
00:24:48,090 --> 00:24:49,990
你还对谁胡说八道了
who else you've been flapping your gums to.

545
00:24:50,480 --> 00:24:52,330
你埋戴维森那事吗
About you burying Davidson?

546
00:24:53,230 --> 00:24:56,520
没对比彻说  目前没
Not Beecher. Not yet.

547
00:24:56,880 --> 00:24:59,060
你越界了  居然给卡特打电话
You crossed a line when you made that call to Carter,

548
00:24:59,060 --> 00:25:01,480
把戴维森被杀引向我
pointing her towards me in the Davidson murder.

549
00:25:01,480 --> 00:25:02,820
越什么界
What line is that?

550
00:25:02,820 --> 00:25:04,950
越"哥我不在乎了"这条界
The line where I don't give a crap anymore.

551
00:25:05,770 --> 00:25:07,200
给我小心点
So watch your back.

552
00:25:09,930 --> 00:25:12,150
你知道这种话我听过多少次了吗
You know how many times I've heard that?

553
00:25:13,060 --> 00:25:16,450
可我还在这里  潇洒着呢
And here I am, beautiful as ever.

554
00:25:18,830 --> 00:25:20,120
回家吧  弗斯科
Go home, Fusco.

555
00:25:30,790 --> 00:25:32,510
你来干嘛  西蒙斯
What are you doing here, Simmons?

556
00:25:33,150 --> 00:25:34,780
我说了  回家
I said, go home.

557
00:25:40,130 --> 00:25:41,800
这是手机定位轨迹
There's our cell phone trail.

558
00:25:41,800 --> 00:25:42,710
貌似艾比和尚恩
It looks like Abby and Shayn

559
00:25:42,710 --> 00:25:44,920
要去汉诺威街1400
are heading for the 1400 block of Hanover.

560
00:25:44,920 --> 00:25:46,230
问题是  哪儿呢
Question is, what's there?

561
00:25:46,230 --> 00:25:48,760
这片所有商户我都列出来了
I've listed every business name on the block,

562
00:25:48,760 --> 00:25:52,470
和查普的下载也反复比对过
cross-checking against the download of Chapple's computer.

563
00:25:52,990 --> 00:25:56,770
有了  是家投行  莫顿·瓦特
Bingo. An investment bank, Merton Watts.

564
00:25:56,770 --> 00:25:58,600
也许他在那儿有账户
Maybe he has an account there.

565
00:26:00,780 --> 00:26:02,680
电脑记录上可没有
Not according to his computer records.

566
00:26:02,680 --> 00:26:05,020
-那保险箱呢  -存什么
- Then a safe deposit box? - What would he keep in it?

567
00:26:05,020 --> 00:26:07,320
账户显示  查普钱不多
According to his accounts, Chapple's not rich.

568
00:26:07,320 --> 00:26:09,030
艾比说他一堆贷款的赎回权
Abby said hundreds of the loans he made

569
00:26:09,030 --> 00:26:10,300
都被取消了
were foreclosed on.

570
00:26:10,300 --> 00:26:12,230
没准儿是银行给提成
If he's getting kickbacks from the banks--

571
00:26:12,230 --> 00:26:13,300
有这可能
You may be right.

572
00:26:13,300 --> 00:26:14,860
莫顿·瓦特对查普抵押的房产
Merton Watts has first lien

573
00:26:14,860 --> 00:26:17,240
拥有第一置留权
on any properties Chapple loans money on.

574
00:26:17,240 --> 00:26:19,410
就是说他们可以拍卖所有抵押产业
That means they handle all foreclosure sales.

575
00:26:19,410 --> 00:26:21,130
然后和查普分账
And split the profits with Chapple,

576
00:26:21,130 --> 00:26:23,960
都存在银行保管箱里
which he keeps in his safe deposit box at the bank.

577
00:26:24,520 --> 00:26:26,540
也就是艾比和尚恩要找的
That's what Abby and Shayn are after.

578
00:26:26,730 --> 00:26:28,590
她干嘛这样  为尚恩吗
Why is she doing this? For Shayn?

579
00:26:29,290 --> 00:26:31,250
对  还有她弟弟
Yes. And for her brother.

580
00:26:31,250 --> 00:26:32,900
她总觉得亏欠
She still feels a debt.

581
00:26:33,790 --> 00:26:35,910
亡灵的力量  你懂的
The dead have a power like that, as you know.

582
00:26:38,320 --> 00:26:40,060
那他们要怎么做
So, how are they going to do this?

583
00:26:40,110 --> 00:26:42,240
塞姆汀塑胶炸药加建筑设计图
Semtex and building plans.

584
00:26:42,580 --> 00:26:44,580
先找个薄弱点
They'll find a soft entry point

585
00:26:45,220 --> 00:26:47,040
轰开缺口进入保险库
and blast their way into the vault.

586
00:26:48,010 --> 00:26:49,530
我喜欢这俩孩子
I like these kids.

587
00:26:49,550 --> 00:26:50,960
我喜欢他们活着
I'd like them to live.

588
00:26:51,760 --> 00:26:54,470
拜托抢在查普雇的凶徒之前找到他们
Please try to get to them before Chapple's thugs do.

589
00:26:58,210 --> 00:26:59,340
系统在备份
System's back up.

590
00:26:59,340 --> 00:27:00,620
他们从保管箱拿走东西了吗
They get anything from the safe?

591
00:27:00,620 --> 00:27:02,970
密码和钥匙
The box code and the keys.

592
00:27:03,130 --> 00:27:05,480
可他们进不去银行的保险库
But there's no way they can get into the vault at the bank,

593
00:27:05,480 --> 00:27:05,990
对吧
is there?

594
00:27:05,990 --> 00:27:07,140
你以为呢
What do you think?

595
00:27:07,270 --> 00:27:09,130
警方都说他们偷了爆炸物
Police band says they stole explosives

596
00:27:09,130 --> 00:27:10,400
还有工程平面图
and engineering plans.

597
00:27:10,400 --> 00:27:12,860
那赶紧去  搞定他们
Well, get down there. Deal with them.

598
00:27:12,870 --> 00:27:14,600
那你得掏钱多雇人了
You have to pay for another man.

599
00:27:15,340 --> 00:27:16,730
那片儿地方太大
It's a big area to cover.

600
00:27:16,730 --> 00:27:20,460
不计成本  必须搞定
Whatever you need. Just finish it.

601
00:27:32,810 --> 00:27:35,100
卡特  你马上过来
Carter, I need to see you immediately.

602
00:27:41,550 --> 00:27:42,870
能把手机交出来吗
Can I have your phone?

603
00:27:43,670 --> 00:27:45,320
怎么了  唐纳利
What's going on, Donnelly?

604
00:27:45,530 --> 00:27:48,630
抱歉  不过我认为此人所服务的组织
I'm sorry, but I think the organization our man works for

605
00:27:48,630 --> 00:27:52,080
掌握颇多先进科技
has some sophisticated capabilities.

606
00:27:52,090 --> 00:27:54,170
比如窃听警方电话
Like wire-tapping cops?

607
00:27:55,140 --> 00:27:56,630
怎么回事
Has something happened?

608
00:27:57,040 --> 00:27:58,900
我想我们有突破了
I think we got our break.

609
00:27:58,950 --> 00:28:02,060
西装男参与了上东区的一桩
The man in the suit was involved in a robbery at a charity

610
00:28:02,060 --> 00:28:03,220
慈善组织抢劫案
on the upper east side.

611
00:28:03,220 --> 00:28:04,520
你怎么知道
How do you know that?

612
00:28:04,520 --> 00:28:06,800
在我告诉你之前  我必须确定
Now, before I can let you in, I have to know

613
00:28:06,800 --> 00:28:09,250
你是否接受局里提供的临时雇员职位
if you'll accept the temporary assignment to the bureau.

614
00:28:10,590 --> 00:28:12,120
好  我接受
Okay, yes.

615
00:28:12,690 --> 00:28:15,180
好  你不会后悔的
Good. You won't regret it.

616
00:28:15,750 --> 00:28:19,280
我们追踪此人有十个月了
So, we've been tracking this man for ten months.

617
00:28:19,370 --> 00:28:20,560
每次我们一靠近
Every time we get close,

618
00:28:20,560 --> 00:28:22,060
他都能从我们眼皮底下溜走
he slips right out from under us,

619
00:28:22,060 --> 00:28:24,170
就好像有守护天使一样
as if he has some guardian angel.

620
00:28:24,550 --> 00:28:28,940
之后我就全力搜寻线索  任何线索
All I've looked for since then is a lead, any lead,

621
00:28:29,020 --> 00:28:31,670
后来我意识到了  电话
and then I realized, the phone.

622
00:28:31,840 --> 00:28:33,920
他和他的联络员一直保持着通讯
He's in constant communication with his handlers.

623
00:28:33,920 --> 00:28:35,010
我也想到过
I thought of that.

624
00:28:35,010 --> 00:28:37,050
交叉对比了他所到的犯罪现场周边
Cross-checked crime scenes he was reported at

625
00:28:37,060 --> 00:28:39,100
手机基站日志中的手机串号
with cell tower logs of IMEIs.

626
00:28:39,100 --> 00:28:41,770
-一无所获  -对  一无所获
- Came up with nothing. - Exactly. Nothing.

627
00:28:41,940 --> 00:28:44,740
匡提科的工程师分析了他从下市区
Our engineers at Quantico analyzed the cell tower traffic

628
00:28:44,740 --> 00:28:46,750
溜走那晚的手机基站通信数据
from that night he gave us the slip downtown.

629
00:28:47,080 --> 00:28:49,000
在无线网络和收音机噪音之下
Under the wireless and radio noise,

630
00:28:49,000 --> 00:28:51,720
他们发现了一个有独特标识的
they found short bursts of a cloned IMEI

631
00:28:51,720 --> 00:28:53,390
克隆手机串号的短波信号
with a unique signature.

632
00:28:53,960 --> 00:28:56,870
我分配了联调局的机群搜寻该信号
I tasked an FBI computer cluster to search for that signature.

633
00:28:56,870 --> 00:28:59,130
24小时前  机群上线
24 hours ago, the cluster came online.

634
00:28:59,180 --> 00:29:01,690
它发现了另一个克隆手机串号的信号
It spotted another burst of cloned IMEIs

635
00:29:01,690 --> 00:29:04,330
与抢劫案的时间地点完全吻合
at the exact time and location of the robbery.

636
00:29:04,760 --> 00:29:05,830
是他
It's him.

637
00:29:05,830 --> 00:29:07,710
我已经让特警队待命了
I've got SWAT teams standing by.

638
00:29:07,710 --> 00:29:10,180
只要他用那个电话  我们就能逮住他
If he uses that phone, we'll have him.

639
00:29:30,690 --> 00:29:34,640
艾比  你做得够多了
Abby, this is far enough.

640
00:29:35,050 --> 00:29:36,050
下面我来吧
I'll handle this from here.

641
00:29:36,050 --> 00:29:37,410
回公寓等我
I'll meet you back at the apartment.

642
00:29:37,410 --> 00:29:40,010
不  要么一起  要么不做
No. No, together or nothing.

643
00:29:40,010 --> 00:29:41,710
你已经冒了太多险  艾比
You've risked enough, Abby.

644
00:29:41,940 --> 00:29:43,260
这不是你的战争
This isn't your fight right now.

645
00:29:43,260 --> 00:29:46,420
这就是我的战争  你就是我的战争
This is my fight. You're my fight.

646
00:30:25,730 --> 00:30:27,260
要我就不会那么做
I wouldn't do that.

647
00:30:28,190 --> 00:30:29,230
或这么做
Or that.

648
00:30:29,720 --> 00:30:31,140
说实话
Now, the truth...

649
00:30:33,040 --> 00:30:35,320
不然我亲自把你们带给警察
or I take you to the cops myself.

650
00:30:36,450 --> 00:30:38,600
我知道你们是来这偷查普的钱
I know you're here to steal Chapple's money.

651
00:30:38,750 --> 00:30:39,810
偷完以后呢
What then?

652
00:30:40,510 --> 00:30:42,940
我们想把钱还给被偷的人
We want to give it back to the people he stole it from.

653
00:30:43,170 --> 00:30:44,230
怎么还
How?

654
00:30:47,150 --> 00:30:49,430
我们还没想到那么远
We haven't thought that far ahead.

655
00:30:49,480 --> 00:30:51,620
你们根本就没想远过
You haven't thought very far at all.

656
00:30:51,870 --> 00:30:53,800
为什么不找警察或者律师
Now, why not go to the cops or a lawyer?

657
00:30:53,800 --> 00:30:54,680
艾比找了
Abby did.

658
00:30:54,680 --> 00:30:57,100
她去找地检官  可查普先到一步
She went to the DA, but Chapple got there first,

659
00:30:57,100 --> 00:30:58,400
打点了那里
spread his poison.

660
00:30:58,620 --> 00:31:00,230
地检甚至威胁要起诉她
The DA even threatened to prosecute her

661
00:31:00,230 --> 00:31:01,760
盗窃和诽谤
for theft and slander.

662
00:31:01,850 --> 00:31:02,960
等我回到公寓
When I got to my apartment,

663
00:31:02,960 --> 00:31:05,070
查普的打手也在那
one of Chapple's mercenaries was there.

664
00:31:05,100 --> 00:31:06,570
他揍了我一顿
He beat me up.

665
00:31:06,570 --> 00:31:08,090
告诉我如果我再多说一个字
He said if I said another word,

666
00:31:08,090 --> 00:31:10,460
他会回来用枪打爆我的头
He would come back and put a bullet in my head.

667
00:31:14,190 --> 00:31:16,070
穿过这里就是银行了吧
I assume the bank's through there?

668
00:31:17,080 --> 00:31:19,020
我们炸了这堵墙  我们在银行底下
We blow that wall, we're underneath it.

669
00:31:19,030 --> 00:31:20,990
约翰  这太过分了
John, this has gone far enough.

670
00:31:20,990 --> 00:31:21,950
是吗  芬奇
Has it, Finch?

671
00:31:21,960 --> 00:31:24,520
是的  阻止他们  我来搞定查普
Yes. Stop them. I can deal with Chapple.

672
00:31:24,530 --> 00:31:26,100
查普伤了他们  芬奇
Chapple hurt them, Finch.

673
00:31:26,100 --> 00:31:28,410
他们试过走法律途径  可是没成功
They tried the law. The law wasn't interested.

674
00:31:28,700 --> 00:31:30,260
他们还剩什么选择
What have they got left?

675
00:31:30,260 --> 00:31:32,950
再说了  我向来对那些
Besides, I've always had a thing

676
00:31:32,950 --> 00:31:35,080
坑退伍士兵的人颇有意见
about people who screw with veterans.

677
00:31:35,080 --> 00:31:36,570
约翰  这太冒险了
John, it's far too risky.

678
00:31:36,570 --> 00:31:38,070
你说什么来着  哈罗德
What did you say, Harold?

679
00:31:38,250 --> 00:31:40,430
没有无风险的人生
No such thing as a risk-free life.

680
00:31:42,020 --> 00:31:43,260
动手吧
Let's do it.

681
00:31:44,290 --> 00:31:45,690
等地铁通过
Wait for the subway.

682
00:31:49,040 --> 00:31:50,020
现在
Now.

683
00:32:05,950 --> 00:32:08,440
这就是保险箱的位置
This is where the safe deposit boxes are.

684
00:32:08,490 --> 00:32:10,660
我们意识到无法从银行里面接近它
We realized we couldn't get to them from inside the bank,

685
00:32:10,660 --> 00:32:13,340
所以我们决定让它来接近我们
So we decided to bring them to us.

686
00:32:13,760 --> 00:32:15,640
你们要把房顶炸了
You're gonna blow the roof.

687
00:32:24,310 --> 00:32:25,690
我们这有情况
We got something here.

688
00:32:27,350 --> 00:32:28,910
约翰  你那边如何
John, what's your situation?

689
00:32:30,080 --> 00:32:31,390
再给我十分钟
Ten more minutes.

690
00:32:31,490 --> 00:32:33,590
我这发现了一种情况  只能描述为
I'm seeing what I can only describe

691
00:32:33,590 --> 00:32:36,750
干扰了我们电话连线
as interference on our phone link.

692
00:32:37,330 --> 00:32:38,280
是根吗
Is it Root?

693
00:32:38,280 --> 00:32:41,050
不是  是种广谱扫描
No, it's a broad spectrum sweep,

694
00:32:41,060 --> 00:32:42,780
出自重型计算机
heavy-duty computer power.

695
00:32:42,780 --> 00:32:43,800
根会精致很多
Root's more subtle than that.

696
00:32:43,800 --> 00:32:45,500
一定是联调局的朋友
It must be our FBI friend.

697
00:32:45,690 --> 00:32:48,030
马上下线  立刻出来
Stay off the line and please get out now.

698
00:32:48,030 --> 00:32:50,320
如果尚恩和艾比不出来  抛下他们
If Shayn and Abby won't come, leave them.

699
00:32:51,480 --> 00:32:52,910
我从不抛下别人
I don't leave people,

700
00:32:52,960 --> 00:32:54,960
而且他们在打击坏蛋
and they're bringing down a very bad man.

701
00:32:55,120 --> 00:32:57,290
这的实验不就是为了这个吗
Now, isn't that what your experiment's all about?

702
00:32:57,290 --> 00:33:00,330
我的实验是为了救人命
My experiment is about stopping people from getting killed,

703
00:33:00,330 --> 00:33:01,610
不是为了抢银行
not robbing banks.

704
00:33:01,610 --> 00:33:03,230
五分钟后我们立刻出来
Five minutes and we're out.

705
00:33:15,960 --> 00:33:18,710
三  二  一
In three, two, one.

706
00:33:24,890 --> 00:33:25,840
走
Let's go.

707
00:33:34,490 --> 00:33:36,290
那个  158
There, 158.

708
00:34:00,010 --> 00:34:01,790
他的账户在委内瑞拉的一家银行
His account's in a bank in Venezuela.

709
00:34:01,790 --> 00:34:03,730
-这就是你们要找的  -一直都是
- Is this what you need? - Is it ever.

710
00:34:03,730 --> 00:34:05,470
这里有三千多万美金
There's more than $30 million here.

711
00:34:05,820 --> 00:34:07,780
他的慈善组织偷了三千万美金
His charity stole $30 million.

712
00:34:07,790 --> 00:34:09,720
走吧  原路返回
Then let's go, back the way we came.

713
00:34:10,150 --> 00:34:11,190
趴下
Get down!

714
00:34:18,500 --> 00:34:20,520
-你还好吗  -现世报啊
- You okay? - Karma at last.

715
00:34:20,530 --> 00:34:22,780
这些凶徒都是查普雇的  是吧
It's those thugs Chapple hired, isn't it?

716
00:34:22,780 --> 00:34:24,490
银行半小时后开门
The bank opens in 30 minutes.

717
00:34:24,490 --> 00:34:26,120
我们必须在那之前离开
We've got to get out before then.

718
00:34:26,200 --> 00:34:27,260
等我命令
Hang tight.

719
00:34:32,760 --> 00:34:33,840
911来电
911 call.

720
00:34:33,840 --> 00:34:35,970
华尔街附近的地下疑似有爆炸案
Possible underground explosion near Wall Street.

721
00:34:35,970 --> 00:34:38,680
我们在同样的区域追踪到了手机串号信号  是他
We're tracking IMEI bursts in the same area. It's him.

722
00:34:38,680 --> 00:34:39,960
我们马上召特警队来
Now, we hook up a SWAT en route.

723
00:34:39,960 --> 00:34:41,430
-你来吗  -当然
- Are you with us? - Uh, yeah, of course.

724
00:34:41,430 --> 00:34:42,860
我打完电话就去
I just need to make a phone call.

725
00:34:42,860 --> 00:34:44,190
好  快点
All right, make it quick.

726
00:34:47,390 --> 00:34:50,420
妈  你能送泰勒去学校吗
Hi, mom, can you make sure Taylor gets to school?

727
00:34:50,420 --> 00:34:52,150
妈  你喝酒了  卡特
Mom? You been drinking, Carter?

728
00:34:52,150 --> 00:34:54,400
告诉哈罗德  唐纳利正要前往华尔街
Tell Harold, Donnelly is headed to Wall Street.

729
00:34:54,410 --> 00:34:56,650
他说约翰在那  他一直在跟踪他的电话
He says john is there. He's tracking the phones.

730
00:34:56,650 --> 00:34:59,290
好的  妈  多谢  我爱你
Okay, mom. Yes. Thank you. I love you.

731
00:35:05,130 --> 00:35:06,470
我是弗斯科
Hey, it's Fusco.

732
00:35:06,530 --> 00:35:08,370
你家神奇小子在哪儿都好  最好不在华尔街
Wherever Wonder Boy is, I hope it's not near Wall Street,

733
00:35:08,370 --> 00:35:09,810
因为唐纳利正要过去
because that's where Donnelly's heading.

734
00:35:09,810 --> 00:35:11,190
约翰就在那里
That's exactly where John is.

735
00:35:11,190 --> 00:35:13,370
莫顿·瓦特投资银行  汉诺威大街
Merton Watts Investment Bank, Hanover street.

736
00:35:13,370 --> 00:35:14,470
对了  卡特还说了什么
Yeah, plus Carter said something

737
00:35:14,470 --> 00:35:15,860
你们的手机问题
about him being up on your phones.

738
00:35:15,860 --> 00:35:17,120
果然如我所虑
Just as I feared.

739
00:35:17,120 --> 00:35:19,950
尽量帮我们在银行搞出点干扰来
Anything you can do to run interference for us at the bank,

740
00:35:19,960 --> 00:35:21,980
警探  我感激不尽
Detective, I would be most grateful.

741
00:35:48,490 --> 00:35:50,550
看来你认识这位先生
I take it you know this gentleman?

742
00:35:51,210 --> 00:35:54,270
彼得·约格洛夫  俄罗斯黑帮的执刑人
Peter Yogorov, enforcer for the Russian mob.

743
00:35:54,270 --> 00:35:57,010
至少以利亚除掉他老爹之前是
Least he used to be until Elias took out his old man.

744
00:35:57,350 --> 00:35:59,860
这点可能对我们有利
Seems like something that might be to our advantage.

745
00:36:00,480 --> 00:36:02,230
反击以利亚
To hit back at Elias?

746
00:36:02,790 --> 00:36:04,760
组建另一个收入来源
To build another revenue stream.

747
00:36:05,100 --> 00:36:06,390
约格洛夫在任务控制中心
Yogorov's at MCC,

748
00:36:06,400 --> 00:36:08,650
和他弟弟拉兹罗一起候审
awaiting trial with his little brother Lazlo.

749
00:36:09,290 --> 00:36:11,970
地检死死咬住他一堆罪名
DA's got him dead to rights on a dozen different counts.

750
00:36:11,970 --> 00:36:13,610
可以在这上面做点文章
Maybe we can do something about that.

751
00:36:15,600 --> 00:36:17,810
需要地检官的资料吗
You need something on the district attorney?

752
00:36:18,200 --> 00:36:19,510
我来处理
Let me handle that.

753
00:36:20,490 --> 00:36:22,590
给我们的使者以斯巴达式回应
By going all Spartan on our emissaries,

754
00:36:22,600 --> 00:36:26,230
以利亚表达得很清楚了  关系完蛋了
Elias has made it clear-- that relationship is over.

755
00:36:26,960 --> 00:36:28,440
我们要交些新朋友
We need new friends.

756
00:36:30,790 --> 00:36:32,780
你要我去跟俄国人谈判
You want me to talk to the Russians?

757
00:36:32,990 --> 00:36:34,650
公开谈判
Open negotiations?

758
00:36:34,960 --> 00:36:37,550
他们有条件  但如果和我们合作
They have all the right pieces, but with us behind them,

759
00:36:37,550 --> 00:36:39,720
现金流不会再是问题
cash flow would no longer be an issue.

760
00:36:39,890 --> 00:36:41,470
了解  老大
Understood, boss.

761
00:36:42,280 --> 00:36:44,310
刚刚听说了些有趣的事
Just heard something interesting.

762
00:36:44,940 --> 00:36:47,170
看起来我们的眼中钉唐纳利
Looks like that pain-in-the-ass Donnelly

763
00:36:47,530 --> 00:36:49,660
被西装男给迷住了
finally caught up with the man in the suit.

764
00:36:50,560 --> 00:36:54,450
不到早上七点  今天已如此美妙
Not even 7:00am, and already a perfect day.

765
00:36:58,850 --> 00:37:00,080
银行就要开始营业了  约翰
The bank's about to open, John.

766
00:37:00,080 --> 00:37:01,160
你在哪里
Where are you?

767
00:37:07,800 --> 00:37:09,310
里瑟先生  发生什么事了
Mr. Reese, what's happening?

768
00:37:12,470 --> 00:37:13,440
我讨厌这么说  芬奇
I hate to say this, Finch,

769
00:37:13,440 --> 00:37:15,140
但是我们被困住了
but we're in a bit of a pickle here.

770
00:37:15,140 --> 00:37:16,390
上楼去大厅
Get upstairs to the foyer.

771
00:37:16,390 --> 00:37:18,550
我给你们准备了身份证和通行证
I have IDs and passes for all of you.

772
00:37:18,930 --> 00:37:19,960
掩护我们
Cover us.

773
00:37:28,910 --> 00:37:30,120
你在找什么
What are you looking for?

774
00:37:32,140 --> 00:37:33,270
衣服
Clothes.

775
00:37:33,320 --> 00:37:34,970
你们需要换装
You need to get changed.

776
00:37:36,760 --> 00:37:38,680
我们得打扮成银行职员的样子
We're gonna dress up like bankers.

777
00:37:39,070 --> 00:37:40,460
我们要爬上去
We're gonna climb up there

778
00:37:40,950 --> 00:37:42,510
走出前门
and walk right out the front door.

779
00:37:42,510 --> 00:37:43,540
来吧
Come on.

780
00:37:47,460 --> 00:37:49,720
总部刚刚捕获到一次目标信号
Base just picked up another burst of comms from the target.

781
00:37:49,720 --> 00:37:51,020
-同样位置  -是  长官
- Same location? - Yes, Sir.

782
00:37:51,020 --> 00:37:53,170
你能追踪到他  但是听不到声音
So, you can track him, but you can't hear what he's saying?

783
00:37:54,660 --> 00:37:56,290
知道他在跟谁谈话吗
Do you know who he's talking to?

784
00:37:56,550 --> 00:37:57,670
暂时不知道
Not yet.

785
00:38:03,420 --> 00:38:06,690
把枪给我  你带艾比走
Give me the gun. You take Abby.

786
00:38:08,460 --> 00:38:09,400
你做得够多了
You've done enough.

787
00:38:09,400 --> 00:38:11,280
害我们陷入困境的是我
I'm the one who got us into this mess.

788
00:38:12,420 --> 00:38:14,920
害我们陷入困境的是我们自己
We all got ourselves into this mess.

789
00:38:15,060 --> 00:38:17,290
我们得自我拯救
We're all going to get ourselves out.

790
00:38:18,150 --> 00:38:20,830
当你们上到大厅之后  找哈罗德
Now, when you get up to the foyer, look for Harold.

791
00:38:21,570 --> 00:38:23,100
我随后跟上
I'll be right behind you.

792
00:38:23,770 --> 00:38:24,800
现在
Now.

793
00:39:00,050 --> 00:39:02,160
看来里面什么都没发生
Looks like nothing's going on inside.

794
00:39:02,350 --> 00:39:04,370
不  信号仍在活动  911报警电话称
No, the signal's still active, and the 911 call

795
00:39:04,370 --> 00:39:06,390
爆炸发生于地下  记得吗
said the explosion was underground, remember?

796
00:39:06,400 --> 00:39:07,420
他在里面
He's in there.

797
00:39:09,200 --> 00:39:10,290
好的  一队跟我从前面进去
All right, one team in front with me,

798
00:39:10,300 --> 00:39:11,230
第二队  绕到后面
second team, around the back.

799
00:39:11,230 --> 00:39:12,560
半小时内行动
We move in 30.

800
00:39:12,870 --> 00:39:14,080
抱歉  女士
Excuse me, ma'am.

801
00:39:16,800 --> 00:39:18,310
我是银行的客户
I'm a client here at the bank.

802
00:39:18,320 --> 00:39:20,510
我想现在进入地下室
I need to get into the vault now.

803
00:39:27,380 --> 00:39:29,870
你们好  拿好这些
Hello. Here. Take these.

804
00:39:30,350 --> 00:39:33,330
我叫哈罗德·冉  开了一家保险公司
My name is Harold Wren. I own an insurance company.

805
00:39:33,330 --> 00:39:36,980
你们是我的同事  我们在家里有预约
You are my associates. We have an appointment here.

806
00:39:37,450 --> 00:39:38,060
约翰呢
Where's John?

807
00:39:38,060 --> 00:39:40,340
联调局  所有人都靠在墙上
FBI! Everybody back against the wall!

808
00:39:40,680 --> 00:39:42,240
-待在原地  -不要动
- Stay where you are! - Don't move!

809
00:39:42,240 --> 00:39:44,310
-举起手来  -看到你们的手
- Hands up! - See your hands!

810
00:39:44,570 --> 00:39:45,550
大厅安检
Foyer's secure.

811
00:39:45,550 --> 00:39:46,950
检查身份证  统统不许离开
Check every ID. No one leaves.

812
00:39:46,950 --> 00:39:48,280
一半人留下  一半跟我走
Half your men here, half with me.

813
00:39:48,280 --> 00:39:48,830
是  长官
Yes, Sir.

814
00:39:48,830 --> 00:39:50,410
-我们走  -手举起来  让我们看见
- Let's go! - Hands where we can see them!

815
00:39:50,410 --> 00:39:51,990
你  不要动
You! Don't move!

816
00:39:52,170 --> 00:39:54,250
-请出示您的身份证明  -约翰  能听到我吗
- See your ID, please? - John, can you hear me?

817
00:39:54,250 --> 00:39:55,370
尚恩和艾比都安全了
Shayn and Abby are safe.

818
00:39:55,370 --> 00:39:57,640
联调局的到银行了  快走
FBI are in the bank. Get out now.

819
00:40:05,100 --> 00:40:05,950
我们有同伴了
We got company.

820
00:40:05,950 --> 00:40:08,050
扔掉武器  快给我出来
Lose the weapons and get the hell out.

821
00:40:11,950 --> 00:40:14,080
约翰  能听到吗  你得马上走
John, can you hear me? You must get out now.

822
00:40:14,080 --> 00:40:15,270
炸开了地板
Blew out the damn floor.

823
00:40:15,270 --> 00:40:17,210
A  这里是D  地下室安全
Alpha, this is Delta. Vault level is secure.

824
00:40:17,220 --> 00:40:18,590
我出不去了  哈罗德
I'm not gonna make it, Harold.

825
00:40:18,590 --> 00:40:20,090
抱歉我搞砸了
Sorry I screwed up.

826
00:40:20,970 --> 00:40:22,790
我昨天说的是真心话
But I meant what I said yesterday.

827
00:40:24,550 --> 00:40:27,510
谢谢  哈罗德  很好玩
So, thanks, Harold. It was fun.

828
00:40:27,640 --> 00:40:28,630
约翰
John?

829
00:40:33,740 --> 00:40:34,720
身份证
ID?

830
00:40:35,510 --> 00:40:37,780
哈罗德·冉  环球人寿保险
Harold Wren, Universal Heritage Insurance.

831
00:40:37,780 --> 00:40:39,140
我的同事
My associates.

832
00:40:39,770 --> 00:40:40,820
你们来银行干嘛
Why are you in the bank?

833
00:40:40,830 --> 00:40:44,170
我们和公司的策略副总裁有个会议
We have a meeting with the vice president of corporate strategy.

834
00:40:48,680 --> 00:40:49,690
身份证
ID.

835
00:40:51,830 --> 00:40:53,600
拿到想要的了吗
Did you get what you wanted?

836
00:40:53,750 --> 00:40:55,960
查普偷的所有钱
All the money Chapple stole.

837
00:40:55,970 --> 00:40:57,550
超过三千万
More than $30 million.

838
00:40:57,760 --> 00:40:59,600
你能利用这些账目做些什么吗
Can you do anything with the accounts?

839
00:41:05,610 --> 00:41:06,740
能
Yes.

840
00:41:08,270 --> 00:41:10,530
我会清空它们  把全所钱都
I'll empty them, deposit every last cent

841
00:41:10,530 --> 00:41:13,360
转到知名的军人慈善组织账户下
into the accounts of reputable military charities.

842
00:41:13,360 --> 00:41:14,530
可以吗
Would that do?

843
00:41:17,420 --> 00:41:18,720
我要送你们俩离开这里
Then I have to get you out of here

844
00:41:18,720 --> 00:41:20,400
离开本州
and out of this state.

845
00:41:21,060 --> 00:41:22,750
只要我们在一起就行
As long as we're together.

846
00:41:26,410 --> 00:41:27,610
检查上层
Check the top level.

847
00:41:28,380 --> 00:41:29,530
检查下面
Check down back.

848
00:41:32,330 --> 00:41:33,890
别担心  我掩护你们
Don't worry. I got you covered.

849
00:41:35,110 --> 00:41:36,180
那约翰呢
What about john?

850
00:41:36,190 --> 00:41:38,240
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

851
00:41:38,240 --> 00:41:40,260
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

852
00:41:41,110 --> 00:41:42,210
{\an8}*Baby*

853
00:41:44,330 --> 00:41:46,420
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

854
00:41:46,420 --> 00:41:48,530
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

855
00:41:50,840 --> 00:41:52,400
终于抓到你了
We finally got you.

856
00:41:52,460 --> 00:41:54,470
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

857
00:41:54,470 --> 00:41:56,430
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

858
00:41:56,430 --> 00:41:58,000
长官  有点问题
Sir, there's a probl.

859
00:41:58,000 --> 00:41:59,040
退后
Step back.

860
00:42:00,270 --> 00:42:02,600
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

861
00:42:02,600 --> 00:42:04,470
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

862
00:42:04,470 --> 00:42:07,180
{\an8}*Yeah, yeah, yeah*

863
00:42:12,210 --> 00:42:13,820
你能认出来他吗
Well, do you recognize him?

864
00:42:19,550 --> 00:42:20,630
不能
No.

865
00:42:20,760 --> 00:42:24,130
{\an8}*Gimme, gimme shelter*

866
00:42:24,130 --> 00:42:24,920
全拷上
Cuff 'em all.

867
00:42:24,920 --> 00:42:28,020
{\an8}*Or I'm gonna fade away*

868
00:42:28,910 --> 00:42:31,920
{\an8}*War, children*

869
00:42:32,580 --> 00:42:34,650
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

870
00:42:34,650 --> 00:42:36,680
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

871
00:42:36,680 --> 00:42:38,890
{\an8}*It's just a shot away*

