Previously on Pretty Little Liars.
I'm scared.
All I can think about is
when the next bad thing is gonna happen.
He left my apartment to go beat her.
The next day she was missing.
He was with my mother the entire night.
Did he tell you that?
You're going back to Bucks County?
I am exactly where I need to be.
I found these in his dresser.
Those are mine.
I don't think Byron knows
we have those pages.
If you want, I can take them... no.
Don't worry. I hid them.
I don't want to see you, I
don't want to hear from you,
and I don't want to know you.
What is this?
Some kind of herb thing. It's
Meredith's cure-all recipe.
I don't think it's working.
You look terrible.
Thank you.
Oh, God...
I couldn't have picked a
worse time to get sick.
Have you heard from your dad?
He left a message, but I
haven't talked to him
since he left for his conference.
Hey. How's the patient?
Not great.
Well...
I brought over everything
that helps me when I'm sick.
Trash...
Ginger ale...
And three seasons of "saved by the bell."
Thank you, Hanna.
Are you sure you want to
stay here by yourself?
Guys, I'm fine. You don't look fine.
So I've heard.
You sure you don't want us
to drive you to your mom's?
No, it's her week with Mike, so
the guest room's already taken.
And besides, I promised Meredith
that I wouldn't tell her about Ali's diary
until we talked to my dad, so
if I just stay away from her,
it's easier to keep that a secret.
I can't believe we're trusting Meredith.
I think she's really just
as devastated as I am.
You're not giving her the pages, right?
No, they're hidden in a safe place,
and they'll stay there
till my dad get home.
Then we'll give him the
chance to tell us the truth.
And if he doesn't?
I don't want to believe that
my dad could have hurt Ali.
But if he did do it...
This is a family secret that I can't keep.
We're set for tomorrow.
It's too soon. Did Spencer
say something to you?
She's still lying to me...
pretending "a" went away when
they took you to Radley.
That bitch can keep a secret.
I respect that.
I still feel like we're rushing this.
I told you... I'm not the
one calling the shots.
Fear cuts deeper than a sword.
They need to understand
that she's in charge.
Well, then, I'll take care of it.
Sync by YYeTS
Corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
Today's drip. Black.
Thanks, em. Thank you for letting me hang.
Mmm . How'd they get you to
open up the brew this morning?
Kinda got drafted. I'm running
over to Spencer's for a shower.
The plumber won't be here until nine.
Great.
I've got some reading to do.
"Lord of the flies." Your pick or theirs?
Theirs. I don't mind.
I kind of identify with those boys.
Feel like I've been on that island.
With the girls.
We did it the right way... we
stuck together no matter what.
You are thick as thieves.
We knew "a" was trying to tear us apart.
Mona actually brought us closer together.
And we know that now.
We're stronger for it.
So you actually have
something to thank her for.
I wouldn't go that far.
Now that she back in rosewood,
Mona's leaving you alone, right?
She... Seems to be a model citizen.
You'd tell me if things started up again...
Wouldn't you?
Of course.
I gotta get back to the flies.
Oh, hey, em, could you
lock up on your way out?
Sure.
Hey, Spence. Mission accomplished.
He's on his way to your
house, and I got the keys.
Okay...
Which one screams "young and hot"
without being too trendy?
You're asking me?
Hanna, I've had this
hoodie since I was twelve.
Caleb, come on, this is important.
I have to impress Corin.
It's a job interview. You're
not walking the runway.
She's the hottest designer in Philly.
It'd be a privilege to
get her a cup of coffee.
She wants you to do it in five-inch heels?
Yeah, at least.
All right, go with the dress.
But just to be sure, you should
probably try it on for me.
I'll be right back.
Hey. Ohh. Forgot my shoes.
Yeah, I thought a lot about it.
I'm in.
I'm not gonna let her do
anything else to Hanna.
We'll talk this afternoon.
Who were you talking to?
Um, it was my mom.
It's four-thirty in California.
Do you always call her this early?
She's not in Montecito. She's, um...
In Chicago, uh, for business.
So why were you talking to
your mom about Mona and me?
She knows that Mona bullied you,
and she's just worried about
her being back in school.
Mona had someone run your mom off the road.
You shouldn't be talking
about her to anyone.
Hanna, Mona tried to run you
over when you were friends.
God only knows what she's gonna
do now that you've dumped her.
Maybe she won't do anything.
Of course she will. She's "a."
We need to stay one step ahead of her.
Look, just promise me that you
won't do anything stupid.
Hanna... promise me.
Fine. I won't do anything stupid.
Now let's see something
hot and not-too-trendy.
I promise today is the last time
that they'll have to shut
the water off in the loft.
I already told you, I don't
really have a problem with it.
You sure you can't come over later and...
Check out the new tub?
I hate that I can't see you tonight.
But they're honoring my dad at this dinner,
so of course I have to be there.
I understand.
We will celebrate tomorrow. Yeah.
Toby.
Ahh.
You know that I could fix this, right?
Three years ago I made an exact replica
of Mary queen of scots' execution dress
for my Halloween costume,
and I didn't have a pattern.
Is there anything that you can't do?
Yes. Get out of this stupid dinner
that's keeping me from
you on our anniversary.
Uh... I was just about to go in
the other room and get dressed.
I thought I'd help you decide
on what to wear to the dinner
that you're so obviously agog about.
Are you sure that dad'll
be upset if I don't go?
Well, he has to sit through it,
so he wants his family
to sit through it, too.
Misery loves company.
I'll... I'll find my way out.
Toby.
You forgot your shirt.
Bye.
How'd I do? Awesome. He has no clue.
I copied grandma's recipe.
Oh, thank you.
Ohh. What?
I made that lasagna for your
father on our first anniversary.
Toby's gonna love it. Thank you.
And thank you for my cover story.
I hope he likes surprises.
I'm counting on it.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
Not that great.
Have I been sleeping all day?
No, it's not quite lunchtime.
I had a break in classes, so I
thought I'd check in on you.
You feel really warm.
I think I need to see a doctor.
I was gonna call my mom...
my phone was just right here.
I'll look for it.
But we need to get you upstairs.
You'll sleep so much better in bed.
Can you just have my mom call me?
Yeah. I'll find her as soon
as I get back to the school.
I'm sure she'll come over right away.
Thank you.
I bet the stress of your dad
and those diary pages brought this on.
I can't even think about that right now.
No, of course not.
But you put those pages
in a safe place, right?
Aria?
Rosemary chicken? Kale salad?
What did I do to deserve this?
I thought since you
weren't up for going out,
I'd bring all your favorites to you.
So, have you given any thought
to what I said the other night?
About what?
About seeing someone to
help you with the anxiety.
Actually, I did. I found someone.
And I made an appointment
for this afternoon.
Really? I figured talking to someone
who understands what I'm
going through can only help.
Thanks for the push.
Of course.
Hey. Sorry to interrupt.
Uh, I have to borrow Emily
for some girl talk.
Not girl-on-girl talk, just... Girl talk.
Um, right now?
I'm really sorry. It's just important.
She's all yours. Okay.
What's up? I called you a couple times.
Yeah. I been busy.
I need a favor from you, and I
normally wouldn't ask this,
but I have an interview today,
Aria's sick, and Spencer
is surprising Toby...
okay, slow down. I need you to follow Caleb
after school and see where he's going.
Follow him. Why?
I heard him on the phone this morning,
and he's meeting someone.
They were talking about Mona.
I think he's gonna shut her down.
Okay. I love you, Hanna,
but I'm not in the C.I.A.
I don't know the first thing
about tailing someone.
It's easy. You just stay far
enough away so he doesn't see you,
but not so far that you lose him.
What if he does see me? You lie.
You just say that you
happened to be in the area.
How do you know this?
My mom used to take me with her
when we were following my dad.
When she thought that he was
hooking up with Isabel.
He was hooking up with Isabel.
Yeah. My point exactly.
Look, if the roles were reversed
and Paige was in danger,
you know I'd do it for you.
Ella. I was just coming to see you.
Ah. Here I am.
I stopped by to see Aria on my break.
I thought you'd want to know
she's feeling a lot better.
Oh. That's great.
I didn't want to call and
wake her if she was sleeping,
but I'll give her a call now.
Um, thanks for letting me know.
Of course.
And, uh, thanks for checking on her.
My pleasure. Really. She's a lovely girl.
Corin?
Hello?
Hello? It's Hanna marin.
Oh, my God.
Help!
Somebody help me!
Uhh!
Come on.
Thanks for meeting me. I'm
sorry you had to lie to Hanna.
Some lies are worth the risk.
It took me and Emily so
long to get to a place
where we could trust each other.
If she knew we were doing
this... same with Hanna.
She would find a way to stop us.
I've been running scared
since the lighthouse,
getting more afraid every day.
Then the other night I realized
I'm not afraid for me...
I'm afraid for Emily.
She's been dealing with this for so long
it's almost like she's numb
to how dangerous it is.
Yeah.
We know that Mona has people
watching their every move.
But there's no way that's she has someone
watching all of us all the time.
So while the girls are
playing sitting duck,
I'm ready to circle the pond and...
nail her psychotic butt to the wall.
Yeah, something like that.
Before she went to Radley, Mona had, like,
all the girls' secrets locked
away in a motel room...
they were her trophies.
Her prized possessions.
That's what she used to keep the
girls from going to the cops.
So if we find her trophy room,
we can put an end to this.
Corin moved her store to
society hill a month ago.
Did you tell Mona you applied
for a job there? No,
I applied months ago online.
She's just doing this to get
back at me for cutting her off.
No, it wasn't her. I saw
her at school around four.
Then it was her Minion.
Is she threatening to cut your face off?
Or throw acid at her.
You guys, come on.
Shall we give this key to the cops?
There's a numerical code on it.
Maybe they could trace it.
Even if they could trace it,
are you ready to talk about Mona 2.0?
That's what we would have
to do if we turned it in.
For all we know, it's not
just Mona and her Minion.
Maybe she's built this whole "a" army.
We still don't know what her endgame is.
I do. It's to cut my face off.
I hear you guys,
but she still has all those
pictures of us at Ali's grave.
You know what? I don't care anymore.
She has to be stopped.
You're right. But this decision
is going to affect all of us.
Aria has to be in on it too. Has
anyone talked to her today?
I tried her phone, but
all I get is voicemail.
Me too. She's probably still sleeping.
Let's just wait. We'll talk
about it in the morning.
I gotta get ready for tonight.
Spence, have fun tonight.
We'll worry about all this tomorrow.
Thanks.
If you really want to surprise Toby,
have on five-inch heels and
nothing else when he
walks through the door.
What? I've heard guys like that.
Thanks for the tip.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm taking back what's mine.
Is this a dream?
No, sweetie,
I'm more real than I've ever been.
Tell me what it's like. Tell me everything.
Well...
I don't know who said knowledge was king...
just an old fart, probably...
but he was right. I see everything now.
I missed so much when I was here.
Do you see "a"?
Everywhere I turn.
So do you.
You all do.
I'm surprised Spencer
hasn't figured that out.
Did it really happen, what
you wrote in those pages?
Were you blackmailing my dad?
Byron's really coming around, isn't he?
I mean, when the chips were
down with Ezra's mom. Ali...
I need to know the truth.
If I tell you the truth, you
don't have to believe it.
Please.
I was desperate for that money.
How could you do that to my family?
To me?
It was just a threat.
I never called your mom.
Did my dad kill you?
Do I look dead to you?
I wouldn't drink that.
What do you mean?
Meredith is looking for these pages too.
Ali, wait.
You know why I picked you, right?
What the...
hello!
Feed scalp. Feed beauty. Still hurts?
Kyle Bown, on the boys' swim team,.
He can bend his wrist
all the way to his arm,
and it doesn't even hurt him.
I think he's double-jointed.
And you're telling me this because?
What do you mean you can't refill it?
You refilled this prescription last week.
Yeah, I know, but I...
misplaced my pill bottle.
I'm sorry, ma'am. Clonazepam
is a class 3 medication.
You can ask your doctor to
call in another prescription.
I don't have time to call my doctor.
I need those pills now.
There's nothing we can do for you tonight.
We're closing in a few minutes.
Great. That's just great.
Ring me up.
It says clonazepam is most
commonly used for anxiety,
but some people also use
it to help them sleep.
Either Meredith is a major insomniac
or she's trying to knock out a cow.
I do not like the idea of that
woman nursing Aria back to health.
I'm calling her again.
Straight to voicemail.
You scared me.
I'm sorry. I wanted to surprise you.
You did. Why aren't you at work?
I'm on a break, and since I'm
not gonna see you tonight...
Happy anniversary.
Oh... they're beautiful.
Thank you.
I feel so bad, though. I
didn't get you anything.
It's okay, I didn't expect you to.
Let me go put these in water.
"A"?
Oh. It's not what you think.
Melissa left it here. She has
a storage unit in Philly.
They're so pretty.
I better get back to work.
Yeah. I better go get
dressed for that dinner.
The sky's looking pretty dark.
Maybe I'll get to come home early.
Will you call me if you do?
Love you.
I love you too.
Is this what you're looking for?
Quite the clever girl.
I've searched every inch
of this house, twice,
and I can't find those pages anywhere.
Have you been drugging me?
Don't be so dramatic.
I gave you something to help you sleep.
Yeah, and you locked me in my room.
There's no way I'm letting
you turn those pages over to the police.
It's not really your decision, is it?
Shut up and sit down!
I lied to you. My friends
know about that diary.
So whatever it is that you're
thinking, it's not gonna work.
What?!
Come on.
She has to be here.
Aria!
Aria, are you in here?
Hey. I just wanted to check in on you.
I think I'm gonna make it home
before the storm really hits.
Well, good. I'm glad you're on your way.
So how's the dinner?
Ah, it's moving along.
Will you be careful? Will do.
Okay, bye.
Here's the key.
Aria?
Come on.
She's not here.
I'm calling her.
Meredith? What are you girls
doing out in this storm?
Where is Aria? She went down
to the basement to look
for some flashlights.
She has been down there a little while.
Maybe we should check on her.
Aria? Are you down here?
Oh, my God, it's locked.
Locked!
Hang on.
Okay.
Hanna. What?
I don't think we're alone down here.
Oh, my God!
Aria? Aria, are you okay?
Wake up, wake up. Aria!
Wake up!
Aria.
It's gonna be okay, Aria.
No, it's not. She lost it. She's crazy.
What is she doing up there?
If Spencer was here she'd
say that she was pacing
while she plots her way to get rid of us.
She'd probably be right.
There's three of us and one of her.
Let's give her the pages
and then we'll take her down.
Take her down?
I have no problem opening a can
of whoop-ass on that woman.
It's your dad.
He... he wasn't supposed to
be home till tomorrow.
She must have called him.
Is he in on this?
I don't know what I believe anymore.
Meredith?
Hey, I only heard half your message.
I've been trying to call,
but the phones are out.
Meredith? What... what's wrong?
Aria knows everything.
She knows about the blackmail.
And she knows that you saw
Alison that night. That you...
she has proof, Byron.
And her friends know, too.
What are you doing with that?
We don't know what they're planning.
My dad would never hurt us.
Aria? Are you sure about that?
Aria?
Are you okay?
You don't need to be afraid of me.
I swear. I...
you don't need I didn't hurt Alison.
I didn't bring any money.
Then we both know how this is gonna end.
You know how much it'll hurt
Aria if you make that call.
And I don't think you're
that horrible of a person.
Then you clearly don't know me that well.
Last chance to save yourself.
Yes, it is.
You made your bed, Mr. Montgomery!
What do I have to do, call
911 to get your attention?
I was prepared to tell your mom the truth.
Then Alison went missing.
And the longer she stayed missing,
the harder it became for me to tell anyone.
Is this what you're looking for?
Spencer.
How long have you known?
Spencer?
Hi, honey.
Is everything okay?
What is it, honey?
Mommy!
I-I called the police, and they
checked Meredith's apartment.
She's gone.
You told us about the affair. Why
didn't you tell us about this?
When they found Alison's body,
it was clear that she had been murdered,
and there were no suspects.
I saw her the night she died,
and I knew how that would look.
You mean how it does look.
What started this? How did you find out?
We found an old diary of Ali's.
She wrote about you.
Why didn't... why didn't
you come and talk to me?
I wanted to.
But Meredith made me believe
that you actually...
I was scared.
Aria, I need to know if
there's any part of you
that still thinks that I
could have done this.
I understand.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna do something I should
have done a long time ago.
I'm gonna tell the police everything.
And hopefully after whatever
investigation they do
you will realize that I had nothing
to do with Alison's death.
What are you doing?
I believe you.
I know you're in there.
Will you...
Will you just tell me that what
I saw tonight wasn't real?
Please!
Just tell me that there's
more to this story...
That there's something that I don't know.
Please. Please, Toby...
Please, Toby.
Sync by YYeTS
Corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com