1
00:03:28,620 --> 00:03:29,630
{\an4}美

2
00:03:28,620 --> 00:03:29,630
{\an4} 少

3
00:03:28,620 --> 00:03:29,630
{\an4}  女

4
00:03:28,620 --> 00:03:29,630
{\an4}   的

5
00:03:28,620 --> 00:03:29,630
{\an4}    谎

6
00:03:28,620 --> 00:03:29,630
{\an4}     言

7
00:03:29,630 --> 00:03:30,960
美少女的谎言

8
00:03:29,430 --> 00:03:30,960
{\an6}第三季 第十四集

11
00:03:10,430 --> 00:03:15,430
{\pos(70,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

12
00:03:10,430 --> 00:03:15,430
{\pos(70,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

13
00:03:10,430 --> 00:03:15,430
{\pos(60,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

14
00:03:10,430 --> 00:03:15,430
{\pos(86,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

15
00:03:10,430 --> 00:03:15,430
{\pos(100,254)}人人影视
YYeTs.com

16
00:03:10,430 --> 00:03:15,430
{\pos(101,267)}原创翻译  双语字幕

17
00:03:10,430 --> 00:03:15,430
{\pos(240,267)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

18
00:03:15,440 --> 00:03:19,430
{\an8}翻译： 鱼小姐 圈圈 慕秋雪 蔷薇 小林安娜 便秘熊 glorydai

19
00:03:19,440 --> 00:03:23,430
{\an8}时间轴： 贝壳 cherry  后期：  Ghost

20
00:03:23,440 --> 00:03:27,430
{\an8}校对： TanKnoX 往兮 glorydai  总监： 爱吃屎的鱼

22
00:00:00,720 --> 00:00:03,030
{\an8}迷失森林度假村

23
00:00:01,150 --> 00:00:02,850
《美少女的谎言》前情提要

24
00:00:02,850 --> 00:00:04,410
欢迎来到迷失森林度假村
Welcome to the Lost Woods Resort.

25
00:00:04,410 --> 00:00:05,730
可能你还记得我们的朋友  
Maybe you remember our friend, 

26
00:00:05,730 --> 00:00:06,550
薇薇安·德克布鲁
Vivian Darkbloom.

27
00:00:06,550 --> 00:00:07,720
大家之所以入住迷失森林
You check into the Lost Woods

28
00:00:07,720 --> 00:00:09,070
就是因为不想被找到
because you don't want to be found.

29
00:00:09,070 --> 00:00:10,260
你来这里干嘛  
What are you doing here? 

30
00:00:10,260 --> 00:00:12,610
我来看看他  他毕竟是我儿子的父亲  
I was curious. He's the father of my son.

31
00:00:12,610 --> 00:00:13,930
对  他应该有知情权
Yeah, he deserves to know that.

32
00:00:13,930 --> 00:00:16,830
我没杀艾莉森  但詹娜以为我杀了她
I didn't kill Alison, but Jenna thinks I did.

33
00:00:17,590 --> 00:00:19,420
-就这样  -我又回去了
- That's it? - I went back.

34
00:00:19,430 --> 00:00:21,950
-你在撒谎  -我走时  她还活着
- You're lying. - She was alive when I left.

35
00:00:27,290 --> 00:00:28,490
梅雷迪斯被聘用了  
Meredith got the job. 

36
00:00:28,490 --> 00:00:29,590
玫瑰镇高中的职位吗
The job at Rosewood High.

37
00:00:29,590 --> 00:00:32,660
艾瑞亚  我都忘了你还在这念书
Well, Aria, I forgot you're still a student here.

38
00:00:36,290 --> 00:00:38,740
计划有变  我们很快会再见面
Change of plan. I'll see you soon.

39
00:01:18,870 --> 00:01:21,020
-来的不是时候吗  -你在这儿干嘛
- Is it a bad time? - What are you doing here?

40
00:01:21,020 --> 00:01:23,730
-医生让我出院了  -大半夜吗
- My doctors released me. - In the middle of the night?

41
00:01:23,730 --> 00:01:25,690
汉娜  你得帮我
Hanna, I need your help.

42
00:01:25,870 --> 00:01:27,760
我爸妈要逼我回学校
My parents are forcing me to go back to school,

43
00:01:27,760 --> 00:01:30,390
-我害怕极了  -梦娜...
- and I'm so scared. - Mona...

44
00:01:30,390 --> 00:01:31,810
大家都知道我的所作所为  
Everyone knows what I've done, 

45
00:01:31,810 --> 00:01:33,650
我也没有朋友支持我了
and I have no one in my corner.

46
00:01:33,940 --> 00:01:35,720
如果你指望我和我的朋友们原谅你...
If you're expecting me and my friends to forgive you...

47
00:01:35,720 --> 00:01:40,380
我不指望他们会  可汉娜  你不一样
I don't expect them to, but, hanna, you're different.

48
00:01:42,490 --> 00:01:43,990
任说过你是我的守护天使
Wren said you were my guardian angel.

49
00:01:43,990 --> 00:01:45,530
你为我辩护过
He said that you stood up for me.

50
00:01:45,530 --> 00:01:47,500
你对此又不是毫无防备  梦娜
You are not defenseless, Mona.

51
00:01:47,930 --> 00:01:50,400
这两年你不就在钻研如何折磨他人吗
You spent the last two years majoring in torture.

52
00:01:52,190 --> 00:01:54,770
你不相信人能改过吗
So you don't believe that a person can get better?

53
00:01:55,210 --> 00:01:57,080
汉娜  我崩溃过
Hanna, I had a breakdown,

54
00:01:57,560 --> 00:01:59,040
但我已经爬起来了
but I've turned a corner.

55
00:01:59,160 --> 00:02:01,540
如今我洗心革面  不同于昨日了
I'm on new meds, everything's changed.

56
00:02:01,640 --> 00:02:02,890
我对过去很愧疚
I'm not proud of who I was.

57
00:02:02,890 --> 00:02:05,890
但请你看看现在的我
Just try to see me for who I am. Now.

58
00:02:05,890 --> 00:02:08,530
我看着你呢  梦娜  你吓到我了
I do see you, Mona. You're freaking me out.

59
00:02:09,520 --> 00:02:10,600
汉娜
Hanna!

60
00:02:11,010 --> 00:02:12,020
那是谁
Who's that?

61
00:02:12,220 --> 00:02:13,540
怎么了  外婆  
Yeah, grandma? 

62
00:02:13,540 --> 00:02:15,640
你房间有别人吗  我听见有说话声
Are you alone in there? I heard voices.

63
00:02:15,770 --> 00:02:17,510
没有没有  只有我
Uh, no, no. It's just me.

64
00:02:17,510 --> 00:02:21,250
我在大声读书  接着睡吧
I'm... reading out loud. Go back to sleep.

65
00:02:23,170 --> 00:02:24,240
谢谢
Thank you.

66
00:03:35,330 --> 00:03:37,680
{\an8}正式通知  梦娜回来了  -汉娜

67
00:03:41,540 --> 00:03:44,890
他来安装新警报器  抱歉  宝贝
He's here to install the new alarm. Sorry, babe.

68
00:03:44,940 --> 00:03:46,860
我原以为等你去学校之后
I didn't think they'd get to the second floor

69
00:03:46,860 --> 00:03:48,630
他们才会安到二楼
until after you left for school.

70
00:03:48,840 --> 00:03:50,780
你要在我窗前装警报
You're putting an alarm on my window?

71
00:03:50,780 --> 00:03:54,620
每个窗都装了  你母亲想要最好的警报系统
On every window. Your mom wants the best system around.

72
00:03:54,620 --> 00:03:58,010
我手机上有个软件可以远程开关
There's an app where I can turn it on remote from my phone.

73
00:03:58,080 --> 00:03:59,990
那我要怎么知道它开着
So how will I know when it's on?

74
00:04:00,320 --> 00:04:02,140
考虑到镇上这两年发生的事
Well, considering what's been happening in this town

75
00:04:02,140 --> 00:04:04,610
我想还是时刻开着吧
for the past two years, think 24/7.

76
00:04:04,840 --> 00:04:05,950
你吃过了吗
Did you eat?

77
00:04:05,990 --> 00:04:07,870
一会儿吃点
Yeah, I'll grab something.

78
00:04:09,350 --> 00:04:11,040
希拉里·雷诺兹打电话来
Hilary Reynolds called.

79
00:04:11,140 --> 00:04:13,010
她气得连话都说不出来了
She's so angry, she can barely speak.

80
00:04:13,010 --> 00:04:17,360
等等  加勒特的母亲  她想干嘛
Wait, Garrett's mother? Why? What did she want?

81
00:04:18,920 --> 00:04:20,710
{\an8}《玫瑰镇观察家报》  雷诺兹谋杀案  警方无斩获

82
00:04:19,250 --> 00:04:20,770
她希望儿子复生
She wants her son back.

83
00:04:20,810 --> 00:04:22,200
但这不可能
But she can't have that.

84
00:04:22,220 --> 00:04:24,650
所以她要质问玫瑰镇警方
So she's going after the Rosewood police.

85
00:04:24,650 --> 00:04:25,700
我跟她说我明晚
I told her I would be there

86
00:04:25,700 --> 00:04:27,210
也会出席社区大会
tomorrow night at the community meeting.

87
00:04:27,210 --> 00:04:28,980
-你为什么要参加  -为什么不参加
- Why would you go to that? - Why wouldn't I?

88
00:04:28,980 --> 00:04:32,010
她说的没错  他们放一个无辜的人出狱
She's right. They let an innocent man out of jail,

89
00:04:32,120 --> 00:04:33,940
却没有采取任何保护措施
and provided no protection for him.

90
00:04:34,230 --> 00:04:37,180
我认为"无辜"这词和加勒特沾不上边
I don't think of the word "innocent" when I think of Garrett.

91
00:04:37,290 --> 00:04:38,930
显然  不只你一个人这么认为
Evidently, you're not alone.

92
00:04:38,970 --> 00:04:40,600
看来有人想亲自出马
Looks like somebody else thought it was their right

93
00:04:40,600 --> 00:04:42,290
执掌正义呢
to take justice into their own hands.

94
00:04:42,290 --> 00:04:45,340
爸爸  艾莉森的案子还没破呢
Dad, Alison's murder has never been solved.

95
00:04:45,340 --> 00:04:47,290
你还认为是加勒特干的
You still think Garrett did it?

96
00:04:48,250 --> 00:04:49,030
是不是
Do you?

97
00:04:49,030 --> 00:04:51,550
我要迟到了  我的运动鞋在楼下吗
I'm gonna be late. Are my sneakers downstairs?

98
00:04:51,550 --> 00:04:53,650
我觉得你还是别去参加长跑了
I'm not so sure you'll go on that run.

99
00:04:53,650 --> 00:04:55,180
我和你妈妈都不大放心
Your mom and I just aren't comfortable

100
00:04:55,180 --> 00:04:56,550
你天黑了还呆在外头
with you being out after dark.

101
00:04:56,550 --> 00:05:00,450
-我筹到了274美元  -我知道
- Dad, I raised $274 in pledges. - I know.

102
00:05:00,630 --> 00:05:02,490
你可以让佩奇过来
You're welcome to have Paige over,

103
00:05:02,490 --> 00:05:04,630
但不准出门
but you are not going out.

104
00:05:07,910 --> 00:05:09,650
又来一套新世界秩序了
So this is the new world order?

105
00:05:09,650 --> 00:05:12,060
我们每天都得和梦娜打照面了
We're gonna have to face off with Mona in school every day?

106
00:05:12,060 --> 00:05:14,870
她跟汉娜说她已经好多了  哪方面好多了
She told Hanna that she's better now. Better at what?

107
00:05:14,870 --> 00:05:17,240
我跟你说  她要是半夜三更溜进我家
I'll tell you what. She sneaks in my house past midnight,

108
00:05:17,240 --> 00:05:18,900
我枕头下的铁撬就候着她
I'm sleeping with a crowbar under my pillow.

109
00:05:18,900 --> 00:05:21,410
问题是  我们要无视她吗
The only question is, do we ignore her?

110
00:05:21,410 --> 00:05:22,800
给你个提示  是的
Here's a hint. Yes.

111
00:05:23,790 --> 00:05:27,200
梦娜对玛雅的事了解很透彻
Mona had serious insight into what happened to Maya.

112
00:05:27,200 --> 00:05:29,790
或许她能告诉我们加勒特的死因呢
What if she could tell us why Garrett was killed?

113
00:05:30,370 --> 00:05:32,880
这么说你觉得梦娜还藏着更多秘密
So now you think Mona's the keeper of more secrets?

114
00:05:32,880 --> 00:05:34,920
显然她对我们的秘密了如指掌
She certainly knows all of ours.

115
00:05:35,200 --> 00:05:38,090
如果她和N.A.T.社团有什么联系呢
What if she has some kind of connection to the N.A.T. Club?

116
00:05:38,090 --> 00:05:41,640
斯宾塞  社团解散时她还没丑女大翻身呢
Spencer, that club ended while she was still Loser Mona.

117
00:05:41,640 --> 00:05:43,460
四眼田鸡还带着牙套
Pre-lasik and metal mouth.

118
00:05:43,620 --> 00:05:45,510
如果那些变态没想过偷窥她
If those pervs didn't even wanna peep in her window,

119
00:05:45,510 --> 00:05:47,330
他们怎么会和她一起玩呢
why would they wanna hang out with her?

120
00:05:48,030 --> 00:05:49,730
也许是她偷窥他们
Maybe she was peeping at them.

121
00:05:50,220 --> 00:05:52,560
N.A.T.社团的两个成员已经死了
Look, two members of the N.A.T. Club are dead.

122
00:05:52,560 --> 00:05:55,000
或许杀害艾莉的凶手还在紧张
Okay, maybe the person who killed Ali is still freaked out

123
00:05:55,000 --> 00:05:57,670
流传在外的那卷录像带
that there's a tape floating around somewhere out there.

124
00:05:58,670 --> 00:05:59,720
你有没有...
Did you...

125
00:06:00,250 --> 00:06:01,960
你有没有问过你爸爸
Did you ever ask your dad?

126
00:06:03,320 --> 00:06:04,400
问他什么
Ask him what?

127
00:06:05,030 --> 00:06:06,560
加勒特说的话
About what Garrett said.

128
00:06:06,600 --> 00:06:08,760
他那晚和艾莉见面的事
You know, about him meeting up with Ali that night.

129
00:06:08,760 --> 00:06:11,030
我和我爸好不容易才和好
My dad and I are finally getting along.

130
00:06:11,770 --> 00:06:13,870
加勒特胡编乱造出故事只是想脱身
I'm not gonna slap him with some whacked-out story

131
00:06:13,870 --> 00:06:15,770
我是不会因为这个和自己父亲反目的
Garret made up so he could clear his own name.

132
00:06:15,780 --> 00:06:17,660
-我知道  但是  -但是什么
- I hear you, but-- - But what?

133
00:06:18,260 --> 00:06:19,390
斯宾塞  加勒特这个人谎话连篇
Spence, Garrett lied about a lot.

134
00:06:19,400 --> 00:06:22,060
为什么要突然相信他说的话呢
Why are we suddenly gonna believe anything he ever said?

135
00:06:27,620 --> 00:06:28,210
这是什么
What's that?

136
00:06:28,210 --> 00:06:31,110
有人为你烤了些松饼  放在门口了
Someone baked you some muffins and left 'em at the door.

137
00:06:33,010 --> 00:06:34,040
M是谁
Who's "M"?

138
00:06:35,790 --> 00:06:38,060
-梦娜  -梦娜
- Mona. - Mona?

139
00:06:38,600 --> 00:06:40,240
你不想吃就别吃了
You don't have to eat these.

140
00:06:40,240 --> 00:06:42,340
我做了墨西哥式煎蛋
I've got huevos rancheros,

141
00:06:42,340 --> 00:06:45,170
猪肉香肠  还有土豆饼
pork sausage, and hash browns.

142
00:06:45,170 --> 00:06:47,420
-别说了  -不舒服吗
- Please stop. - Are you sick?

143
00:06:47,420 --> 00:06:48,620
有点
I could be.

144
00:06:49,170 --> 00:06:51,770
这个梦娜是不是就是...
Is this Mona the same Mona...

145
00:06:51,770 --> 00:06:55,240
是  她想重新做人
Yeah. She wants a fresh start.

146
00:06:55,250 --> 00:06:57,030
那你准备原谅她了吗
Are you ready to give it to her?

147
00:06:57,490 --> 00:06:59,180
没那么简单  外婆
It's complicated, grandma.

148
00:06:59,760 --> 00:07:01,080
我明白  亲爱的
I hear you, honey.

149
00:07:01,420 --> 00:07:02,740
海什表亲出来的时候
When cousin Heshy came back,

150
00:07:02,740 --> 00:07:05,460
大家都像躲瘟神一样躲着他
no one wanted to touch him with a ten-foot pole.

151
00:07:05,700 --> 00:07:07,120
海什表亲是谁
Who's cousin Heshy?

152
00:07:07,130 --> 00:07:08,780
阿尔伯达家的老幺
Alberta's youngest.

153
00:07:08,780 --> 00:07:10,260
他从小就不合群
He was always a little off,

154
00:07:10,270 --> 00:07:13,640
但上高中的时候  真的出大问题了
but in high school, he jumped the tracks.

155
00:07:14,120 --> 00:07:15,200
他干什么了
What'd he do?

156
00:07:15,390 --> 00:07:18,750
一天吃早餐时  他给自己的父母
One morning at breakfast, he served his mom and dad

157
00:07:18,760 --> 00:07:23,060
端上了两碗放着生锈铁钉的牛奶
two bowls of rusty nails with milk poured over 'em.

158
00:07:23,430 --> 00:07:25,230
他父母说不吃的时候
And when they refused to eat,

159
00:07:25,290 --> 00:07:27,310
他拿起一把铁钉
he snatched up a fistful,

160
00:07:27,310 --> 00:07:30,760
攥在手里  直到攥出血来
and just squeezed until blood came out.

161
00:07:31,610 --> 00:07:34,190
抱歉  为什么要谈论这个人
I'm sorry. How are we related to this person?

162
00:07:34,190 --> 00:07:35,760
不  我的重点是
Oh, no, my point is,

163
00:07:35,760 --> 00:07:38,580
他们把他送到医院待了四个月
they sent him away for about four months.

164
00:07:38,800 --> 00:07:40,550
出院后就完全好了
He's been fine ever since.

165
00:07:43,200 --> 00:07:45,980
你真的认为人是可以改变的吗
So you really think people can change?

166
00:07:46,150 --> 00:07:47,340
海什就变了
Heshy did.

167
00:07:48,100 --> 00:07:50,890
我的意思是  过去的事就让它过去
I mean, the thing is, what's done is done.

168
00:07:51,120 --> 00:07:53,960
-事过之后...  -我累了
- And when the rink gets icy... - Yeah, I'm exhausted.

169
00:07:53,960 --> 00:07:55,870
没办法了  不舒服就不舒服吧
I can't deal. I'm taking a sick day.

170
00:07:55,870 --> 00:07:57,800
汉娜  去学校吧
Hanna, you go to school.

171
00:07:57,850 --> 00:08:00,280
你应该给她一个
Maybe you need to let this girl

172
00:08:00,280 --> 00:08:02,230
和你重新做朋友的机会
have a chance to win you back.

173
00:08:02,490 --> 00:08:03,410
知道吗
You know,

174
00:08:03,830 --> 00:08:07,030
如果我是她  我一定会竭尽全力
if I were her, I'd fight to the death

175
00:08:07,340 --> 00:08:09,490
争取和你做朋友的
to have you as my friend.

176
00:08:18,030 --> 00:08:19,950
我基本上就是被软禁了
I'm basically under house arrest.

177
00:08:18,100 --> 00:08:22,990
{\an8}玫瑰镇高中
长跑俱乐部筹款会

178
00:08:19,950 --> 00:08:22,460
我妈想让我爸从我这里问出来
My mom's now using my dad to squeeze information outta me

179
00:08:22,460 --> 00:08:24,040
万圣节那天在灯塔岩客栈发生的事
about Halloween, the Lighthouse.

180
00:08:24,050 --> 00:08:25,820
-你告诉他什么了  -什么都没说
- What have you told him? - Nothing.

181
00:08:25,930 --> 00:08:27,230
如果让他知道我们经历的事
If he knew half the crap we'd been through,

182
00:08:27,230 --> 00:08:28,710
他一定会把我弄到关岛去的
he'd ship me off to Guam.

183
00:08:30,920 --> 00:08:32,540
还以为你在给梦娜当保镖呢
Thought you were playing Mona's bodyguard.

184
00:08:32,540 --> 00:08:34,880
我只是跟她说有事可以找我
Okay, I said I'd be around for her.

185
00:08:35,190 --> 00:08:37,520
我觉得我们都应该和她做朋友
I'm thinking maybe we all should be her friend.

186
00:08:38,220 --> 00:08:39,700
如果梦娜知道为什么加勒特
I mean, if Mona knows why Garrett died,

187
00:08:39,700 --> 00:08:41,810
在泄露艾瑞亚父亲的事后被杀
right after he told that story about Aria's dad--

188
00:08:41,810 --> 00:08:42,830
别说了
Stop.

189
00:08:45,380 --> 00:08:46,370
-怎么回事  -没事
- What's going on? - Nothing.

190
00:08:46,370 --> 00:08:48,400
-我们还是不要说了  -别啊  说吧
- We're not gonna talk about that. - No, go ahead.

191
00:08:48,410 --> 00:08:49,870
随便说  等我不在再说
Talk about it. Just do it when I'm not here.

192
00:08:49,870 --> 00:08:51,440
-艾瑞亚  -下一步干嘛
- Aria-- - What's next?

193
00:08:51,440 --> 00:08:52,430
是不是要调查一下
Are we all gonna start wondering

194
00:08:52,430 --> 00:08:54,860
-当时我爸爸是否也在万圣节火车上  -什么
- if my dad was on the Halloween train, too? - What?

195
00:08:54,860 --> 00:08:57,790
你真相信我的亲生父亲会给我下药
You actually believe that my own dad would drug me,

196
00:08:57,790 --> 00:08:59,360
然后把我关在箱子里吗
and then lock me in a box.

197
00:09:14,230 --> 00:09:15,500
你好  艾瑞亚
Hello, Aria.

198
00:09:16,860 --> 00:09:17,770
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?

199
00:09:17,770 --> 00:09:19,110
这不是你该来的地方
Yeah, you shouldn't be here.

200
00:09:27,400 --> 00:09:30,250
梦娜加强版开始了
Welcome to Mona 2.0.

201
00:09:34,930 --> 00:09:38,090
-艾瑞亚  对不起  我不是想...  -没事
- Aria, I'm sorry. I wasn't trying-- - Don't worry about it.

202
00:09:38,090 --> 00:09:40,110
-没人相信你爸爸会...  -我知道
- None of us really believe your dad-- - I know.

203
00:09:40,540 --> 00:09:41,900
是我太激动了
I overreacted.

204
00:09:43,020 --> 00:09:44,590
重点是  加勒特确实说了
The thing is, Garrett did say it,

205
00:09:44,590 --> 00:09:45,890
所以先是不能面对自己的男朋友
and it's really freakin' hard

206
00:09:45,890 --> 00:09:48,520
现在又不能面对自己父亲  真的很困难
when you can't look at your boyfriend, and now your own dad,

207
00:09:48,740 --> 00:09:50,800
-我真的...  -怎么样
- without... - Without what?

208
00:09:50,910 --> 00:09:52,360
等等  以斯拉怎么了
Wait, what's with Ezra?

209
00:09:52,660 --> 00:09:55,930
-我还没跟他说他的...  -儿子
- I still haven't told him about... - His son.

210
00:09:56,310 --> 00:09:59,170
对  每次我跟他在一起的时候
Yeah. You know that I plan on telling him

211
00:09:59,220 --> 00:09:59,930
我都打算告诉他
every time we're together,

212
00:09:59,930 --> 00:10:01,850
但是我退缩了
but I just bail.

213
00:10:05,360 --> 00:10:06,570
格里祖蒂老师去哪里了
Where's Mrs. Grizzuti?

214
00:10:06,570 --> 00:10:08,510
应该是休产假了
Uh, I'm guessing she had her baby.

215
00:10:08,510 --> 00:10:10,410
梅雷迪斯是代课老师吗
And now Meredith's her replacement?

216
00:10:11,470 --> 00:10:13,320
一定是做噩梦了  快弄醒我
Please stick a fork in my neck.

217
00:10:20,100 --> 00:10:21,900
为了防止某个机构
The check and balance system was established

218
00:10:21,900 --> 00:10:24,900
拥有绝对权力  独断专行
so that no branch could wield absolute power

219
00:10:24,900 --> 00:10:26,570
确立了分权制衡体系
over another branch.

220
00:10:27,760 --> 00:10:31,250
对开国元勋来说  这点为什么这么重要呢
Why do we think this was so important to our Founding Fathers?

221
00:10:32,590 --> 00:10:33,670
阿瑞亚
Aria.

222
00:10:34,230 --> 00:10:35,200
怎么了
What?

223
00:10:35,500 --> 00:10:38,950
同学们  我不知道格里祖蒂老师上课时的纪律
Look, guys, I don't know what Mrs. Grazzuti's take was,

224
00:10:38,950 --> 00:10:42,280
但是在我的课上不准玩手机
but while I'm here, no phones in class.

225
00:10:42,280 --> 00:10:44,270
我没有...没有玩手机
I wasn't... I wasn't on my phone.

226
00:10:44,570 --> 00:10:45,730
你玩了
Yeah, you were.

227
00:10:46,760 --> 00:10:49,380
拿出来  给我
Tell you what. Give it to me.

228
00:10:52,390 --> 00:10:54,610
这样你就不会上课分神了
This way, you won't even be tempted.

229
00:10:57,480 --> 00:10:59,640
这对我们的开国元勋非常重要
It was important to our founding fathers

230
00:10:59,640 --> 00:11:03,560
因为他们要保证没有人拥有绝对权力
because they wanted to be sure that no one had absolute power.

231
00:11:07,850 --> 00:11:08,940
艾瑞亚
Aria.

232
00:11:09,820 --> 00:11:11,560
我能跟你说几句话吗
Can you stay for a few minutes, please?

233
00:11:17,630 --> 00:11:19,420
既然你们形影不离
I guess since you travel in a pack,

234
00:11:19,420 --> 00:11:20,710
就都留下吧
you can all stay.

235
00:11:22,750 --> 00:11:24,920
趁着事态还没变得不可收拾
Just so we don't get off on the wrong foot,

236
00:11:25,030 --> 00:11:26,250
我们讲清楚
let's be clear.

237
00:11:26,470 --> 00:11:28,060
教书是我的工作
I have a job to do,

238
00:11:28,450 --> 00:11:31,500
如果几位女士还想毕业
and if you ladies want to graduate,

239
00:11:32,100 --> 00:11:33,180
你们也得做好自己的工作
so do you.

240
00:11:34,430 --> 00:11:36,140
我看到你们互相发短信了
Look, I saw what you were texting.

241
00:11:36,140 --> 00:11:38,760
课堂上只能讨论美国历史
You're in this class to discuss American history,

242
00:11:38,760 --> 00:11:40,800
不包括我的私事  明白了吗
not mine. Got it?

243
00:11:42,380 --> 00:11:43,400
明白
Yeah.

244
00:11:44,790 --> 00:11:48,010
谢谢  过得愉快
Thank you. Have a nice day.

245
00:11:54,240 --> 00:11:57,460
梦娜  等等  我不能丢下艾瑞亚
Mona, wait. Mona, I couldn't leave Aria.

246
00:11:57,460 --> 00:12:00,700
没关系  我懂  她一定很不好受
No, that's okay. I get it. It must be really tough for her.

247
00:12:04,960 --> 00:12:07,000
梦娜  那是什么  脑子吗
Mona, what is it? Is that a brain?

248
00:12:07,640 --> 00:12:09,040
把柜门关上
Close your door.

249
00:12:09,770 --> 00:12:11,590
快关上
Close your locker.

250
00:12:09,960 --> 00:12:11,830
{\an8} 你与疯牛无异

251
00:12:12,240 --> 00:12:14,440
关上  我们离开这儿  你要干嘛
Come on, let's get out of here. What are you doing?

252
00:13:13,130 --> 00:13:16,260
卢卡斯  她跟你说什么了  谁干的
Lucas, what did she say to you? Who did that?

253
00:13:26,900 --> 00:13:30,660
等等  那是有人从生物实验室偷来的吗
Wait, wait. Someone stole that from the bio lab?

254
00:13:30,710 --> 00:13:32,360
实验室里有牛脑
They have cow brains up there?

255
00:13:32,470 --> 00:13:34,220
-我都不知道  -那是因为在解剖课上
- I didn't even think-- - That's because you got excused

256
00:13:34,220 --> 00:13:36,610
你以素食主义为由请假了
from dissection based on vegetarian grounds.

257
00:13:36,610 --> 00:13:38,690
姐妹们  大家会认为是我们干的
Guys, people are gonna think that we put that in her locker.

258
00:13:38,690 --> 00:13:40,600
这不是素食主义  是人道主义
It wasn't vegetarian, it was humanitarian.

259
00:13:40,600 --> 00:13:42,280
-你还记恨我吗  -很有可能
- Are you still hating on me? - Possibly.

260
00:13:42,280 --> 00:13:45,030
姐妹们  听好了  大家会怀疑我们的
Guys, pay attention. People are gonna think that was us.

261
00:13:45,030 --> 00:13:46,770
怎么能  时间对不上
How? When? 

262
00:13:46,770 --> 00:13:48,850
我们下课后被梅雷迪斯胁持着呢
We were all being held hostage by Meredith.

263
00:13:48,850 --> 00:13:50,570
第一节课前那东西又没在她柜子里
It wasn't in her locker before first period.

264
00:13:50,570 --> 00:13:53,330
现在我们指望梅雷迪斯作不在场证明了吗
So now we're depending on Meredith to be our alibi?

265
00:13:53,760 --> 00:13:54,780
监狱里见
See you in jail.

266
00:13:54,780 --> 00:13:56,470
不得不说  梦娜可比我强多了
I gotta say, Mona's a lot stronger than me.

267
00:13:56,470 --> 00:13:58,090
我可能会崩溃的
I would've lost it.

268
00:13:59,280 --> 00:14:02,280
-我替她感到难过  -是的  我也是
- I feel sorry for her. - Yeah, me, too.

269
00:14:03,510 --> 00:14:05,320
好了  我们可以别再感到难过了吗
Okay, are we done feeling sorry?

270
00:14:05,320 --> 00:14:07,780
她可是对我们做了很多坏事  姐妹们
Because she's done a lot worse to us, guys.

271
00:14:07,780 --> 00:14:08,960
很多
A lot.

272
00:14:20,740 --> 00:14:23,000
梦娜  你不会以为我们
Mona, you don't think we had anything 

273
00:14:23,000 --> 00:14:25,460
和这事有关系吧
to do with that, do you?

274
00:14:25,540 --> 00:14:26,440
当然不会  
Of course not. 

275
00:14:26,440 --> 00:14:28,980
你怎么会在我帮了你以后又抛下我呢
Why would you dump on me after I helped you?

276
00:14:29,960 --> 00:14:31,100
帮我
Helped me?

277
00:14:32,330 --> 00:14:34,690
查出是哪个变态杀了你女朋友
Figure out who the creep was that killed your girlfriend.

278
00:14:37,540 --> 00:14:39,980
我知道我们之间还是有间隙
But I know that there's still bad blood between us,

279
00:14:40,740 --> 00:14:42,760
我知道我得赢得你们的信任
and I know that I have to earn your trust,

280
00:14:42,760 --> 00:14:44,560
证明我值得你们信任
and prove that I'm worthy.

281
00:14:45,230 --> 00:14:47,440
我会的  拭目以待吧
But I will. You'll see.

282
00:14:50,420 --> 00:14:51,570
我变好了
I'm better now.

283
00:15:08,790 --> 00:15:10,210
你确定要这么做吗  
Sure you wanna do this?

284
00:15:10,410 --> 00:15:11,770
面对现实吧  凯勒  
Face it, Caleb. 

285
00:15:11,770 --> 00:15:13,010
我们什么时候不惹人注目了
We were never under the radar.

286
00:15:13,010 --> 00:15:14,230
你听说梦娜的事了吗
Did you hear about Mona?

287
00:15:14,230 --> 00:15:16,970
听说了  可惜没赶上
Yeah, I did. Sorry I missed that.

288
00:15:17,910 --> 00:15:19,600
有点不对劲
Something weird is going on.

289
00:15:19,950 --> 00:15:22,170
你觉得有没有可能是梦娜自己做的
Do you think it's possible that Mona did that to herself?

290
00:15:22,560 --> 00:15:25,050
有可能  但是梦娜和卢卡斯之间
It's possible, but something's definitely going on

291
00:15:25,060 --> 00:15:26,380
绝对有问题
between Mona and Lucas.

292
00:15:26,380 --> 00:15:29,300
-他腿为什么瘸了  -可能是被她踢的
- Why is he limping? - Maybe she kicked him.

293
00:15:29,610 --> 00:15:31,070
你得和他谈一谈
You've gotta talk to him.

294
00:15:31,070 --> 00:15:33,410
问清楚他是不是在万圣节弄伤的腿
Find out if he hurt that leg on Halloween.

295
00:15:33,480 --> 00:15:34,710
我不明白了
I'm lost.

296
00:15:37,170 --> 00:15:38,440
艾瑞亚被困在箱子里的时候
When Aria was in that box,

297
00:15:38,440 --> 00:15:41,110
她刺伤了那个想要把她扔出火车的人
she stabbed someone who was trying to throw her off the train.

298
00:15:41,110 --> 00:15:42,570
那是几周之前了
That was weeks ago.

299
00:15:42,570 --> 00:15:45,480
但她用的是很脏的旧螺丝刀
And it was also a dirty old screwdriver.

300
00:15:45,480 --> 00:15:46,730
也许没这么快愈合
Maybe it didn't heal.

301
00:15:49,270 --> 00:15:51,030
求你了
Just... please.

302
00:15:51,030 --> 00:15:52,620
跟他谈谈  好吗
Talk to him, okay?

303
00:15:54,120 --> 00:15:55,120
好的
Okay.

304
00:16:00,390 --> 00:16:03,230
我没接到她电话  我手机关机了
I couldn't pick up her call because my phone was turned off.

305
00:16:03,510 --> 00:16:05,340
爸爸  我要上课呢
Dad, I have classes.

306
00:16:05,340 --> 00:16:06,660
我总不能每隔十分钟
I can't step out every ten minutes

307
00:16:06,660 --> 00:16:08,880
就给妈妈报备告诉她我还活着吧
just to report to mom that I'm still alive.

308
00:16:10,420 --> 00:16:11,710
不  放学不能直接回家
No, not straight from school.

309
00:16:11,710 --> 00:16:12,870
我有工作
I have work.

310
00:16:13,340 --> 00:16:15,750
我连兼职都不能做了么
I'm supposed to give up my job now, too?

311
00:16:18,860 --> 00:16:22,180
什么  好  我下班后直接回家
What? Yes, yes. I'll come home right after work.

312
00:16:22,700 --> 00:16:23,690
拜拜
Bye.

313
00:16:30,650 --> 00:16:32,580
欢迎来到迷失森林度假村
Welcome to the lost woods resort.

314
00:16:37,500 --> 00:16:38,980
给她点教训是很不错的
It would've been nice to have had more warning,

315
00:16:38,980 --> 00:16:42,220
但我们知道她不能在疗养院待一辈子
but we knew she couldn't stay in that place forever.

316
00:16:42,740 --> 00:16:44,400
你放学后还想跑步吗
Do you still wanna run after school?

317
00:16:44,760 --> 00:16:45,870
好啊  跑
Yeah, sure.

318
00:16:46,520 --> 00:16:47,790
我想你了 
I missed you.

319
00:16:48,770 --> 00:16:50,250
昨晚你怎么没有联系我
How come I didn't hear from you last night?

320
00:16:50,250 --> 00:16:52,770
我很早就困了  没收到你的短信
I fell asleep early. Didn't get your message.

321
00:16:53,640 --> 00:16:55,190
能问你点事吗
Can I ask you something?

322
00:16:56,600 --> 00:16:58,330
你保证听了不会生气
Promise that you won't get upset.

323
00:16:59,240 --> 00:17:00,290
问吧
Ask.

324
00:17:01,530 --> 00:17:03,350
你觉得詹娜转学是因为
Do you think that Jenna transferred schools

325
00:17:03,350 --> 00:17:06,190
加勒特死后  她怕自己成为下一个
because after Garrett, she was afraid that she might be next?

326
00:17:06,190 --> 00:17:09,430
杰森是N.A.T社团仅剩的唯一成员
Jason is the last member of the N.A.T. Club left.

327
00:17:09,430 --> 00:17:10,710
我知道她没有正式加入...
I know that she wasn't an official member...

328
00:17:10,720 --> 00:17:12,870
你怎么总纠结于这件事呢
Why do you obsess about this stuff?

329
00:17:12,880 --> 00:17:14,790
我怎能不纠结
How can I not obsess about it?

330
00:17:14,790 --> 00:17:16,230
警察还没有抓到杀死加勒特的凶手
The cops still don't know who killed Garrett.

331
00:17:16,230 --> 00:17:18,500
连杀死他的那把枪都没找到
They can't even find the gun he was shot with.

332
00:17:22,390 --> 00:17:23,580
难以置信
Unbelievable.

333
00:17:25,700 --> 00:17:26,780
看她现在抱着谁呢
Look who she's cozying up to now.

334
00:17:26,780 --> 00:17:28,970
-斯宾塞  别管了  -不  我做不到
- Spencer, leave it alone. - No, I can't.

335
00:17:28,980 --> 00:17:31,310
他抱着的根本就是一枚手榴弹
He's basically hugging a hand grenade.

336
00:17:37,310 --> 00:17:38,630
清理梦娜柜子的是他
He was cleaning up Mona's locker.

337
00:17:38,630 --> 00:17:40,480
但他对我视而不见
He looked right through me.

338
00:17:41,830 --> 00:17:44,540
-或许不是他  -肯定是他
- Maybe it wasn't him. - It was him.

339
00:17:45,410 --> 00:17:48,430
也许变态哈罗德还有个怪胎同胞兄弟
Maybe creepy Harold has a creepy twin.

340
00:18:07,500 --> 00:18:09,110
他为什么会有梦娜的东西
Why does he have Mona's stuff?

341
00:18:10,730 --> 00:18:12,600
或许他准备物归原主
Maybe he's returning it.

342
00:18:33,820 --> 00:18:34,580
你带过这个
You've worn this?

343
00:18:34,580 --> 00:18:36,780
每次跑马拉松我都带
Yeah, in every marathon I've ever run.

344
00:18:37,570 --> 00:18:38,910
来  带上它
Here. Wear it.

345
00:18:39,180 --> 00:18:40,530
会给你带来好运的
It'll bring you luck.

346
00:18:41,330 --> 00:18:43,890
不  我不能要这个
No. I can't take that.

347
00:18:44,040 --> 00:18:46,190
-要是弄丢了怎么办  -那我也弄丢你
- What if I lose it? - I'll have to lose you.

348
00:18:47,240 --> 00:18:48,430
开玩笑的
That was a joke.

349
00:18:49,450 --> 00:18:51,790
-怎么了  -没事
- What's goin' on? - Nothing.

350
00:18:51,960 --> 00:18:53,490
没事  我只是...
Nothing. I'm just...

351
00:18:54,580 --> 00:18:56,440
我在犹豫自己是否真想这么做
guess I'm just deciding if I really want to do this thing.

352
00:18:56,440 --> 00:18:58,250
不  你必须去做
No, no, no. You have to do this.

353
00:18:58,250 --> 00:19:00,940
理由很充分  朋友们都指望你呢
It's for a good cause, friends are counting on you,

354
00:19:00,940 --> 00:19:04,950
而且我还牺牲了半年的失业的时间
and I pledged half of last year's unemployment.

355
00:19:05,770 --> 00:19:07,000
你会没事的
You'll be fine.

356
00:19:07,170 --> 00:19:10,310
只要  换双鞋就行
Just... change your shoes.

357
00:19:16,390 --> 00:19:17,360
怎么了
What's wrong?

358
00:19:18,090 --> 00:19:19,730
没事  可能是我妈
Nothing. It just might be my Mom.

359
00:19:20,410 --> 00:19:21,270
她今天称病请假了
She called in sick today,

360
00:19:21,280 --> 00:19:23,980
但我猜是因为梅雷迪斯今天第一天上班吧
But I'm guessing it's 'cause it was Meredith's first day.

361
00:19:24,330 --> 00:19:27,900
{\an8} 变态哈罗德在学校  他有包梦娜的东西  咖啡店见

362
00:19:27,460 --> 00:19:30,030
-是你妈妈吗  -是的
- Is it your mom? - Yeah.

363
00:19:30,030 --> 00:19:31,700
我得...过去一下
Yeah, I'm gonna have to... swing by her place

364
00:19:31,710 --> 00:19:34,210
安慰安慰她
and do a little hand holding.

365
00:19:34,220 --> 00:19:35,570
她的很不好
She's pretty bugged out.

366
00:19:35,590 --> 00:19:38,020
我可不像她那么幸运  能拥有你
She's lucky to have you, since I can't.

367
00:19:40,300 --> 00:19:41,230
给我打电话
Call me?

368
00:19:43,480 --> 00:19:44,640
我会的
I will.

369
00:19:54,670 --> 00:19:56,800
{\an8} 是个男孩

370
00:20:02,540 --> 00:20:07,380
像婴儿那样  谎言也会成长  会开口说话  你呢

371
00:20:17,490 --> 00:20:21,070
没到十分钟  赢了
Oh, under ten! Beat it.

372
00:20:21,870 --> 00:20:23,690
我想我们赢了个热水澡
I think we earned some hot tub.

373
00:20:24,200 --> 00:20:27,020
斯宾塞  要我先去放热水么
Spence, you want me to fire it up?

374
00:20:28,860 --> 00:20:30,730
好  等我一会儿
Yeah. Just give me a second.

375
00:20:34,430 --> 00:20:36,170
杰森
Hey, Jason.

376
00:20:37,860 --> 00:20:39,100
你好  斯宾塞
Hey there, Spencer.

377
00:20:40,270 --> 00:20:41,910
你和梦娜是怎么回事
What's going on with you and Mona?

378
00:20:42,510 --> 00:20:44,520
是你去找她的  还是她主动找上你的
Did you go to her or did she come up to you?

379
00:20:46,310 --> 00:20:49,460
我知道她第一天回来会让人不大舒服
Look, I know that her first day back wasn't exactly a bubble bath.

380
00:20:49,460 --> 00:20:52,490
不过  你应该当心点
Okay, but... you should be careful.

381
00:20:53,680 --> 00:20:55,010
我漏了什么重点
What am I missing here?

382
00:20:55,670 --> 00:20:57,440
杰森  她很危险
Jason, she's dangerous.

383
00:20:57,800 --> 00:20:59,240
伊恩和加勒特都死了
Ian and Garrett are both dead.

384
00:20:59,240 --> 00:21:00,950
詹娜被吓跑了
Jenna's awol.

385
00:21:00,980 --> 00:21:02,630
我觉得梦娜可能...
I'm starting to think that Mona might have--

386
00:21:02,640 --> 00:21:04,970
明白了  我会注意的
Got it. I'll keep that in mind.

387
00:21:04,980 --> 00:21:07,750
不用回避托比  他知道她是什么人
Toby can hear this. He knows her resume.

388
00:21:07,750 --> 00:21:10,380
她曾经试图通过拧松脚手架来杀死他
She once tried to kill him by unscrewing a piece of scaffolding.

389
00:21:10,980 --> 00:21:12,850
你不能相信她
She cannot be trusted.

390
00:21:12,850 --> 00:21:15,500
这里的人也曾经这么评价过我
People around here used to say the same thing about me.

391
00:21:16,190 --> 00:21:17,790
我觉得在没有证据证明有罪前
I like to give people the benefit of the doubt

392
00:21:17,790 --> 00:21:19,240
应该相信他们是无辜的
before I cut them off.

393
00:21:20,440 --> 00:21:23,170
再见  谢谢提醒
Good-bye. Thanks for the tip.

394
00:21:32,170 --> 00:21:33,860
你真的没有告诉她吗
You sure you didn't tell her?

395
00:21:34,110 --> 00:21:36,380
我怎么可能告诉梦娜  以斯拉有个孩子
Why would I tell Mona that Ezra has a kid?

396
00:21:36,550 --> 00:21:37,600
我不知道  但我告诉你
I don't know. But I'm telling you

397
00:21:37,600 --> 00:21:38,750
如果当时是以斯拉开的门
if Ezra would've opened that door--

398
00:21:38,840 --> 00:21:40,850
不是他开的  好吗  放松
He didn't, all right, so just breathe.

399
00:21:41,040 --> 00:21:42,160
你怎么处理那个礼品篮
What'd you do with the basket?

400
00:21:42,160 --> 00:21:45,050
扔了  怎么了  你想吃里面的软心糖吗
I trashed it. Why? Do you want the jelly beans?

401
00:21:45,050 --> 00:21:47,540
艾瑞亚是对的  汉娜  梦娜一定在搞鬼
Aria's right, Hanna. Mona's up to something.

402
00:21:47,540 --> 00:21:49,350
她第一天回来就发生的这些事不是巧合
It's not a coincidence the first day she's back,

403
00:21:49,350 --> 00:21:51,870
哈罗德也在  还装作不认识我们
Harold's also there, and somehow doesn't recognize us.

404
00:21:51,870 --> 00:21:53,370
我没说这些不奇怪
I'm not saying it wasn't weird.

405
00:21:53,380 --> 00:21:55,530
我就是觉得  他接受工作
I just think maybe he took the job

406
00:21:55,530 --> 00:21:56,760
就是因为想要见到她
because he wanted to see her.

407
00:21:56,760 --> 00:21:58,970
-他为什么想见她  -她在那里待了很久
- Why would he want to see her? - She spent a lot of time there.

408
00:21:58,970 --> 00:22:01,460
-或许他们是朋友呢  -朋友关系该结束了
- maybe they were buddies. - The buddy-moon's over.

409
00:22:01,470 --> 00:22:03,210
我们得冲进变态的密室
We need to bust into creepy's closet

410
00:22:03,210 --> 00:22:04,670
看看他还为她留下了什么
and see what else he saved for her.

411
00:22:07,020 --> 00:22:09,750
-你和卢卡斯聊过吗  -他不怎么谈得开
- Did you talk to Lucas? - He's not feeling very chatty.

412
00:22:09,750 --> 00:22:12,720
-不过我找到些别的东西  -是什么
- But I did find something else. - What is that?

413
00:22:12,720 --> 00:22:14,390
是一份校长和梦娜以及她家长
It's a transcript from the meeting the principal had

414
00:22:14,400 --> 00:22:16,530
上星期会面时  会议记录的副本
with Mona and her parents last week. 

415
00:22:16,820 --> 00:22:18,110
你是怎么搞到的
How did you get this?

416
00:22:18,110 --> 00:22:20,020
知道学校密码还是能有些特权的
There's perks to knowing the school's pass code.

417
00:22:20,020 --> 00:22:22,770
-我们要看什么  -第二页
- What are we looking for? - Page two.

418
00:22:23,240 --> 00:22:24,680
梦娜的父母并不希望
Turns out Mona's parents did not 

419
00:22:24,690 --> 00:22:26,310
她回到玫瑰镇高中
want her to come back to rosewood high.

420
00:22:26,310 --> 00:22:27,940
是梦娜要求回到这里的
It was Mona who begged to come back in.

421
00:22:27,950 --> 00:22:31,030
等等  她不是告诉你是她父母逼她的
Wait. I thought she told you her parents were forcing her.

422
00:22:31,040 --> 00:22:32,690
我想她在撒谎
I'm guessing she lied.

423
00:22:32,970 --> 00:22:35,360
梦娜回来是为了完成之前未完成之事
Mona's back to take care of unfinished business.

424
00:22:35,360 --> 00:22:36,370
我得走了
I gotta go.

425
00:22:36,410 --> 00:22:38,270
拿些吃的  我饿死了
Hey, feed me. I'm starving.

426
00:22:38,960 --> 00:22:42,040
梦娜有没有在松饼篮上签上"M"或"A"
Did Mona sign that card on the muffin basket with "M" Or "A"?

427
00:22:42,040 --> 00:22:44,280
-先别这样  我们...  -我们怎样
- Could we just take a second before we-- - before we what?

428
00:22:44,340 --> 00:22:46,300
让她把我们的生活再毁一次吗  不行
Let her destroy our lives again? no.

429
00:22:46,300 --> 00:22:48,150
如果以斯拉从"A"那里得知自己有个孩子
If Ezra finds out that he has a kid through "A"--

430
00:22:48,150 --> 00:22:50,220
不要让"A"掌握主动权  艾瑞亚
Don't give "A" All the power, Aria.

431
00:22:50,220 --> 00:22:51,640
告诉费兹  他有个儿子
Tell Fitz he has a son.

432
00:22:51,640 --> 00:22:52,750
-我不能  -为什么
- I can't. - Why not?

433
00:22:52,750 --> 00:22:54,960
因为那孩子有母亲  她不准我说
Because that son has a mother, and she asked me not to.

434
00:22:54,960 --> 00:22:56,640
是啊  那每过一天
Yeah, and every day that goes by is another day

435
00:22:56,640 --> 00:22:58,590
孩子与父亲团聚的日子就少一天
that kid goes without meeting his dad,

436
00:23:00,340 --> 00:23:01,220
相信我
And believe me,

437
00:23:02,120 --> 00:23:04,540
那孩子要很久才能适应
that kid might be dealing with it for a long time.

438
00:23:31,830 --> 00:23:33,330
你在想什么
What are you thinking about?

439
00:23:34,990 --> 00:23:36,070
没什么
I'm not.

440
00:23:39,540 --> 00:23:41,410
那你在郁闷什么
What are you stewing about?

441
00:23:43,640 --> 00:23:45,420
为什么杰森就是不明白呢
Why doesn't Jason get it?

442
00:23:45,710 --> 00:23:47,700
他明知梦娜是个危险人物
He knows that Mona's dangerous.

443
00:23:47,710 --> 00:23:49,940
杰森是成年人了  他会照顾好自己的
Jason's a big boy. He can take care of himself.

444
00:23:49,940 --> 00:23:51,890
没错  但是没有人支持他
Yeah, but nobody's got his back.

445
00:23:52,260 --> 00:23:56,380
我有我的朋友  还有你  而他却孤身一人
I've got my friends, I've got you. He's completely alone.

446
00:24:01,710 --> 00:24:04,680
什么声音  你听见了吗
What was that? Did you hear that?

447
00:24:06,260 --> 00:24:07,200
喂
Hello?

448
00:24:09,690 --> 00:24:11,190
有人在那儿吗
Hey, is someone out there?

449
00:24:20,930 --> 00:24:22,150
放松
Relax.

450
00:24:27,520 --> 00:24:29,340
我想进屋
I wanna go inside.

451
00:24:29,900 --> 00:24:31,720
不好意思  我现在没心情
I'm sorry. I can't do this right now.

452
00:24:41,880 --> 00:24:42,850
请进
Come in.

453
00:24:44,140 --> 00:24:45,140
在家呢
Hi there.

454
00:24:45,340 --> 00:24:48,150
家里太安静了  我还以为没人在家呢
I wasn't even sure anyone was home, it's so quiet.

455
00:24:48,370 --> 00:24:50,350
迈克去怀亚特家学习了
Mike went to Wyatt's to study.

456
00:24:51,910 --> 00:24:55,220
那么...今天在学校怎么样
So... how was school today?

457
00:25:00,230 --> 00:25:02,580
-你和梅雷迪斯谈过了吗  -谈过了
- Did you talk to Meredith? - I did.

458
00:25:02,900 --> 00:25:05,120
我都忘了你也报了那门课
I'd completely forgotten that you were in that class.

459
00:25:05,120 --> 00:25:06,920
我不能不去上  通过了才能毕业
I can't drop it. I need it to graduate. 

460
00:25:06,920 --> 00:25:08,380
为什么不去上呢
Why should you? 

461
00:25:08,400 --> 00:25:11,920
你已经像成年人一样来处理这种情况了
Sounds like you handled that situation like an adult.

462
00:25:12,530 --> 00:25:13,940
谢谢你
Thank you for that.

463
00:25:14,490 --> 00:25:16,520
梅雷迪斯跟你说什么了
What did Meredith tell you?

464
00:25:16,520 --> 00:25:19,000
她说你和你的朋友们
Well, she said that you and your friends

465
00:25:19,000 --> 00:25:21,960
对她都小心翼翼的
were cautiously welcoming.

466
00:25:22,540 --> 00:25:25,450
任何新老师所期望的也就是这些了
That's the most that any new teacher can expect.

467
00:25:26,520 --> 00:25:28,380
天晓得  我也是过来人
God knows, I have been there.

468
00:25:29,140 --> 00:25:31,300
你们这些小鬼最会耍滑头了
Kids can be very cruel.

469
00:25:33,300 --> 00:25:34,270
爸
Hey, dad.

470
00:25:36,890 --> 00:25:38,450
你喜欢艾莉森吗
Did you like Alison?

471
00:25:39,620 --> 00:25:40,570
什么
What?

472
00:25:41,580 --> 00:25:44,090
你觉得她这个人怎么样
Like, what did you think of her as a person?

473
00:25:45,440 --> 00:25:47,200
你的朋友我都喜欢
I like all of your friends.

474
00:25:47,290 --> 00:25:49,970
为什么这么问
Why do you ask that?

475
00:25:50,690 --> 00:25:53,640
我才知道妈妈和她有矛盾
I just know that mom had some issues with her.

476
00:25:53,710 --> 00:25:55,610
她觉得艾莉是罪有应得
She thought Ali was entitled.

477
00:25:56,860 --> 00:25:59,330
我觉得有这些看法都是因为
I think most of that just comes from

478
00:25:59,330 --> 00:26:01,710
艾莉是个处于青春期的孩子
being at an awkward age.

479
00:26:05,440 --> 00:26:10,140
你没有和她真正独处过  对吗
You never spent any real time alone with her, though, did you?

480
00:26:11,840 --> 00:26:13,460
我为什么要和她独处
Why would I have?

481
00:26:18,350 --> 00:26:20,100
你还是很想她啊
You still really miss her, huh?

482
00:26:23,090 --> 00:26:24,060
嗯
Yeah.

483
00:26:47,580 --> 00:26:49,700
从我小时候一直到初中
Ever since i was little and all through junior high

484
00:26:51,330 --> 00:26:54,610
我一直被认为是个失败者
I was considered, a loser.

485
00:26:54,620 --> 00:26:58,690
我被羞辱  被欺负  被折磨
I was humiliated, picked on, and tortured.

486
00:26:59,330 --> 00:27:02,290
那些痛苦与折磨是那样的...
And as hard as all that misery and torture was...

487
00:27:07,490 --> 00:27:09,480
这是她发给你的吗
She sent this to you?

488
00:27:09,790 --> 00:27:11,960
没错  她还在网上发给了所有人
Yeah, and everyone else in cyber space.

489
00:27:11,960 --> 00:27:13,420
有1600多人点了"赞"
It has 1,600 likes.

490
00:27:13,420 --> 00:27:15,910
这孩子比我的脚趾头还扭曲
That child is more twisted than my toes.

491
00:27:15,910 --> 00:27:17,700
她做的太过火了
She's trying way too hard.

492
00:27:17,700 --> 00:27:19,640
是你告诉我再给她一次机会的
You were the one who told me to give her a second chance.

493
00:27:19,640 --> 00:27:22,470
那是在我看见她的"竞选宣言"之前
That was before I saw her campaign.

494
00:27:22,530 --> 00:27:25,390
现在我觉得梦娜是我们反对克隆人
Right now, I think Mona may be the best argument we got

495
00:27:25,390 --> 00:27:27,430
最好的证据
against human cloning.

496
00:27:30,350 --> 00:27:31,990
在关掉它之前
Before you turn this off,

497
00:27:31,990 --> 00:27:33,280
或者往屏幕上丢臭鸡蛋之前
or throw something at the screen,

498
00:27:33,280 --> 00:27:35,660
请听我说完
please just hear me out.

499
00:27:35,850 --> 00:27:38,660
我已经在拉德里被关了七个月
I've been in Radley for over seven months now.

500
00:27:38,660 --> 00:27:40,800
我想告诉你们我经历的...
And I wanna tell you about what I...

501
00:27:44,630 --> 00:27:45,420
卢卡斯
Lucas?

502
00:27:45,420 --> 00:27:47,700
我知道你正准备出门
Hi. I know you're on your way out. 

503
00:27:47,700 --> 00:27:48,970
没有  进来吧
No, no. Come in.

504
00:27:48,970 --> 00:27:49,980
我不想打扰你
I don't wanna keep you. 

505
00:27:49,980 --> 00:27:51,680
我认真的  进来吧
Seriously, just come in.

506
00:27:58,150 --> 00:27:59,430
你能把这个交给凯勒吗
Could you get this to Caleb?

507
00:27:59,430 --> 00:28:01,670
我试着找过他  但我想他已经搬走了
I tried to find him, but I guess he's not living in the same spot.

508
00:28:01,670 --> 00:28:04,480
-这是什么  -这是我欠他的最后一笔钱
- What is this? - It's the last of the money I owe him.

509
00:28:04,480 --> 00:28:06,210
我花了很久才筹到钱
Took me a while to get it.

510
00:28:06,210 --> 00:28:08,170
你想喝点什么吗
Do you want something to drink or anything?

511
00:28:08,170 --> 00:28:09,790
不用了
No, I'm good.

512
00:28:10,270 --> 00:28:11,340
你的腿怎么了
What happened to your leg?

513
00:28:11,340 --> 00:28:14,560
我玩滑板的时候出了点意外
Oh, I had an accident skateboarding.

514
00:28:14,680 --> 00:28:16,270
解释起来比较复杂
It's kind of hard to explain.

515
00:28:19,110 --> 00:28:20,890
你和梦娜之间发生什么了
What happened between you and Mona?

516
00:28:21,580 --> 00:28:24,960
什么都没有  我和她几个月没联系了
Nothing. Nothing. I haven't spoken to her in months.

517
00:28:24,960 --> 00:28:27,260
梦娜是不是有你的什么把柄  卢卡斯
Does Mona have something on you, Lucas?

518
00:28:27,260 --> 00:28:29,720
你是不是做了什么真的很让你后悔的事情
Did you do something that you really regret?

519
00:28:30,610 --> 00:28:33,030
是不是有人在万圣节把你的腿刺伤了
Did someone stab you in that leg on Halloween?

520
00:28:33,030 --> 00:28:35,930
-我们下次再说这个吧  -不  告诉我
- We'll talk about this another time. - No, I need answers.

521
00:28:36,190 --> 00:28:39,250
她为什么突然回学校了  她为什么要回来
Why is she suddenly back at school? Why is she coming back?

522
00:28:39,990 --> 00:28:42,480
汉娜  昨天不是她回来的第一天
Hanna, yesterday wasn't her first day back.

523
00:28:42,710 --> 00:28:43,720
她早在得到医生许可之前
She was sneaking out of there

524
00:28:43,720 --> 00:28:45,640
就偷偷溜出来过了
way before she had the doctor's permission.

525
00:28:45,640 --> 00:28:48,290
为什么  她去哪里了  她做了什么
Why? Where was she going? What was she doing?

526
00:28:48,290 --> 00:28:52,490
不好意思  我只能告诉你这些了
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That's the best that I can do.

527
00:28:53,880 --> 00:28:55,510
好的  我知道了
Okay. I get it.

528
00:28:57,660 --> 00:28:58,680
我很想你
I miss you.

529
00:29:01,220 --> 00:29:02,630
我也很想你
I miss you, too.

530
00:29:15,820 --> 00:29:18,470
我知道你最终必须坦白
I know that you ultimately have to own up,

531
00:29:19,710 --> 00:29:21,550
坦白你的所作所为
own up to what you've done,

532
00:29:22,430 --> 00:29:24,320
坦白你身上发生了什么事情
and what's been done to you,

533
00:29:24,330 --> 00:29:27,380
然后你需要学会原谅你自己
and then you have to learn to forgive yourself.

534
00:29:27,380 --> 00:29:29,220
世上无难事  只怕有心人
She shoots, she scores.

535
00:29:29,430 --> 00:29:31,750
真是难以置信
Un-freakin'-believable.

536
00:29:32,210 --> 00:29:33,040
等到星期二  
By Tuesday, 

537
00:29:33,040 --> 00:29:35,060
机场和医生办公室都会播这个视频了
that'll be playing in airports and doctor's offices.

538
00:29:35,160 --> 00:29:39,340
{\an8} 急救亭

539
00:29:36,670 --> 00:29:38,410
我们要再搬点水
We need more bottles.

540
00:29:46,990 --> 00:29:48,320
真难以置信
I don't believe it.

541
00:29:52,060 --> 00:29:53,670
她来这儿做什么
What is she doing here?

542
00:29:57,940 --> 00:29:59,040
斯宾塞
Spence.

543
00:29:59,660 --> 00:30:02,250
斯宾塞  最近好吗
Hey, spencer, how are you?

544
00:30:02,250 --> 00:30:03,790
挺好  你呢
I'm good. How are you?

545
00:30:08,810 --> 00:30:10,410
她还真有一套
She's such a piece of work.

546
00:30:10,430 --> 00:30:13,330
这叫拉拢人心
Yep. That's called greeting your converts.

547
00:30:17,110 --> 00:30:18,510
能问你件事吗
Can I ask you something?

548
00:30:23,650 --> 00:30:24,820
你有没有...
Have you ever...

549
00:30:25,970 --> 00:30:27,260
想过如果六七岁时
thought about what your life would be like

550
00:30:27,260 --> 00:30:29,150
你爸爸陪在你身边
if your dad had been around

551
00:30:29,150 --> 00:30:31,670
你的人生会是什么样子
when you were, like, six or seven?

552
00:30:33,770 --> 00:30:35,690
蠢问题  当我没问
Dumb question. I shouldn't have asked that.

553
00:30:35,690 --> 00:30:38,360
不  不蠢
No. No, it wasn't dumb.

554
00:30:40,880 --> 00:30:44,580
小时候  我满世界找他
Yeah. When I was young, I... I looked for him everywhere.

555
00:30:45,600 --> 00:30:48,560
大街上  商店里
In the streets, in stores.

556
00:30:49,200 --> 00:30:50,800
甚至梦中
I even looked for him in my sleep.

557
00:30:53,000 --> 00:30:56,580
但在我13岁的时候  我突然放手了
But when I was about 13, I just stopped.

558
00:30:57,040 --> 00:30:58,040
为什么
Why?

559
00:30:59,280 --> 00:31:01,040
我猜我只是厌倦了
I guess I was just tired of...

560
00:31:01,820 --> 00:31:03,160
精疲力竭的感觉
using all that energy, ya know.

561
00:31:03,160 --> 00:31:06,180
我应该更关注我自己
I just needed to focus on me.

562
00:31:08,180 --> 00:31:10,400
而后来事情的发展我也全盘接受了
And I'm totally fine with the way things turned out.

563
00:31:11,590 --> 00:31:13,460
真的  不过
Really. But... 

564
00:31:14,940 --> 00:31:17,030
如果我说我从未渴望过
I'd be lying if I said there weren't days

565
00:31:17,030 --> 00:31:20,510
我幻想中的那个人是活生生存在的
that I wish I could replace the guy I made up in my head

566
00:31:21,260 --> 00:31:22,290
那我一定是在撒谎
with a real person.

567
00:31:31,200 --> 00:31:34,890
你们会在地图上看到有四个检查点
If you look at your maps, you'll see four checkpoint stations.

568
00:31:34,890 --> 00:31:37,110
长跑终点是校门口
the run will end in front of the school,

569
00:31:37,110 --> 00:31:38,300
在那里你们将领到纪念奖章
where you'll pick up your medal

570
00:31:38,300 --> 00:31:40,640
附带一个交换袋
and a complimentary swag bag.

571
00:31:40,640 --> 00:31:42,410
我们将在三分钟后开始
We will begin in three minutes.

572
00:31:42,410 --> 00:31:44,780
恕我冒昧  谁负责唱国歌
Excuse me. Who's singing the national anthem?

573
00:31:44,780 --> 00:31:47,160
-我们没这项计划  -我来吧
- Oh, we really didn't plan on-- - I'll do that.

574
00:31:48,860 --> 00:31:52,220
*哦  你可看见*
*Oh, say can you see*

575
00:31:52,220 --> 00:31:55,210
听着  我们可以在第二个检查点前
Look, you guys. If we ditch the track right before checkpoint two,

576
00:31:55,210 --> 00:31:56,970
从学校后面的树林抄近路过去
we can cut through the woods behind school.

577
00:31:56,970 --> 00:31:58,300
我们怎么进去呢
How are we getting in?

578
00:31:58,340 --> 00:32:00,880
没有锁  那里的浴室要开放给
It's not locked. They're keeping the bathrooms open for people

579
00:32:00,880 --> 00:32:02,300
负责终点线的人
that are working the finish line.

580
00:32:02,300 --> 00:32:04,090
你确定艾米丽来不了吗
Are you sure that Emily can't meet us?

581
00:32:04,090 --> 00:32:06,910
对啊  除非她逃出自己家
Yeah, unless she can escape fort Fields.

582
00:32:07,920 --> 00:32:09,860
为什么你外婆在上面唱歌
Why is your grandmother singing?

583
00:32:09,860 --> 00:32:11,430
她愿意呗
Because she can.

584
00:32:11,430 --> 00:32:14,680
*招展*
*Wave*

585
00:32:14,690 --> 00:32:18,460
*在这自由乐土*
*O'er the land of the free*

586
00:32:18,460 --> 00:32:20,820
我觉得梦娜那晚在万圣节列车上
I think Mona was on the Halloween train that night.

587
00:32:21,600 --> 00:32:22,710
再说一遍
Say that again.

588
00:32:23,070 --> 00:32:25,460
*勇士的*
*home of the*

589
00:32:25,530 --> 00:32:29,930
*故乡*
*brave*

590
00:32:29,930 --> 00:32:34,360
*依稀可见*
*On the shore, dimly seen... *

591
00:32:39,660 --> 00:32:41,390
不会太久的
I don't think this'll last too long.

592
00:32:41,390 --> 00:32:42,760
你自己在这可以吗
You okay here by yourself?

593
00:32:42,760 --> 00:32:45,480
当然  有什么软件能让我撬开窗户吗
Yeah. Is there an app to let me crack open a window?

594
00:32:45,480 --> 00:32:48,650
没必要  我下楼调调恒温器就好了
Don't need to. I'll adjust the thermostat downstairs.

595
00:33:12,870 --> 00:33:14,940
行了  我几小时后回来
Okay, I'll be back in a couple of hours.

596
00:33:26,980 --> 00:33:27,820
警报器已解除

597
00:33:47,120 --> 00:33:48,240
艾米丽
Emily?

598
00:33:49,020 --> 00:33:50,930
艾米丽  你怎么过来的
Em, how did you get here?

599
00:33:50,930 --> 00:33:52,310
说来话长  但拜托你们
Long story. Just do me a favor.

600
00:33:52,310 --> 00:33:54,400
明天前不要给我打电话或者发短信
Don't call or text me until tomorrow.

601
00:33:54,580 --> 00:33:55,630
打不开
This isn't working.

602
00:33:55,630 --> 00:33:57,060
因为这是曲别针
That's because it's a paper clip.

603
00:33:57,060 --> 00:33:58,760
你要用发夹
You have to use a bobby pin.

604
00:33:58,780 --> 00:34:00,310
我教的你都忘了吗
Have I taught you nothing?

605
00:34:11,390 --> 00:34:13,680
当时那个包就在那儿  不是吗
The bag was right here, wasn't it?

606
00:34:20,370 --> 00:34:22,110
他当时就是在写这个
That's the book he was writing in.

607
00:34:24,320 --> 00:34:25,480
上面说什么
What does it say?

608
00:34:25,480 --> 00:34:27,740
貌似他在给梦娜写一封长信
Looks like he was writing a long letter to Mona,

609
00:34:27,740 --> 00:34:29,060
因为他以为这是她的日记本
'cause he thinks that this is her diary. 

610
00:34:29,360 --> 00:34:31,390
是吗  汽车旅馆里的那本是这个吗
Is it? Was this in the motel room?

611
00:34:31,390 --> 00:34:34,120
没错  但这不是梦娜的
Yeah, it was, but, you guys, this isn't mona's.

612
00:34:34,620 --> 00:34:35,900
是艾莉森的
This is Ali's.

613
00:34:55,470 --> 00:34:57,720
这跟你在梦娜的老巢看到的是一样的吗
Is this the same one you saw in Mona's lair?

614
00:34:59,420 --> 00:35:01,550
-完全确定  -我看看
- I'm positive. - Let me see this.

615
00:35:03,110 --> 00:35:04,860
艾瑞亚  这写的是你爸爸吗
Aria, is this about your dad?

616
00:35:07,870 --> 00:35:09,810
你现在是系主任了啊
So you're department chair now.

617
00:35:10,670 --> 00:35:13,280
你是个很强大的男人  蒙哥马利先生
You're a powerful man, Mr. Montgomery.

618
00:35:15,710 --> 00:35:18,150
我不会再跟你讨论这件事了
We're not having this conversation again.

619
00:35:18,490 --> 00:35:21,610
好啊  不说更好
Fine. I'd rather not talk.

620
00:35:22,290 --> 00:35:23,700
那你得花
That's gonna cost you

621
00:35:24,960 --> 00:35:27,600
-上次那么多钱  -是吗
- same amount works for me. - Oh, does it?

622
00:35:27,600 --> 00:35:29,090
看来你运气不太好
Well, you're out of luck.

623
00:35:29,090 --> 00:35:30,970
那个人已经退出我的生活了
That person's not in my life anymore.

624
00:35:30,970 --> 00:35:32,920
几个月前就了断了
It ended months ago.

625
00:35:34,550 --> 00:35:37,930
难道蒙哥马利太太会因此觉得宽慰吗
Will that make it any easier for Mrs. Montgomery?

626
00:35:37,940 --> 00:35:40,370
我是说  做了就是做了
I mean, it did happen.

627
00:35:40,370 --> 00:35:42,190
你该走了  艾莉森
It's time for you to go, Alison.

628
00:35:42,190 --> 00:35:44,080
如果有学生打电话给院长
If a student called the dean

629
00:35:44,080 --> 00:35:46,010
说梅丽狄斯发神经是因为
and told him that Meredith was flipping out

630
00:35:46,010 --> 00:35:47,480
她的一个教授
because one of her professors

631
00:35:47,480 --> 00:35:50,100
在她身上揩够了油  并且
wiped his feet on her after he--

632
00:35:50,100 --> 00:35:52,400
你敢打电话  就等着后悔吧
You make that call, you'll be very sorry.

633
00:35:52,400 --> 00:35:55,810
没错  那我就先打给你老婆吧
You're right. I'll just start with your wife.

634
00:36:00,400 --> 00:36:02,020
拨号中  蒙哥马利家

635
00:36:08,880 --> 00:36:10,700
没准儿我一个人的时候会再打电话
Maybe I'll call when I'm alone.

636
00:36:10,700 --> 00:36:13,130
我不能再给你那么多钱了
I cannot give you that kind of money again.

637
00:36:13,210 --> 00:36:15,000
埃拉会发现的
Ella will know it's missing.

638
00:36:15,190 --> 00:36:17,430
给你时间好好考虑吧
You can take some time to figure it out.

639
00:36:18,250 --> 00:36:20,570
我要离开一段时间去看望奶奶
I'm leaving town to visit my nana.

640
00:36:20,600 --> 00:36:22,570
劳动节周末回来
I'll be back Labor Day weekend.

641
00:36:22,570 --> 00:36:24,180
够你考虑了吗
Does that work for you?

642
00:36:24,680 --> 00:36:27,340
很好  到时候见
Excellent. I'll see you then.

643
00:36:31,730 --> 00:36:33,880
一周愉快  蒙哥马利先生
Have a nice week, Mr. Montgomery.

644
00:36:46,270 --> 00:36:47,660
-艾瑞亚  -别
- Aria. - Don't.

645
00:36:50,870 --> 00:36:51,840
艾米丽  藏你夹克里
Emily, put this in your jacket.

646
00:36:51,840 --> 00:36:53,150
也许我们应该把它留在这里
Maybe we should leave it here.

647
00:36:53,160 --> 00:36:54,200
如果他发现不见了
If he knows that it's missing,

648
00:36:54,200 --> 00:36:55,020
会怀疑我们的
he'll think it was one of us.

649
00:36:55,020 --> 00:36:56,380
我们  他都不知道你是谁
Us? He doesn't even know who you are.

650
00:36:56,380 --> 00:36:57,830
-快拿着吧  -给我
- Just take it. - Give it to me.

651
00:37:04,710 --> 00:37:06,250
你们到下面来做什么
What are you doing down here?

652
00:37:09,690 --> 00:37:11,030
楼上的洗手间都满了
Um, all of the bathrooms upstairs were full,

653
00:37:11,030 --> 00:37:11,880
所以我们下来...
so we came down here,

654
00:37:11,880 --> 00:37:14,100
我们可以去用二楼的
but we can use the ones on the second floor.

655
00:37:14,340 --> 00:37:16,280
抱歉  咱们走吧
We're sorry. You guys, come on.

656
00:37:20,030 --> 00:37:22,260
-你手上拿的是什么  -给我
- What have you got there? - Give it to me!

657
00:37:22,710 --> 00:37:23,820
斯宾塞
Spencer?

658
00:37:26,160 --> 00:37:28,580
怎么了  你们还好吧
What's going on? Are you guys okay? 

659
00:37:28,580 --> 00:37:29,370
我们没事
Yeah, we're fine.

660
00:37:29,370 --> 00:37:31,420
就是想拿回我不小心弄丢的东西
We just had to get something I accidentally threw away.

661
00:37:37,880 --> 00:37:39,270
{\an8}玫瑰镇高中
长跑俱乐部筹款会

662
00:37:39,650 --> 00:37:41,080
还好你下来了
Thank god you came down there.

663
00:37:41,080 --> 00:37:42,330
你怎么知道我们在那
How did you know we were there?

664
00:37:42,330 --> 00:37:43,900
我提前到了终点线
I got to the finish line early,

665
00:37:43,910 --> 00:37:46,470
然后看到你们中的三个从后门溜进去了
and then, I saw the three of you go in that back door.

666
00:37:46,470 --> 00:37:49,430
这无所谓  还好你下来了
It doesn't even matter. We're just so lucky you were here.

667
00:37:54,160 --> 00:37:54,780
我的上帝
Oh, my god!

668
00:37:54,780 --> 00:37:55,640
梦娜
Mona!

669
00:37:56,420 --> 00:37:57,830
后退
Get back! 

670
00:37:58,550 --> 00:37:59,520
梦娜
Mona!

671
00:38:09,030 --> 00:38:11,460
没  我没收到别人的短信
No, I didn't get any messages,

672
00:38:12,150 --> 00:38:13,500
只有我女儿发来的
only my daughter's.

673
00:38:13,500 --> 00:38:16,200
我们不小心拿错了对方的手机
We accidentally switched phones.

674
00:38:16,200 --> 00:38:17,350
是的
That's right.

675
00:38:17,600 --> 00:38:19,900
感谢您提供的信息  晚安  先生
Thanks for the update, sir. Good night.

676
00:38:22,060 --> 00:38:23,480
是你们学校的校长
That was your principal.

677
00:38:24,580 --> 00:38:26,330
受伤的是那个新老师
It was that new teacher, Miss Sorenson,

678
00:38:26,330 --> 00:38:27,920
索伦森小姐
who got hurt by that stunt.

679
00:38:27,920 --> 00:38:28,880
梅雷迪斯吗
Meredith?

680
00:38:29,120 --> 00:38:30,960
你对老师都是直呼其名吗
You call her by her first name?

681
00:38:30,960 --> 00:38:32,590
不是  我只是  她是...
No, I just... she's...

682
00:38:34,190 --> 00:38:35,300
算了
Never mind.

683
00:38:38,340 --> 00:38:42,120
好了  我们不要再争论
All right. Maybe we should stop fighting

684
00:38:42,120 --> 00:38:43,300
为何我不让你出门
about why I won't let you out,

685
00:38:43,300 --> 00:38:45,580
我们该谈谈为何你什么都不跟我说了
and start talking about why you're not letting me in.

686
00:38:48,010 --> 00:38:49,750
我离开得有那么久吗
Have I been gone that long?

687
00:38:55,080 --> 00:38:57,260
艾米  我知道我无法
Emmy, I know that I don't fully understand

688
00:38:57,260 --> 00:38:59,130
完全理解你所经历的一切
everything that you've been going through.

689
00:39:01,080 --> 00:39:03,420
但我知道痛失身边人的感受
But I know what it's like to lose people.

690
00:39:06,070 --> 00:39:08,100
唯一能让我熬过去的
And the only thing that gets me through that

691
00:39:08,390 --> 00:39:11,140
就是"我快回家了"的信念
is knowing that I'm coming home to my family.

692
00:39:19,170 --> 00:39:21,100
我不想做你的看门人  艾米
I don't wanna be your gate keeper, Emmy.

693
00:39:21,730 --> 00:39:23,120
我想做你的父亲
I wanna be your dad.

694
00:39:37,400 --> 00:39:40,830
从我小时候开始  整个初中...
Ever since I was little, and all through junior high...

695
00:39:40,830 --> 00:39:43,400
我都被当做失败者...
I was considered a loser...

696
00:39:43,680 --> 00:39:44,730
宝贝
Baby.

697
00:39:45,180 --> 00:39:46,480
我觉得她的视频
I think you've seen 

698
00:39:46,490 --> 00:39:48,370
你今天看得已经足够多了  不是吗
enough of her for one day, don't you?

699
00:40:05,960 --> 00:40:07,210
梅雷迪斯怎么样了
How's Meredith?

700
00:40:08,130 --> 00:40:09,820
我刚把她从急诊室送回了家
I just took her home from the E.R.

701
00:40:09,830 --> 00:40:11,460
医生处理了她的烧伤
Doctors dressed her burn,

702
00:40:11,460 --> 00:40:13,570
给她开了止痛药  让她情绪稳定下来
gave her some painkillers, kept her calm.

703
00:40:13,650 --> 00:40:15,190
我觉得不该让她一个人在家
I didn't think she should be home alone,

704
00:40:15,190 --> 00:40:17,100
所以我邀请她到这里过夜
so I invited her to stay over.

705
00:40:17,630 --> 00:40:19,300
-她来了吗  -没有
- She's here? - No.

706
00:40:19,300 --> 00:40:22,310
没有  她不想过来
No, she didn't see that as a very tempting offer,

707
00:40:22,310 --> 00:40:24,630
因为今晚早些时候发生的事
based on what happened earlier tonight.

708
00:40:26,900 --> 00:40:27,870
什么东西
What is it?

709
00:40:31,330 --> 00:40:33,200
{\an8}你能为提前离开的人拿两个礼包吗  谢了

710
00:40:32,950 --> 00:40:34,720
在梅雷迪斯的剪贴板上发现的 
It was put on Meredith's clipboard,

711
00:40:34,720 --> 00:40:37,270
所以她才去仓库的
sending her over to the storage shed.

712
00:40:38,540 --> 00:40:41,350
-是你的朋友写的吗  -我的朋友
- Did one of your friends write that? - My friends?

713
00:40:41,420 --> 00:40:43,240
我知道她们擅长哪一套
I know what they're capable of.

714
00:40:44,620 --> 00:40:46,040
你在说什么
What are you saying?

715
00:40:48,070 --> 00:40:49,670
梅雷迪斯以为是我们写给她的吗
Does Meredith think that we sent this to her?

716
00:40:49,670 --> 00:40:51,930
是啊  肯定是
Yeah, she sure does.

717
00:40:51,940 --> 00:40:52,760
她还告诉了我
Now that she's told me 

718
00:40:52,760 --> 00:40:54,660
第一天发生了什么事
the truth about what happened on that first day,

719
00:40:54,660 --> 00:40:56,150
我不认为她是在胡乱猜测
I don't think it's such a crazy thought.

720
00:40:56,150 --> 00:40:57,130
爸爸  我们绝不会...
Dad, we would never...

721
00:40:57,130 --> 00:41:00,060
是不是你和你的朋友干的
Did you and your friends do this to her?

722
00:41:00,060 --> 00:41:01,170
是或不是
Yes or no?

723
00:41:01,180 --> 00:41:03,880
不是  不是
No. No.

724
00:41:03,880 --> 00:41:06,320
说出来  艾瑞亚  趁你还有机会
Speak up now, Aria, while you can.

725
00:41:07,330 --> 00:41:09,150
那些秘密回来折磨我们了
These kind of secrets come back to haunt us.

726
00:41:09,160 --> 00:41:10,410
你的秘密呢
What about yours?

727
00:41:12,020 --> 00:41:13,130
这话什么意思
What does that mean?

728
00:41:15,900 --> 00:41:18,490
没什么  没什么
Nothing. Nothing.

729
00:41:19,440 --> 00:41:21,190
能帮我把门关上吗
Will you close my door, please?

730
00:41:42,630 --> 00:41:43,410
嘿
Hey.

731
00:41:47,480 --> 00:41:49,910
听说我错过了终点线上的焰火
Heard I missed some fireworks at the finish line.

732
00:41:50,500 --> 00:41:51,330
是的
Yeah.

733
00:41:53,410 --> 00:41:55,720
可梦娜却安然无恙
But Mona walked away without a scratch.

734
00:42:00,110 --> 00:42:01,570
我不会再说第二遍了
Look, I won't say this again. 

735
00:42:01,570 --> 00:42:04,830
不用了  这次我听到了
You don't have to. I hear you this time.

736
00:42:12,480 --> 00:42:13,290
晚安
Good night.

737
00:42:20,660 --> 00:42:22,350
艾瑞亚  什么事
Hey, Aria, what's up?

738
00:42:24,610 --> 00:42:26,320
-A给我们下了套  -什么
- "A" set us up. - What?

739
00:42:26,320 --> 00:42:27,680
是她让梅雷迪斯去仓库的
That's why Meredith opened that shed.

740
00:42:27,680 --> 00:42:29,660
A把她弄到那里  伪装成是我们干的
"A" sent her over there, and made it look like we did.

741
00:42:29,660 --> 00:42:31,070
A正好叫做梦娜吗
Does "A" go by the name of Mona?

742
00:42:31,070 --> 00:42:33,680
这是她证明自己的方式吗
Is this her way of proving to us that she's worthy?

743
00:42:34,850 --> 00:42:36,260
-我得挂了  -等下  艾瑞亚
- Hey, I gotta go. - Wait, Aria.

744
00:42:36,260 --> 00:42:39,210
是你爸爸吗  你想来我家过夜吗
Is it your dad? Do you wanna come over and stay at my place?

745
00:42:39,210 --> 00:42:41,090
他绝不会允许的
He's never gonna let that happen.

746
00:42:50,850 --> 00:42:52,900
我觉得这个绷带可以盖住它
I think this bandage will cover it.

