[♪]
Spider, are you okay?
Check this.
What the hell?
We've got to go find it.
Dammit!
Okay, I'll go find it.
You get that video out there.
[Viewing counts beep]
[Beeping rapidly]
[♪]
Primeval New World 01x09
Breakthrough
Original Air Date January 22, 2013
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com
I'm not sure it's good
for company morale
for people to see you
staring into space.
Not to mention your morale.
I'm doing okay.
And the company?
Well, I think I can
stave off bankruptcy
if I devote myself full-time
for the next three months
to updated product
and aggressive sales calls.
Well, your enthusiasm
is inspiring.
Thanks.
Truth is, I'm not
much of a cheerleader.
That was always Ange.
Doing this without her
just feels weird.
Have you talked to her at all?
She's not coming back,
if that's your question.
Do you have a plan
to replace her?
You know what I mean.
The job.
Yeah, I'm getting resumes.
But anyone smart enough
to do that job
will be smart enough
to find out that
that old chem bunker
has been converted
into the headquarters
of my dinosaur-hunting team.
Well, that just makes us
sound glamorous.
Have you called Mac?
No.
I'm giving it some time.
How much?
I don't know.
I mean, what am I
supposed to do?
Give him a call?
Leave him a voice mail
explaining that the real reason
we're friends
is that because
in some alternate reality,
he went back in time
and saved my life?
I think his frozen body
in the basement
is actually
the harder part to explain.
Do you know anything
about cost reports?
Not a damn thing.
[Knocks] Hey, guys?
We got a problem.
A dinosaur problem?
A triceratops?
In West Van?
Looks like the cost reports
will have to wait.
Wait, how do you know
what kind of dinosaur?
[Toby]: Did you notice
the hit count?
When I first came upstairs,
it was under 9,000.
Now it's over 35,000.
That's a lot of eyeballs.
No chance it's a hoax?
No, I'm pretty plugged in
to the homebrew
animation community.
This isn't a fake.
This is
a "freakin' real dino."
And it was taken today?
A couple of hours ago.
I've got a sniffer running
on all dino stuff.
I caught it early.
So a few thousand people
click on a dinosaur video,
in between piano-playing cat
and faceplant-of-the-week.
No one'll take it seriously.
I'm not worried about
some guy in Singapore
tweeting it to his friends.
I'm worried about locals
recognizing that skate park
and going out there
to check it out.
Can you take this down?
Yeah, with a little effort.
I mean, I'm on it.
I'll grab the gear.
Let's get out there.
What's the status
on the anomaly detector?
Oh, we're still 12 hours
away from operational.
Any way I can help?
No.
We'll be okay.
Once we're
in the general vicinity,
the handheld can get us
the rest of the way.
What about Mac?
Are we going to call him?
No.
Let's leave him alone.
Okay.
Not sure how much these'll do
against a full-grown
triceratops.
This is bigger than anything
we've been up against before.
That's comforting.
It's a prey animal.
A herbivore.
There's a good case that
it'll just den down,
if it can find a safe spot.
Somewhere with
edible plants and water.
Just so long as it doesn't
spew magic mushrooms
all over me,
I'm good.
There.
Just past the baseball diamond.
That's where it was.
Maybe we can pick up its trail.
I think we know
who shot the footage.
You all right?
I'm good, man.
Hey!
You're the freakin'
real dino guys, right?
Yeah, cool, huh?
Want me to sign your shirt?
[Chuckling]
You guys know
which way it went?
I tried going after it,
but it was gone.
[Van honks]
Evan...
Hey, Toby.
Two news crews just showed up.
This thing's
getting out of hand.
What do you mean "getting"?
The video is mirrored on over
a dozen different websites.
"Freakingrealdino"
is trending on Twitter.
I can't shut down
the whole Internet
and the local news.
Okay, um...
Call Ken Leeds.
See if he can help.
Copy that.
Hi, yeah, can I speak
with Ken Leeds?
What is it regarding?
Uh, tell him that I need help
containing a situation.
What is the nature
of the situation?
Can I just talk to him?
This is sensitive.
All matters that this office
handles are sensitive.
You'll have to be more specific.
Who are you?
I'm Warrant Officer
Lisa Merriweather.
I'm the lieutenant's
new assistant.
Oh, okay, great.
So assist him
and let him speak with me.
Not until you tell me
what it's regarding.
Fine!
A TV crew is about
to interview people
who have seen
a live triceratops
for a special report
on the news
tonight.
Now can I speak with him?
I'll be sure
he gets your message.
That thing is so big,
I'm surprised
no one's found it yet.
You're right.
It's huge.
There.
It came this way.
I'm getting a reading
from this direction.
Great. We've left
the crowd behind,
and now we're trespassing.
Why is it that some people
feel they need
10,000 square feet
of personal space?
Well, a lot of tech guys
live in this area.
We're not the most
sociable bunch
to begin with.
This is pushed outward.
It looks like
there are tracks here
going back and forth.
Well, maybe
they're on vacation.
When do we ever get that lucky?
[Chuckles ruefully]
The anomaly should be
just past that arch somewhere.
What kind of address is that?
"Alpha."
The first letter
of the Greek alphabet.
That's not an address,
unless the guy who lives here
is trying to make
a serious statement
about his position in the pack,
in which case, peeing
on the door every morning
might be quicker.
It's the symbol
for the fine structure constant
of the universe,
and that right there
is bad news.
Why?
[Evan]: This place
belongs to Howard Kanan.
Guy's a legend.
Key patents in mobile
communications,
medical imaging,
remote oil-field
sensing...
Every arena he worked in,
he was brilliant.
Certifiable genius.
Genius?
Like he could understand
how that thing works?
We've got to find that creature
and get it out of here
before Kanan sees it.
If he knew, he'd want in.
Do you know that he buried
every single company
that got in his way?
You know a lot about him.
Yeah, we've crossed paths.
I'm lucky I still
have my company.
[Shouting, behind them]:
Evan Cross!
You thieving prick.
So, you two know each other.
Mostly from court.
He tried to sue me
for patent infringement,
but he didn't have a case.
I lost.
Doesn't mean I'm not right.
And, uh, you are...?
Dylan Weir.
I don't hold any patents.
Hmm.
Why are you on my property?
Bird watching.
I heard there was
a rare specimen out here.
Likes to roost near water.
Would that be
the black oyster-catcher
or the long-billed curlew?
Hermit thrush.
You, I like.
Conditionally.
How about you, Cross?
You here to watch the birds
or just steal them?
You know what,
I think it's about time
you and I straightened out
this whole misunderstanding.
You did not pioneer
photonic circuitry.
I did.
So which part
am I misunderstanding?
I invented it, and he stole it.
If you'd like, I can prove it.
He can't prove that.
Yes, I can.
Come on in.
Hang on, if you think
you have proof,
I should be the one
that you show.
Call me if you need anything.
Back at you.
How can he be busy?
Unless a flying saucer
has landed downtown,
we're the only thing
that Project Magnet does!
Yeah, great, awesome.
Why don't you give him
another message?
[Door slams]
Mac!
Hey, Tobes.
[Stammering awkwardly]
Wow, affection really
doesn't work for us, does it?
I love you on the inside.
Where's Evan?
[Sighing]
We need to have a serious chat.
He's on another dino-hunt,
along with every other
lookie-loo in Vancouver.
So the dinosaurs are
finally out of the bag?
Yeah, and I have
to figure out a way
to put them back in the bag,
but I don't have a bag.
Leeds is AWOL, Ange quit,
Evan and Dylan
are doing the fun stuff,
and if I don't
figure out a way to stop this,
then we're going to have
a lot of people
asking a lot of questions
that we don't want to answer.
Like, "Why my body
is in a freezer?"
Forgive me
if I'm having trouble
getting worked up
about public relations,
but I'm not sure if
I'm alive or dead.
Ow!
What was that?
You're alive.
So how can I be
downstairs on ice?
Oh, come on, do you
really want a discourse
in comparative theory
of time displacement?
Can you summarize?
That's not you
in the cryo chamber, Mac.
You are you.
No, I'm not.
I'm Evan's me,
the version he created
when he pulled me
out of that life
and brought me here.
[Sighs]
Well, come on.
What?
Where?
Hey...
Keep your eyes to yourself.
Howard?
How long have you
been living like this?
Like what?
Like a...
Junk Food Survivalist?
Minimizing my distraction
so I can focus on
my next innovation.
In harmonics?
Hey.
I didn't bring you in here
so you could steal more patents.
All right,
that makes two of us.
So what's your so-called proof?
See?
Operational...
Photonics.
I was working on the
manufacturing specs
when you came out of nowhere.
Geared up in three months,
cornered the worldwide market
before anyone knew
what happened.
It's just business.
A lot of people were doing
parallel research.
Yeah.
Sure, maybe.
And you just happened
to have the breakthrough.
Yeah. I did.
And the fact that
you couldn't use
a uniform superconductor?
How did you solve that one?
The nanowire?
Coated that with gold.
[Laughs]
That's a cute trick.
But I had teams running
manufacturing tests
on every option.
After 20 months of trials,
we were finally
narrowing in on a solution,
and boom!
Evan Cross comes in
out of nowhere,
and you go into production
without one single trial?
How do you explain that?
I don't have to explain it.
Check my patents...
I did!
And what it shows
is that you knew
the right answer
right from the beginning,
no sweat equity at all.
So...
It come to you in a dream?
It happens.
Yes, it does.
Most definitely.
But here's the thing.
If you're that brilliant,
if you're that much of a genius,
it would happen again
and again.
And since then...
Nothing.
I don't understand.
Either you're a patent thief...
Or whatever you've been working
on for the last five years
is so big you're keeping it...
What, under wraps?
Or maybe things just
didn't go as expected.
[Grunting and snuffling]
Oh, my God...
[Triceratops
munching and grunting]
There's a bright line,
isn't there?
Between then and now.
[Package crackling]
Between everything
so full of promise...
And everything so dark.
Howard?
What happened to you?
You've got this huge house,
and you're holed up in here
obsessing over what went wrong.
Maybe things...
Just didn't go as I expected.
[Triceratops grunting]
[Quietly] Evan.
I'm out by the pool.
You've got to see this.
Excuse me.
I have to check on my friend.
The birdwatcher?
Don't suppose
you're going to tell me
what she's actually looking for?
You wouldn't understand.
[Clears throat]
[Shivering]
If this wasn't here,
would you have believed Evan
even if he did tell you?
You're saying
he kept it for me?
I don't know.
But, I mean, if he planned on
keeping this a secret forever,
then storing your body
was a pretty stupid move,
and Evan Cross isn't stupid.
He stole my life.
He saved your life,
and he was ready
to die to do it.
Think about it.
The moment he changed
your future,
he must have known
that your future self
wouldn't be there
to stop him from getting killed
by a dinosaur.
So if I wasn't there
to save him, why isn't he dead?
I don't know,
and you know what, I don't care,
because you're both alive,
and if what he did
is responsible for that,
then I'm glad that he did it.
Because of the
choices available,
this one's
a hell of a lot more fun.
So where do you suppose
"I" came from?
Out of an anomaly, apparently.
So that must have been
my job then,
saving people?
I mean, I'm wearing a uniform.
That's not really
that much to go on, Mac.
You know, everyone around here
seems to think
you're pretty clever.
I'll bet you could figure out
what that arc symbol means
if you put your mind to it.
I might consider helping you.
But only if you help me
put the triceratops
back in the bottle.
Well, I might have
an idea about that.
Look at what I found.
Great.
Now we just need to
find out where it goes.
I've got this.
You get that.
Where's crazy eyes?
Inside...
With his powerbars and regret.
Isn't it magnificent?
I've never had a chance
to just sit and watch one.
Evan, come on.
They're not all
vicious killers.
This one doesn't mean any harm.
He's just...
out of place, is all.
It's still dangerous.
Look at it.
The thing's bigger
than an elephant,
and those horns,
they're like Spears.
Not to mention the little
problem we'd have
trying to explain it
if someone else saw it.
Wait.
We don't want to have
to carry it.
[Grunting and growling]
[Roaring]
Move!
[Bellowing]
That's one hell
a a hermit thrush.
That's it, right?
I mean, this is it!
This is the big secret
that you've been working on
for the last five years, right?
Am I right?
The great breakthrough
by the great Evan Cross!
Not exactly.
This is huge!
I mean, you're no
genetic engineer, my friend,
which means that thing came...
from a distant past.
[Laughing giddily]
I mean, I knew you guys
were hiding something, right?
Right, but triceratops?
That wasn't even on the list!
[Weepily] And I love surprises!
What happened to that thing
not meaning any harm?
We must've frightened it.
Or else it thinks
the pool is its home,
and it was just
defending its territory.
I'll find it.
You find the anomaly.
Find the anomaly...
[Scanner dripping]
Oh.
Is it dead?
Yeah, it might need
a little CPR.
Need help?
And, uh...
Where did you get it?
I built it.
No, it's way too sophisticated.
It's a pet project.
You want me to believe
that you found
doorways through time,
and yet your breakthrough
secret project
isn't from the future?
Maybe stolen?
Maybe from my future?
Or mine?
Do you realize
the implications of that?
Confirmation
of Feynman's Postulate
of branching timelines.
Look, nothing's been confirmed.
And this isn't going to
help your case in court.
Oh, forget court!
This is Nobel territory!
Beyond Nobel territory!
Howard, no.
None of it can leave this room.
Are you k...
None of it.
Okay, you want my silence?
Tell me the truth.
Come on!
This has got to be killing you!
You have to be desperate
for someone to talk to
who can actually understand.
No. Not really.
Evan...
Knowledge like this
isn't power.
It's isolation.
Yes, Miss Nance,
I'll be sure
he gets the message.
Now, was that "triceratops"
with one "r?"
Hello?
[Sighing in disbelief]
[Text message chirps]
Mac, I thought you were
going to help me.
And so I have.
What the hell?
His name's Spikey.
[Triceratops grunting]
There you are.
Okay.
Slowly this time.
[Grunting]
Yeah, see?
There's nothing to worry about.
[Grunting and huffing]
What is going on with you?
You can't think
all of this is your territory.
It's the red.
You think I'm a rival.
Okay.
Let's try this again.
[Grunting]
[Triceratops falls silent]
You're just scared.
Why wouldn't you be?
I'm just going to make sure
you don't get into
any more trouble.
[Evan]: This is fried.
I'd have put in a limiter
to stop it from overloading.
Oh, really?
Well, thanks for the advice.
Do you have anything?
Yeah.
Yeah, I've got something
you could kludge in there.
Get it up and running.
For a price.
This isn't a joke, Howard.
No, I get that.
This is
the space-time continuum.
It has world-ending potential,
and you don't want to be
the next Oppenheimer.
Exactly.
Hmm.
So why are you messing with it?
I don't have a choice.
As dangerous as
these anomalies may be,
it's the only thing we have
to put these creatures back.
Have you ever been through one?
To the other side?
Yeah.
Once or twice.
And...
was it amazing?
And frightening.
Look, the only thing
I'm trying to do
is keep every single thing
where it belongs.
How did that
get to be your job?
You know that bright line
you talked about
between then and now?
That happened for me
when a dinosaur killed my wife.
I get that.
When my wife died...
If I could have gone
after ovarian cancer
with your rifles...
I would have.
[Dylan, over radio]: Evan.
Dylan.
You all right?
Better than all right.
I got me a dinosaur.
Where?
Tennis court.
The creature's fenced in,
not that that'll matter
if it decides to take off.
But I'm going to find it
some food and water,
get it to hunker down.
How long till we've got
an anomaly detector?
We're working on it.
Work faster.
I've gotta find enough food
to fill a school bus.
Roger that.
I have to get this thing
finished.
We have to put that triceratops
back through that anomaly
before it closes.
How long do you have?
No idea.
You don't know?
I don't have a timer.
I've been working on one, but...
Evan, I can help.
You and I working together,
there's very little
we can't solve.
I want in.
Perfect.
Hey...
And I think know
what you like to eat.
It was, like, 20 feet tall,
with these big, massive horns,
and... there it is!
There's the dinosaur!
[Crowd gasping and shouting]
[Crowd groaning
in disappointment]
Oh no.
Hey! Stop!
Hmm? Oh.
[Tranq darts firing]
[Roaring]
What the hell are you doing?
Dylan, I hadn't realized
you were already on the scene.
Well, we are,
and I have everything
under control
if you'll just get
these people to back off.
Uh, yeah, uh,
lower your weapons.
And, um, pull back.
I'm here to help.
Yeah, well,
you're not helping, okay?
If you tranq that thing here,
we're going to have to drag it
all the way to the anomaly,
which, let me tell you
from experience,
is harder than you think.
Yeah, I have a truck.
That's not the point.
This is a docile animal,
and it can move
under its own power.
Understood.
[Stammers in confusion]
I thought that Toby sent you
to the skate park.
Yeah, real-time
satellite imagery
revealed a remarkably large
mobile heat signature
on this property.
I'm here to offer
full operational coordination
with your field efforts.
We are on the same team.
Then I have
just the job for you.
[Scanner beeps]
The portals,
you call them anomalies, right?
Yeah.
You like that?
Sure.
Then this is your theory
on how they work.
Yeah, they appear,
they fluctuate,
they disappear.
There's a pattern to it,
but it's different
every single time.
I haven't been able
to figure out
the Fourier series for it yet.
That's because you're
going about it wrong.
You're trying to find
a value lost in chaos.
That can't be predicted.
Elaborate on that.
What if it's not about
overlapping sine waves?
What...
Let me explain.
The anomalies,
they're magnetic, right?
So every time they appear,
there's going to be
a unique signature
caused by an interference
with the earth's
magnetic field.
Done.
So it's not a pattern
you're trying to predict.
Of course.
It's a harmonic signature.
Right.
It's not the standing field
I should be trying to measure.
It's the initial event.
It's like a musical note
that fades.
Yes, and when it decays
past the critical threshold...
The anomaly collapses.
Exactly.
Predictably.
So all we need to do
is suspend a crystal
in a fluid matrix.
We don't have time for that.
I have to find the anomaly.
But thank you, Howard.
Thank you.
Great.
Just there.
[Woman]: Excuse me.
Excuse me!
What the hell do you people
think you're doing?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I have official authorization
to commandeer these flowers
for reasons
of national security.
But they're
my prize-winning flowers!
Yes, I understand
that they're beautiful...
Gentlemen, that's...
That's plenty.
Thanks, great.
Yup. Just...
[Gasping in shock]
In these
uncertain times, ma'am,
we all have to make sacrifices
for freedom.
You look lovely today.
Oh, my goodness...
[Hastily starting engine]
Go.
[Tires squealing]
[Scanner warbling]
[Static crackling]
[Pings softly]
You think this will work?
The only better lure
than food is sex.
Yeah, truer words.
When Evan tells us where to go,
we'll just walk it back,
nice and slow.
There's no need
for all that excitement.
For once.
My God...
Look at...
Howard, don't get too close.
Look at the shard layer.
It's the edge of space and time
just blown apart.
I think it's from the impact
of colliding
four-dimensional surfaces.
I think it might just be
the way the human eye
perceives it, but...
It is beautiful.
Yeah...
It's the bright line.
Between then and now.
May I?
It's okay.
Your timer, sir.
How did you make that
so quickly?
[Laughs]
I just tweaked a resonator
I've been working on
for over a year.
It's almost like
it was destiny.
[Devices powers up]
[Timer scan drones]
And it works.
And we have less
than two minutes.
[Dylan, over radio]:
Two minutes? You're sure?
A minute and 50 seconds.
Assuming this thing
is accurate.
The calculated
margin for error is .006%,
give or take.
Where are you?
Uh, 200 metres east
of the Bowling Green.
Be there in 90 seconds.
[Leeds]: What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Anomaly.
No time to explain.
How can I assist?
Get out of the way.
This baby's going home!
Is this analogous
to a bullfighter's cape?
Because bulls
are colour-blind.
They're more attracted to...
Shut... up.
Hey!
[Growling]
[Triceratops bellows]
Evan!
It's 15 seconds.
She's not gonna make it.
She will.
Look out!
Whoa!
And with seconds to spare.
You okay?
Howard...
Goodbye.
[Howard's laughter echoes]
[Leeds]: Who was that?
How long has he been here?
Be nice.
He was very helpful
getting fodder for the big guy.
There was a man here.
Where did he go?
It was Howard Kanan.
And you know where he went.
Interesting development.
Why would he do that?
I don't know.
Curiosity? Arrogance?
Complete stupidity?
Or all of the above.
He's going to die in there.
Or worse.
Thanks, Mac.
You really saved my ass.
All of our asses, really.
Well, it was your ass
that I did it for.
You might want to
rephrase that.
Um... no.
Don't tell Evan about this.
Why?
I need to get
some answers first.
With your help.
Okay, a deal's a deal.
But I will say that
it's not the same here
without you.
And...
oh, my God, I can't believe
I'm saying this.
[Sighs heavily]
I miss you.
[Chuckles]
Then do me a favor and
visit me from time to time.
I must get lonely
down there in the freezer.
[Chuckles]
I'd like to think
you were checking up on me.
Deal.
[Evan, across the room]:
Toby, what the hell's this?
Oh, it's, uh...
It's just that...
never mind.
You get the Internet shut down?
Actually, I did
better than that.
[News report]:
...And on the lighter side,
an elaborate dinosaur hoax
swept the Internet today
following a prank
at a local skate park.
[Spider]: There it is!
There's the dinosaur!
So remember,
if somebody shows you footage
of a freaking real dinosaur,
think twice
before you believe it.
Over to you, Sam.
Nice.
Yeah, well, I figured
it's not the last time
someone's gonna get
a video of a dinosaur, right?
So might as well
make them all seem fake.
You called Mac in.
Um...
Sort of.
But, uh,
you were right.
He's gonna need some time.
Good work.
Hey, show me that thing
one more time.
Yes.
Massive horns, and...
There it is!
There's the dinosaur!
Any calls?
Just Colonel Hall.
He'd like an update.
Oh, terrific.
Something's bugging you.
Is that where I'm headed?
Am I the next crazy eyes
living alone
in a mansion somewhere?
You going down this road
because of Mac?
You know he'll be back, right?
I was thinking
about this, actually.
Three years I've been
working on this tech,
thinking it would
solve everything.
Make up for everything.
Fix everything.
But what if it doesn't, hmm?
The first time I saw you,
you had one of
those things in your hands.
You couldn't keep
your eyes off it.
I thought you'd kept your phone
from the '90s or something.
[Laughs]
Yeah, well, I always make
a good first impression.
But that thing,
it gave me a gift today.
I've, uh...
I've been really struggling
with this work,
because it isn't like
predator control.
This isn't
mostly harmless animals
with the occasional killer.
These creatures
are almost all killers.
But today we finally
had one that wasn't,
and all we had to do
was show it the way home,
and we did that.
We did it.
You have a feel
for these things
that I don't have.
I'm not sure if
I'll ever have it.
I used to coil razor wire
back home.
We had wolves that would
come down out of the forest
and try to eat our sheep.
My dad said we had
to keep them out,
but every month or so,
I would come out,
and I would f-find...
They would get tangled
in the wire sometimes.
They'd chew their own paws off.
That's really when I got it,
you know?
It isn't their fault, right?
They're just being who they are.
We're the problem.
We're the ones who want
everything to be human.
Now we've covered
the whole damn world
in razor wire,
so where are...
Where are the animals
supposed to go?
But today,
you came up with
a better way to help them,
to get them back to a time
with no humans in it.
Hey, that thing
that Howard made,
you can make that again?
Then do it.
The tech isn't just
to help you.
It's to help them.
It's the least
we can do, right?
The mission objective
was compromised
by circumstances, sir.
But on the positive side,
the specimen was returned
to its natural habitat.
And there was
an interesting, um, development.
I'll have that in my report.
Uh, yes, sir,
that goes without saying.
We are on the same team.
Yes, sir.
[♪]
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for addic7ed.com