Morning.
It's day 182
of project cooplets.
We're at 26 weeks. Multiples are
usually born around 32.
So I'm savoring every
last minute of this pregnancy.
I mean, just look
at my gorgeous wife.
I know what you're thinking.
How did I get so lucky?
I swear, I have no idea.
All I know is that this is what
I've wanted my entire life--
to take care of my pregnant wife
and a house full of kids.
Oh.
You know, I'm really not much
of a morning person,
but there's so much to do now,
it's really all about
multitasking.
The babies are the size
of lettuce this week.
You know,
there is an app for that.
Brain development has kicked
into high gear,
so it's important that Charlotte
get all the right nutrition.
And yes, sometimes
when I give her her vitamins,
she throws them at me,
but I don't take it personally.
This is what I can do
to contribute
while she is doing all
the heavy lifting, literally.
Yes!
Breakfast is Charlotte's
least favorite meal,
so I like to give her
plenty of options.
Thanks for making
me pancakes, dad.
You got it, Mase.
Rise and shine, beautiful.
Time to get up.
Enough
with the damn breakfast buffet.
It's too early.
I let you sleep
as long as I could.
No, Coop.
My water just broke.
The babies are coming.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
_
You knocked me up.
My guys prevailed.
Sweetie, we're having a baby,
you and me?
We're having a baby.
No, Cooper.
We're having three babies.
Three? Three babies.
That...
Is amazing. I'm-- Wow. Okay.
I can't react.
She-- she doesn't want one.
She's definitely
not gonna want three.
But I'm totally excited.
You get that, right?
Wow.
That's one word for it.
I can think of a few others,
all four letters.
Are you okay?
No. You heard me, right?
Three babies.
I know when the night
of conception was.
- We were in the shower, and she
did this thing... - No, I'm not all right.
- And then I did this other thing... - This
thing's supposed to be 99.9% effective.
...and I made sounds come out of her
that you do not hear in nature.
I was the man.
How hard it's gonna be to take
care of three rug rats?
Okay. I know it's a lot
to take in.
Is it okay that
I'm a little bit excited?
As long as you don't expect
me to be.
Ugh.
_
Okay.
This is gonna be awesome.
You've seen
plenty of ultrasounds.
Not when they're our kids
and not when
they're the size of plums.
Oh, come on, Charlotte.
You know you're excited.
All ultrasounds look the same.
They're like the sketches
of "America's Most Wanted."
You can't identify someone
from those.
All right.
There they are.
There's baby one,
baby two...
Oh, you see it, right?
Those are clearly our kids.
She has no idea
what she's talking about.
Hi, kids.
I made you.
This means I can't go
to the urology conference
in Spain in October.
We're not gonna be able to go
to Hawaii for Christmas.
Oh, come on, Charlotte.
You're pregnant.
You're not terminally ill.
I'm gonna be a double-wide
with feet.
More of you to love.
Look, all three look great.
You said with triplets,
one of 'em might not make it.
No, what I said was that
with multiples,
there's a 53% chance
of spontaneous reduction,
but since that usually happens
in the first trimester,
you are almost in the clear.
Yay for me.
Look, there are inherent risks
with carrying triplets to term.
We should go back to my office
and talk about it.
I have to get back
to the hospital.
No, what you need to do
is hire a new ER doc
and focus on the plums.
_
Sorry.
I'd, uh, just as soon
keep this to myself,
but since that's not possible,
I'm, uh,
I'm pregnant...
with triplets.
- Wow.
- That's so wonderful.
- Congratulations!
- That's so great. Yeah.
Okay, who already knew?
Time-out. If there's
a time and a place to lie,
it's right here and right now.
And don't you dare lie
to a pregnant woman.
Let's go, people.
Show of hands.
- Ow! - Is it impossible for you
to keep your mouth shut?
- You told Addison.
- She's my doctor.
- What's your excuse for telling Violet?
- Doesn't count.
- Thanks, Coop.
- You know what I mean.
- I'm sorry. I told Jake.
- But only so she could pick my brain
about pregnancy with multiples.
I saw Cooper trolling
the Internet for baby names.
And not that you asked,
but your kid will be pantsed
every day if you name him Otis.
And Coop was asking me
when Naomi started wearing
maternity clothes.
- Mm.
- You think I look fat?
No, you look beautiful.
Beautiful and fat,
but beautiful.
I may be the last one to know,
but this is fantastic news.
Seriously. New life.
You-- you must be so excited.
I'm excited about the odds
that my body might absorb
- at least one of these freeloaders
before birth. - That's terrible.
- That's terrible.
- That's Darwin.
Survival of the fittest.
You gonna find out the sex?
Well, the ultrasound
won't be definitive
until closer to 18 weeks.
If this technically wasn't
a high-risk pregnancy,
I wouldn't want to see
another ultrasound.
I mean, I want the mystery of
that. I want the anticipation.
I want to know
as soon as possible.
But I mean, it would be awesome
if it was a surprise, right?
I am pregnant with triplets.
That's surprise enough
for a lifetime.
So we're having triplets.
Great.
Congratulations, man.
I threw out almost everything
or donated it to charity.
But I still have
Pete's toothbrush.
- I can't stop thinking about babies...
- I haven't touched it.
But babies are life, and Violet
wants to talk about death.
I need to focus.
I need to focus on death.
And I just stare at it
every morning...
- It sounds wrong, doesn't it?
- In the bathroom.
I don't know.
I mean, I know he's not actually
gonna come back to use it,
but it just makes me
feel better to see it there,
next to mine on a sink.
Whatever works, right?
That's right.
Don't you think--
I mean, shouldn't you be
talking to someone?
I'm talking to you.
Come--
I mean-- I mean,
I have grief group,
which sort of helps.
I guess. I don't know.
Look, I mean,
Pete is dead, and, um...
and that sucks.
It's gonna suck
until it doesn't.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Vi.
Okay.
She's mourning the loss
of her husband,
and he was my friend.
I just can't go there right now.
I am in baby land.
I mean, I want to be doing
cartwheels, which is funny,
'cause I've never done
a cartwheel in my whole life.
I need to stop this.
Okay, her husband is dead.
I cannot show her my baby glee.
I need to smile and nod
and pretend I'm listening.
Okay.
Thanks. Thanks, Cooper.
- For what?
- For listening.
- All right.
- I'm gonna be late for my group.
- Okay.
She thanked me for listening.
I wasn't listening.
I'm a bad friend.
I mean, she needs help.
She is suffering,
and I'm... just an ass.
I mean, go.
Go-- go be with Violet.
Seriously, I'm good. Go.
Violet?
You're not in grief group.
Gabi, hi.
Uh, yeah, I was
checking on a patient.
Guess I lost track of time.
Oh, me, too.
I was visiting Ally.
I didn't know
she was at St. Ambrose.
Yeah. This is like my second
home. I'm here every day.
You know, I read to her,
play music.
You know, just let her know
I love her.
That's really nice.
Well, if we go now,
we won't be too late.
Is it awful
that I wanna play hooky?
Oh, God. No.
It's hard, the work
that we do over there.
Yeah, it's also hard to hear
over Kasey's sobbing.
That's terrible.
I'm sorry.
No, just the actual number of
tissues that she uses, you know,
like a whole box, really?
What about the rest of us?
Yeah,
but it's also that there's
a kind of pecking order,
you know?
I mean, I know I'm entitled
to miss my girlfriend,
but her son was like,
what, 26 when he died?
How do you compete with that?
You play hooky.
Do you want company?
Okay, everything looks good.
The first trimester tests
came back
negative for trisomy 13 and 18,
which means it's unlikely
that the kids
will have
any chromosomal abnormalities.
We can go ahead and do an amnio
at 16 weeks to be sure.
Sounds great.
Right, char?
Fantastic. Are we done?
No. No. We have to discuss
your options.
No, I know my options.
I'd like to hear the options.
With multiples,
there's a very high probability
of preterm delivery, resulting
in low birthweight infants,
- which are at risk.
- I know what they're at risk for.
A dead mother.
That's what they're at risk for,
because I just may kill her
right now.
The problem is,
she's carrying my babies,
so I guess I should wait.
Ideally,
we want to get to 32 weeks.
That gives the babies
the best chance.
Anything before 26 weeks,
and you're looking
at the possibility
of cognitive
and neurological impairments.
Great. Got it.
You did your job.
She has to understand the risks.
Can-- can you talk to her?
Tell me what we need to know.
Can't sleep?
Ah, bloodsucking ticks are
giving me heartburn.
Can't wait till
they keep me up kickboxing.
Anything I can do?
Hmm. Go back in time,
wear a condom.
So I was talking to Addison
this afternoon after you left.
And with triplets,
you're looking at a lot
of possible
obstetric complications.
Remember when you asked if there
was anything you could do?
Stop talking.
You're at risk
for preterm labor,
premature ruptured membranes,
gestational diabetes,
preeclampsia,
and postpartum hemorrhaging,
which means you could die,
Charlotte.
Cooper, I'm a doctor.
I know what I'm at risk for.
Oh, my God. I take back
the whole killing her thing.
- Okay?
- Quit being so dramatic.
Is it gone?
Quit being so dramatic.
I think we need to talk about
selective reduction.
How many times do I have to say
I don't need to hear this?
Reduction from triplets
to twins,
decreases the risk
of severe prematurity
and the risk
of losing the whole pregnancy
falls from 15% to 4%.
I won't abort.
You were hoping that one of them
would be absorbed anyway.
What's the difference?
Absorbed is
my higher power at work.
Abortion is me making the call.
Selective reduction
isn't exactly abortion.
It's a shot to the heart
of a fetus
with potassium chloride.
You know how you pick?
Whichever one's closest.
That's who gets the needle.
I'm not doing that.
I have to pee.
Okay, that's horrible,
but if losing one means
you can save two,
if losing one means Charlotte
would be okay? I don't know.
I don't know. I'm the dad,
so I should have a say,
but right now mom's doing
all the hard work.
It's Charlotte's body,
it's her life, it's her choice.
But I can't lose her and
I don't want to lose any of my babies.
So what the hell do I do?
What do I do?
Cooper.
We told Mason he was
having three siblings.
Then Mason's having
three siblings.
_
Wow. They have
a lot of strollers here.
Yes. Oh. Here you go.
Look at this one.
No. Baby in the front
will be 3 miles away.
I won't be able to see it.
Someone could snatch it
and I wouldn't know till,
like, an hour later.
- Well, I-I can help.
- She's insane. Right? I mean, it's 3 feet.
Unless she's legally blind,
she'll be able to spot danger.
- ...with one of the babies. - You're
gonna make a hell of a big brother.
Can I help you folks?
Yes. We are looking
for strollers, but, um,
there's a lot to choose from.
We have some excellent models,
but the truth is, it's really
best to carry the baby
and hold them close.
I did that with mine.
Yeah, well, I'm pregnant with
triplets,
so how do I hold all three
at the same time?
Do you put one in a basket
on your head? Or-- or maybe
with three it doesn't really
matter if I drop one
now and again,
'cause I've got spares.
- Oh, good. She's making friends.
- You don't really mean that, right?
I'll bet this lady wishes
she called in sick today.
- I can carry one.
- Thank you for your help.
Uh, we'll let you know
if we need anything. Thanks.
With my luck, she'll be waiting
for me in the breast pump aisle
so she can tell me how
she nursed all of her kids
until they're 27.
- Ew! People really do that?
- No.
When you're pregnant,
everyone's got an opinion,
and they all
wanna offer advice.
Okay, does someone need
a hug? Three...
- Two...
- One.
Who's cranky?
You can let go.
- You can stay.
- Okay.
You didn't talk about Lucas
in group today. How's he doing?
He doesn't ask about Pete
anymore.
I'm worried that he won't
remember his dad,
but sometimes I think
that's better.
Sure. If you don't remember,
there's nothing to miss.
Maybe that's what I need--
amnesia.
Although I'm already
starting to forget things.
Like what?
Our first date, Ally and I went
to this hole-in-the-wall
restaurant in Mexico
while we were working
down there.
I was writing
for National Geographic.
She was taking the pictures.
I've been racking my brain
for the past three days,
but I can't recall
the name of the place.
Ally would know.
But she hasn't
answered me in a while.
I am so sorry.
I can't imagine
how hard this is for you.
I keep hoping that
I can will her to wake up.
None of the doctors can agree
as to when that might be.
But as long as a chance exists,
I can't give up.
I won't.
They are beautiful!
Oh, my-- I'm so excited
for you guys. This is amazing.
Amazing? I can't have
too much coffee.
I can't eat sushi. I'm supposed
to watch my mercury levels
and be on the lookout for
toxoplasma, listeria, E Coli.
Yeah, she should keep
complaining to Amelia...
about pregnancy because
it must've been really fun
to go through the nine months
and then give birth to a baby
with no brain.
...and even herbal tea.
Herbal tea.
And then the damn shopping
has to get done
before they get here--
the bottles, the diapers.
And what the hell's a layette?
I can't even go
to the store anymore, though,
because I'm so gassy and itchy--
my boobs, my bump.
I don't have time for this crap.
I have a job. Two jobs.
You know, if we threw you
a shower--
- No.
- Come on. Think about it. It could be fun.
Charlotte hates showers.
Mostly she hates the women
that have showers...
because they're all that woman...
You know, the ones that think
the world needs to stop
because they're pregnant,
like they're the first ones
to ever do that.
...sugary baked goods.
I hate showers.
You know who has showers?
That woman--
the one I hate,
the one who thinks
the world's gotta stop
because she's having a baby.
Like she's the first
one to ever do it.
Okay, first of all,
there is no danger
of you ever becoming
that woman.
Second, you do realize that you
need everything in triplicate.
So if I throw you a shower,
you won't have to worry
about any of it.
I'll register for you,
and by the time the babies
are born,
you'll have
everything you need.
So you can be gassy
in the comfort of your own home.
So really,
you're just buying me stuff?
Okay.
What she meant to say was
"thank you."
_
20 minutes for you, 30 for me,
and ten minutes for
"American Bake Off."
- Uh...
- Okay, I'll give you five in "Bake Off,"
but my 30 is nonnegotiable.
I need every minute of it.
What are we talking about?
Us, commiserating
about our lives
over corned beef on marble rye.
Right. Lunch.
I totally forgot.
Did you forget?
- Of course not.
- You forgot.
I forgot.
And Addison's about to do
Charlotte's ultrasound
- in, like, ten minutes.
I didn't tell you that? - No.
Oh, my God.
Please don't let her be mad.
I mean, I just can't handle that
right now.
I just want to see
my little sweet potatoes.
You're not mad, are you?
I'm furious.
Yeah, blow off
your wife's ultrasound
and have lunch with me.
You know, if you still want one,
we can do an amnio.
No.
I realize that there are
associated risks,
but I do know what I'm doing.
Oh, it doesn't matter. Even
if an amnio tells us each kid
has two heads and is covered in
gills, they're still our babies
and they'll stay our babies.
Mm.
Hi, King-Freedmans
or Freedman-Kings.
Did you miss me?
Well, how could they miss you?
You talk to 'em every damn day.
I read in one
of the pregnancy books
that if you talk
to your children every day...
they're more secure
and well-adjusted.
I don't know. At least
they'll know me right away.
Is hiding behind the other two.
It is pretty crowded in there,
but your girls...
- Look good.
- Girls?
- All three of 'em?
- All three of 'em.
Girls are awesome!
Oh, my God!
- Oh, man!
- Oh!
What the hell am I gonna do
with three girls?
Charlotte?
You okay?
It's 7:00 P.M.
I'm tired.
I'm always tired.
It's because
I don't sleep anymore.
Everything's tight.
My socks are tight.
My towels are tight.
The freaking mangoes are
making me miserable.
You'd never know because she's
so shy about her discontent.
Really keeps it all inside.
And I'm doing this for girls.
Why do they all
have to be girls?
Girls are awesome.
You were a girl.
Ah.
Girls...
are silly and stupid.
When they turn 12,
we're giving them away
because 12-year-old girls make
Stalin look like Gandhi.
Sure, they're disgustingly sweet
to their daddies,
but girls hate their mamas
from puberty to at least age 20.
Mm. The only thing that's worse
is when they become women.
Sure, they'll talk your ear off
about sisterhood
while simultaneously
stabbing you in the back
and sleeping with your husband.
Women are awful.
You're not awful.
You're perfect.
And you will raise them
to be just like you.
Mm.
And then hopefully,
they will each meet a man
as patient and selfless
as I am.
Although, I probably won't let
them date until they're 30
because before I was selfless
and patient,
I was a man-whore who knocked
a woman up in a parking lot
and met my wife on a sex site.
I have my work cut out for me,
don't I?
Thanks for taking a look.
I know that ally's
on life support,
but what are the odds
that she--
No, there are no odds.
Ally has no cortical activity.
I'm gonna have a hard time
imagining
any doctor saying otherwise.
I mean, she's brain-dead.
She's not waking up ever.
I'm sorry, Violet.
What are you doing?
Hey, Gabi.
Uh, this is Dr. Shepherd.
She's a neurosurgeon
and a friend.
I didn't ask you
to get another opinion.
No, I realize that. But I just
thought that since she's here--
Get out, both of you.
_
All right, what about this one?
There's a swimming pool
in the back,
a 6-car garage,
and 8 bedrooms.
Okay. How much?
$15 million.
Is-- is that too much?
No, not if we win the lottery.
Okay, what about this one?
See, five bedrooms,
big backyard.
We could build a tree house.
I thought I'd surprise Charlotte
with a house.
Who am I kidding?
This is Los Angeles.
We can't afford a house
for this brood.
Maybe if all the kids
share rooms.
Will their friends
make fun of them
for not having their own space?
Maybe they won't have friends.
Maybe if we don't buy
the $15-million house
with the pool,
they'll be shunned.
It doesn't just happen
with the amish, right?
It kinda looks haunted.
Oh. Yeah.
Well, the good news is,
if you have to share your room
with a ghost, he won't
take up much space.
Hey, when the babies come,
are you gonna like them
more than me?
Mason.
I mean, it happens.
People like babies.
Babies are cute.
I spend a lot of time
with babies,
and they can be
quite disgusting.
They got bald,
little pointy heads.
All they do is eat, sleep,
poop, and cry.
I mean, you're way more fun
that that.
Really?
Really. And besides,
we're gonna be the only dudes
in that house.
We gotta stick together.
Right?
Our survival depends on it.
Welcome, mommies and daddies,
to the incredible journey
of childbirth.
Let's start with
some breathing exercises.
Dads, prop up your wives
so they can focus
on their diaphragms.
Just like that.
Good. Get comfy.
Okay.
Now take a slow, deep inhale
through the nose.
Followed by a long, slow exhale
out through the mouth.
Like these people really
don't know how to breathe.
Breathe in love...
and breathe out fear.
Ugh.
For crying out loud.
It's hard for me
to breathe in love
when you're being so negative.
Showtime.
That's what
you're worried about?
Once you bear down to push
an enormous head
through a not-quite-big-enough
opening
that no amount
of kegel exercises
will ever whip back into shape,
you won't give a rat's ass
whether or not
you paid attention
during breathing exercises.
You're gonna be too busy
screaming for drugs
and wishing that son of a bitch
who knocked you up
had never been born.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my fabulous wife.
You're all doing great. Another
five minutes of breathing,
and we can move on
to some ball work.
Which is what got us
here in the first place.
Good job.
Keep breathing.
Yeah, this one--
think maybe a turkey baster.
Oh. Missionary position.
Lights off,
blinds drawn, two minutes,
and done.
What about the creepy twins?
Oh. Sex swing
and a ball gag for sure.
- Shh.
- Are you two going to ruin
this beautiful experience
for everybody?
- Honey, lighten up.
- That's it.
I think it's time
you both left.
♪ Hey, little darlin' ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ you wear me out ♪
Help.
♪ You're suspicious, baby ♪
If I knew getting kicked out
of class was gonna turn you on,
I'd be signing up for adult ed
all over town.
Oh. You'll give yourself a hernia.
Okay.
Do you mind? I'm trying
to screw my husband.
Man, do I love my wife.
Oh.
_
So this, uh, mother
of a patient of mine
asked me if it was okay for her
to be having sex
this far along
in her pregnancy.
How far along is she?
Uh, like, you know,
second trimester-y.
Wait. Doesn't her OB
have that covered?
I don't think she likes him,
and apparently, she saw
this thing on the Internet
of this woman
who experienced sex
and then went into labor early,
- and the baby wasn't fully cooked.
- Dude, it's sick.
I hope that was her word
and not yours.
Did she, uh, did she experience
any discomfort?
- Not that she mentioned.
- Is it a high-risk pregnancy?
It's...
multiples. I think
it's multiples, so...
Oh, really? So, uh, when did
you and Charlotte have sex?
Like a week ago.
What are you doing
trolling the Internet
- for medical advice anyway?
- It's not my fault.
It's Al Gore's fault
for inventing the Internet,
and all those people that
make it this horrible place
where all my darkest fears are
so conveniently realized.
Charlotte is fine.
If anything was gonna go wrong,
it would've happened by now.
But since you are at 22 weeks,
you know, it might be a good
idea to keep it in your pants.
Yeah. Charlotte's not the one
to worry about.
Uh, you're already at what,
stage one daddy freak-out.
- Just wait until the babies come.
- Stop it. I'm a pediatrician.
Yeah, who's worried
that he might induce labor
with his little Cooper.
Okay.
I'm around kids all day.
Charlotte runs the hospital.
- We're prepared.
- No, you're never fully prepared.
Plus, you're having three.
You're gonna be outnumbered.
Dr. Cooper Freedman,
pediatrician.
No, it's different.
- How?
- It just is.
That's deep.
Look, my advice?
Cancel the Internet.
Okay. I make this, I'm gonna be
officially recognized
as the best,
most prepared father
in history of the world.
- Get it! Two out of three. Two
out of three. - All right. Try again.
Two, one. Freedman!
It's been a long time
since I've made a new friend.
You know, a real friend.
And I know by getting a consult
for Ally, I overstepped,
but, um, I think of you
as a friend,
and I wanted to help.
I'm sorry.
We are.
We are friends.
But you have to understand,
two doctors told me
the same thing that
your friend did months ago.
But I...
I couldn't hear it.
So I went to see a psychic--
which is insane, I know--
but she said there was hope.
I understand
wanting to hold on, I do,
but at a certain point...
Was Pete the love of your life?
Ally is.
I was married
to a wonderful man
for eight and a half years.
He was my best friend.
And I didn't know that there
could be more until I met Ally.
And that kind of love?
I can't even tell you
how she made me feel.
But I felt that way every day
for ten years.
Every single day.
And if I pull the plug,
if-- if she's gone,
really gone,
I'm afraid that no one will
ever love me like that again.
And who thinks like that?
I mean, she's the one
lying there, stuck in limbo,
and I'm worried about me.
I'm a terrible person.
When Pete died,
I felt relieved.
I've never told that
to anybody,
never said it out loud.
I mean, I miss him. I do. I miss
him all the time, every day.
But Pete was...
Pete.
He was complicated
and difficult,
and I tried for so long
to work out our issues,
and...
I mean, the thing was,
we don't have issues anymore.
You know, he won't fight,
he won't leave,
because Pete is-- is...
Pete's dead.
The argument is over.
So yeah, yeah, he--
he was the love of my life,
and it-- and it hurts
that he's gone,
but I felt r-relief.
I'm...
I'm relieved.
She is the love of my life,
and I don't feel relieved.
I just want her back.
_
Isaac invited me
to his brother's Bar Mitzvah
next month.
Can I go?
Sure.
Am I gonna have one of those?
Do you wanna be Jewish?
I don't know. Maybe.
Well, that's cool if it's
something you wanna do.
You can pave the way
for the triplets.
We're raising them Jewish?
Uh, I know we haven't talked
about it,
but I was thinking... maybe.
Well, you don't go to temple.
But those traditions are
part of who I am,
and that spiritual heritage is
- something I want for the children.
- Well, so do I,
which is why I think
they should be baptized.
If they aren't baptized,
they won't go to heaven.
Okay, I know I eat pork
and shellfish...
and I don't feel
I need to go to Israel...
and I married a Christian,
so one could argue
that I should be flexible...
when it comes
to religious instruction.
But baptism? No way.
All my ancestors would roll over
in their graves.
My mom took me to church
sometimes,
like, for Christmas,
Easter, too.
Well, those services
are nice, right?
I want the babies to wake up
on Christmas morning
to presents under a tree.
I want to hide Easter eggs.
Okay, I don't think we should
base our children's religion
on what the most entertaining
holidays are.
- Why not? - Because that is
a battle I would totally lose.
I mean, nobody wants to fast
at Yom Kippur.
And you eat matzo
and you don't poop for a week.
Although christianity
isn't all fun and games.
The son of God gets nailed to
a cross and his father loved it.
How does that not give a kid
nightmares?
Video game day.
That would be so cool.
Or we could expose them
to both religions.
- Let them decide.
- Doesn't that seem confusing?
I'm not confused.
Two religions, twice the gifts.
Think about it, Coop.
We got plenty of time.
_
It's too soon! They're only
lettuce! They won't make it!
It's gonna be okay, Charlotte.
It'll be okay.
Dr. Montgomery's
five minutes out.
We'll need a BOA kit
and an OB bed.
And give her nifedipine,
10 milligrams.
I'm only 26 weeks!
You gotta stop the labor!
Addison's gonna take care
of everything. Don't worry.
- Is she gonna be okay?
- She's gonna be fine. Okay?
You remember nurse Fiona? You go
to school with her daughter.
Okay, Amelia's gonna come
and pick you up.
It wasn't supposed
to be like this.
Labor's not supposed to be
for another six weeks,
and I was gonna bring her
ice chips and rub her back
and all the babies
were gonna be healthy
and Charlotte was
gonna be incredibly happy
because she would've known
that I would've done
everything I could to keep her
and the baby safe.
It wasn't supposed to
be like this.
I started the tocolytics,
- but she's still laboring. - Okay,
Charlotte, let's see what's going on here.
What? What is it?
One of the triplets is
presenting as a footling breach.
- We need to deliver right now.
- The lungs ar-aren't developed.
We don't have a choice.
I need three resuscitation kits
and three incubators.
Let the nicu know they could be
getting up to 3 26-weekers.
Okay, Charlotte, we're gonna
start delivering now.
- Okay? You ready? Let's go.
- Okay.
Good.
Good. Good. There you go.
Aah!
Aah.
2.5 tube and a straight blade.
- What's happening?
- Addison's working on it.
- Addison?
- Charlotte, I'm going to examine you
to see if the remaining
membranes are intact, okay?
- Okay. Okay.
- It's okay.
Is she breathing?
Why-- why isn't she crying?
All right. Come on, kid.
Help me out here.
Okay, the membranes are intact,
and if the meds
that Dr. Peterson gave you
worked, then--
- What? Then what?
- The contractions will stop.
Until 32 weeks?
Because these babies
aren't ready to be delivered.
- I can stitch up your cervix.
- What?
That'll delay delivery
for a few weeks,
give the other babies
a chance to mature.
Jake, is that safe?
There are significant risks.
Maternal morbidity in delayed
interval birth is about 30%.
Charlotte could die?
How is she?
She's got ectopia cordis.
The chest wall hasn't developed
completely to cover the heart.
She'll need surgery.
Oh, what do we do, Cooper?
I just-- I don't want
to lose these babies,
but I'm scared.
What do we do?
Okay, look at me. Look at me.
Here's what's gonna happen--
Addison is gonna sew up
your cervix,
and I'm gonna go be
with our daughter,
and this plan is gonna work.
You're gonna be okay.
You're not gonna die.
Okay?
Okay. Say it.
I'm not gonna die.
- Promise me.
- I promise you.
- Okay. I love you.
- I love you.
I love you.
Okay.
♪ You come back home ♪
You ready?
No.
But it's time.
♪ You get back home ♪
Thank you for loving me.
Thank you for being
the love of my life.
♪ I've been like a plug
in your wall too long ♪
♪ Nothing like... ♪
Hmm.
Okay, so tell me
about the procedure.
Well, we're gonna place
a mesh over her chest
that will cover her heart.
Tissue will grow over that.
And then in a year,
she'll need a skin graft.
She's just so tiny. Can we wait
till she's a little stronger
and then do it?
No, she won't get stronger
without the surgery.
Then I don't have a choice.
Yeah.
♪ ...of time this year ♪
Okay. Let's do it.
All right.
♪ Nothing like
a flickering light, oh ♪
Hey, Cooper.
- Hi.
- I just heard.
I'm so sorry.
Thanks.
- I've been a bad friend.
- Oh, stop it.
No, I've been so wrapped up
with Charlotte.
And I'm proud of you for that.
You've been moving heaven
and earth
to get Charlotte through this.
That's your job.
It's good to see a man do that.
I love you.
Love you.
Go see your daughter.
Okay.
Almost done.
I'll need another 4-0 nylon
on a driver.
What's happening?
Heart rate's dropping.
Pressure's crashed.
Scissors. I need to cut
these sutures.
- Come on, Sam. Do something.
- Cooper, maybe you should wait outside.
I'm not leaving.
Come on, sweetie. Hang in there.
Hang in there. Hang in there.
The heart is twisted
underneath the graft.
I need to flip it back.
Come on, sweetie. Hang in there.
Hang in there. Hang in there.
Hang in there. Come on.
♪ Nothing like ♪
Okay. There. Got it.
♪ A flickering light ♪
Pressure's coming back up.
♪ Nothing like ♪
♪ A flickering light, oh ♪
Being a parent sucks.
Don't get me wrong.
Mason's the best thing
that ever happened to me,
but his mother did all the hard
work. She got him there.
I look at my baby and I know
she might not make it,
and even if she does, I hear
Addison saying, "cognitive"
and...
"Neurological impairment."
What does that even mean?
Maybe I should've fought harder
to reduce.
But we're a team.
We are a team, and Charlotte's
lying in a hospital bed,
trying to keep
our other babies safe.
And I don't know
how to do this.
How the hell do I do this?
I need more time.
I'm just not...
ready.
But who gets enough time?
Pete certainly didn't.
Violet didn't get enough time
with him.
My family needs me.
Charlotte and Mason
and baby King-Freedman
and the two heads of lettuce--
they all need me,
because I'm the dad now.
And so it's time to step up
and do my job,
because being a dad is
the greatest gift in the world.
So...
it's time.
Hey. How's Charlotte?
Good. Uh, she tolerated
the procedure well.
Contractions have stopped,
and she's sleeping.
- So are we out of the woods?
- Not entirely.
I had to put her into
trendelenburg.
It could prevent her
from going into labor again.
- And how long does she have to stay
like that? - Probably until she gives birth.
And in that position,
she's at risk for blood clots,
headaches?
Yeah.
She's not gonna be able
to see her baby.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
No. Thank you.
Hey, little girl.
I'm sorry you don't have
a name yet.
Your mom and I haven't had time
to decide.
But whatever your name is,
I need you to fight.
Okay? I need you to stay
in this family.
Because we don't even know
who you are yet--
If you're a science geek
or some kind of crazy,
outdoor wilderness jock
that likes to camp
and rock climb--
two things I hate,
by the way--
but I will gladly take them up
if that's what you're into,
'cause your...
Your dad's gonna jump
right in there with you.
Because you're not even
a day old,
and you have me
wrapped around your finger.
I love you.
And we can't lose you.
♪ Oh, my hero ♪
Hi.
♪ Sit up straight ♪
So...
your mom's Christian,
and I'm Jewish,
and I don't know what you're
gonna choose-- maybe neither--
but I want to hedge my bets.
If your mom's God is listening,
I want him on our side,
and...
Well, Jesus is Jewish, so maybe
we're already covered.
I don't know.
But...
don't tell your mom,
but I stole this
from the chapel down the hall.
And I hope God doesn't hold it
against us.
Okay.
♪ I'm some sick hound ♪
♪ digging for bones ♪
♪ if it weren't
for second chances ♪
Dad's looking out for you.
Okay.
♪ My hands, they were strangers
lost in the night ♪
♪ oh, they're waving around
in that parking lot light ♪
Cooper.
♪ And I'm waiting in the wings
while the trees undress ♪
Hey.
Thanks for bringing him.
Mm. No problem.
I'll be outside.
Okay. Hey, buddy.
Hey.
♪ I'm a ghost in the garden ♪
Can I touch her?
Yeah. Here.
This.
Put your hand in there.
Okay, rub them together.
Okay.
Now reach in there.
Be really gentle, okay?
♪ And I'm running from nothing ♪
♪ no thoughts in my mind ♪
Is she gonna die?
♪ And my heart was all black ♪
I don't know yet, Mase.
♪ Thought that part was yours ♪
What's her name?
We haven't decided yet.
I thought we were
gonna have more time.
Guess we're gonna have to
talk about that.
♪ Blood and knuckles ♪
Hey, little sis.
Happy birthday.
♪ Longing for home ♪
♪ if it weren't
for second chances ♪
♪ we'd all be alone ♪
Charlotte's always been
the strong one,
and I love her for that.
It's my turn now.
Is she dead?
She's alive.
Our daughter is alive.
Oh.
Oh, God.
♪ If it weren't
for second chances ♪
♪ we'd all be alone ♪
♪ mm, mm, mm ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com