Damn it.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
_
Even though I won't be back
in my office until I give birth,
I'm still running things here.
So y'all need to come up
with five ways
to improve
the patient experience.
'Cause I'm here to tell you,
it sucks.
That's it.
Did Addison say this is okay?
She said I had to sray in this
position for 48 hours straight.
Well, this is not bed rest.
This is running a hospital
from a bed.
Potato. Po-tah-to.
How's my girl?
This is an hour ago.
She's so tiny.
Small but mighty,
like her mama.
I think she's getting tired
of "baby King-Freedman"
on the side of her incubator.
- She tell you that?
- Mm-hmm.
I can't name her
until I meet her.
You'll meet her soon.
I promise.
I still like Mathilda.
You're joking, right?
I'm gonna put it on the board.
Don't worry, baby.
He'll call you Mathilda
over my cold dead body.
I wonder if there's asbestos
under there.
Not good for the babies
or any other patient
in this place.
Lord, I'd sell my soul
for arms long enough
to scratch those toes.
Boy, do I need a pedicure.
Charlotte, tell Sheldon
he has to see Nick.
Nick the pedophile?
His name is Nick Calhoun.
Who cares what his name is?
You're talking about a man
who took a 7 year old
from my hospital and did
God knows what to her.
That is the Nick
you're referring to, right?
Why on earth
would you visit him?
He called me, depressed. He'd
been in solitary confinement.
Excuse me, Dr. King.
I need to place another IV.
Get on with it then.
I haven't decided what to do.
Sheldon, he reached out to you.
You have to see him.
Well, now that he's been
incarcerated,
I'm not exactly sure
if he's still my patient
or what my obligation is--
Your only obligation is to you.
Ow!
Have you done this before?
Stephanie.
Go. Now.
And don't come back.
Where the hell we'd find her?
She can't restart an IV.
My 9 year old could do that.
You know, when I went
to see Katie,
I thought it was about her,
but really, it helped me.
How would visiting
Nick the pedophile help Sheldon?
Can you stop calling him that?
The guy who took Sarah Nelson?
Uh, sorry.
Not my conversation.
Okay, look,
we are supposed to help.
I tried to help him
and I failed.
No, he failed.
Now he deserves to rot, alone.
All done.
Do you know...
how is Sarah?
Well, I recommended
a pediatric psychiatrist,
one who specializes
in sexual trauma.
Her parents are
cautiously optimistic.
I'm glad.
I'd like to castrate
Nick the pedophile,
but I'm glad.
I like her.
Charlotte, I'm your doctor.
You have to listen to me.
To stop the labor,
we need to keep you supine
with your legs 30 degrees
over your head.
It's called Trendelenburg.
Dr. Trendelenburg would've had
a lot of fans
during the Spanish Inquisition.
Sadistic bastard.
- Yes, Dr. King?
- It's bad enough I'm living upside down.
Can't I get a decent pillow?
Tough day?
Oh, what tipped you off?
Well, two weeks in bed is
a long time.
That's nothing compared
to the six weeks
I still have coming.
How was school today, buddy?
It was fine.
Oh, can I go get a snack
before I start my homework?
Sure.
So much for today's
mother-son quality time.
He talking to you?
Uh, some. You know,
he's processing everything.
Ooh!
Lucas loves
having him stay with us.
I'm afraid he's gonna demand
an older brother
after you guys come home.
Mm.
I can't get Cooper
to leave the nicu at night.
He looks like death on toast.
You know,
not that I'm one to talk.
Well, you're in a period
of transition,
and the stress related--
Stop.
I don't need a shrink.
Right.
I need for my daughter
to get stronger.
I need to keep these buns
in the oven.
But I don't need a shrink.
Of course, being able to pee
in the toilet would be nice.
Yeah. Well,
I can't help you there,
but if you ever find yourself
on the verge of losing it,
distraction works well.
Some people count to ten,
and taking really deep breaths
can help.
I know it sounds lame,
but it works.
These... are good, too.
Stress balls.
Squeeze them instead of
biting somebody's head off.
It's almost as good
as talking to a shrink.
Can I get you anything else?
These are plenty.
Hang in there, mama.
How long does it take to find
a damn pillow?
_
She's got her daddy's hands.
Pulse ox has improved.
Her heart rate is stable.
I'm gonna teach you piano first
because then guitar's
gonna be a snap.
She's triggering the vent
all by herself.
Wait. What?
She's breathing on her own?
Yeah. I can take her
off the ventilator now.
Is it-- is it okay? Really?
- Yeah. She's ready.
- I mean, we don't have to rush it, right?
Oh, I'm done.
Wow. Okay.
What's-- what's next?
Kangaroo care.
I-I get to hold her?
Yeah. Unbutton your shirt
and sit down.
Whoa. It sounds so different
when Charlotte says it.
Skin-to-skin contact
has been known
to improve oxygen saturation,
respiration,
heart rate.
Here we go.
I'm ready.
Okay, sweetie.
There.
Okay.
Hi, sweetie.
I'm daddy.
You got her?
Yeah.
Oh, my goodness.
Oxygenation's improving.
Look at that.
It's like magic.
Oh, here.
Okay.
Say, "hello, mama."
Hello, mama.
The ball is thrown away...
We've got
better news for you tomorrow.
What'd she do?
What, steal your man?
Run over your dog?
Damn, girl.
You fight dirty.
No hair pulling?
- Huh.
- Is that your baby daddy?!
Huh.
So this is what it feels like
when your brain cells die.
- Oh, hell, no.
- Oh, no, you didn't!
Oh.
You only have to press it once.
What's going on out there?
Work, which I should
be getting back to.
Hey, do you like your job?
Is this a trick question?
- No.
- Then yes.
I mean, I know some people
think that nurses are
just frustrated doctors,
but I like being more hands-on.
Then it's your lucky day.
I'm making you
my private nurse.
No one else here knows their ass
from a hole in the ground.
I'm the Floor Manager,
Dr. King.
I can't cater
to just one patient.
You can now.
Figure it out.
- Off the vent.
- Oh, my God.
- Hi.
Let's see.
I haven't seen you
around here much.
I-I've been busy.
Okay. I'll, uh...
- Okay. Take care. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Okay, uh, I'm gonna...
- Sam, thank you so much.
- Yep.
- You should go, too, Coop. Home.
- Mm.
She'll be okay without you
for one night.
I'll go get some clothes,
I guess.
Damn it.
Contraction.
I think it was, um,
just the one.
No, you've been having
contractions
- every three minutes.
- That was just pressure.
- I don't think it's actually a contraction.
- Okay.
Look, we've got you
on tocolytics
and we've put you
in Trendelenburg.
I mean, we could-- we could add
a magnesium drip.
It's not standard treatment
anymore, but it's worth a try.
It will provide
neural protection
and it might stop
the contractions.
Might? You said 48 hours.
That's all I had to go
without a contraction
to be able to lay flat.
That was my big prize--
not standing up,
not getting to use
the actual toilet,
not seeing my baby.
Laying flat...
I was living for that.
I only needed 16 more hours.
I did not sign up for this.
_
Okay.
Looks like good news.
This is all just a bad dream,
and I'll be home for Christmas
with three healthy babies?
No, but you have stopped having
contractions for two days,
so you get to lie flat.
Ohh, great.
How's that feel?
Ah. Still not the angle I want
to see Christmas from.
Mm.
It was gonna be great.
I was gonna sit my fat ass
on the couch
with three babies cooking
in my enormous belly...
while I drank virgin eggnog.
I'm sorry, Charlotte.
I am gonna keep you
on the magnesium drip
because it seems to be helping,
but if you have
any other contractions, I gotta
put you back on Trendelenburg.
You're lurking.
What do you want?
I'm here
on behalf of the board.
Uh, we thought maybe,
um, given your condition,
maybe--
Spit it out, Lisa.
How do you feel about
passing along
some of
your chief of staff duties,
just
for the foreseeable future?
I have compiled a list
of candidates here.
Have you?
Well, thanks,
but there's no need.
Uh, well, the board is just
thinking of your health.
Really?
That's what they were thinking
when they sent a mid-level
human resources manager
to relieve me of my duties?
You want to know what
the scariest thing in the world
is to an HR Department?
A pregnant woman.
Juries love pregnant women.
They especially love
when we have twins,
and oh, my,
do they adore triplets.
You see, right now,
it seems to me like
my employers are trying
to fire a pregnant woman,
and if that's the case,
I will sue you and them
and the whole hospital.
And the only one
who will still be here
in the foreseeable future
is a very rich me.
You're sitting at the bar,
alone.
I sidle up next to you,
order a Martini.
I'm in thigh-high black boots
and a silk slip
that's not quite
long enough to be decent.
Lips?
Cherry red.
Oh, I love this one.
Mm, you never heard this one.
We don't know each other.
We don't?
Nope.
I touch your hand,
ask you for a light.
But I drop my cigarette,
and when
I lean over to get it,
the slip rides up
just enough for you to see
that I am not wearing
- any--
- Oh, you're killing me.
What if my wife catches us?
Well, is she hot?
Maybe we can all--
- Oh, I gotta go.
- Wait. What?
Wait. Wait. Wait. No, I h--
I-- You can't leave me hanging
like this.
Female orgasms bring on
uterine contractions.
No.
You want two more preemies?
Oh, that's not true.
Please tell me that's not true.
Well, if I can't finish,
neither can you.
I love you.
Drip.
Where the hell's that idiot
from engineering?
I put in a request to fix
the faucet yesterday
and the day before.
He's fired.
When I get out of here,
everyone's fired.
Oh, a pillow can muffle
a gunshot,
but not that damn drip?
8:07. Here she comes.
Look... at... her.
You just know
her name's Ashley.
Enjoy those perky boobs
while you can, missy.
Before you know it,
you'll need a push-up bra
to keep those girls
at attention.
Ow!
Oh.
No.
That's not a contraction.
Gas. That's all.
Just gas.
Who'd they bribe to escape this
hellhole with a healthy baby?
Ow!
Son of a bitch,
that felt like a contraction.
No. Don't go there.
It's probably just-- Ah! Oh.
Okay.
That's four. This is bad.
Very bad.
If this keeps up, Addison'll
put me back upside down,
and candy striper Ashley
will steal my husband,
and the happy family will take
Mason and my baby,
and the faucet
will just keep dripping.
Addison doesn't have to know.
That should do it.
Hey.
Come give me a hug.
Mm.
What happened to your shirt?
I ripped it during recess.
Is that a bite mark?
Who did this to you?
Just this kid at school.
Okay?
He's bigger than me,
beat me up.
Well, you all right?
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
What's his name?
Neal Segal.
Go ask Stephanie
to clean that up. Okay?
Think you can beat up
on my kid?
Think again, Neal Segal.
Let's just find your parents.
What's wrong?
Get this tray away from me.
The only thing worse
than trying to get it down
is waiting for it
to come back up.
I can't wait to see
the Christmas buffet
you put out.
Ugh. How do people
eat this stuff?
Yeah. Too bad one of us
doesn't have control
over the quality of food
in this place.
Hey. How you feeling?
Steph.
Hi.
Same as I was when you
asked me an hour ago.
This one giving you
a hard time?
Oh, it's nothing
I can't handle.
Yeah, well, at least you can
stick her with needles.
Oh, needles.
Okay. Well, I'll let you
get your rest.
Tell me something--
you still into Sam?
That's none
of your damn business.
Well, the least you can do is
entertain me.
No, I may be
your beck-and-call girl,
but I'm not
your social director,
and I definitely
don't have to talk to you
about my personal life.
So you are still into Sam.
Oh.
Your IV bag emptied faster
than I expected.
Really?
Yeah. At the flow rate I set,
there should be plenty left.
You gonna give Sam
another chance?
Your brother wants to have
a party when you come home,
with balloons and streamers
and a clown.
Although honestly,
clowns are a little creepy.
If you need a break, I'm here.
No, I'm good. Thanks.
Her pulse ox is
a little lower than normal.
On these little ones,
it can vary quite a bit.
Yeah. But her heart rate's
been creeping up.
I don't think you have
anything to worry about.
Doctor parents are always
a little overanxious.
Mm.
She's got rhinorrhea
and intercostal muscle
retractions when she breathes.
I'll make a note in her chart.
No, she needs a chest X-ray,
and she needs arterial blood gas
- and nasal washings.
- I will let the attending know--
Okay, you're not listening
to me.
I'm not waiting
for the attending.
I'm a doctor, I'm her father,
and I'm telling you
to go get tests.
You go get
the damn tests. Now.
...Alabama
versus Tennessee.
Whoo! First down, Bama.
Roll tide's gonna stampede
all over rocky top.
Alabama's the Crimson Tide,
but their mascot's an elephant.
Make any sense to you?
That's what volunteer fans
always latch on to
when they're getting
their butts kicked.
Maybe you guys should
just turn it over now.
Too much excitement might not
be good for the babies.
These babies are fine. They got
Southern blood in their veins.
The first one's
off the ventilator.
That's great news, Charlotte.
So you've been adjusting
your magnesium drip?
Yes, I have,
and it stopped the contractions.
And you know how I knew
that would happen?
Because I'm a doctor
and the chief of staff.
No, now you are a patient,
Charlotte.
You can't self-medicate,
Charlotte. It's dangerous.
It's Addison's fault.
She's the one who left an addict
with access to drugs.
Magnesium is not a narcotic.
Nice try.
But since you clearly cannot be trusted...
I am locking the pump.
Tennessee's defense
is gonna have to tighten up
against the pass
or this could be a long game.
I already suspect the worst.
Is it the worst?
Chest X-rays show an infiltrate
on her lungs.
Yeah. The labs?
RSV pneumonia.
We're gonna have to put her
back on the ventilator.
I so wanted to be wrong.
All right,
I can't tell Charlotte.
She's already in hell.
There's no treatment
for this virus,
and w-with a baby so small...
- We're not-- - With a compromised
immune system. She could just--
we're not there yet.
All right, we'll put her
back on the ventilator.
We'll watch her.
We're not there yet.
Are you all right?
Why did you tattle to Addison?
That's-- that's why
you called me in?
'Cause I thought you actually
needed something.
I do. I need to know
why you ratted me out
about the magnesium drip.
'Cause it was
for your own good.
I'm thirsty.
I need some water.
What are you, 5?
It's not my job to jump
whenever you're bored.
- Get me another nurse.
- No.
- You're fired.
- No, I'm not.
You are definitely fired.
Oh, yeah?
You kick me to the curb,
there'll be nobody else
to take care of you.
Every other nurse out there
would sooner quit
than walk in this room.
Okay?
I get that you're uncomfortable,
I get that you're scared,
but you're not the first woman
to have a high-risk pregnancy,
so there is no need for you
to be such a monumental
pain in the ass
and make it impossible
for anybody
to feel compassion for you.
Now I am trying my very best
not to smother you with a pillow
every time I walk in this room,
but you are seriously
trying my patience.
So please,
for your health, for the health
of your unborn children,
do not even think about pressing
that call button again
unless you're in labor
or you're dying.
I completely agree.
Yes.
I assure you,
it's under control.
What's wrong?
If you were paying attention
to our son,
you might've noticed
the bite mark on his arm.
Somebody bit him?
Is he okay? What happened?
He's fine. Apparently,
Mason was picking on
a kid in his class--
Neal Segal.
Oh, come on.
Mason's a good kid.
There's gotta be more
to the story than that.
The principal said Mason was
provoking Neal.
That's why he bit Mason.
- Well, biting's not okay.
- Well, neither is bullying.
Taunting a kid is
just asking for trouble,
and if it happens again,
the principal's threatened
to suspend him.
I will go down to the school.
I will talk to the principal.
No, you need to talk to Mason.
We need to cut him some slack.
He is scared and stressed about
what's going on here.
You need to quit making excuses.
We have to punish him.
He needs stability.
He needs nurturing.
What he needs is a clear sense
of right and wrong,
and if his father's too much
of a wuss to teach it to him,
then I'll do it,
just like I do everything else.
Really?
Well, I'm sorry I've been
in the nicu 24 hours a day,
trying to keep
our daughter alive
and watching Sam put her back
on a ventilator and--
Wait.
What the hell are
you talking about?
She...
She has RSV pneumonia.
Since when?
I noticed something
this morning.
I had them run the tests.
Why didn't you tell me?
I've been trying
to protect you, Charlotte.
Like you're trying
to protect Mason?
You are such an idiot, Cooper.
You are not the only one
trying to keep
this family together,
Charlotte.
No, I am the only one
stuck in this bed...
- Oh!
- every damn day. Just get the hell out.
Yeah. Gladly.
♪ beep, beep, back it up,
what? ♪
♪ lay it down like
a cement truck, what? ♪
♪ standing in the back,
mad like an umpire ♪
♪ try to run, run,
but I'm gonna catch you ♪
♪ gonna pop, pop, firecracker ♪
♪ got you locked in my sights
like a satellite ♪
♪ five, four, three, two, one ♪
♪ bull's-eye, cute face ♪
♪ big... to measure ♪
♪ but the dudes got me
throwing off my vision ♪
♪ drop it down like a bye
from an airplane ♪
♪ red, white, like,
like the tin can ♪
_
♪ what? ♪
Muscles.
Bones. Brain.
They're all going soft
and mushy
and dissolving in this bed.
- ♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of holly ♪ - Oh, God. No.
- No. No. No. No. No.
- ♪ fa, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
- I may not be able to get out of bed...
- ♪ 'tis the season to be jolly ♪
but I should not have to
suffer through a bunch...
of ye olde choir rejects
singing Christmas carols.
- Do not come in here. Do not!
- ♪ fa, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
Stop singing!
"You see, Wendy, when the first
baby laughed for the first time,
its laugh broke
into a thousand pieces,
and they all went
skipping about,
and that was the beginning
of fairies."
You're gonna laugh for me
one day.
You have to.
Surprise!
It's your nonshower shower!
Why aren't you with my baby,
Addison?
Because Cooper is. Hey,
I thought of a good baby name.
What do you think of Olive?
I think
it's a Martini ingredient.
Why didn't you bring
Mason by today?
He didn't want to come,
and Cooper said it was okay.
Well, screw, Cooper.
If I want to see my damn kid,
- that's my God-given right.
- You want a cupcake?
Do I look like
I want a cupcake?
So that's a no then?
Yes, it's a no.
I don't want your cupcakes
or your flowers
or your presents.
What part of "I don't want
a shower" was unclear, Amelia?
We thought that
this would cheer you up.
You know
what would cheer me up?
If you got your asses
out of my room.
Mmm. That's not gonna happen.
Hey, Charlotte,
for patients who are on bed rest
in the same room
for an extended period of time,
- it's natural they develop a kind of cabin
fever... - One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten.
And on top of that, you want
to see your baby girl...
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
It's hard for persons
used to being in control...
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
...take care of things
and them.
Smell that.
Which one's a trapezoid?
It's a square at an angle?
No. No. Wait. That's a rhombus.
All those years in school,
and the only thing I remember
is that cinema class.
By the way,
Elsa didn't love Rick.
Love story, my ass.
Every good romance
ends in death.
Without a plane crash,
consumption,
or third-degree burns,
two people can't just stand
the test of time.
Mama.
Didn't you hear me?
I heard you didn't want
to see me.
I didn't want to get yelled at.
Neal bit me.
Because you provoked him.
And when you push someone
too far, well--
Someday I'll show you
"The Burning Bed,"
and then you'll understand.
I never did it before.
That's not the same
as never doing it at all.
Everyone hates Neal.
He's weird.
Well, that's even worse.
You want to be a sheep?
Follow the herd?
Or do you want to be a man?
The kind of person
who sticks up for others?
Not only did you bully a kid,
which is horrible and cruel
and never okay,
but you lied to me.
- Did you apologize to Neal?
- No.
- Well, you have to.
- Why are you being so mean?
Why are you being so selfish?
I'm the one stuck in this bed.
Your dad's racing between me
and your baby sister
in the nicu.
And instead of being helpful,
you're just acting out.
- What the hell's wrong with you?
- Are you finished?
Don't you get fresh with me.
We still have to discuss
your punishment.
Dad already did. No TV
or video games for a week.
Not a week. A month.
And you will apologize to Neal
and to his parents.
- That's not fair.
- Well, life isn't fair. Get used to it.
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate me, too.
I got your page.
What's going on?
Well, sats are dropping.
BP and heart rate are unstable.
What's her chest X-ray
look like?
Worse. Diffuse infiltrate.
I haven't told Cooper yet.
I want to present him
with all the options.
If we oxygenate the blood
outside the body,
there's a chance that--
No. Ecmo's too dangerous
and invasive.
Well, then what other option
do we have?
I don't know, but ecmo you can't
even do until 34 weeks.
She's still too young.
Plus, there's no guarantee
of survival,
and then you run the risk
of bleeding, infection,
clotting, strokes.
Well, pneumonia presents
just as big a threat.
The ectopia cordis
and the prematurity--
I mean, she's--
she's already looking
at such a hard life.
I-I just...
I don't know if such
an aggressive approach
is what's best for her.
Well, it's not for her.
We'd be doing this
for Cooper and Charlotte.
Do what for us?
It's a long shot, but...
they think that ecmo is
our best option.
How long would she be
on bypass?
A week.
And blood thinners.
So Amelia would do
an ultrasound
every day to make sure
there's not a brain bleed.
And if the ecmo doesn't work?
Well, then our--
our daughter will die.
I thought we'd have this magical
first Christmas with Mason.
Mm, buy the biggest tree
on the lot,
drink hot chocolate,
lie around in our PJs
on Christmas morning,
come up with names
for our girls.
Just be a family.
But now?
I know.
No, you don't.
You've held her
and you've kissed her head
and you've talked to her.
She knows her daddy.
But me?
Our daughter may die before
I ever get to meet her.
Pump is primed.
Venous catheter's in.
Okay.
I got some bleeding here.
What bleeding? What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong, Coop.
We got this, okay?
Hello, precious girl.
This is your mama.
Sorry you don't have
a name yet.
I want so much to be with you
right now,
hold your little hand,
tell you everything's
gonna be okay.
And let you know
you are blessed.
It may not seem like it,
but you are.
I should be praying.
Right now,
I don't even know how.
I can't do this.
I can't just wait around.
♪ The choice is yours,
don't be late ♪
I don't give a crap what
Addison says. I'm getting up.
♪ Take a rest as a friend ♪
♪ As an old memoria ♪
Was that a kick?
♪ Memoria ♪
How the hell am I supposed to
be a mother to all of them?
Ready to release the clamp.
Arterial clamp off.
♪ Memoria ♪
Venous clamp off. Pump on.
Pulse ox is coming up.
Now what?
Now we wait.
♪ Soaked in bleach ♪
♪ as I want you to be ♪
♪ as a trend, as a friend ♪
She's, uh...
she's hanging in there.
♪ Memoria ♪
Can I get you anything?
♪ memoria ♪
This is my fault. All of it.
I was an ungrateful bitch.
I called them tapeworms
and ticks.
I said they were sucking
the life out of me.
I actually hoped
for a miscarriage.
What was I thinking?
I'd give my life
for any one of them.
Is there anyone up there?
Is anyone listening?
You have to take a life,
you take me.
Take me.
Save my babies.
♪ I don't have a gun ♪
♪ no, I don't have a gun ♪
♪ And I swear that I don't ♪
It's clear.
She made it another day.
That's good.
♪ No, I don't have a gun ♪
It wasn't
supposed to be like this.
I'm sorry I complained.
I take it all back.
It wasn't supposed to
be like this.
Oh, no.
This can't be happening.
Oh.
Oh, wait.
Oh, where is everybody?
Please hurry. Please.
You're the worst patient ever.
I-I couldn't hold it.
I'm sorry.
Truth is, you just saved me
from committing a homicide.
You know that new
L&D nurse-- tai?
She's great in the OR,
but the woman has got
to close her mouth
when she's chewing gum.
My mother wouldn't let me
have any as a kid.
Said it looked like a cow
chewing on her cud.
She got that right.
Thank you.
♪ ...have a gun ♪
♪ and I swear that I don't have a gun ♪
_
All right. X-ray's clear.
Blood gas is improved.
Vitals are good.
She is a fighter.
Charlotte's daughter.
Mm.
So now?
Now she comes off ecmo.
She'll still have to be
on the ventilator.
Yeah, but she's stable and she's
heading in the right direction.
♪ Memoria ♪
Aw, Cooper. It's okay.
I didn't think
she was gonna make it.
Mm.
_
Hey, stranger.
Where you been?
Dad hasn't let me do much
since you grounded me,
but I guess that's
kind of the point, huh?
Yeah, it is.
Ask Coop.
I apologized to Neal.
He was pretty nice about it.
Maybe when I'm not grounded
anymore, he can come over?
Oh, that sounds good.
I'm sorry I disappointed you.
Oh, sweetie, come here.
Look,
I know it's pretty scary,
seeing me like this.
I know you got
some pretty bad memories
of your mama in this hospital.
I'm not gonna die like she did.
How can you be sure?
Because I'm pregnant, not sick.
Because I'm too mean to die.
You just ask
any of those nurses.
It's okay to be afraid,
but you gotta talk to me
about it,
not take it out on other kids.
Okay?
Okay.
Good.
Now go over and get me
what's in that drawer.
Do you want some paper?
Nah.
I was running out of ways
to annoy the nurses.
You wanna try?
Do it again.
She's off the ventilator?
For good this time?
Yep. Cooper's holding her
right now.
Oh.
It's good. It's really good.
All right. I should get back.
No. Wait. Tell me more.
I want to know more.
Okay. Uh, well, she's gonna
get stronger every day.
We're back to this again?
I know she's pregnant,
but just let me just get
one good smack in.
Now calm down.
This is a woman worth fighting
for, and I hate most of 'em.
You'd be a fool to let her
get away, so man up.
Okay. You know what? Enough.
Now this is none
of your damn business.
I am a grown man.
I will choose
who I want to be with.
I choose you.
Now I didn't tell you
everything before
because I thought
that you'd run.
And I won't make
that mistake again.
So you've never bought
a Christmas tree?
No, I'm Jewish.
You gotta help me pick out
the right one, okay?
What size?
Big.
Like, how big?
Like, crazy big.
Okay, you guys.
Slow down.
How about this one?
Perfect.
All right,
so what do we do now?
We get a truckload
of ornaments, right?
And then we hang enough lights
to double our electric bill.
We put it in the living room
so it's all set up
for when mama comes home.
That's not what we do?
Well, yeah, but...
it doesn't go
in the living room.
Dr. King?
Well...
I've been waiting for some sort
of a thank-you.
This will do.
Oh, please. You should
be giving me flowers
and gift certificates
for massages
and department stores and stuff
for my house.
These are from the board.
The board of directors
bought me flowers?
I can't imagine
it's because they like you,
so they must
really be scared of you.
What the--
How did you get this
past security?
I told them it was
for the chief of staff.
Santa says you've been
an exceptionally good girl
this year.
Although
I like it when you're bad,
especially when you're wearing
cherry red lipstick.
But it's
not even Christmas yet.
That's the best part. We get
to have two Christmases.
I know it's not exactly what
you had in mind, but...
Thank you, Coop.
But you still have to
buy me presents.
Ready? One, two, three.
Ah.
- Yeah!
- Yay!
I think you found
your calling, kiddo.
♪ dead leaves, dead trees ♪
Thank you.
♪ To ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
Yeah.
These twinkle lights are
oddly soothing.
Mm.
Maybe we should have a Christmas
tree up all year round.
All right, guys, hold up
your hot chocolate mugs.
I want sissy to see what her first
Christmas was like.
Yeah, we gotta name that baby
before she's stuck
with "sissy" forever.
All right, but I'm not budging
on Marjorie.
I do not like it.
Well, let's go back
to the board.
Okay, um...
- What?
- Mama?
- My water just broke.
- The babies are coming?
- Yeah.
We gotta do something.
I'll get a nurse.
- Mase!
- Wait. Let him go.
I don't think they'll answer
the call button anymore.
Oh, my God.
I can leave the room.
This is it. I'm free.
I can sit up.
This is it, Cooper.
Oh, my God.
Kiss me.
All right, I'm gonna need
a surgical tray
to open the cerclage,
two isolettes,
and a nicu team on standby.
Wait. Stop.
Are you okay?
We're almost there.
I need to go to the nicu.
I need to see her.
- You're in labor. - No. No. No.
You gotta go to delivery, recovery,
- and then the nicu.
- These two ain't coming this second.
Now I'm your damn boss.
Take me to my baby right now.
All right, Mase,
let's go get sissy ready.
Oh, my God.
She's beautiful.
Georgia.
Your name is Georgia.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Let's get this show on the road.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com