Well, you're right, Maw Maw.
The old gray mare--
she ain't what she used to be.
You're not gonna believe
what I just saw.
I just watched
an 86-year-old woman
give herself a Brazilian wax.
Try me.
I'm mowing the Andersons' yard
and I hear this commotion.
I look over the bushes, into the park,
and I saw him forcing
his way on top of her.
Oh, my God, Burt.
It was horrible; she was
fighting to get away.
What did you do?
I shouted, "Get off of her!"
He looked up at me with
that caught look in his eye.
He took off running.
Was she okay?
I don't know. She scurried
up a tree and was gone.
Burt... are we talking
about a human?
Squirrel.
Damn it,
Burt, if you're going to come
home with these stories,
you have to lead with the species,
so I know if I should care or not.
Well, that's easy for you to say.
You're not on the front lines
of Mother Nature's twisted playground.
I'm faced with squirrel rapists,
birds ripping innocent
worms from their homes,
and I saw that whole
family get electrocuted.
They were moths.
I bet you'd be crying your eyes out
if it was a family of butterflies.
A moth is just
an ugly butterfly, Virginia.
Racist.
Whoo!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
(in low voice): Do not get
out of that bed, Hope.
You hear how low my voice is?
That means I'm serious.
Good parenting, Jimmy.
Kids will do anything if you just say it
low enough.
(in low voice): Run to the store.
We need some more beer.
(in low voice):
And take 45 minutes.
Your father and I are feeling frisky.
30 minutes should be fine.
Okay, I know it's stupid, but
I have tried everything else.
Okay, Sabrina's here.
I will start the intervention,
but you two promised to help.
Hey, guys.
Enough talk-- it's time
for you to listen.
Now sit down.
You're up, Jimmy.
Okay.
You know I love you, and
as difficult as this may be,
I think it's time
that we have an honest,
heart-to-heart talk
about something
that we all feel is becoming a problem.
Okay, yes, sometimes I eat dirt.
So what? Einstein
ate dirt-- Einstein.
This wasn't about the dirt, was it?
Is this about me mentally
counting the number of words
I say in every sentence?
13.
You know what?
Burt was right;
I should just listen, okay.
We feel you--
once in a while, but not often,
yet more than we'd like,
but sometimes...
Don't pull your weight when
it comes to taking care of Hope.
Sorry, Jimmy, but the baby
would have been a grown-up
by the time you finished that sentence.
I do lots of stuff with Hope.
Yeah, but you only do the fun stuff.
I thought you were taking her
to the dentist.
Oh, did you say "dentist"?
Because we both thought
you said "play in the mud."
I'm gonna grab some towels
and we can clean her up.
W-Where have you been?
We sent you out for socks.
We're late for the church pageant.
We went to the carnival.
Show her what we won.
You're gonna need to buy a
filter and a tank for that
within the next three hours.
Bye, Hope.
Bye, Mr. Swimmy-pants.
Hair, gum.
Bummer.
Okay, you're right.
I do avoid the tough stuff.
It's okay.
You can change.
What if it's hereditary?
What if I just don't
have the parenting gene?
Okay, it's called geophagy.
I sense you have questions.
Go ahead.
(sighs) Do you have to wash
your hands before you eat dirt?
If it falls on the ground,
is there a five-second rule?
Have you ever tried sand?
Is Mexican dirt spicy?
If you swallow an apple seed,
will you poop a tree?
Oh, she's up again.
Oh, it's the fifth time.
(in low voice):
Hope, you have to go to bed.
No.
I don't know what to do.
My voice doesn't go any lower than this.
You want to find out if you
have the parenting gene?
Why don't you spend the next two hours
trying to keep her in that bed?
(sighs)
Okay, I can do this.
Okay.
Hope,
it's bedtime.
I want you to go into your room
and I want you to get in your bed
and I don't want you
to come out until morning.
Okay?
Okay.
(chuckles)
I'm gonna be good at this.
It's killing you, isn't it?
Of course.
I'm a landscaper.
I'm surrounded by dirt.
What if I've been wasting
money on food my whole life?
Did you see that?
Hope went into the bedroom.
She's never done that for me.
Look, don't beat yourself up about it.
You're like a Mr. Mom.
Maybe Hope sees Sabrina
as the Mrs. Dad, you know,
the one who lays down the law.
There are tons of sensitive,
nurturing fathers
raising kids all over America
and on almost every TV show--
except for Tim Allen.
He's all man.
Ooh-ooh-ooh.
Anyway, my point is,
Hope will be proud of you
no matter what you are,
just the same way
you're proud of your dad.
Ugh!
Nope, nope.
I'm still gonna need to pack a lunch.
♪ Oh-oh, oh-oh-oh...
(humming along)
Hey, hey, hey!
(blowing whistle)
VIRGINIA:
Burt.
I saw him.
I saw the squirrel.
Beady little eyes, fluffy white tail?
Yes, he's a monster.
Right there in broad daylight.
He saw me watching,
and I think he liked it.
That little pervert has no shame.
We got to do something about this.
If we don't help the victims, who will?
The possums, the groundhogs?
They're afraid of their own shadow.
Humans are the smartest
in the animal kingdom,
except possibly the dolphins,
but those arrogant bastards
aren't gonna do a damn thing.
So what are we gonna do?
We are going to make it
our life's mission
to catch that squirrel and put an end
to his rampage of unwelcome humping.
This might be the most
important thing we ever do.
Hey, you guys don't see me
as a Mr. Mom, do you?
FRANK:
Not me.
I just think of you as a guy
who's obsessed with his kid--
driving her all around,
making sure her tights match her outfit.
That's exactly
what a Mr. Mom does.
Oh, then, you are getting
a mug on Mr. Mother's Day.
You know, I must concur with Frank.
The James we all know has a tender heart
and a gentler touch,
which is why I always have
you stack the avocados.
So what?
You're a maternal guy
with beautiful, soft hands.
There are worse things you could be.
True, I could be a dirt-eater.
Einstein ate dirt-- Einstein.
You know, I can sympathize
with you, James.
Being raised by two moms,
I wasn't always the strong
masculine authority figure
I am today.
What helped me tap
into my rough-and-tumble
was becoming an auxiliary policeman.
That's why they call me
Badass Barney around here.
No, it's 'cause you have
an unattractive rear end.
It's both reasons.
Listen, James, I'm going
to be on patrol all weekend.
You should come with me.
Oh, that would be amazing,
but I can't.
I got to take care
of Hope all weekend.
No, Jimmy, you should go.
Get your rough-and-tumble on
with Barney.
I could watch Hope till Monday.
Are you sure?
Yeah, of course.
My God, that would be great.
I have a uniform you can
borrow. N-Now, of course,
I can't let you borrow
my achievement star,
but I can show you how I made it.
You're welcome to tag along, too, Frank.
There gonna be a lot of marching,
hanging out with dudes?
Not really.
Pass.
Yeah, little creep's up there
just wagging his big white tail,
not a care in the world.
Are you sure these pellets
won't hurt the other squirrels?
They're perfectly safe.
I use these pellets to relocate gophers
all the time.
The little black pellets
put the gophers to sleep
so they don't suffer
when the little white pellets kill 'em,
but, see,
I always take
the little white pellets out.
So the gophers just go to sleep?
Yeah.
How can you be sure you haven't
accidentally killed one?
I've been trapping and relocating
the same gophers for years.
They summer at the Millers'
and winter at the golf course.
Crafty.
How many gophers?
Five-- Jackie, Tito, Marlon,
Jermaine, and Michael.
(chuckles) Once,
when they were knocked out,
I put a little glove on Michael.
You should have seen him dancing around,
trying to shake it off.
(laughs)
I'm remembering it now.
(laughing):
That's hilarious.
I'm sorry you're missing this.
Me, too.
I'm surprised they haven't
come up with something
that you can plug into both our heads
so we can see each other's memories.
You know, I bet they will.
I bet they will.
(laughs)
What's he doing now?
He's still just dancing around.
(snickering)
(mumbles)
Ha-ha.
Anyone else smell pig?
You know, I'm surprised
that thing fits you.
Wasn't that Barney's uniform
from when he was fat?
I look better coming than going.
Oh.
You and I
are going to have
so much fun this weekend.
(whispering): You want
to go steal some candy
while the fake cops are distracted?
(grunts)
BARNEY:
Well, James,
are you ready to clean up the
mean streets of Natesville?
I just hope you don't come
across any criminal mastermind
who figures out how to do this.
Uncool, Frank.
Don't worry, James.
A good auxiliary policeman
always carries safety pins.
It's the only weapon
we're allowed to carry.
I need you to open it, though.
I always prick myself with the
pointy part and get an ouchy.
So, what do we do now?
Call the dispatcher,
let her know we're on duty,
and she'll give us the
location of our first call.
Eagle Nine awaiting assignment,
preferably not in a hilly neighborhood.
Oh, God,
that's that idiot from the grocery store
who made his own badge.
Shh.
10-4, Eagle Nine.
Patrol South Natesville.
We're expecting some rough
stuff down there this morning.
There's nothing going
on in South Natesville.
I know, but if I make him feel
like a cop,
he gives me
half-priced rump roast.
It's good to know we've got
your boots on the ground.
Sorry, James, I was gonna
let you sit up front and steer,
but sounds like we have
a date with danger.
(bell dinging)
Turn signals... out!
I hope it worked.
Oh, it worked.
Ah.
I forgot how much
Dancin' Dan likes corn.
Let's just figure out which one
is our guy and go catch him.
I don't see him.
Starting to get a weird feeling
like this whole thing's
some kind of trap.
Ooh, there he is!
Get the skimmer ready.
Soon as he hops on one of
those roofied squirrel girls
and gets distracted, we'll catch him.
What the heck's he doing?
Maybe the sick bastard only
likes it when they fight back.
(squeaking)
Ooh, ooh!
Go, go, go!
Ah!
Should we kill him?
We can't kill him.
I only believe in the
death penalty for people.
We should gouge his eyes out
like in the Bible.
You only gouge his eyes out
if he's an eye-gouger.
"Eye for an eye" means you do
to him what he did to them.
Well, I'm not doing that.
I guess we got to give
him life in prison.
Isn't that basically
us having a pet squirrel?
Pretty much.
BURT:
Hey, Jimmy.
How'd the rough-and-tumble
go? Bust any skulls?
Not great. I spent eight hours
staring at Barney's sweaty neck.
And I only got to experience
one real crime scene.
This is... disgusting.
(sighs)
No matter how many times
you walk these streets,
some things will still
turn your stomach.
Now let's put these recyclables
where they belong.
Glass.
Aluminum.
Oh, my God!
That's a foot!
That's a human foot!
(screams)
It's a human foot!
Oh, hold the boat.
It's just a shoe with
a half-eaten burrito in it.
Hopefully tomorrow will be better.
What's with the empty cage?
Lockdown!
Clear.
(whispering): He's still
here somewhere, I know it.
(whispering): Why did you
have a squirrel in a cage?
Clear.
I think he could have gotten away.
(screams)
It's on me!
The claws! The claws!
(grunting)
He's in my ear!
Why did you have a squirrel in a cage?!
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, mostly.
I don't really want to talk about
what he tried to do to my ear.
That squirrel is way too dangerous
to be kept in a house with Hope.
Well, if we can't kill him
and we can't keep him here,
what are we gonna do, release him?
We're gonna have to.
But we can't just send him out there
to be a repeat offender.
I think we have to...
castrate him.
Okay.
I'll get the knockout pills.
You get the scissors.
No, we can't do it ourselves.
Jimmy's missing part of an ear
from a haircut we gave him.
We're not dabbling in tiny testicles.
I'm so happy I'm not really
involved in this story.
DISPATCHER: Would the closest
unit please respond
to 827 Variel Street
for a domestic disturbance call.
Neighbors report lots of yelling.
Hey, let's take that call.
We're not allowed to do that.
It's just a noise disturbance.
With a lot of yelling.
We can handle it!
James, do not.
(grunts)
I really don't think we should!
Damn it, James, I let
you steer as a treat!
If you have any final words
for your testicles,
I suggest you say them now,
'cause in five minutes,
you're gonna be squeaking soprano.
Oh, look, a pet squirrel.
Unusual, impractical, and unsanitary.
(chuckles):
No, no, no.
We're not crazy people
who keep squirrels as pets.
No, we just need to have
this little bastard castrated.
Excuse me?
That little guy's a sexual predator!
He was chasing down the females
and taking them against their will.
Just because they're not
wearing clothes,
doesn't mean they're asking for it.
Hide your cats, hide your mice,
'cause he's raping everybody up in here.
Have you guys ever been
to the zoo in springtime?
Not that we don't appreciate
the vacation suggestion,
but we're in a bit of a hurry.
No, I'm just trying to say
that what you saw
is a completely natural process.
It's how animals mate.
In fact, the female was probably
giving off pheromones to encourage him.
Oh.
I see what's going on here.
Good old boy's club, huh?
Blame the victim.
Obviously we came to the wrong place.
We'll just go to another vet.
But if this little guy dies in
some back-alley neutering job,
it's on your conscience.
I can't let you take this squirrel.
I'm releasing him into the wild.
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no!
He's gonna hump!
Virginia, cover your ears!
If your daughter was a squirrel,
you would never have done that.
(girl screams)
(glass shatters)
MAN: How many times
have I told you
to keep your hands off my work bench?!
All right, you two, hold her down.
We got to do something.
If you don't stand still,
I'm gonna cut off your finger.
Cover me.
Ah! Dang it!
I have to start wearing
my thimble again.
Natesville Auxiliary Police.
Uh, you have the right to
voluntarily open up this door.
What do you want?
I'm busy.
Hurry up! It hurts!
I know! Shut up!
Do you know how to get rid of splinters?
I'm watching my sister's kids,
man; I'm in way over my head.
Give me that safety pin.
♪
Thank you, Officer.
That vet sure treated us
like we're idiots.
We're not idiots.
Of course not.
I mean, even if that is
how animals have sex,
how were we supposed to know that?
Well, you're supposed to be the expert.
You're a landscaper.
Your whole workday is outside.
From 9:00 to noon,
you're in their world.
I don't stare.
I'm not a pervert.
Who do you think I am,
that creepy crow that hangs out
by the playground?
I don't care what the vet says.
Any normal person who saw what we saw
would have hunted down
that squirrel, captured him,
kept him in a cage till he escaped,
and then with no other options,
sentenced him to castration.
We're not gonna tell anybody
about this, are we?
Absolutely not.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I had to bring her home.
I just couldn't do it.
I just don't think I have
what it takes to be a mother.
I mean, God tried to tell me
by giving me narrow hips,
but I just didn't listen.
First, she wanted to watch her
Dee Dee the Dancing Dolphin DVD.
And I love Morgan Freeman,
but somebody has got to
tell that guy that it is
okay to turn down a job.
And when that was finally over,
Hope wanted to watch it again.
And again.
(dolphin squeaking)
And again. And again.
And then she wanted to play
"knock down the block tower."
So I built her a block tower
and she knocked it down,
while she watched
Dee Dee the Dancing Dolphin.
Again.
And again. And again.
(groans)
And then she wanted to
hear Harriet Hugs a Hippo,
which, by the way, is ten
"H" words strewn together
to make sentences, all right?
"Harriet happily hugs a hairy
hippo while a horse hugs a ham."
And how do I know that? Because
I read it to her 20 times
while she knocked down the block tower,
while watched Dee Dee
the Dancing Dolphin.
Again. And again. And again.
And that's when I passed out.
And that's when this happened.
And that is when I started calling
random nannies from my childhood,
so I could go to the bathroom
and drink a peach martini
and read US Magazine.
And that is when I realized:
I'm just like my mother.
You're not like your mother.
You love being with Hope.
You're just better at the fun stuff,
and I'm better at being nurturing.
And it's okay,
as long as Hope has both of us.
Oh, hey.
While I was on patrol,
I stumbled across
someone's organic garden,
and I brought you a treat.
(chuckles)
They grew strawberries in this.
I love strawberries.
(chuckles)
(sighs)
Hope, what are you doing out of bed?
It's late.
Let me do this.
It's the one thing I'm good at.
Hope, I need you to go back to bed
and go to sleep, okay?
No!
Why isn't this working?
I don't know.
Hope, I said it's time to go to bed.
No, Mommy.
She called me "Mommy."
JIMMY: Sabrina may not have
proved to herself
she was mother material,
but by spending a whole weekend
doing all the hard work,
she proved it to Hope.
And while being called Mommy
didn't make all the monotonous,
boring parts of raising a kid
any easier,
it made them worth it.
Of course, the downside was
that once a kid bonds with you
and knows that you love them
unconditionally,
they aren't afraid of you anymore.
(doorbell rings)
Right on time.
Come in!
So, sometimes you have to call
a professional authority figure.
Hope, go to bed this instant!
(gasps)
Well, glad I could help.
I have to head down to the hospital now
and get a statement from Dancin' Dan.
Apparently some sicko drugged him
in the park, gave him a nasty ear infection.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com