Previously on Revenge...
Tell me who hired you
to take my sister.
She's probably dead.
Marco here claims
he set up an account
that was mysteriously drained
a week before Nolcorp
went public.
I'll write you a check.
51% controlling interest
and your continued good faith
as its C.E.O.
The Ryans think your dad
killed their old man.
Is it true some old-timer
nearly bought it out there?
Daniel.
- Ashley.
- Hey.
- Daniel, this isn't what you think it is.
- What is it exactly, huh?
- No!
- Get off me. You disgust me!
We need to discuss
your son's future.
You so much as lay
a hand on my son,
and I will kill you myself.
So it's official.
He's the new C.E.O.
There is no room for you
on the board
unless someone
willingly vacates,
and I don't see that happening
anytime soon.
I'd like to speak to you about
a matter of grave importance.
It's about Daniel.
Power...
Born out of nature,
coveted by man.
Wars rage on,
and victors are crowned...
Ugh!
But true power
can never be lost or won.
True power comes from within.
You're in top shape.
I have to be.
The sun's nearly up.
Round two?
How about we switch gears?
Morning, early riser.
Well,
that's an encouraging sign
given your hard-won
new title.
Being C.E.O.
of a global investment firm
isn't exactly
a 9-to-5 commitment.
Then I promise,
I'll only take a moment of your time.
I gather this meeting
isn't as impromptu as it feels.
The conglomerate I represent
is very particular
about where we invest,
in business and in people.
I agree.
It's important to know
who you're getting into bed with.
Before you delve deeper
into our complex association,
let me suggest you dig
a little closer to home.
Meaning?
You've already uncovered one of
your father's secret assets in Nolcorp.
Apply the same principle that led you there,
and you will find that there's
far more buried inside Grayson Global
than meets the eye.
Secrets that will make you
wealthier and more powerful
than your father ever dreamed.
Morning.
Must have slept through
my alarm.
I turned it off.
You were tossing
and turning all night.
I wanted you to sleep in.
What's going on, Jack?
Is there something
I need to know?
Yeah. I've, uh...
I've been keeping
a secret from you.
Our sea glass?
I was thinking you could
wear it to our wedding.
It's something new
from something old.
It's something borrowed
from the sea.
And something blue.
I love it, and I love you.
Mm.
I'd tell you two to get a room,
but, uh,
look what that led to...
your own little stowaway.
Hey, Nate.
What you got there?
Uh, supplies.
Hey, uh, why don't you put your
hands to better use, J.P., huh?
Maybe wipe down the bar
before we open.
You got it.
Since when do you take orders
from the Ryan brothers?
Just trying to keep
the peace, babe.
They're our partners now.
At least for the time being.
Something's not right
about 'em, Jack.
I can feel it.
Are you going to answer that?
Need I remind you that Daniel
is having his coffee
in your former office
right now.
Yes, an office
he's vastly unprepared for.
Why do you think
the phone keeps ringing?
The investors are probably
in a panic.
They're not the only ones.
The longer Daniel remains in power,
the more likely
the Initiative is to use him
the way they used us
all those years ago.
Daniel's shortcomings will soon
readily become apparent,
and they will just move on.
How can you be so glib?
Because Daniel refuses
to listen to either one of us.
And short of telling him the truth
and sealing his doom,
we've done everything we could
to try and get through to him.
Not everything.
I just got off the phone
with Patricia Barnes.
She and her husband are going to
be spending the weekend with us.
Patricia and Judge Barnes?
The man's weeks away from
a Supreme Court confirmation.
You'd think our home would be
the last place he'd want to be seen.
Oh, but not Patricia.
I just bought us the head table
at her annual Liberty Project benefit.
And why, pray tell,
would you want to do that?
Because her organization
is dedicated
to helping the falsely convicted
appeal their unjust verdicts.
And as a man wrongly accused
of a crime yourself,
this benefit
is the perfect venue
for you to begin
rehabilitating your image.
Well, if they sold stock
in irony,
I would be richer than
the sultan of Brunei.
When Daniel inevitably falters
as the head of Grayson Global,
the board is sure to welcome you back
with open arms.
Well, the question remains,
how do we convince Daniel
to abdicate?
We don't.
Emily Thorne does.
"Dear Mr. Clarke,
"as Dr. King once said,
"'Injustice anywhere is a threat
to justice everywhere,'
"and I'm afraid you've
suffered a grave injustice.
"My position during your trial
"afforded me an inside access
to the system,
"a system I truly believed in
"until I witnessed a man
charged with upholding the law
"act outside of it.
Judge Barnes has failed you,
as have I."
It isn't signed.
Yeah, but I'm almost certain
that James Palmer wrote it.
Who's James Palmer?
The courtroom clerk
during my father's trial.
My father's theory was that
Palmer alerted Judge Barnes
to the one member of the jury
who still believed
my father was innocent.
- And then Barnes passed that juror's name...
- To the Graysons.
Exactly.
I've expressed the court's
heartfelt condolences
to juror number seven and his family,
and have recused him from service.
An alternate juror has been
added to the panel.
The trial will proceed
without delay.
Thank you.
That's Palmer,
right next to Barnes.
He was killed
in a subway accident
three days after this
was postmarked.
They got to him before you.
If I can position myself
in front of Barnes
and raise the specter of James,
maybe I can trip him up.
You'd think if there were any
evidence of judicial impropriety,
that the Senate subcommittee
would've found it by now.
I don't know. Maybe. Maybe not.
Hey.
It's okay.
If you need to leave,
you need to use the back door.
I can't have Victoria
seeing you here again.
Okay.
So glad you could
make it, Emily.
What a lovely view
of my beach house.
I hardly noticed.
You certainly did
the other night.
Well, I do apologize for
interrupting the evening
without your new paramour.
- You said Daniel's in trouble.
- Yes.
I'm afraid he's gotten himself
in over his head
with this new job.
How so?
Running a company
like Grayson Global
requires a ruthless temperament,
and I...
That's not a quality that
comes naturally to Daniel.
It seemed to come naturally
when he unseated his own father.
I assume Conrad
didn't go willingly.
No.
I'm not sure I understand
your concern.
Ever since
your engagement ended,
I've witnessed some disturbing
changes in Daniel's behavior.
He's become petulant and angry.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I knew you would be.
Unfortunately, my son has walled
himself off from me completely,
but I believe that you still have
the power to reach him.
And what makes you think that?
Because in spite of my interference
and your transgression last winter,
I'm of the opinion that my son
is very much in love with you.
And assuming that
you ever loved him, too,
I'm asking you to step in
and help stem the tide before it's too late.
Unless of course your feelings for him
were less than genuine all along.
Of course not.
I loved him very much.
Then remind him of the man
that he aspired to be when he was with you.
Persuade him to drop
his interest in Grayson Global,
and I will stand behind you
every step of the way,
come what may.
You really believe
he still loves me?
I would bet my life on it.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
Victoria.
Robert.
- Patricia.
- Hello.
It's so lovely to see you both.
I'd like to introduce
a very dear family friend
and neighbor...
Emily Thorne.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
Judge Barnes,
this must be a thrilling time for you.
Indeed.
Pleasure, Ms. Thorne.
Victoria,
we are so grateful to you
for offering to host us
while we're in town.
It's a much-welcomed respite
from the hearings.
Well, you're about the only thing
that both parties can agree on.
You're a shoo-in.
From your mouth to congress' ears.
I'll leave you two
to get settled.
Victoria,
thank you for the lemonade.
Ms. Thorne,
I hope to see you again.
Oh, you will.
Emily, you are coming
to dinner tonight, aren't you?
Daniel will be there as well.
Who can say "no" to Victoria?
Don't you think my parents
should pay for
Jack and Amanda's wedding,
considering Amanda never even
called a lawyer
after cartwheeling off
the second-floor balcony?
They'd be stupid not to offer.
Earth to Declan.
Come in, Declan.
Okay.
When Nate and Kenny
come back in here,
I need you to help me
do something, okay?
Sure. What?
Okay.
Mm. Get this.
My mom's latest charity case?
Ex-convicts.
Which is cool, but...
but I don't know.
They're all so damaged.
Prison seems like hell.
What? Did I say something wrong?
Don't, little brother.
She doesn't want to hear about that.
Where'd you boyfriend go
to get more bourbon, Kentucky?
Yeah, you know what?
I'll go check on him.
He probably got lost.
Wait.
What?
You don't want me to hear?
Oh!
- Son of a bitch.
- Okay.
Well, back when I was
young and dumb,
I used to live with a bunch of guys
who were, uh, what?
Purveyors of recreational...
curiosities, shall we say.
The D.E.A. busts in.
They raid the place.
Guess who's the only sucker
at home.
You. Oh, my God.
I went inside for five years
for something
I had nothing to do with.
And I'll tell you
something else.
It isn't like hell.
It is hell.
Seriously,
I never would've guessed.
Yeah, well,
I guess I clean up nice.
Obviously,
your boyfriend did get lost.
I'll be right back.
Wait.
I'll go get him.
No. I'll tell you what...
you stay here.
I'll go get him. Okay?
What the hell
is taking you so long?
Nothing.
It's just really hard to find stuff
with all your junk in the way.
What is it anyway?
Wholesale coffee beans.
It's a side business,
and it's none of yours.
Hey, Grace, if you could hold
all my calls till after lunch.
- Yes, Mr. Grayson.
- Thank you.
Okay.
Hi, Grace. Uh, Daniel have a minute?
I'm sorry. Mr. Grayson's gone to lunch.
You just missed him.
Ah.
Would you like me
to give him a call?
Nah. No, the poor guy deserves
an hour to himself.
Uh, let him enjoy
his sushi in peace.
Actually, I had him down for
a reservation at the Rider House.
Oh, well, even better.
I'll... I'll catch him later.
Okay.
He's headed to Rider House
on Fulton.
Then so are we.
Hurry down.
They're running drugs
through the bar, Jack.
What are we gonna do?
We're not gonna do anything.
What if they'd caught you?
But they didn't.
One of them is always here
when they try to move
that stuff, so I...
how else was I supposed
to find out?
Not by involving Charlotte,
for starters.
I just told her
that I needed to make sure
they weren't
skimming inventory.
Just leave her out of it
from now on.
I want us all out of it
Mr. Duncan is still
in the hospital
after the ass beating
they gave him.
I know, Dec.
I know.
- Do you remember Eddie Solomon?
- Yes.
The guy used to jump me
when you two were in high school.
- He's a cop now.
- Well, that's shocking.
I think I might have
a way out of this.
Fazio.
- Hi.
Hey. I expected you to go
at least a month
before waving the white flag.
Oh. Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint.
I'm here because
I've heard rumors
you stashed away a number
of secret investments
inside the company walls.
I haven't the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
Oh. That's how it's gonna be,
is it?
Oh, yeah, Daniel. This is pretty
much exactly how it's gonna be.
You stole my company.
If there's anything else you're after,
you're just gonna
have to steal that, too.
Ooh.
Speaking of lost assets,
looks like Takeda's boy
is following right in your footsteps.
That Emily's
a real man-eater.
Whatever your problem is
with Daniel,
it has nothing to do with me.
My problem isn't with Daniel.
It's with this restaurant.
You knew he was gonna be here.
- That's crazy.
- Oh, is it?
Because I'm beginning to think
that the only reason
you've been dating me
is so that you can
keep tabs on your ex.
Oh, that is hilarious.
You asked me out.
If I'd have known that
you were this insecure,
I wouldn't have said "yes"
in the first place.
Well, maybe you shouldn't
have bothered.
Believe me, I wish I hadn't.
Good-bye, Aiden.
Don't call me again.
- Are you okay?
- Daniel, I'm sorry.
- Emily, wait.
- What's going on?
What's it look like?
Your ex-fiancée
just broke up with me.
Nolan,
I see you found my office.
Isn't this where I wait to get
my Grayson Global I.D. badge?
When I said I wanted to meet,
I figured we'd get one on the books.
Haven't you heard?
Books are obsolete.
What's up, boss?
I need to know if you can create
a program to identify rogue files
intentionally hidden
inside our computer system.
Oh, listen to you,
trying to sound all... techy.
What am I looking for?
That wasn't the question.
Can you do it or not?
Mm. Only because I want
to make a good impression
my first week on your payroll.
Where's the London Fog?
I thought you two
were attached at the hip.
Probably off somewhere
licking his wounds.
Emily broke up with him today.
Really?
Hmm.
Quelle surprise.
Hey, toss me that pacifier.
Words I never thought
I'd hear you say.
Going somewhere?
Actually, you are.
I'm gonna need you and Carl
to go over to Emily's for a couple of nights.
Give us a minute, okay?
Yeah.
I grew up around
a lot of crappy families,
all different kinds of messed up people.
But the one thing they all had in common?
They lied to each other.
We're not gonna be
those people.
You're right.
The Ryan brothers
aren't good guys.
They rigged it so they could
buy into the bar
and use our slip
to move drugs through here.
They're the ones that put your
dad's friend in the hospital.
Which is why I need you to take Carl
and get out of here tonight.
Jack, we're a family.
I'm not gonna leave you here
to fend for yourself.
I won't be. I reached out
to my buddy on the force.
- Oh...
- He's gonna bust 'em.
Look, they'll never know I was involved.
I know it's not your style
to run away from a fight.
But I invited these people
into our lives.
I need you to trust me
to take them out.
- I do trust you.
- Okay.
- I can't tell you how much I hate this.
- I know.
Me, too.
I love you.
Prince Oedipus
just granted me access
to the Grayson Global intranet
to snoop for him.
It could provide
the access we need
to unearth the Initiative.
Well, that's great news.
Well, lemons to lemonade.
Oh.
B.T. Dubs, I was so sorry to hear about
your breakup with Remington Steele.
Though there really wasn't
enough room
- in your sidecar for both of us.
- Hello, Nolan.
Hey, buddy. Mm.
What? Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
You two...
A fake up?
Color me impressed.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say
Daniel's already thinking...
Make up.
- That's the idea.
- For now.
I still think I can win back
Daniel's confidence.
Well, bros before hos
only works
if he's not still in love
with the ho, bro.
This has nothing to do
with love, Nolan.
I have an opportunity
to expose Judge Barnes
for his part
in my father's conviction.
If I have to play nice with Daniel
for a little while, then...
It's a small price to pay.
- I'll call you later.
- Yeah.
Hmm. Could get tricky.
If memory serves,
the line between...
Emily and Daniel
and the Initiative
has always been
decidedly blurred.
Then you do me a favor.
Help me stay
one step ahead of the boy.
Any information about
the Initiative you uncover,
in particular a woman
by the name of Helen Crowley,
you let me know first.
Sure.
Greg, we're happy to be
a part of your success, right?
- And long may it continue.
- Hello, Daniel.
Oh, forgive me
for interrupting.
Interrupting is the least of your offenses.
- Greg, I'll call you back.
- It's time we mend fences.
And I've come to offer you
my services.
Your services aren't required.
But if I ever need advice
on betrayal,
I'll be sure
to give you a call...
After Dad.
Well, he does have
his considerable shortcomings.
But he did take this firm
from a budding hedge fund
to a pillar of Wall Street,
and he didn't do it alone.
Are you really patting yourself
on the back right now?
I'm simply giving credit
where credit's due.
Where do you think your father
brokered his biggest deals,
in this office
or over cocktails at polo matches
and galas that I hosted?
What are you offering to do, Mom,
throw me a party?
Well, there is
a dinner tonight.
And the next U.S. Supreme Court justice
will be in attendance.
And if you're serious about
your long-term success, so will you.
Oh. Um...
Emily Thorne just became
a major donor
for Patricia Barnes'
pet charity.
She'll be there as well,
if that helps sway
your decision.
You trying to hack into
Grayson Global's intranet?
Not that it is
any of your business,
but I am following the orders
of my child boss...
your pal Daniel.
You really expect me to believe
that Grayson asked you
to hack into
his own company's files?
I don't really care
what you believe, Marco.
I am not the bad guy here.
But if you keep siding
with Daniel Grayson,
the only bad guy here is you.
Nolan, look, we have to stop
doing this to each other.
Let's go get some drinks.
Sorry.
You had your chance.
Ahh. And I'm in.
Good night, Marco.
- Thank you.
- Good evening, Ms. Thorne.
Emily, you look terrific
as always.
Thank you.
I hope this isn't too awkward.
Are you okay...
After what happened today
at lunch with you and Aiden?
Yeah.
Yeah. A-Aiden's a good guy.
He's smart. He's... driven.
But... I don't know.
Maybe he's just not for me.
Well, at least you found out
before it got too serious.
Luckily, the same can be said
for me and Ashley.
Emily. Oh, you're just on time.
Come join us.
Shall we?
I actually audited a torts class
when I was considering
law school as an undergrad
back in... 2002.
- Really?
- Mm.
I didn't know that.
Daniel, it seems
that your tendency
to overlook critical detail
is not just exclusive to business.
Mm. The occasional oversight is far
less damaging than willful ignorance.
Oh, enough, you two.
We have guests.
Oh, a little competition
between men is healthy, Victoria.
After all, it's the foundation
of our great nation, huh?
That's what
my professor said.
In fact, Judge Barnes,
I believe you knew him.
Um, James Palmer.
Yes.
Yes, of course I knew James.
He was a clerk
in my court for a time.
Mm. His accident that winter
shook up the entire campus.
Well, he was a good man.
His passion for justice
was unparalleled.
Patricia, you knew him, too?
Only in legacy.
Which, if I'm not mistaken,
includes the infamous
David Clarke trial.
I own the man's house.
Conspiracy theorists show up
on my doorstep all the time.
To say nothing of
David's own daughter Amanda.
She and Emily have become
quite friendly lately.
Well, no disrespect to your friend,
Ms. Thorne,
but when it comes to that
contemptible father of hers,
believe me,
justice was well served.
Sounds like your certainty
gives you great comfort.
I haven't lost a night
of sleep over the man,
if that's what you're asking.
No, that would be my job.
But, Patricia,
surely the Liberty Project
has been approached
countless times about an appeal.
No.
Actually, it hasn't.
None of my husband's verdicts
have ever been second-guessed
by the organization.
His opinions
are above reproach.
Hence
the Supreme Court nomination.
Hear, hear.
Victoria,
thank you
for the lovely dinner.
But there's much work to be done
before tomorrow's benefit.
I'm coming down
with a bit of a headache.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Should I have something sent to you?
Thank you.
I think I'll join you, darling.
Good night, all.
Pleasure, Daniel, Ms. Thorne.
Sorry for
dropping in on you like this.
The Stowaway's been rowdy.
Carl hasn't been sleeping,
so I haven't been sleeping.
You can stay
as long as you need.
"Broken collar bone,
fractured wrist"?
Whose records are these?
Patricia Barnes.
She's the wife of the judge
in my father's trial.
"Dear Mr. Clarke"...
Did she write this?
I'm beginning to wonder.
It says here,
she had a criminal record.
Join the club.
Her judgment was expunged,
just like mine.
There must be something here.
Apartheid protest, 1988.
- Patricia was a badass.
- Maybe back then.
Wait.
I don't believe this.
That's James Palmer
next to her.
Who?
Barnes' court clerk.
He and Patricia were friends.
Which means,
if she did write the letter,
whoever killed Palmer
believed he wrote it, not her.
That would scare
anyone into silence.
Especially if the threat
lives under the same roof.
Well, since you've already
mastered the links, Grayson,
how do you plan to spend
the rest of your retirement?
Retirement is a long way off, Robert.
This is but a respite from
my stewardship of the company.
Well, it's just
one man's opinion,
but I think a man of your acumen,
wealth, and guile belongs in politics.
Oh, don't go putting ideas
in his head, Robert.
It's the last thing
this family needs.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I have a speech to work on.
As do I.
And one without numbers,
spin, or projection.
I could get very used to this.
Oh, God help us all.
So what were you able
to find out?
Oh... very little.
- Until I stumbled across this gem.
- What?
Conrad has his surveillance system
backed up and archived.
This one's from
the investor's lunch.
- Helen.
- Mm.
I enhanced the image...
And I figured out
the number she was calling.
- Is it still working?
- Well, sort of.
It's voice-activated access.
Problem is, Aiden,
I can't read lips.
I've tried everything from
"integrity" to "interpol"...
Ingredi.
She's saying ingredi.
- It's... it's Latin for...
- "Entry."
Very good.
Ingredi.
Mr. Mathis,
I presume?
Yes.
I've been expecting your call.
I think it's time we meet.
I couldn't agree more.
This one is on the house, doll.
Anything else you need,
you know who to come to.
Thought we were in this
to make money.
And we will when she brings in
all her good-looking friends, too.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're closing The Stowaway
early this evening
by order of the Montauk P.D.
Put your drinks down, people,
and head for the exits.
That means you.
Drinks down!
You're in the deep end now,
Mr. Mathis.
- I hope you know how to swim.
- So it's true.
You're with the Initiative.
You destroyed my family.
Nothing personal.
You realize I'm three moves
away from snapping your neck.
Well, if you do that,
how will you ever
reunite with your sister?
- Colleen's dead.
- Actually, no.
When you murdered her kidnapper
back in 2006,
we realized keeping her alive
might someday prove useful.
Seems someday is upon us.
So tell me, where have you been
these last six years? Hmm?
Ah. Strong and silent.
Good for you.
Bad for Colleen.
Where is she, bitch?
One more step and it's all over.
Next time we meet,
you bring your manners,
and I'll bring an offer.
You mention this meeting
to anyone,
and you'll never see
your sister alive again.
Good-bye, Mr. Mathis.
Well, since it looks like
we're gonna be here a while,
I'd be happy to grind up
some of those
fine columbian coffee beans
for you officers.
No narcotics here, Sergeant.
Dogs would've found it.
Check the slips.
Nolan, happy Thanksgiving.
What is all this?
Because of me, we never had
a chance to have this dinner.
And I...
I need you to understand...
No, Marco. You knew me.
Oh, yeah, you knew me
better than anyone else.
Did you really think that I
would aid and abet a terrorist
or... or greedily keep
a young girl's inheritance, really?
I want a chance to start over.
And there are
so many reasons why...
that's never gonna happen.
Not the least of which being,
ha, I've fallen
for someone else.
Then I will wait.
I'll wait as long as it takes.
What's this?
This is the most powerful
piece of coding I've ever seen.
Wait. Carrion?
I found some reference docs
while I was cleaning up
the system files today...
No, no, no.
This program is cyber-plutonium.
I abandoned that project
for a reason.
Maybe it's time you revisit it.
This could be the most important
R&D in the industry,
a useful weapon
against your enemies,
or... in this case,
your parent company.
Look...
Like I said...
I'm in your corner.
Well, I'm assuming
that Conrad's speech
will be coming before yours.
Can we also assume
that Patricia will be
introducing him?
Oh, I'm afraid my wife's
migraine has not subsided.
She'd prefer to stay out
of the spotlight if she can.
Conrad will have the honor of
introducing himself tonight.
Happily.
There you are.
Didn't think they'd let you in
after last night's sparring match.
Well, you'd be surprised
what people will put up with
when you agree to be
a platinum-level donor.
Speaking of,
I'm sorry things got
so intense at dinner.
Oh, don't be.
It was a nice reminder
how passionate
Emily Thorne can be.
I'm gonna go apologize.
You love breakfast for dinner.
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's just gonna suck
when you burn this boat down.
You need to relax.
Freeze!
Montauk police!
Declan, what's going on?
Don't move!
Patricia.
I just wanted to apologize
for last night.
I didn't mean to...
insult you or your husband.
He seemed quite upset.
A man in his position learns to
keep his temper to himself.
Last I checked,
migraines don't cause bruising.
Victoria mentioned that I'm close
with David Clarke's daughter Amanda.
After...
she lost her father,
Amanda was...
forced into
the foster care system.
She ended up in a number
of abusive homes.
That letter gave her the hope
she needed to survive.
The thing is,
she thought it was written
by James Palmer.
No, it wasn't.
He wouldn't
have left it unsigned.
He was brave.
That letter saved
Amanda's life.
Tonight you have the opportunity
to save a whole lot more.
Maybe even your own.
We found narcotics
and a handgun hidden in the bilge.
Oh, my God.
My brother gives you a pass.
This is how you repay him?
What pass?
Declan, what's he talking about?
The kid broke into my brother's
house a couple of months back.
We never said anything 'cause
Kenny figured he learned his lesson.
Obviously, he got it wrong.
Declan Porter,
you're under arrest...
No, wait! Wait, wait.
Stop. It's mine.
- Jack.
- All of it.
- Jack!
- The boat's in my name.
My brother had no idea
there were drugs hidden on it.
Then, Jack Porter,
you're under arrest
for possession
with intent to distribute
and possession of a firearm.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney...
To be falsely accused
is a gut-ripping experience.
And that's why I plan
to redouble my efforts
to help the wrongfully accused
by donating not only my finances
but my time
to the Liberty Project...
With the hope
that someday we may truly
live in a world
of liberty and justice for all.
Thank you, Conrad.
Ladies and gentlemen,
allow me to introduce my wife...
Patricia Barnes.
Thank you.
A man far wiser
and braver than I once said,
"There may times when we are
powerless to prevent injustice,
but let there never be a time
when we fail to protest."
When I was in law school,
I met a man named James Palmer.
He was young and bright-eyed,
full of hope and integrity.
Robert hired James
to be his court clerk
during the trial
of David Clarke.
For years after the trial...
James had wanted
to come forward
with information that,
at the very least,
would've resulted
in a mistrial.
But out of concern for my safety,
he kept that dark secret hidden.
Three days before his death...
That secret came out
in a letter
written to Mr. Clarke
in federal prison.
"Dear Mr. Clarke,
I'm afraid you have suffered
a grave injustice."
Patricia.
Robert.
"My position has provided me
"unparalleled access
to the system.
Judge Barnes has failed you,
Mr. Clarke, as have I."
You see, what James knew
is what Judge Barnes knew,
which is that
the verdict rendered
in the David Clarke trial
came from a tainted jury.
I believe that this letter
cost James the ultimate price.
But James didn't write it.
I did.
And today my husband,
Robert Barnes,
stands to inherit
a great deal more power.
And...
The greater the power,
the greater the potential
for abuse.
My wife and I are shocked
to learn the true nature of a man
we all thought we knew,
and I pledge to pool my resources
to ensure Judge Barnes' wrongdoings,
both judicial and domestic,
are avenged.
Rest assured,
justice will be served.
Thank you.
Hello.
Hello, Daniel.
I saw you and your family
had another interesting public evening.
Well, except this time,
the press may actually work
in my father's favor.
How are you faring in your hunt
for those
elusive Grayson assets?
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you sent me
on a wild goose chase.
You turned to Nolan Ross
for his assistance,
am I correct?
Yeah.
In doing so, Mr. Ross left a trail
of digital breadcrumbs,
a trail your I.T. department
will be able to follow right back
to Nolcorp and its secrets.
One in particular,
I think you'll find very lucrative.
I'm listening.
- Charlotte get home all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, not without a lot
of explanation, though.
She deserves it
after a night like this...
Your boat impounded,
your brother arrested.
Jack's a good guy, taking the fall.
Kenny, you know
that wasn't our stuff.
I'm sorry for what happened.
Truly.
Hey, whoever called the cops today
made a huge mistake.
I just hope that they come to their senses,
or things might get worse around here.
A lot worse.
Kenny, you coming?
Oh, uh, Declan, be a pal, huh?
Clean up a little bit.
Hello.
- Amanda. Uh, hey, it's me.
- Jack, you okay? What happened?
The police found drugs and a gun
on the Amanda.
I'm in jail.
Jack, oh, my God.
Don't... don't worry.
I don't want you to worry.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- I gotta go.
- Time's up, man.
- I love you.
- Come on. Let's go.
Power can be hoarded
by the mighty
or stolen from the innocent.
Ems,
I'm gonna take a shower.
Okay.
Power provides
the ability to choose...
But has a proclivity
for corruption.
Daniel.
Hey. Do you have a second?
Yeah.
Sorry to stop by unannounced.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. I just...
I tried to tell you this earlier,
but of course
my mother interrupted.
It's what she does.
I wanted you to know,
the reason I fought so hard
to become C.E.O.
was to set things right.
You see, the only thing larger
than our company's
image problem
is our charitable foundation.
Emily, you're the most
philanthropic person I know,
and I could really use
your help
steering our resources
in that direction.
- Well, I'm flattered, but...
- You don't have to answer now.
Just tell me
you'll think about it.
Daniel.
I don't need to think about it.
My answer's "yes."
The use of power is not
to be taken lightly...
For it is never
without consequence.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com