Previously on Revenge...
Mr. Grayson here made some kind
of deal with the court.
Helping you would be beneficial
towards restoring his public profile.
Daniel's adding a new feather
in the company cap.
Stonehaven United.
- Nolan Ross is hiding the Carrion program.
- We're counting on you.
Helen Crowley
made contact with me,
- told me that my sister's still alive.
- Then we need to draw her out.
(Gasps)
(Gunfire)
- Who were those guys?
- I have my suspicions.
- Brava.
- Now let's see if she buys it.
(Emily) Every human is born
of collusion.
We come into this world
the result of a covenant.
Sometimes made of love...
Sometimes of circumstance...
But almost always
made in secret.
(Newspaper rustles)
I have to assume that you're reading
that rag at that decibel for my benefit.
What in this house
isn't for your benefit, dear?
Though I did catch wind of some news
that I'm sure will interest you.
Jason Prosser is vying
for Stonehaven United.
Now that's a lead
from the Initiative
you were once
in sole possession of.
Well, what are you implying,
Conrad?
That you're trying
to subvert the deal
to prove Daniel's
incompetency to Helen.
Don't get me wrong.
I approve of the plan.
Just not with your visibility.
I've had my communications director
assemble a Montauk dossier.
As I go forward with my plans
to clean up the docks,
I expect you by my side
as the wife you've recommitted to be.
So you're still using
Amanda Clarke's hardships
to feed your delusions
of one day occupying
the governor's mansion?
Morning, all.
Darling, Happy Birthday.
- Thanks, Daddy.
- Just don't spend it all in ten places.
Sweetheart. Oh.
Is it possible that I have
a 24 and 18-year-old?
- Where does time go?
- And where is Daniel?
Oh, believe it or not,
he's already in the office.
So driven that apparently
he forgot his little sister's big day.
- Good morning.
- Oh, good morning.
Charlotte, would you
excuse us for a minute?
It seems that the cat
has dragged itself back in.
- There's the report you requested.
- Thank you.
So this is the new
communications director?
Don't you know that politicians
tend to keep their concubines
in the closet?
Spoken like a woman that
no one is sleeping with.
You'll be happy to hear
that Ms. Davenport and I
have put our past behind us,
and we are now
looking to the future.
Well, I can only imagine what kind
of horrifying footage that will yield.
You look like
the loneliest man in the world.
First I'm banned from Grayson Global,
now your house.
How long till our scheming
gets me banned
from the Hamptons entirely?
That's why I called.
I needed an honest moment.
I miss you.
Me, too.
As most of the time
I'm with you,
I'm resigned to playing
the jealous ex.
Well, you played it perfectly
last night.
Thank you.
(Chuckles)
How are you doing with it?
As well as a woman
leading on her ex-fiancé
can possibly feel
about herself.
He's taking me to lunch,
to a new oyster bar.
Oysters. Subtle.
Hey, well, at least our
mission is on track.
Aiden, I know how hard
it must be,
waiting for a lead
on your sister,
but until they give you
proof that she's alive...
I can subsist on hope,
which is more than I've had
for the past decade.
So what's your next move?
Unfortunately, it's not mine.
It's Helen's.
She's holding all the cards.
Whatever happens,
we're gonna figure it out, okay?
I promise.
I know what you're up to.
You had the seller
stage this place
with all my favorite decor,
didn't you?
Anything to end
your never-ending house hunt.
You've hated
all the other places
for the most nit-picky reasons.
Well, we've only looked at...
twelve.
At an average of
20,000-square-foot per,
- which adds up to...
- A marathon.
I see your point,
and I think...
I do love this house.
Great!
I'll call the agent.
And this can be yours tomorrow.
Okay.
What's wrong now?
Well, the key...
it's a little... pedestrian.
Okay, 'kay, 'kay.
Well, nothing's perfect.
Except maybe you.
(Emily) I thought
we were going for lunch.
(Daniel) We are.
You love Kumamotos, right?
Well, they're only fresh
on the west coast,
and since the oysters
can't come to us...
No, I know
what you're gonna say...
we gotta take this slow.
But Stonehaven wants face time
with everyone in the running,
and I'm at my best
with you by my side.
Daniel...
(Sighs)
I can't just pick up and leave.
I didn't even bring
anything with me.
Don't worry.
I packed you a bag.
I even bought you a couple
of new outfits for Los Angeles.
It's all on board.
Listen, Em...
You helped me land
Takeda Industries and Nolcorp.
But this is
my first real play as C.E.O.
Help me make it a trifecta.
Please.
Great.
Now I promise,
this is a business trip.
All right?
We can take it as slow as you like.
Unless...
Easy, tiger.
Let's get Stonehaven first.
Then we'll decide
how to celebrate.
(Alarm chirps)
You could've just called.
That's so impersonal
after all we've been through.
And besides,
it's in my best interest
to keep the ball in my court.
I have my suspicions
you were behind
that little stunt
at the wine auction.
Oh, you flatter me.
If you recall,
they gassed us both.
A perfect cover for your partner
to run the interrogation.
You and Victoria Grayson
have much to gain
by working together...
You to save your sister,
she to save her son.
I assure you, I had no part
to play in our abduction,
nor would I ever collude
with that woman.
I work alone.
And until I see proof
of my sister's well-being,
that's how it's going to stay.
(Beep)
(Man) What's your name again,
darlin'?
Colleen.
That right?
You got a family somewhere?
I have a brother.
What do I have to do?
Kill Victoria Grayson.
You have 24 hours.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
(Conrad) Not only
do I appreciate your plight,
it may surprise you,
Mr. Porter,
but we have
a considerable amount in common.
We're both entrepreneurs,
both in
complicated relationships.
We took over
our father's businesses,
and we inherited their sins.
Clearing the drug charge won't
be a problem for my lawyers,
but murder...
(Sighs)
Jack didn't kill anybody.
We know, but we also know
that the gun used
to kill Joe Ryan
was registered to his father.
I thought that's why we were here,
so you could help us with that.
Or is it the other way around?
Are we just the poster children
for your new public image?
Oh, you mean do I have a
selfish motivation for this? You bet.
See, my daughter chooses
to spend her leisure time
in your
questionable establishment,
putting herself in harm's way.
It's a concern I'm sure
you share for your son Carl,
a child proudly named
after the man
whose legacy you're willing
to go to jail to uphold.
The shooter's name
is Matt Duncan.
The Ryan brothers put him
in the hospital
trying to get him to talk,
but he wouldn't break.
I'll get the authorities
on the line.
No, look, without Matt Duncan,
my dad would've lost
The Stowaway six years ago.
He protected us then.
I'm standing by him now.
(Conrad) Oh, I can see
we're both stubborn, too.
But unlike you, Mr. Porter,
I value self-preservation and the living.
I'm afraid
I'm unable to help you
if you're unwilling
to help yourself.
Feel free
to show yourselves out.
I knew this was a mistake.
The only mistake
being made here is yours.
Father's friend or not,
Matt Duncan is a murderer.
If you don't call him out,
Carl loses his dad,
and I lose my husband...
(Crying)
Assuming I even get to call you that
before they lock you up.
(Sobs)
(Woman)
After the Northridge Quake,
my father was inspired
to use the profits
from our military contracts
to create a privatized
disaster-relief firm.
Stonehaven and its employees
meant everything to my father.
And I'm not interested
in handing it over to someone
with plans to break it up
and sell it for parts.
Believe me,
that's not my intention at all.
Forgive me, but your company's
rather dubious reputation
doesn't offer much comfort.
Well, I think we can all agree
that Grayson Global needs its
own kind of disaster relief.
Why don't you mention what we
were talking about earlier?
Right. My goal is
to re-brand our image
so that the "global" refers
to world view,
not world domination.
(Chuckles)
Thank you for your candor.
And I can tell you
that your bid is on top
of a very short list
of competing offers.
Well, thank you very much
for this opportunity,
Ms. Carlisle.
It's been a pleasure.
- Lovely to meet you.
- You, too.
You see?
If it weren't for you,
I may have lost her just now.
Thanks for the assist.
Well, we haven't won yet.
But it's looking up.
Should we head to the hotel?
(Objects rattle)
(Cell phone vibrating)
(Beep)
Yes.
The pieces of the puzzle
are beginning to come together,
Ms. Lahari.
All but yours.
I'm doing everything I can.
Remember what's at stake
for you
if you don't find
the Carrion program.
Not a moment goes by
that I don't.
You're one of many irons
I have in the fire.
Don't give me a reason
to pull you out.
(Objects rattling)
Looking for... something?
Damn.
I was trying to hide this
so you'd find it later.
I can't do anything
about the pedestrian key,
but I can change
what you keep it on.
His name is Hanuman.
He's an avatar of Shiva
and a deity that wins
against demons and bad spirits.
He'll keep you safe
in your new home.
You stopped listening at "avatar,"
didn't you?
I heard every word you said.
Thank you...
For always looking out for me.
(Amanda) Happy 18th, Charlotte.
(Laughs)
From your nephew.
Aw.
It's Carl's little handprint.
- It's so sweet.
- 18 is a big one.
You're independent, free.
In my case, I literally was,
since that was the year
I was released from juvie.
It was also the year
our dad died.
Yeah...
It was.
I wish I had known you then.
I can't imagine
what it was like
to lose the only family
you had.
Speaking of...
Where's yours?
Daniel forgot.
My father is hopefully getting
the Ryan brothers
out of your hair,
and I'm meeting my mom
in the city tonight for the ballet.
It's kind of a tradition.
(Cell phone ringing)
Speak of the devil.
(Beep)
So what's the program tonight?
I pray it's Balanchine.
(Victoria) Well,
that's just it, Charlotte.
Everything's okay,
but I had to leave town suddenly,
and I won't be back
until tomorrow.
But I promise
to make it up to you.
Are you serious?
You do know that I love you,
don't you?
- Yes.
- Good.
Then keep that
close to your heart
till I get back tomorrow.
(Beep)
What does it mean when your mom
cancels your birthday?
I'd say it's her gift to you.
I guess being a Grayson
just means learning to live
with disappointment.
You're not a Grayson.
Not really.
Victoria?
(Laughs)
I'll get right on it.
Jason.
I am peeved with you.
It seems
that you've thrown your hat
to the Stonehaven ring.
Simply my compulsion
to leave no stone unturned.
Well, then as a major
shareholder of Grayson Global,
let me disabuse you
of your pessimistic outlook.
Aren't you still
my competition?
Business makes
for strange bedfellows.
My son,
though well-intentioned,
is not ready
for this acquisition.
So I'm here to protect
the family business.
There's something
you're not telling me.
Only that you would make an
excellent steward for Stonehaven.
(Chuckles)
And should that come to pass,
I hope you'll allow me
to thank you later.
As for now,
I have a meeting to get to.
Oh, you're not serious.
I can't believe you.
You crossed the country
to lure that rat
into helping you.
I just bumped into him.
- Oh.
- I'm here for you, Daniel.
Although I see that you
brought reinforcements.
Yeah, it's nice to have
someone's unconditional support.
Well, then allow me
to offer you mine.
Now if your intention
is to rehabilitate
Grayson Global's image,
I would encourage you
to not go through
with this acquisition.
Why, because I'll affirm
my standing as C.E.O.?
No, quite the opposite.
These disaster-relief companies
swim in dirty pools,
and Stonehaven is no exception.
They're not humanitarians.
They are profiteers.
Are you really trying
to take the moral high ground?
(Lowered voice)
Have you forgotten what you are,
what you've profited from?
I suggest you that you
do your research
- and find out why these people want you to...
- You want me to do my research?
You should probably go upstairs
before you say something
you regret in public.
- Think about it.
- Yeah.
I assume, per our agreement,
you're here to dissuade my son
from going through
with this acquisition?
You need to explain to me
exactly why
you are so set against it.
Did you not understand
a word I said?
This is not
in Daniel's best interest.
And unlike my son,
Prosser can hold his own.
Now he's sitting on the fence,
and I'm here to push him
in the right direction.
(Cell phone auto-dials)
(Phone rings)
(Line clicks)
(Aiden) There you are.
Aiden,
listen, I don't have
a lot of time to explain,
but Daniel decided to
sweep me off to L.A.
to help him get Stonehaven.
And I'm sure he thinks
you'll seal the deal
in that blue dress
you're wearing.
Behind you.
(Beep)
What the hell
are you doing in L.A.?
Funny, I thought the same thing
when I saw you
in the lobby with Daniel.
You're saying
you didn't follow us?
While I'm not thrilled
your lunch date
turned into a change of time zones,
I do trust you, Emily.
Then what are you doing here?
Helen found me.
Our little ruse
at the auction worked.
She believes Victoria's
behind everything.
Now she wants proof
of her meddling
with the Initiative's plans.
How can I help?
Go back to New York.
If they believe you're
in league with Victoria,
it could have
dire consequences.
I can't leave, Aiden.
If Daniel loses Stonehaven,
we lose our link
to the Initiative.
Well, then our missions
are at odds.
(Sighs)
Maybe not.
Prosser knows
that I'm with Daniel,
so I can't dissuade him,
but maybe you can.
To what end?
Making Stonehaven
a sure thing for Daniel
forces Victoria
to expose her true intent.
And if I'm successful,
you'll go?
I'll have no reason to stay.
They release you?
Oh, hey.
No, uh...
Insurance ran out,
so I figure I'd give my girls
a chance to take care
of the old man.
How you doing, Jack?
Not so good.
The Ryans framed me
with a drug charge.
I was arrested,
and the police
found a gun on my boat.
And since
it's a murder weapon...
I told you
to stay away from them.
You should've listened.
That's not gonna change
the past, Matt.
They're gonna pin
Joe Ryan's murder on me.
Do you understand that?
The one that you're guilty of.
And you want me to confess?
I know this still weighs
on your conscience,
or you wouldn't have told me
you did it.
You don't know what it's like
to have someone
hurt your child.
And, yeah, it weighs on me.
But I learned to live with it.
Wish I could say the same
for my dad.
You heard about
what happened, right?
Heart attack at 52.
My kid never got a chance
to meet him.
You want him growing up
without a father, too?
- Another copy of my room key, please.
- Okay.
Always the sign
of a good visit.
Now you already know this,
but that Forbes cover
did you no favors.
Airbrushes
are for super models.
Last thing I need
is for people believing
I've gone soft.
The man who shorted
the sub-prime collapse?
No chance.
So, uh,
what brings you to L.A.?
You know who I am.
What do you think?
That you're here
for Stonehaven.
My boss has a significant interest
in Grayson Global.
He sent me
to monitor negotiations.
Right. Satoshi Takeda.
I recognize you
from the wine auction.
Mm-hmm. I...
I did read the Forbes piece
about your passion
to acquire businesses
that are good for the soul.
Is... is that for real?
It's my new philosophy, yes.
Well, then there's something
you need to know.
A friend at the D.O.J.
informed me
that Donna Carlisle is looking
to dump her father's company
in advance of an indictment,
and the lucky winner
inherits the lawsuit.
Why are you telling me this?
Professional respect...
And for my soul.
But look on the bright side.
More time to spend with
whoever's getting that key.
(Beeps)
Get me Donna Carlisle.
It's Jason Prosser.
I'll have your oldest scotch.
Neat.
You have my father's tastes.
And your father would've been
Joe Ryan, correct?
Yeah, his name came up
when I was at the Montauk P.D.,
helping to clear your partner's
bogus drug charges.
Hey, does the name
Matthew Duncan ring a bell?
In this envelope
is Mr. Duncan's confession
to your father's murder.
I'm gonna make this...
(Whispers) very easy for you.
(Normal voice)
There's $50,000 for your signature
and a swift departure.
Oh, come on.
Haven't you put
these boys through enough?
(Knock on door)
Hi.
Victoria.
I wanted to find out
how the meeting went.
And I see I have my answer.
Were you planning on leaving
without saying good-bye?
It seemed consistent
with your aversion
to open communication.
Some guy in the lobby
told me about Stonehaven's
pending lawsuit.
- Well, then you were lied to.
- Over and over, it seems,
starting with the moment
you began priming me
for this sour deal
in the first place.
- I'm no one's rube, Victoria.
- No, you're not.
You've always had a strength
and clarity of purpose
that I admired
from the first day we met.
And I remember the night...
Conrad parading you
around that party
at the governor's mansion
like he owned you.
But you're no one's possession,
are you?
No.
Least of all Conrad's.
The next morning,
the David Clarke scandal broke.
That's right.
David made himself vulnerable
to the wrong people.
The same people who are about
to take hold of my son.
Unless?
Unless you win Stonehaven.
Jason, please.
I beg of you.
I don't want Stonehaven.
What I want is you.
But you've known that
all along.
(Clicks)
Do what I ask...
And I'm yours.
(Keypad clicking)
(Chimes)
- Hey.
I'm so glad Prosser bowed out.
Finally gives us a chance
to relax.
Well, we always did
make a good team.
And this time I promise
to appreciate it.
I don't want to lose you again.
Daniel, please...
No, no, whatever it was,
I'm... I'm not
that guy anymore.
I'm just happy that
you're giving me a chance
to prove it to you.
What's in the bag?
Oh, it's a present
for Charlotte.
For her birthday.
Oh, my God.
I completely forgot.
Well, it can be
from both of us.
- To teamwork.
- Teamwork.
(Cell phone rings)
(Ring, beep)
Hey, Donna.
Come to a decision yet?
Right.
No, no. Yeah. No.
I understand.
Yeah, best to be cautious.
No, we'll see you at 8:00.
All right.
(Beep)
Prosser's back in the game.
What?
I'm sure my mother did
whatever she could
to keep him
wrapped around her talon.
Carlisle wants to hear final pitches
side by side tonight,
only I've already
said my piece.
About Stonehaven.
But not about your competition.
(Rings)
(Sighs)
(Ring)
(Beeps)
Hey, big honcho.
Or is it head cheese?
Listen, Nolan, I need a favor.
I'm in L.A.
and under a time crunch.
You think you could do
a little digging for me
- on Jason Prosser?
- Sure.
Uh, question is, why would I?
Because you're my employee.
And your friend Ms. Thorne
suggested you...
Might be able to access
the inaccessible.
Did she now?
- I'll get right on it.
- Thank you.
Please stay on the line.
Your call is very important to us.
(Clicking)
(Chimes)
(Mouths words)
You sold our stake in the bar?
What the hell
were you thinking?
That it's time
to put this to bed.
Matt Duncan confessed.
That's what we wanted.
That's not what Dad wanted, Ken.
He made plans for us,
which the Porters
and the rest of these bottom-feeders
on these docks cut short.
Trying to turn these docks
into anything more
than what they already are
is a waste of time,
especially now that they've got
Conrad Grayson on their side.
Conrad Grayson
is a businessman.
And I'm gonna convince him
to sell The Stowaway back to us.
I'm gonna make Dad proud, okay?
With or without your help.
And simply put,
my goal is for Stonehaven
to continue on
the same path ideologically.
That is exactly my hope.
Personally,
I admire your mission
to protect
your father's legacy.
My dad was a good man,
and not just to his own kids,
to any child,
especially disaster victims.
He'd see their faces and how terrified
and innocent they were...
I was living in Bushwick
during the blackout of '77.
I thought the world was ending.
My father's camera store was looted,
burned to the ground.
Really?
You know, my father helped
to rehabilitate that whole borough.
You were probably one of
the kids who inspired him.
Well, then I have a personal
obligation to repay him.
I'd like to raise my offer
if you'll consider it.
Well, as moving as your story
about the blackout is,
Ms. Carlisle wishes to uphold
her father's mantle, not destroy it.
Perhaps you'd like
to explain to her
how you colluded
to inflate gas and oil prices
after 9/11?
I was never involved
in those transactions.
But your subsidiaries were.
In my short time as C.E.O.,
I've learned
I'm not only accountable
for my own actions,
but for those of everyone
working under me.
Why is none of this
public record?
Well, because the lawsuits
were all settled and buried.
That's a fine allegation
coming from a Grayson.
Oh, don't confuse my record
with my father's. All right?
Listen, Donna,
I never knew your father,
but I assume
he'd be greatly disappointed
if one of the children he helped
now helps to destroy
what he created.
Yes, he would be...
As am I.
(Chuckles)
I'll have my lawyers
draw up the contract,
and we'll go from there.
(Cell phone ringing)
I'll leave you two
to talk details.
Excuse me.
(Ring)
(Ring, beep)
Hello.
Uh, as requested,
I hacked Aiden's phone.
I'm sending you the file
he just received
from Helen Crowley.
Ems, they've got his sister.
(Cell phone chimes and beeps)
(Man) So, uh, where are
you from, Colleen?
You ask too many questions.
Our time's almost up.
You're right.
Let's, uh, kick things up a notch.
Try it.
You'll like it.
Like you said,
time's running out.
(Exhales)
Why the hell wouldn't Aiden
tell me about this?
Well, perhaps
it has something to do
with the subject line...
"A life for a life"?
We know he's trying
to save his sister, but...
Who's the target?
Victoria.
Track his phone
before it's too late.
Jason.
You and your son
make an admirable team.
You set me up,
and he and that woman
on his arm knock me down.
What are you talking about?
What happened?
Exactly what you knew
would happen.
Another Grayson victory.
Jason,
my son is in grave danger.
I swear that I have...
Whatever trouble he's in,
he deserves it.
And you've earned
whatever heartbreak it brings.
What are you...
- Aiden!
- Damn it!
Why didn't you tell me?
And if I had?
I know Victoria belongs to you.
I saw the video.
I had Nolan
hack into your phone.
Is it really her?
I'm certain of it.
Look, I know
what they're promising you,
but you can't let them
turn you into their assassin.
If I don't, then I've failed her
for the second time.
And if you do,
then you give them all the power.
Listen to me, right now Daniel's
victory is their main concern,
and they have that.
You kill his mother,
you distract him
from their main purpose.
Tell Helen that you realized this,
and instead,
you helped seal Daniel's
victory over Prosser.
Okay?
Look, I'm going back tonight.
You should, too.
We're gonna find your sister.
But on our own terms,
not theirs.
And when we do,
we are gonna make them pay
for every second
they kept you apart.
Do you understand that?
Home again. Home again.
(Sighs)
Yeah, we don't have to be, you know?
I mean, we can refuel the jet,
head to the Bahamas,
the Azores...
anywhere without business
or my mother.
I think I just want my own bed.
But, you know, maybe we can
plan another trip sometime soon.
(Padma) Just got your e-mail.
Bidding on the house?
Did you know that there was
a secret passage?
Because I am totally hosting
a murder-mystery dinner.
That's what finally
got you to commit,
a secret passage?
Mm, and, uh...
Someone
to walk through it with?
I don't know, Nolan.
After everything with Marco...
Hey, my feelings
for Groucho Snarx
were fleeting and...
And a mistake.
I mean, he was only after one thing,
and it wasn't me.
Just...
Some dusty
old computer program.
You mean Carrion?
Right.
(Knock on door)
Victoria.
How was your flight back?
You know, you and I
could stand here all day
trading barbs and nettling
each other's last nerves,
or we can cut the crap.
Why did you accompany my son
to California?
Because he asked me to.
And I thought I could sway him.
Yes, but in which direction?
I was forced to walk
a fine line
between my allegiance to you
and my relationship
with Daniel.
Surely you could understand,
seeing as you've just done
the same with Prosser.
Well, the difference is
that my son floats through life
on crests of women,
unable to make
his own decisions.
You could've dissuaded him at any point.
Why didn't you?
I guess I wanted
to see him win.
You selfish little girl.
In doing so, you may have
caused him his greatest loss.
(Emily) Nolan?
(Nolan) Welcome back.
I read about
how the west was won.
I hope I helped the cause
with your faux beau.
I think I'm gaining
his confidence back.
But I might be
losing Victoria's.
It's only a matter of time
before she poisons me
to Daniel.
Well, not if you
poison her first,
which is a far more fitting end
than a bullet,
don't you think?
Speaking of which,
have you heard
from Thomas Crown?
Well, I've tried
triangulating his phone.
He's either jammed it
or dumped it.
I just hope
I made the right decision.
I know I didn't.
With the house?
Isn't this the one
that I'm buying you?
I don't think so.
It seems nothing
can save me from evil spirits.
Eleven years ago,
I started working on something.
Have I told you
what Carrion is?
Rotting meat?
Mm, in the form
of a million lines
of binary brilliance that...
have the ability to knock
Manhattan off the power grid
in less than a millisecond.
(Sighs)
That's what Marco
was looking for.
Right program,
wrong C.F.O.
Last week, Padma referred
to Carrion as a person.
And today
she called it a program.
I never told her that.
I'm sorry, Nolan.
- Did she get her hands on it?
- No.
And even if she had,
it's unfinished.
I keep the final sequence
locked up in here.
The timing
can't be a coincidence.
Padma played
an instrumental role
in acquiring Nolcorp
while seeking out Carrion,
and now Daniel's latest purchase
is a disaster recovery firm?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's the Initiative's
master plan,
turning out the lights?
What concerns me
is what happens when they do.
What's your plan for Padma?
I don't know yet.
My advice?
Play her
like she's playing you.
Dad?
Mom?
Bon anniversaire, ma belle.
Ohh.
I thought you canceled
my birthday.
- Never.
- (Daniel) We rescheduled it.
We're celebrating you,
sweetheart,
not the Gregorian calendar.
Go on.
Blow out the candles.
I only have one wish this year.
Anything.
I have spent the last two days
thinking about family
and what it means
to be a daughter,
a sister, and now an adult.
And my only wish
is that you support
my first adult decision.
I'm changing my name.
I filed papers
at the courthouse today.
You can now call me
Charlotte Clarke.
Happy Birthday, Charlotte.
From me and Daniel.
Emily.
Well, I didn't realize
we'd extended invitations.
Emily doesn't need one.
Let's get you a drink.
Love you, sis.
I hope I didn't interrupt
your time with your family.
Trust me,
I didn't want to be around
for the aftermath
of Charlotte's announcement.
I can't imagine what hell
my dad's giving her right now.
Is everything all right?
Oh, I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
I need to be honest with you.
A few weeks ago,
Victoria asked me
to rekindle our relationship.
She wanted somebody
to keep an eye on you
during your transition at work.
I said yes.
So you're the one
who leaked Stonehaven to her.
Which is why I fought so hard
to help you win it back.
Believe it or not,
I thought I was doing it
for the right reasons.
You must think I'm an idiot.
There isn't a single aspect
of my life
that my mother
hasn't meddled in.
You knew?
I mean, I...
I strongly suspected.
Her plans so rarely
break in my favor,
I guess I just
stuck my head in the sand.
In all fairness,
I guess I was using you
as much as you were me.
I was curious to see how far
you were willing to go.
Well, now you know.
You think we'll ever get back
to being the people
we once were?
Maybe.
Just not tonight.
(Declan) Hey, can you just
tell me what you said to Matt?
Honestly, not much.
He must have had
a crisis of conscience.
You did the right thing, Jack.
Daddy saved us.
I'm just glad Conrad
stood by his word.
He got the drug charges dropped
- and banished the Ryans.
- Yeah, because now
we're business partners
with Conrad Grayson.
I know. It's not ideal.
Ideal? The guy was stealing
money from his daughter
while she was locked up
in rehab.
Enough, Declan.
I'm instating a ban
on all complaining,
frowning,
and negative attitude.
It's not good for any of us.
(Nate) I didn't sign off
on this deal.
Ink's already dry.
You're gonna have to take that
up with your brother, Kenneth.
I'll buy it back.
$60,000.
$65,000.
Let me save you
this embarrassing display.
Exclusive of
your six-year vendetta
against the wrong man,
I know why you think
you want The Stowaway.
I have been approached
by investors for decades
with plans
to develop the docks,
and each one has resulted
in the same conclusion...
the owners have
very deep roots,
and they aren't going anywhere.
You live in the castle
above the village.
You don't know what I know,
what my father knew,
how these people work.
He almost had the waterfront
in the palm of his hand.
All we need is The Stowaway,
and we can regain
that foothold that he once had.
By what, changing community opinion
with town hall meetings?
Nah. With muscle.
Applying the proper amount
of pressure,
I can have roulette wheels
spinning by Memorial Day.
Ah.
Overly arrogant and ambitious.
I like that.
Think about it.
Think about all those jobs
you'll be creating.
It's right in line
with your new public image.
Conrad, we should
talk about this.
You're right.
We absolutely should
talk about this.
Ashley, could you please
close the door?
You don't always have to pay
for dinner, you know.
Well, chivalry isn't dead.
It's just somewhere
in my office.
You said
it's your platinum card?
It's probably
next to my computer somewhere.
Aah!
(Inhales sharply)
Ooh.
I forgot to warn you
about that trick drawer.
Don't worry.
I'll clean it up.
I still don't see
your platinum card.
It'll turn up.
I guess it is
your turn to pay.
Deal.
(Beeps)
(Rapid beeping)
Aiden, what happened?
- The Graysons could see you...
- I don't care.
(Coughs)
(Moans)
(Labored breathing)
(Man) It's done.
They made it look like
an overdose.
Aiden...
Aiden, I'm so sorry.
But you can't trust
these people.
You can't trust this.
- Listen to me...
- Listen to you?
I did listen to you,
and that's exactly
how this happened.
You made me believe that
they were manipulating me,
giving me false hope,
when it's you
I shouldn't have trusted.
If there's a chance
that my sister's alive,
then I'm gonna find her.
- Aiden...
- And if she is dead...
Then this is on you.
Aiden.
Aiden!
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com