Your cleanliness is your
responsibility, but I expect it
taken serious. I shall advise on
girdle, corsage, garter and bustle,
advice by which you will abide if
you wish to thrive. Now the house
takes 60% of all earnings. It is a
good sight less than most, girl.
In return, you shall find yourself
free from harassment of any kind.
If you have a complaint to make,
I will take your side,
no matter the grounds
nor the Thomas in question.
In short, you will find yourself
fed, safe and solvent.
Think on it. Return once you have.
Yes, ma'am.
Lucy!
Oh, Lucy!
Oh, darling.
I'll sweep and scrub the floors,
change the girls' linen,
cook for them, do whatever
you ask of me.
Ah, Lucy. You, a char? You would
make step-sisters of my girls
and I would have mutiny in a week.
Now, tell me. Where have you been
these last years?
Did one of our gentlemen
make you his own?
Lucy? Please, Miss Susan.
Will you not let me work?
You know I cannot.
Then I know not
what will become of me.
Lucy, look at you.
The truth of this world is that
men have designed it
for their own purpose and pleasure.
And you, my darling,
there is not one primitive desire
in their child-like minds
that you do not fulfil.
Which is my curse, miss...
one from which
all the world profit...
save myself...
and one, it seems,
I cannot now escape.
Christ on a pony.
Um...
Dead. Murdered.
Who is, lady?
It's all right. It's all right.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Two shillings is all. You spend less
on butter, more perhaps on ale.
But a drop or three will raise
you up when you need raising
and it's going to bring you
peace after.
Help! Help me, somebody.
Hell's bells! Fetch the inspector!
Come sit down here, Miss.
What you been up to?
Lucy? What is this? Who is she?
Her name's Lucy. Lucy Eames.
Known to you how? How do you think?
She was one of Susan's.
Lucy. Blood's not hers, thank God.
Then whose?
Sir, she spoke of murder.
Two murders. Where, girl?
Dog's Neck.
It's what they call the rookery
off the back of Cable.
St George's Cross? That's right, sir.
That slum's due to meet
the wrecking crew today.
Can we get a blanket? Give me a
blanket. Miss, come here. Come here.
Miss, you see this whiskered
gentleman here?
His name is Mr Artherton. You have
need of anything, you ask him.
She may deserve them. She may not.
Best not take chances. Quite so.
Sergeant, that girl's
no stranger to restraints.
Get the telegraph singing. See if
any of our brethren had any cause
to lock up a Lucy Eames.
Tart, I believe. Yes, sir.
She's one of Miss Hart's
girls, you say?
Was. When? Two years ago maybe.
Susan found her lifting her drawers
for the hauliers on Limehouse Cut,
took her in, fed her, waited
till she was 16, let her loose.
She was something, Reid.
Men stood in line half-way
to Hoxton. Lucky girl.
So why did they stop queuing?
Get these people out of here.
Come on. Move along.
It's all coming down today
whether you're out or not.
Order of S&C Railways.
Police coming through.
Stand aside, gentlemen.
Excuse me, madam. Stand aside.
Move! Out!
You, out!
He's gone. Though not long since.
Still warm. You. You stand there
and watch this man bleed out?
That man... I did.
Who is he? Name's Roach.
Collected rents hereabout.
What use was he on the day
this building comes down?
Whatever it was,
they raised hell about it.
She calling him a devil,
he swearing to end her
if she didn't pipe herself down.
The woman?
Yeah, Maggie Eames.
This is her place.
And those her children
that wail out there?
Them and their whore of a sister.
Sergeant, get them out of here.
Have a man take them to their sister
at Leman Street. Yes, sir.
You have the tart?
You saw her? She was seen...
walking out of here like
she'd washed herself in his blood.
You take note of any other?
On this day?! Amongst this exodus?
Satan himself could have sauntered
through and no man remark on it.
Your name? Denton.
Wait outside.
Sergeant, shut the door.
Constable, keep hold of this man.
Yes, sir.
So, she smashes
the bottle into his head.
She stabs his throat with it.
He staggers, he shoots...
No. What?
This wound, the skin,
subcutaneous fat...
See how clean it's penetrated?
She stabbed him with that bottle,
the work would be jagged and the
flesh scragged. This is a lancing.
Just one precise thrust.
Miss Eames, then.
She had no blade on her
when she arrived.
She could've ditched it. Certainly.
But...
But she would have struggled to
reach him from where she stood.
Lucy stood...
here.
See the arc of arterial blood?
The heart's beat projects it
from his severed artery,
strikes this wall, this wall,
this window...
Then hits the girl,
leaving that gap.
Give the man a cigar.
He was cut from behind
by someone else.
Go on. She hits him with
the gin bottle, blam. He shoots.
Gets stabbed from behind. He turns.
He falls with the stripe of blood.
Towards Lucy. But he shoots
and misses. See that?
Missing because he's turning,
aiming for another. Blam.
Blam.
Blam. Towards whoever cut him.
Where's the last? The sixth?
Lower than the others, sir. It is.
It is, but... was it diverted?
By what?
You see this, Captain?
We have six bullets.
We have one in her head.
Four passing directly into the wall
in a correlating tangent.
And the last, the sixth, perhaps
diverted through this window.
Then that's the slug we need.
Got ya.
It did pass through a body
on its way out. It's blooded.
Then...
a fourth stood...
here. In their hand,
the knife that killed this man
and with him the answer as to why
he blew this woman's brains
out of her before he died.
These bodies, mark where they lay
and they are for your dead room.
Sergeant, keep this room sealed.
There will be truth in it,
but we must work it
inch by every inch to find it.
You're police?
My name is Stanley Bone of the LCC.
Mine Reid. H Division.
What does it brings a board
member of our new county council
out to a slum clearance?
Do you offer your home
to those here rendered without?
Mr Reid, I am advocate
for the railway company
that makes this incursion.
Whatever has called you here
takes place on its land.
It is murder that calls me here.
Murder? Of who?
Of a rent collector and tenant.
I am sorry, Inspector.
But whilst I pray
for the poor departed,
that building comes down today.
No longer. It stays upright
until I know what took place there.
And these workmen
will stand idle on full wage
while you discern the details
of a rent dispute?
Whatever it is that's discerned
here, yes, they will.
Or are you not also
advocate of the police?
Yes, of course.
You must do your duty, Inspector.
How now, Inspector? Come to see
the march of progress, have we?
Those who now must find
their shelter where they can?
That your story, is it?
Oh, I am a man of compassion.
The benighted souls who must
make their lives in such places
or meet their deaths there.
Just a name or two, Inspector, eh?
Someone here shall
tell me eventually.
Why should it not be you?
Because I would make your life
harder than it need be, Mr Best.
Not the reverse.
It'll be all right, Lucy.
It'll be all right.
Artherton, a Maria
for St George's Cross.
Have Captain Jackson return
with all... speed.
There, there. Come on. Shush.
What's brought you here?
Erm, our Lucy, Inspector.
Miss Susan sent me to check on her.
And how do you find her?
As you see her, Mr Reid.
Just... silent in her distress.
Get home, girl. Yes, sir.
She seemed calmed
by the girl's presence, sir.
I thought it conducive. Never mind
that, Artherton. Have you traced
her? Not myself, sir. The lad.
Well, Hobbs?
Well, it's only that the girl
seems sad, to me, sir.
Not bad. No. And like you said,
she's worn irons before now,
so I did a round of the asylums.
And you found knowledge of her?
Yes, sir. The Lark House
at Bethnal Green.
And do they send someone?
A Dr Crabbe comes.
Karl Crabbe himself? Sir.
He's made a progress with hysterics
that no other doctor
of the mind has yet.
Good work, Hobbs. You did right.
Choose two men,
take a Maria to Sergeant Drake.
He'll have instructions for you.
Yes, sir. Give me the keys
to those cuffs.
Sit.
No. No, child. That is not what
is... required of you here.
Are you wounded in any way?
Sit.
All I want from you is to talk.
Whatever pleases you, sir.
Drink this.
Can you remember what it was
brought you here?
What happened at the Dog's Neck?
My mama killed, sir.
Not just your mother.
A man, too.
Yes. Do you know him?
What did you see?
Forgive me, Miss Eames.
His blood was shed all upon you.
May I go now, sir?
Where is it that you think
you are, Lucy?
I forget.
Your mama, this man...
Help me help you and think.
What did you see?
Just my darkness.
When I woke up,
they were there laid before me.
And not another soul? No-one.
You are sure?
There's nothing that
I'm sure of in this world, sir.
Lucy, you are aware that
you are with child, are you not?
Dr Crabbe.
Lucy!
Mr Reid.
Sir.
I heard you speak last month.
At Lincoln's Inn.
At the college! A man I know told me
I droned that day.
He cannot have been listening.
And now you have found
and cared for our Lucy.
Dr Crabbe, you should know,
Miss Eames'
mother is killed this day.
Oh, my poor dear girl.
And another man, too, the name of
Roach. Do you know him, sir?
No, I do not. Was Lucy present?
She was.
But remembers not a thing?
Get both these bodies
to my dead room!
The man who drops them will
be assisting me at autopsy.
No! Wait! Wait!
Take them away now! Hurry! Hurry!
Reid, I... I'm sorry.
She is epileptic?
She is ailed by that, yes.
Other conditions, also.
Inspector, I know you must
question her further
but I would lodge her in my care
until you next have need of her.
Artherton, prepare the papers.
Davis, can we lift her?
Thank you.
There Lucy.
All is well, all is well.
Dr Crabbe,
one last question before you go.
For how long has Miss Eames
been a patient of yours?
A little over two years now,
but she is not permanently
resident with me.
You keep no watch over her?
Inspector, to find her health,
it is of considerable importance
that Lucy's life feel
as commonplace as yours or mine.
That cannot be the case if she feel
we assess her every move.
When she is ill, she comes to me.
When well, she lives as she pleases.
Excuse me.
Sir. These nippers?
I have an idea where they may rest
until we know better what will
become of them.
Miss Goren? Miss Goren, I am sorry.
I come to impose on you once more.
Oh! We are friends now, Inspector.
You must never apologise
for your visit.
This is Betsy.
Hello, Betsy!
Girls, say hello to Betsy.
What is this poor child's story?
Er, her mother is dead
and her sister...
Her sister is of
no use to her for now.
No father or uncle?
It's men that are the ruin of this
family, Miss Goren.
Oh, this family and many like them,
Inspector.
You disagree?
No, no. No, merely,
my wife would say the same.
Mrs Reid must be a woman of great
sense and clarity.
She is that, yes.
Then I would like to meet her.
My many thanks again, Miss Goren.
If I have news,
you'll be the first to know.
You remember, Lucy? Your room?
Just as it ever was.
'Strange, were like she weren't
even there.
'Barely even recognised me.'
Anyways, I don't know why you're
getting yourself in such a palaver
about her.
Think she gave two tosses for you
when she swanned off like
Ellen Terry herself?
She was worth ten of you, girl.
Oh, Rose, come here, come here.
I'm so sorry.
I fear for her.
And I blame myself.
Get Reid, Sergeant.
Yes, Commissioner Munro.
Two issues, Reid.
One, whoever did this. From behind.
They had to push upwards
from underneath to do so.
So I reckon they would be shorter.
The blade's about four inches.
A good point, a switch-blade most
likely. A well-made one.
The second issue?
This woman.
There are fibroids in her womb.
Explain.
It's like cankers.
Over time they deform the uterus.
The children?
She ain't been
confined for over ten years.
So what then? Are they Lucy's?
Commissioner Munro
calls for you, Sir.
You're to go with him to
the Dog's Neck railway excavation.
They are but a few weeks old,
but these places already have
the chill of eternity.
Why bring me here, Sir?
Just hear the man out, Reid.
His concern should be ours, also.
Inspector. Inspector, please!
Thank you for responding
so speedily to my invitation.
Yourself in particular, Inspector.
Get to it, Bone, I have two
murders above us need investigation.
And I will have you returned to them
in short order, Mr Reid.
As soon as you've seen just
what is built here.
Track is laid. For a railway.
It is nothing new.
Perhaps not new.
But newly efficient.
Every man -
a yard back from the line!
500 volts run beneath the rivers
of the junction at Liverpool Street,
split there to travel east,
west and onwards, Mr Reid.
Onwards, for ever. Down the next
century and the one that follows -
an organism of transport.
Every borough connected,
one to the other.
The poor, sir -
not simply the rich - will travel,
for the cost of half a pot of jam,
from one end of our city to another.
Their everyday horizon extended,
their aspirations improved
accordingly.
Mr Bone, I have never contested
the value of this machinery
to people's lives.
Then assist it.
Inspector, the investment structure
we have constructed for this
venture, it is as reticulated
as the network we would build.
Each section of line
has a completion guarantee.
That guarantee fulfilled, the next
tranche of capital is released.
Should the demolition crew above
ground stand idle
for many hours more, we risk
the collapse of the entire venture.
I beg you, sir. I beg you.
Let them proceed.
Good day to you, fine sirs.
Who is this gentleman?
His name is Best.
He writes for The Star.
You know me not, Councillor.
But I come to know you, Sir.
This is private land.
Remove yourself or Inspector Reid
shall do so with his boot.
And this here is common land from
which I shall ask Mr Bone
my questions,
of how he feels,
four months into its life,
our new county council proceeds.
If its civic enlightenments are
not compromised by the...
commercial instincts of its
councillors.
I shall not stand here
and listen to these insinuations.
Everything we do,
we do for the good of this city
and the benefit of those who
build their lives within it.
Commissioner, Inspector.
I'm sure they appreciate
your dedication, sir.
Yes, the sacrifices you have made
to your own life.
Your wife, watching the sea roll in
all alone down in Hove.
No children to comfort you.
The pleasures of a home life
foregone in pursuit of others'
happiness.
It must ail you, Sir.
It must play on those
finely-tuned nerves of yours.
Or do you find other
ways of easing that pain...?
Best! Enough. Get gone.
Whatever you say, Inspector.
But do not think me gone long.
For myself, Mr Bone's vision of
a liberal city commune is of little
bearing.
No, sir.
What is of greater importance to me
is this -
that each occasion a slum is
raised to the ground,
it is replaced by the type of brick
and clean steel on which
the bacteria of the criminal classes
can no longer fester.
The greater the number of homeless
we send to the wider world,
the faster our measure
of crime falls.
You have my meaning, inspector.
Whatever it is your men do in that
rookery, it stops by end of day
or they will find themselves
amidst the rubble.
'There will be sign.'
This person might have vanished
as if a ghost,
but a ghost they are not.
Wherever they have passed, the space
through which they have done so must
bear witness.
We three - we take one more
pass of this place together.
On your knees, then.
Oh.
What, Hobbs? What is it?
It's gin, Sir.
Sir? Look at this, blonde hair.
The mother's, most likely.
What's that?
It's a herb.
Dropped. Brushed aside.
One that I have smelled before.
Hobbs. It's time we knew
more about our dead Mr Roach.
Get to Companies House. Find out what
you can about his work,
whether he collected on his own
behalf or for others. Sir.
Sergeant - you're with me.
I have a notion of what may
have passed here.
That's for upstairs, cheeky.
Sergeant Drake!
Get your skinny prick out of here!
Fetch Miss Susan!
Will you arrest me, Sir?
No, girl.
I hope he's not left you
out of pocket.
Mr Drake,
you do say the funniest things.
Your mistress. Where is she?
This had best be a raid.
If you've come simply to say
your good-evenings, I shall
be seeking compensation.
No good-evenings.
This is not a raid, either.
I seek an interview, Madam.
This way.
But leave your sergeant down there.
He may moon at my girl gratis.
I'll be outside sir.
Your accomplice's very own suite.
Will you indulge me, Miss Hart?
Allow me to weary you with some
details of my day?
You? Weary me, Inspector?
That girl you once ran.
Lucy. A good girl.
She left for what
we hoped were better times.
Better or no,
she appears this morning
at my station, striped in blood,
keening after her dead mother.
I've heard of it.
And I mourn for her.
Hmm. Yes.
And the man, too, Roach.
His carotid opened with
a stab of a honed switch-blade?
I prefer you spare me
that imagery, Mr Reid.
Your sensitivities
affronted, are they?
This plant on Captain Jackson's desk.
What of it?
Pennyroyal, is it not?
What that man keeps in this room,
I find I prefer not to inquire.
Then perhaps I might educate you?
I'd be honoured.
Pennyroyal, when brewed strong as an
infusion, may bring on miscarriage.
I confess I am surprised a woman in
your line of work, ignorant of this.
What can I say, Mr Reid?
We are cautious in this house.
Miss Eames is, I would say,
a little under three month pregnant.
Then I mourn for her once more.
As I say - cautious.
You best attend to that, Susan.
A bullet wound might soon go septic.
Think of the names I can speak of!
The many men of yours whose
pleasure's been found in my house!
Those ranked higher than you...!
Will you get her locked down!
You! And you! And you have all been
guests in my house!
With me, Jackson.
No, Reid!
I swear it, I have no clue as to
what she's doing here.
How skilled you are, Captain.
Your claims to know nothing of what
takes place beneath your own roof.
I am dismayed at myself,
that I would trust a man
so transparently false.
The two of you - you and Susan -
the lies that you hide behind,
lies that I have allowed
to go untested.
Allowed in the foolish instinct
that some good might come from it!
That you might be worth the faith
that I have placed in you!
I am, Reid.
You are in a rage
and I understand that rage, but I...
No.
You knew of her guilt and a man who
holds secrets is a secretive man.
And you have the right
to pronounce on that, do you?
That mess about your shoulder.
All who have laid eyes on it,
every man in this station
too afraid to talk about it even
amongst themselves.
Does Drake enquire after it?
Because I'd lay
money on it that he doesn't.
Well, that's loyalty for you, Reid.
A dog unable to question the pain
or motivation of the man
that it tails about the place.
Well, I shall ask you. I'd hear you
speak of what befell your girl...
You ever speak of her again,
I shall not trouble myself with
asking after the secrets
of your life, Captain.
I shall chain you in a cell
underground
and take billy club to you
until they pour from you like water.
Am I clear?
Am I?
My innocence in all this?
There is a suspect down the way
with a bullet wound,
requiring
disinfection and needlework.
'You make no attempt to
hide your guilt.'
Why should I?
I feel no shame for the act.
The animal had killed the woman,
was set to do the same to Lucy.
I did only as you would have done,
Inspector.
I should take your word for that?
Take what you will, Inspector.
It is the truth.
Careful, Quack!
The truth, and the two of you?
Three unlikelier bedfellows a man
would struggle to find. Indeed.
You ask your questions, Mr Reid.
I will answer and then you may
decide if I do so truthfully or no.
What brought you to Dog's Neck?
Lucy. She invited you?
I followed her there. From?
Tenter Street.
Two years and not a word,
not a solitary clue as to
whether she lived or breathed.
Then, dressed fine as a lady,
she knocks on my door.
What did she want?
Her old room back.
But she was dressed fine, you say?
I have no explanation for it,
Sergeant, just the fact of it.
Then what did you say to her, Susan?
That, thoroughbred or no,
three months pregnant, she was
no use whatsoever to your stable.
Then what?
Why ask me?
I imagine, being fond of her,
you felt remorse.
And you hurried after the girl,
Pennyroyal in hand,
to tell her that, were she to find
herself free of her burden,
she might once again be welcome.
Hmm?
But it is what you found there
that interests me the most.
I heard her from the street.
She raged at him. Margaret?
On what topic?
They were flattening the place.
He wanted his dues before
they did so.
No.
She screamed
of what she knew of him.
And that she would be silent
no longer.
And he said that she would
if she knew what would
allow her to keep on breathing.
I heard glass break.
The bottle against his head?
The reports of a revolver.
Lucy screaming. You entered.
Lucy was hysteric.
You produced your blade.
You cut...
from behind.
And what of Lucy?
I left her there.
Squirming in the dirt.
Why d'you stare?
It is a case solved. Reid.
No longer, American, away with ya.
Reid, do you intend to
charge her on this?
For saving a girl's life?
A man was killed by her hand.
A slumlord ape set on murder.
Still a man.
And you never thought it worth
asking why this man took
a pistol to this woman.
Or whose threat he carried with him?
Captain Jackson, I shall be
the master of all enquiries
I make of myself.
Door, please, Sergeant.
Is it worth asking?
Do you think, sir?
Yes, Bennet. I suspect it is.
David, be quiet.
Down and sleep. Goodnight.
Goodnight, Miss. Good night,
good night. Sleep!
'Go'natt. Sov Gott.
Oh, Ellie, I have your dolly.
There... tuck down. Good night.
Go to sleep. Good night.
Oh, no!
Betsy, Betsy.
Betsy? Betsy?
Miss Goren?
It seems all I bring to you is
violence and distress.
Find the children, please,
Inspector.
Lucy Eames.
Two years since, you say she walked
away from your house with no warning?
I do.
The oldest child found in that room,
I guess she approached that age.
Do you agree? Mmm.
Then I suggest this to you.
That you cast her out for the same
reason you cast her out
this day just passed,
that she was pregnant
and no longer welcome in your house.
You think me callous, Inspector.
And perhaps I am that.
But I loved that girl like a sister.
And she never did say what
took her away.
But I had my theories.
Proceed.
The first of her... attacks...
The fits from which she suffers?
It had come two months previous.
Near scared the Thomas with whom she
was engaged, to his death.
There were more?
Perhaps five, graver too.
We found her gone the day after
the last one had left her.
My belief? She went to
find their remedy.
Gentlemen, please, come this way.
In the treatment you
conducted with her,
did she speak at all of
children born unto her?
She did not.
Nor of the child
she carries in her belly now?
Mr Reid, my patients -
past, present, future...
I have no family of my own
and as a consequence,
they are doubly precious to me.
Such love means I will not
judge them nor demand their secrets.
They come to me,
arms wide for assistance
and I render it without condition.
Until Lucy chooses freely to tell me
the details of her life away from
here, I will not ask her of them.
Then that - and I hope you will
forgive me for this, doctor -
that must be my task.
Lucy.
I bring greetings from Miss Susan.
Miss Susan is a lady.
As are you, Lucy.
Not I, sir. I would be so.
But am not.
And who is it says so?
The world. Its law.
God's law.
Because you have children
and are unmarried?
Many reasons, sir.
Tell me, Lucy, what, what was it
brought you to Miss Susan yesterday?
Miss Susan sent me away.
I know, I know.
But, after two years
and with child inside you.
It is desperate of you.
Tell me, Lucy, please,
will you name that despair?
Lucy? Lucy?
The children
that your mother cared for,
the child that is inside you now.
Which man is father to them, Lucy?
It is but one man, is it not?
Do not be frighted, child.
It is in my gift to
guarantee your safety.
No, no I cannot!
No, I cannot, I cannot, no!
Calm. Calm. Calm, child!
There... sshh... all right.
Miss Eames' medication.
Mr Reid would know its contents.
Hobbs, Hobbs, Hobbs, slow down,
say again, say again. Yes sir.
Sir, Gordon Roach - that's
the murdered rent collector, sir -
has a company name of
Roach Collections. Imaginative.
Yes... No.
Roach Collections pays into and
receives stipend from a trust.
Name of?
Stickleton. The Stickleton Trust.
Its board members?
Not listed. The only name
that of a lawyer.
A Mr Pinch.
Now, I visited Mr Pinch -
well, Mr Pinch's clerk, that is.
And impressed on him the value of
this... Yes, yes, Hobbs, skip to it.
Sir, the only trustee of the
Stickleton Trust is Mr Stanley Bone.
Sergeant Drake! With me!
Stanley Bone. Everything you have.
Now.
Hang it.
Fred Best tells you
he needs something shown in return.
You do as I ask, I will give to you
a story that, though you connive
and bribe your way to the devil
himself - it will not be bettered.
Go on. How Stanley Bone -
secret slumlord -
is exposed by the actions
of a whore-runner.
Corruption and sex, Mr Best.
Surely it does not come more
honeyed than that.
Oh, yeah, Mama!
I have you now! Where's Reid?
He's out, he may be some time.
Well you're going to tell me.
Or I'm going to shoot Hobbs here.
Relax, Hobbs. Man, I'm only joking.
I could no more shoot you than
I could shoot my own mother.
Artherton, on the other hand...
As you know, Inspector,
he was one of the first raised
up in January by our new council.
Now in March he and his friends
agree that the Dockhead slum
in Southwark make way for the S&C
Railway and its very first tunnel.
The Dockhead was
also owned and collected by
the Stickleton Trust? It was.
Thus Mr Bone recommends the
compulsory purchase of his own slum.
Mm-hm and profits tidily.
Mr Best, the last I saw you,
you made heavy weather of matters
that relate more closely to
Mr Bone's personal status.
I did. It is true.
Elaborate, if you please?
Mr Bone is a man who came to
ambition late.
His youth was not a happy one.
Beset with fits.
He is epileptic?
Was. He eventually found the cure.
And the cure? Where was it found?
You will let me pass,
or you will suck on this iron!
Sir, stop! You can't go in there!
Drake.
Look, I swear I'm not going to shoot
you, only... tell Reid...
that the vial...
Lucy's medication... Uh...
What? What is it?
It is amphetamine!
The doctor who gave
Mr Bone his cure.
His name is Crabbe, is it not?
It is, Mr Reid.
We go. Ah, one last question.
You jibed about his bachelor status.
What did you mean by this?
That is the last piece of my puzzle,
Mr Reid.
There was tell
he had a woman cached away somewhere
and a set of bastards, too.
And did you find them?
Never could, Mr Reid.
More's the pity, eh?
Indeed.
Your carriage is here.
A carriage that takes you to honour
the latest chapter of your ever more
celebrated life in this city.
Think on that.
Remember how you lived
the first you came to me -
cursed by fits and reliance
on your merciless wife.
Do you think I forget?
Am I not grateful for what you
have done for me?
I question your commitment
to all that still lies ahead of us.
Roach silenced the woman.
I have had the children separated
and removed a hundred mile
from here, as you suggested.
I do not refer to your unloved
bastards, as you well know.
It was your success had this
sanatorium built,
and she my gift to you in return.
A child, blooming into woman,
who would see in you
not the stammering
lunatic of your youth,
but a vision of strength and hope.
You have enjoyed her.
But she is all used now.
And must have her mind
cleaned of all she knows of you.
But she is so young...
She too may find the temperance
you have led me toward.
No. She grows ever more disturbed.
And this Reid draws close.
I will not allow you to make ruins
of the life I have built for you.
She must be silenced
so put her from your mind,
as you have the memory of the man
you once were.
And leave me
to bring her a more permanent peace.
Karl, I would say goodbye.
Thank you, nurse.
Stanley?
Say what you need to say.
Goodbye, Lucy, goodbye, my love.
Stanley? Stanley,
where do they take me?
I... I've got another inside me,
Stanley, I got another. Stanley?
It's all right, Councillor Bone.
We cannot build a railway without
that we demolish a slum or two.
Sta...
Wait. That was Bone!
It can wait. We keep our course.
Hush, Lucy. Shh, imagine it.
A calm entire. Hmm, no questions,
no hurtful thoughts.
No urgent and unhappy desires.
Simply peace.
You found us.
It was not easy.
You've hidden this refuge well.
But that is a benefit
to those you house.
It is. Miss Goren?
Inspector.
Nicholas? Betsy? Hello!
Come here, you!
Come on, let's go inside, shall we?
And show you the room
Mrs Reid has got for us.
Yeah? Come on.
Will you take tea, Miss Goren.
Yes, thank you.
Gentlemen! Ladies! The switch is
thrown. The line is live.
And beneath this earth here,
the electric age forges on.
This railway, this
underground railway is
the capstone of all that we -
your grateful servants -
would build here.
The foundation, ladies
and gentlemen, of a new city.
A city that - though it
rises from dank and fetid earth -
will gleam with the purpose
and clarity of a summer morning.
Because if the future stands
for anything - it stands for hope!
You do not have to do this thing.
I do, Inspector.
H Division's Inspector Reid!
What intrusion is this?
Yes, Stanley. I still have my wits.
Miss, Miss. What is your name?
Her name is not relevant.
Her story is.
I know you, Stanley Bone.
You proclaim to these good people
about the future's gleaming hope,
but the tongue you
speak with is forked.
And the future you speak of,
it is built on evil and corruption.
You had me as your slave,
denied our children...
had my mother murdered and you would
have sent me to a living hell had it
not been for this inspector here.
You are no man, but you are
a beast that has risen
deep from the earth in
which you dig into.
Mr Stanley Bone!
You halt for the police!
Watch yourself, off the track.
Turn it off, somebody!
Christ alive!
You're famous. From a Leman Street
cell to the front page in a day.
Someone must be fond of you.
Hmm, such fame is impermanent.
You'd better hope so.
Otherwise, it's going to be you and
me lacking in permanence.
Whoever we contend with here,
they are no ordinary cracksmen.
Again!
All men stand equal before the law,
do they not? That is the law.
It is your law. Is it yours?
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.