[ cheerleaders cheering ]
Heads up!
Uh, hey, Enzo's here.
Dan.
- Ha ha!
- What up, bro?
- Doing good. You?
- I can't complain. Business is good.
You bring me cupcakes?
Yeah, I got them all
working at the bakery.
Ah.
- How's Marcus?
- Not good. Has to have surgery.
- Same as what happened to you.
- Damn.
Where's he at?
You can clean my ride.
- Then let's talk.
- Okay.
[ door opens ]
Aah! Aah!
[ gasps ]
[ cheerleaders cheering,
rock music playing ]
[ screams ]
Oh, my god.
Call 911!
[ grunting ]
Somebody get us a towel!
- Come on, buddy.
- Let's keep pressure on it.
- Come on, Enzo.
- Come on, buddy.
No, seriously, I don't
mind working on Sundays.
Yeah, murderers tend to take
a break on the Lord's day.
What about that
mattapan triple homicide?
Well, expect for that, yeah.
- Frost, your mom's here.
- Hey, mom.
How'd you get here so fast?
We got off to an early
start, no traffic on the 95.
- Hey.
- Hey, Robin.
[ laughs ]
What are you doing here?
Oh, Cameron's on vacation.
He was bored,
so, never been to Boston.
- Hey, Cam.
- Hey.
We're gonna ride the duck boat.
- Cool, man.
- Hi, Camille.
- Jane. How are you?
- I'm good.
Thank you.
It's been a long time.
This is Robin, my mom's
roommate, and her son, Cameron.
- So nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Jane. Hi.
- Hi.
- This is my brother Frankie.
Frankie: Hey, how you doing?
How come you don't
have a police uniform?
Actually, Detectives
don't wear uniforms.
But I'm just on call today.
We're gonna go play some softball.
Wait for us!
- Are you going bowling?
- No. We want to play
for Boston Police
Department's softball league.
Heads up! Oop.
[ laughs ]
Yeah.
- Good job breaking it in.
- Take off the tag.
Goodbye, playoffs.
Uh... shoot.
The season's almost over,
so, you know, may...
maybe next year.
- Bummer.
- Hold on.
Let me make sure I understand.
Your science colleagues,
who, for all you know,
could be world-class softball stars,
aren't welcome at
your softball practice?
[ both clearing throats ]
Uh... well...
Uh...
[ cellphone vibrates ]
[ beep ]
Rizzoli.
[ cellphone vibrates ]
Dr. Isles.
Okay. I'll be right there.
- We're not done here.
- Okay.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ addic7ed.com ~
3x14 - Over/Under
Victim is Enzo Womack.
The running back from BCU?
The dessertier from End Zone Cakes?
Did you just say "dessertier"?
Enzo Womack is a well-known cakemaker.
He just opened his first
D.I.Y. on Charles street.
D.I.Y.?
"Decorate it yourself."
It's on my bucket list.
- What happened?
- Stabbed twice in the neck.
He was probably here to
support the BCU fundraiser.
Any witnesses?
Happened in the car wash.
Nobody saw anything.
We got a hundred people
in and out of here.
It's a huge intersection.
We don't have one witness?
Once you drive in, it's
just you, your vehicle,
and automated equipment
for six minutes.
Maybe someone was hiding in the van.
- Do we know where he was coming from?
- His bakery, End Zone Cakes.
His nickname was "End Zone"
'cause he made so many touchdowns.
- Who removed his body from the van?
- Dan Mackenzie, team trainer.
He and the coach tried to revive him.
Mackenzie and Enzo were friends.
Yeah, I think they played together.
Yeah, Mackenzie was a kicker.
Played together for four seasons.
- Team's a mess.
- So is the crime scene.
Found his cellphone.
I got a bad feeling this
isn't gonna be much help.
All right, let's get the van
back to the evidence garage.
So much for a slow Sunday.
What if I practiced my
swing in that cagey thing?
It's called a batting cage, Maura.
I'm looking for Sergeant
Detective Korsak.
[ gasps ]
What is he doing here?
Casey.
- Jane.
- Hi.
- I didn't know you'd be here today.
- I work here.
Hello, Maura.
- Casey, how are you?
- I'm okay.
Uh, I'll ... I'll just
meet you downstairs.
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
That wasn't much of a greeting.
[ chuckles ]
- Let me start again.
- Okay.
- Hello, Jane.
- Hello. It's good to see you.
I said I'd, uh, be in
touch when I was ready.
So, I'm guessing you're not ready.
It's complicated.
I'm getting closer, though.
Okay. So ...
so, why are you here?
I need to talk to, uh,
Sergeant Korsak.
Elsie! Hey!
- Hello, girl. Hi, Casey.
- Hey, Vince.
All right, well, you know,
I don't want to get
between you and Korsak.
Oh, I just stopped by to ask
if he would watch Elsie for me.
Oh.
- God, it's good to see you.
- You can see me anytime you want.
I'll be in touch.
- I promise... I will.
- Well, you know where I am.
I am that kid that open the boxes that said
"do not open this until christmas."
Mm-hmm.
- No, I mean in November.
- Uh-huh.
Ma caught me crawling under her bed
looking for my birthday presents.
Huh.
- Are you getting how major this is?
- Mm-hmm.
Maura, you're not even listening.
You have been talking
about Casey for 31 minutes.
I'm having an epiphany here,
a watershed moment.
I am having
a life-altering experience.
Can you hand me the metal probe?
Yes.
I mean, Casey gave me
the perfect opportunity
to be my impatient self ...
you know, to pressure
him and demand answers,
and ... and I didn't.
Me. I was patient.
Isn't that amazing?
Yes.
Can you hand me the forceps?
Okay, you cannot still be
upset about the softball thing.
This "softball thing."
Hmm.
I-I put my pride on the line
and beg to be included in
an extracurricular activity
- in front of my employees.
- Why is it so important to you?
Why is it so important to
build interdepartmental bridges?
You've clearly never
played in a softball league.
You just don't want us to play
because you're too competitive
and you don't think we're any good.
- I'm right, aren't I?
- Yes.
At least you're honest.
He still has remarkable musculature.
- He must not eat his cakes.
- Yeah.
Enzo was the first BCU player
in years who could have gone pro.
I'm guessing that wasn't an option
once he tore his anterior
cruciate ligament.
Scar tissue looks to
be about five years old.
BCU going for the money
with a hand-off to end zone.
Man, he was fast.
Oh, no!
Womack is tackled hard.
He's not getting up.
Folks, this does not look good.
It's amazing how fast
your life can change.
All it took for Casey was
an I.E.D. and some shrapnel.
And a war.
My guess is Casey
dropped by to see you.
[ sighs ] Stop guessing.
You're bad at it.
He came by to see Korsak.
Oh, stop timing me.
I'll stop talking about Casey.
There are hilt marks...
there and there.
Those are probably from the knife.
- A small buck knife, maybe?
- Well, many knives have hilts ...
survival knives, hunting knives,
skinning knives, commando
knives, tanto knives.
Can you please stop?
Hmm.
Some kind of particulate
matter adhered to the wound.
- Well, that must have come off the knife.
- And white fibers ... there.
I'll have the crime
lab analyze all this.
[ cellphone vibrates ]
Okay, the victim's van is in the
evidence garage. I'll be back.
Will you think about
the, uh, "softball thing"?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Sorry, the answer's still no.
Korsak: We got a bunch
of cake-decorating stuff.
It's all covered with arterial
blood spray and car-wash suds.
Killer was smart.
He ruined any chance we had of
making a case with forensics.
Doesn't it seem a little
spur of the moment,
stabbing someone in a car wash?
Yeah.
I'll get it all photographed and tested.
[ police radio chatter ]
- Where's Frost?
- Well, the warrant came through.
He's working on Enzo's laptop
and still trying to
dry out his cellphone.
Okay, I'll have the crime lab
comparison-test all the
tools and knives in here.
Maura thinks that the
murder weapon had a hilt.
- This has a hilt.
- I didn't know he was coming.
Yeah, I figured.
He asked a lot of questions about you.
Really?
- Why did he leave Elsie?
- I'm taking care of her for a while.
He knew if he brought her by,
I couldn't refuse her.
You're taking care of her?
For how long?
Maybe a few months.
- Why? Where's he going?
- He didn't go into details.
You're a Detective.
Didn't you ask?
- I didn't want to pry!
- Oh, that's so male.
[ sighs ]
- You think this is frosting?
- Maybe. Crime lab can test it.
Look, we got at least
several years' worth
of frosting and cake crumbs.
- What the hell is "fun-dant"?
- Fondant.
And it's sticky, sweet, inedible
crap that they put on cakes.
- Don't put it on retirement cake.
- Duly noted.
Ohh.
You're a good girl, Elsie.
- Oh, she's the best.
- And you're a service dog.
Casey needs you,
so what are you doing here?
Hey, Ma.
This is Detective
Frost's mother, Camille.
Oh. Nice to meet you.
I'm Angela.
Hi. Pleasure.
- You okay waiting here?
- Yes, yes.
And thank you so much
for taking us around.
- Sure. See ya, Ma.
- Bye, babe.
What a nice man.
He drove me and my roommate
and her son all over Boston
while we were waiting for Barry.
Yeah, he's a good kid.
And, uh, your son and my
daughter, Jane, are like this.
Oh.
I wish I lived closer.
I feel like I never see him.
- You live in, uh, Virginia, right?
- Norfolk.
I teach at one of the
military universities there.
Nice. What do you teach?
- Civil engineering.
- Wow.
Well, now we know where, uh,
Detective Frost gets his brains.
His father was actually
pretty smart, too.
Uh, we divorced 20 years ago.
[ chuckles ]
I just got divorced.
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- I'm not.
Well, anymore.
Can I get you a cup of coffee?
Oh, no, thank you.
I think I already had
enough on the way here.
I'm actually trying to work up the nerve
to tell Barry that
I'm getting remarried.
Oh. Congratulations.
Why is that making you nervous?
The divorce was hard on him.
And I never dated.
Well, don't get me wrong.
Barry is very respectful,
but knowing him, you know,
he has strong opinions.
Well, we did bring them
up to have their own minds.
Yes, we did.
[ chuckles ]
It's crazy how the
tables turn, isn't it?
I was seeing this guy for a while,
and, uh, my kids went nuts.
- What'd you do?
- Felt guilty.
But then I decided I was
allowed to be a person, too.
- Yes, you are.
- Excuse me.
I think you need to complain
about your lunch order.
There's a phone in it.
Rice is an effective desiccant.
Are you using three-syllable words
because your mother's in town?
Oh, man. I might be.
[ chuckles ]
Can you make it work?
I'm not sure.
Circuits are wet.
But I've been having
fun on Enzo's laptop.
He liked three things.
Let me guess ... women,
cakes, and BCU football.
What a life ... football,
women, and cake.
Enzo was a season-ticket holder.
And he also had every BCU game
from the last 10 years
on his hard drive.
- That's a serious fan.
- Dude was hardcore.
He watched every game
and a lot of replays.
Pretty sure viewing football
on his computer didn't kill him.
Yeah, and I remember him
to be quite the ladies' man.
What about the women in his life?
Ho-ho-ho!
Nice assortment of desserts.
- I meant the cupcakes.
- Yeah, sure you did.
- Most of them are his old girlfriends.
- He hired his old flames?
Which flavor
would you choose, Korsak?
- Chocolate? Vanilla?
- So many cupcakes, so little time.
Okay, I'm about to
file a harassment claim.
- It has to be hostile and offensive.
- Keep talking.
Enzo updated his schedule
on this internal calendar.
Well, he posted he was going
to the car-wash fundraiser.
- Who had access to that calendar?
- Just his employees.
You mean just his ex-girlfriends?
Huh.
Check this out.
Hmm. "What I'd like
to do to my ex-boyfriend."
- Where'd you find that photo?
- She posted it on candidgram.
She posted selfies all day long.
Okay, who's Laura Stephens?
She looks like an employee.
I'll check.
She's 24. She's a cake
decorator at End Zone Cakes.
All right, well, come on.
Maura's mad at me,
so let's give her a cheap thrill,
and she can comparison-test
the cake knives.
Uh...
meet me at the elevator.
What's up?
You know how I drove Frost's
mom and her roommate around?
Yeah.
Well, I think they're, uh...
you know.
- No, I don't know.
- I think they're a couple.
What?!
Does Frost know?
Never mind.
Don't answer that.
It ...
it's none of our business.
No way he knows. She was
married ... to his father.
Well, what makes you
think they're a couple?
- Jane, they're a couple.
- It's not of our business.
What's none of your business?
We were...
just talking about Ma.
It sounded like you were
talking about her love life.
No. Menopause.
- We were talking about menopause.
- Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
It's none of our business
if Ma's in menopause. See ya.
- Ugh. You ready?
- Yes.
We should... get Maura and go.
- Boston homicide.
- What are you doing about Enzo?
- What's your name?
- Valentina Smith.
How could you let this happen?
Car washes are supposed to be safe!
Uh, what was
your relationship to him?
We went to college together.
I'm his office manager.
- Were you two involved?
- In college.
We haven't slept together in years.
- And where were you this morning?
- Delivering a wedding cake.
- We'll need to verify that.
- Whatever.
- I'm not about to kill my boss.
- We'd like to talk to Laura Stephens.
Everybody here was his friend.
We're working on a cake for
his memorial service now.
They're making the Boston Cambridge
University football stadium.
Oh, look! It's a little Enzo.
And this is a representation of heaven.
And I think that that golden ladder
- is so he can ascend.
- Uh, Dr. Isles?
- The comparison test?
- Oh, yes, of course.
Damn, Enzo liked them in all
shapes, sizes, and colors.
- Is that harassment?
- Possibly, yes.
You'll interfere with my
process if you come any closer.
We'd like to talk to
you about Enzo Womack.
Can you just wait a sec?
Crap, you made me bump
the chin strap.
- Are these your knives?
- Don't touch them.
I'll need a clay impression
for a comparison test.
I didn't kill him, all right?
A woman definitely killed
that bastard, though.
How do you know
a woman killed him?
You think you can sleep with a girl,
buy her brunch, whisper
sweet bullshit in her ear,
and then say,
"let's be friends, 'kay?"
You think you can do that
over and over?
We found this photo
you posted, Laura.
- It was a joke.
- It doesn't seem that funny to me.
Maura: Me neither.
- That looks pretty sharp.
- It's a flower pin.
You should talk to everybody.
Enzo strung us all along.
"Let's be friends, 'kay?"
- No, not okay.
- So, why'd you work for him?
Do you know how hard it is to
find a decent job in this economy?
- I have a major in gender studies.
- Ooh. Yeah, I know what you mean.
Well, it seems to me that Enzo gave
you a reason to kill him, Laura.
He did, but I didn't.
I was at the gym.
You can check.
They take a picture when
they swipe it. I want it back.
I have to work out later today.
It's a shame that
Laura has a solid alibi.
Still, I think Enzo was
playing a dangerous game.
You think, uh, too many notches
on the bedpost got him killed?
[ cellphone vibrates ]
Maybe.
Okay, Maura's finished
testing all the knives.
Our murder weapon
is not at that bakery.
So, it's nice that
Robin came with your mom,
you know, so she could
have some company.
My mom's really independent,
but, yeah, I guess.
How do they know each other?
They're both professors at the
naval university in Norfolk.
I didn't know
your mom was a professor.
My mom was in one of the first classes
at the naval academy
that allowed women.
- Are you kidding me?
- She's amazing.
She and my dad
were midshipmen together.
That's how they met.
He had the career she should have.
Huh.
And they're roommates,
y-your mom and Robin?
After Robin's divorce,
they decided to share expenses.
Professors don't make that much.
Well, it's good they have each other.
I mean to ... to share expenses.
- No kidding.
- Come on. Let's call it a day.
We got two games left in the
season, and if we don't get
in a practice today, the drug
unit's gonna kick our ass.
Mnh-mnh.
Since you put it that way...
You think it's okay if...
if I bring my mom?
Oh, and ... and Robin
and Cameron, too?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
[ elevator bell dings ]
[ indistinct conversation ]
- Maura.
- Jane.
Can't believe you weren't
gonna tell us about practice.
[ sighs ] Okay... look,
there are only two more
games left in the season,
and ... and we'll be disqualified.
You're not part of homicide.
Oh, so Frost's mom
is part of homicide?
Jane, we could buck up
sides and have a scrimmage.
Buck up?
Who are you, opie?
- Who's opie?
- Shh. Honey.
Maura, you ... you don't have
enough players for a team.
Oh, we'd be happy to
play for Maura's team.
Robin: Yeah. Why not?
We're just a couple of old ladies
looking for some exercise.
Maura: All right.
All right. So, you're
gonna have to buck up, Jane.
I'd love to.
It's only fair that the
winners buy the losers drinks.
Korsak got to take Cameron
to buy an ice cream.
We got to endure this?
- Lab results, Dr. Isles.
- Thank you.
All the identifiable organic substances
in the van were glucose-based
confectioner's compounds.
- Swell.
- And blood and glycerin from the soap.
- Double swell.
- There was one exception.
The blue substance that you found on
the rear floor mat is bulk field paint.
Field paint?
BCU's colors are blue and...
Susie, can you check and see
if that field paint is from BCU?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thank you.
Hmm.
Oh, just two old ladies
in need of some exercise.
Mmm.
I think somebody lied.
It wasn't a lie.
We are old ladies.
- And we needed exercise.
- It was such an exciting game.
- 6:1. We trounced you.
- "We"?
Camille hit two home runs,
and Robin hit a grand slam.
So 2 for you,
4 for you, and zero for you.
Exactly. And is it a "we"
when you got two ringers?
Oh, my god! You knew.
Well, I figured Robin's
swing had lost some power.
Frost!
And mom ...
you haven't played in a while.
We thought
we were  rustier than we were.
We scored one run ... one.
- I think you played really well.
- The drug unit's gonna destroy us.
Well, not if you let us play.
And by "us,"
you mean Camille and Robin?
You're a very sore loser.
I did make it to the first base.
- You don't say "the".
- What?
You made it to first base
because you were walked.
You know, walking's good.
- To the walk.
- Maura: To the walk.
Walking.
[ laughter ]
[ thud ] Ow!
Why are you kicking my leg?
I s-should hand it to Robin and Camille.
Jane, did you hurt your neck?
Are you having a muscle spasm?
Really?
- I'd like to propose a toast.
- That's great sportsmanship.
See?
Toasting the winning team.
Uh, to two wonderful people
who have taught me the meaning
of love and commitment ...
My mom...
and her partner, Robin.
- Barry, you knew?
- Yeah, mom, I knew.
I had been agonizing
over this for years.
You never brought it up.
It wasn't my business.
[ sighs ]
Honey.
I figured if you wanted
to tell me, you would.
I told you. You've never
given him enough credit.
I just wish I'd known.
How many times have
I invited you to Massachusetts?
I kept hoping you'd make
an honest woman out of her.
- I'm glad you finally have.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Yes, congratulations.
When is the wedding day?
We actually haven't
even set the date yet.
It's ... it was just
time to tell you, Barry.
I couldn't get
married without you.
- You'll be our best man?
- You know I will.
Oh, and I have a great
dress I haven't worn yet.
You haven't been invited.
Listen, when we have our
wedding, you'll all be welcome.
We'd love to have you join us.
All right, well, this
calls for champagne.
- Losing team is buying.
- Hear, hear!
- As long as winning team stops mocking.
- Sorry, sorry!
[ siren wailing in distance ]
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- I wanted to apologize.
- Oh? What did you do?
- Come inside.
- I can't.
I'm so sorry. We ...
we can talk out here.
I don't mean I can't
make it up your stairs.
I mean
I don't want to go inside.
- Where are you going?
- Upstairs to hear your apology.
It might take me a while.
Good.
I have to put my glove away.
No. Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
[ knock on door ]
Um, coming!
Coming.
Coming. Okay.
Hey.
Are you okay?
[ panting ]
Yeah. I'm fine.
Uh, come in.
Um, sit down.
Can ... can I get
you a beer or...
- Maybe a water.
- A water. Okay.
- Thanks.
- Uh-huh.
I remember the last time I was here.
Right before your last
tour in Afghanistan.
[ breathes shakily ]
[ exhales sharply ]
My final tour.
It's like the last run on a ski slope.
You know as you're falling
you shouldn't have taken it.
Thank you for coming up.
I-I know you didn't want to.
I did. I ju...
I didn't want to be this close to you.
Casey.
- Please.
- I'm sorry.
I asked Sergeant Korsak
to look after Elsie
because I'm having surgery.
- Surgery? W-when?
- Soon.
- The stem-cell trials?
- No. I'm not a candidate.
I found a neurosurgeon.
He thinks he can remove
the, uh, shrapnel and bone
shards from pressing
against my spinal cord.
- Casey, that's incredible.
- There are no guarantees,
and, uh... and there
will be months of rehab.
But it's the first crack of light
I've seen in a pretty dark tunnel.
Well, let me ...
let me help you.
I-I want to go through this with you.
That's exactly why I
didn't get in touch.
Casey...
I-it doesn't matter, okay?
- I care about you.
- No.
This is no way to start a relationship,
and this is where we are ...
at the beginning.
Okay, well,
let's get to the middle.
I want to do this.
Taking care of an invalid
is an ugly form of intimacy.
There's no romance in it, Jane.
This injury isn't you.
This is you.
I should have asked you not to go.
I should have asked you to wait.
Did you see someone
else while I was gone?
Yes.
Did you care about him?
- Then you'll find someone again.
- What? No.
Casey, wait a minute. Wait.
It's over with him.
It's ... it's been over.
Look, I realized that
when I saw you again
how much I want this to work.
- This won't work.
- It will.
Casey, please, just
give me a chance. Please.
- Do one thing for me.
- Anything.
Let me kiss you...
and then let me go.
Casey, please, please.
Goodbye, Jane.
[ sighs ]
[ knock on door ]
- Where do socks go?
- All you need is a half-inch gap
for them to slip under
the agitator paddle.
So not sock heaven.
Check your drawers.
Static electricity causes them
to stick to other clothing.
I hope Enzo gets to
go to football heaven.
- Thank you for coming.
- Don't throw them away!
They don't have partners.
They're making me sad.
Okay.
Tell me what he said.
He is having surgery to
remove bone and shrapnel.
What?
What's with the weird look?
- It's nothing.
- Hives, Maura.
Even white lies make you itch.
[ sighs ]
Okay.
Casey's condition is called
cauda equina syndrome.
From what I've observed in him,
it probably involves T-11
and 12 and maybe l-1.
Same question ...
why the weird look?
Surgery on a partially impaired
paraplegic is very risky.
- Well, you're not a neurosurgeon.
- You're right. I'm not.
So no guessing.
I just want to pretend
like it's all gonna be fine.
- Can you do that with me?
- I can try.
Salute, Elsie. Good girl!
Good salute, Elsie.
- That wasn't a salute.
- Yes, it was.
Looked like "shake" to me.
Jane: Anybody want a bagel?
Yeah. Thanks.
All right, so, where are we?
- We are nowhere.
- We better get somewhere
or Cavanaugh's gonna
tear off some heads.
Maybe I can help.
Thanks to the
team-building softball game,
the crime lab stayed up all night
to get these results to you.
I thought they were helping
us solve murders because ...
oh, I don't know...
it's their job.
The blue paint on the
floor mat is consistent
with the paint used for
the BCU field stencils.
That's right where the
killer would have been.
Frost, you said that
Enzo had season tickets.
- Was he at Saturday's game?
- No. His ticket wasn't used,
so I followed up with
his office manager.
- Enzo had to work on a wedding cake.
- It was the first game of the season,
which means Enzo didn't transfer
that field paint inside his van.
Maybe our murderer did.
I didn't mean anything when I
looked at it, but watch this.
Enzo was watching this
clip from Saturday's game.
What kind of call is that?
Jane: Coach Phillips?
What do we know about him?
Jane, what would be the motive? Enzo
hadn't played for him for five years.
Phillips was a contender for
a division I coaching gig.
It went away after BCU lost
that season five years ago.
Am I disappointed?
Yeah, yeah, I'm disappointed.
Coaching a division
1 team is a dream of mine.
But, uh, BCU ...
we had a great run there [sighs]
Till Enzo hurt himself.
Sounds like phillips blames Enzo.
Well, that blue paint only tells us
that our killer was on that field.
Frost, you get the phone working yet?
No.
Got to put the battery back in.
Okay, I want to see what
else Enzo was watching
the night before he was killed.
- His laptop is in bric.
- Okay.
Sergeant Korsak, did Casey tell
you why he needed you to take Elsie?
No. He just said she might
need a home for a few months.
He mentioned something I
didn't want Jane to hear.
What was that?
He made me promise I
would take care of Elsie
if anything happened to him.
- Hey, you guys coming?
- Yep.
Okay.
We got one shot at this.
If there's any moisture,
the circuits will fry themselves.
- Turn it on.
- Do I have witnesses?
Sergeant Detective Korsak
is telling me to turn this phone on.
Turn the damn phone on, Frost.
I want it in writing that this
one is not on me if this phone...
It's dead.
So much for your rice idea.
This is the whole list of
video files Enzo was watching.
Can you play that one?
BCU going for the money
with a hand-off to end zone.
Wow! Look at Womack
as he breaks to the
strong sie and ... oh, no!
He's not getting up.
Folks, this does not look good.
Ugh.
Why was Enzo watching that?
You see the right guard?
- Yeah.
I didn't.
What are you talking about?
Let's see that again.
The normally sure-footed right guard
looks like he slips on the turf.
And there goes hard-charging Der'on
Martin flying in at full speed.
Enzo is down! Ouch!
Frost, play that clip
from Saturday's game.
Marcus to the right on a hand-off.
Oh! How did that happen?
Looks like BCU's right guard
lost his footing and left
running back Jeff Marcus
unprotected for that nasty hit.
Ouch! It reminds me of that hit
that ended Enzo Womack's
carer five years ago.
I think we just figured
out what got Enzo killed.
Oh! That was a nasty hit.
What? What did ...
what did you see?
I'd like to know what got Enzo killed.
Both BCU right guards, who
played five years apart,
faked the same trip on the same play.
Frost: To make sure their running
back got tackled and didn't score.
This is like the day I took
that A.P. calculus exam.
You know, I couldn't
have solved that inverse
derivative problem if
my life depended on it.
Calm down.
Calm down, okay?
For once, I get to
explain something to you.
Frost, can you freeze
both bad plays?
[ keyboard clacking, computer beeps ]
That right guard and at
least one other player ...
probably the quarterback...
fixed that game in 2007.
Okay, and that right guard
fixed the same play five years later.
Are you saying BCU players from
two separate seasons threw games?
Altered games. It's too easy
to get caught if you throw them.
If you just shave points...
Frost, can we see both quarterbacks?
[ keyboard clacking, computer beeps ]
Yeah, right there.
Both quarterbacks
made identical signals.
That says to me,
"we're throwing the play."
Watch their eyes right
before they tap their helmets.
Jane: Yeah, you're right.
We have a shot caller ...
who are they looking at?
Frost, do you have any other angles?
So, Enzo must have realized
the trip that ended his
career wasn't accidental.
But why would the
right guard fake a trip?
Enzo was his teammate.
The players who were cheating
weren't trying to hurt him.
They were just trying
to keep him from scoring.
To change the over/under.
- That's what this is about.
- Of course.
What?
Over/under what?
Over/under is a type of bet.
Oddsmakers announce a number
before a game. It's their
best guess of what the
final combined score will be.
And I can bet over
or under that number.
- Yes.
- Okay, I think I understand.
So if the teams' scores,
when added together,
are lower than predicted, I win.
Yes. And if you know that
there are dirty players
that are fixing the game
to keep the score down,
you bet on the under,
and then you win big.
Yeah, but why would
a college player cheat,
especially at a prestigious
academic university?
Well, BCU is a division 3
football program.
There's no money, no scholarships.
They're having a car-wash
fundraiser to buy equipment.
Got another angle...
sideline camera.
Coach Phillips is the shot caller.
I don't think so.
Play it again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, play both the 2007
game and Saturday's game.
Watch Mackenzie.
You see that?
He dropped the towel both times.
[ cellphone chimes, beeps ]
Uh, the results are back on the
substance found in Enzo's wounds.
It's analgesic heat rub.
And the fibers I found were
from cotton sports tape.
Maura...
you said the murder weapon had a hilt?
Could it be a multipurpose
tool, like this one?
Yes.
[ cellphone rings ]
Is that Enzo's phone?
Okay, you don't get
credit for fixing it.
- Give it to me.
- No.
- I can look at cellphones, too.
- Give it to me and let me plug it in.
Thank you.
Here's his last text message.
To Dan Mackenzie, 7:54 A.M.
Right before he went to the car wash.
"Need to talk. I hope I'm crazy.
I think coach has BCU
players shaving points."
- He thought his coach was dirty.
- "I hope I'm crazy."
We didn't want to accuse
the program he loved
unless he was sure he was right.
So he went to the person
he trusted the most ...
his former teammate Dan Mackenzie.
It shouldn't be so swollen.
How many times I got to tell
you to ice this sucker, huh?
Hey, you can't be in here.
There's no women allowed.
- BCU just made an exception.
- Well, what's this about?
Frost: We checked your stats, Dan.
You were a good field-goal kicker.
But suddenly, you started missing.
- Was that when it started?
- When what started?
You were missing kicks to shave points.
I don't know what you
guys are talking about.
We're talking about basic greed.
Living pretty large for a guy making
$40,000 as a D-3 athletic trainer.
- I want a lawyer.
- You came up with this scheme in college,
but you knew Enzo wouldn't
cheat 'cause he was a good guy.
And he was going to
the pros. You weren't.
He ... he ... he was accusing
the team of cheating.
He was gonna give the
BCU program a bad name.
Enzo sent you a text
before you killed him.
He thought coach Phillips
was corrupting the players.
It never occurred
to him it was his friend.
You're under arrest for
the murder of Enzo Womack.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I know you wanted me to pretend
that everything will be fine.
- What's that?
- It's some research I did
on decompressive lumbar spine surgery.
- I don't want to know.
- Jane, you need to know.
Why? I mean,
he said goodbye, Maura, so...
Jane, if you care
about him, you'll look.
How bad is it?
Bad.
- What am I gonna do?
- I wish I knew.
sync & correction by f1nc0
~ addic7ed.com ~