This is a BNC news special report.
Reporting live from
Washington... Reed Wallace.
We have unconfirmed reports
that shots were fired outside
President Fitzgerald Grant's
birthday gala this evening.
And early reports suggest...
What?
Where is the President?
Why is he...
I've just been told
that the President
has gone to James Madison hospital.
Why has he...
Okay. I'm getting a
report now that confirms
that President Grant
was not wounded.
He was wounded?
Speak up.
(Crowd cheering and shouting)
(Two gunshots)
(Crowd screaming)
(Man) Falcon down! Falcon down!
(Man) Go!
(Indistinct shouting)
(Gasps)
(Siren wailing, helicopter
whirring overhead)
(Indistinct shouting)
I'm fine. Stop! Get away from me!
Get away from me!
(Man) - Ma'am...
(Mellie) - Where are my children?
(Monitor beeping rhythmically)
(Man) Ma'am,
I'd like to do an ultrasound.
(Mellie) I am fine.
(Man) Keep that clear!
Keep that clear!
Someone shot my husband!
You need to check on him!
(Defibrillator whines)
Charge at 300.
Charge.
Clear.
(Man) I.V.'s blown.
Clear.(Voice echoing)
We need the central line.
Charging.
(Man) Let's go, people.
(Man, voice echoing)
Mr. President! Mr. President!
Look at me. Look at me.
You may not die.
Do you hear me?
(Normal voice) You may not die,
so stay with me.
Stay with me!
(Curtain rings swoosh)
(Mellie) Check on Fitz!
Check on Fitz!
(Man) You may not die!
(Gurney wheels rolling,
monitor beeping rhythmically)
(Projector and camera shutter
clicking)
Sync and corrections by bellows
www.addic7ed.com
We need briefings
on security and defense.
We need to raise
the threat level...
Oh, my God. We need to suspend
the stock exchange.
I don't know anything.
I'm not... I'm not keeping
anything from you.
I just...
They're not
telling us anything.
- Is the President alive?
- Edison.
I'm sorry. It's just...
There's a lot of fear out here.
- I have armed escorts.
- They're putting you in the bunker.
Along with
the speaker of the house
and the entire cabinet.
I'm sorry.
You know I don't have a choice.
I have to go to the bunker,
or else I'd... I'd be there
with you, Liv.
I know how hard this must be
for you.
(Cell phone beeps)
(Indistinct conversations)
(Gasps)
I bought it at auction.
President Eisenhower wore it
when he was in office.
There are
only 48 stars on it.
It's very rare.
- You didn't have to.
- I know.
It's your inauguration day.
I wanted to give you
something special.
You are
my something special.
(Chuckles) We said we'd stop
when you were President.
Well, I'm not President
for another...
- 23 minutes.
- Mm.
Liv. I didn't know
you were here already.
I just got here.
(Laughs)
Oh, isn't this the best day?
Can you believe
this is happening?
I read a biography
on Dolley Madison
when I was 10
that I loved,
and now I live in her house,
do her job.
Ooh, Fitz, that's a nice pin.
Where'd you get it?
It was Eisenhower's.
Well, that's just...
(Chuckles)
That is fantastic.
You are wearing
Eisenhower's pin.
The press is gonna love it.
Right, Liv?
- Right.
- Oh.
I, Fitzgerald Thomas Grant III,
(Camera shutter clicking)
Do solemnly swear...
I,
Fitzgerald Thomas Grant III,
do solemnly swear...
That I will faithfully
execute the office
of President
of the United States...
That I will faithfully
execute the office
of President
of the United States...
And will,
to the best of my ability...
Preserve, protect,
and defend
the constitution
of the United States.
Preserve, protect,
and defend
the constitution
of the United States.
So help you God?
So help me God.
Congratulations,
Mr. President.
(Cheers and applause)
(John Philip Sousa's "Stars
and stripes forever" playing)
Where do you want
to put the interns?
I have all the speeches
from the campaign.
Do you want to keep them handy,
or should I archive them?
Did you bring dresses?
- I'm sorry?
- For the inaugural balls tonight.
You brought dresses, right?
Uh, yes. But you're our boss,
and you're working,
- so it's...
- Go.
Go and put on your gowns
and have fun.
Right now.
That's an order.
Really?
Really. Go.
(Laughs)
Um, thank you.
You're... (Sighs)
Thank you.
(Projector and camera
shutter clicking)
You are literally... literally
standing me up for the ball.
I can't take you
to the inaugural ball.
You knew
that I couldn't take you.
I am not like you.
I am traditional.
I am not interested
in flaunting my secrets.
I am not some dirty little
secret. I am your boyfriend!
James, I love you,
but I'm already late.
Can we have this
conversation another time?
Or we could...
Just go!
(Door opens)
(Exhales deeply) Hey, Liv.
Cy.
I was just filling in a reporter
on some inaugural ball details.
(Chuckles) Of course.
I'm heading out to meet
the President and Mellie
at the party ball.
You want a ride?
I have a limo.
I'm not gonna go.
I hate dancing.
Oh. All right.
I'll see you later.
Mm-hmm.
(Waltz playing)
♪
(Telephone rings)
(Ring)
This is Olivia Pope.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
It's my office.
Not bad, huh?
You're supposed to be
at the inaugural ball.
I was
at four inaugural balls,
and now I'm here...
With you.
Where's Mellie?
Two floors
and a whole wing away.
Mr. President.
I like that.
Say it again.
Mr. President.
Mm-hmm.
(Giggles) We can't.
- We can.
- Mm.
(Breathing heavily)
Look around you.
Look where we are.
This can't happen,
not anymore.
(Sighs)
(Exhales deeply)
I think it can happen
right there on that desk.
No.
We decided we have to stop.
I spent
the whole night dancing,
but never with the one person
I actually wanted to dance with.
(Breathing heavily)
Mm. Stop.
No.
(Clatter)
Stop. Stop.
No.
Stop, Fitz. Fitz.
Whew!
(Exhales)
We can't stop.
I can't.
You're the most important
person in my life.
I can't just stop.
Can you?
(Panting)
(Moans)
(Breathing heavily)
♪
The video we're showing
you here suggests
that Grant sustained either
three or four bullet wounds.
The doctors at
James Madison hospital
have yet to release any specific
information about his condition,
although we believe he is in surgery.
(Crowd screaming and shouting)
The White House has to be,
uh, I mean, it's not surprising
that they're remaining silent.
The person making a statement
for the White House
would normally be
the press secretary,
but as I told you earlier...
(Camera shutter clicks)
Press secretary Britta Kagen
was one of those seriously injured...
(Gunshots, crowd screaming)
In the attack
on President Grant.
No word yet on her condition.
The magnitude
of what's going on...
We can forgive them a moment
of chaos within this crisis.
Of course,
there are protocols in place,
the first being that
priority one for the country
is securing the Vice President.
(Camera shutter clicks)
Do we have any information
on the location of Vice
President Sally Langston?
We're going directly to the
Naval Observatory, ma'am.
We're going to the South lawn
of the White House.
We have strict orders to
escort you to the observatory.
The pilot's a marine, correct?
Yes, ma'am.
I am the acting
commander in chief.
He is following my orders,
and I am ordering him
to take me to the South lawn
of the White House.
You are welcome
to catch a ride.
We must all join hands
and pray for our President
who fights bravely
to hold on to life.
And as you bow your heads
and ask for God's mercy,
rest assured, I am in place
in the White House
and in charge
of this situation.
God bless President Grant
and God bless America.
(Mutes TV)
- Liv will call if she needs us.
- Maybe she's wounded.
Maybe that's why we
haven't heard from her.
Did the news say she was wounded?
- No.
- Then she's not wounded.
(Harrison) - This is out of control.
- Did that just happen?
Did she actually just land
on the South lawn
of the White House?
Where is she?
Is she in the oval?
If she's in the oval...
(Indistinct conversations)
(Cyrus) Are you the President?!
No!
You're not!
Why?
Because...
I want the senior
communications staff gathered
and ready to brief me
in 20 minutes.
- You...
- Jeannine.
Hi, Jeannine.
Go to my apartment.
(Keys jangle) Secret
service has the address.
Get me one gray suit,
one blue suit,
one black suit, six blouses,
three pairs of shoes,
some underwear,
and my toothbrush.
Bring them to me here.
Ms. Pope.
Yes?
Does this mean...
Are you...
Back?
Yes.
I'm back for as long
as you need me.
Everything really is
going to be okay.
Do you know who lands
on the South lawn?
Cyrus, you are way out of...
The President
of the United States.
The man has
a bullet in his head.
The country needs leadership.
- The world needs leadership.
- He may have a bullet in his head,
but it's still his lawn, Sally.
I am in charge now, and...
No! You're not in charge!
Have you read
the whole constitution,
or did you stop in rapture
after the second amendment?
I have had quite enough of this.
Allow me to summarize
the 25th amendment for you.
In the case of the removal
of the President from office
or of his death
or resignation,
the Vice President
shall become President.
Since none of these things
have happened,
the only way
you're President
is if the President himself
signs power over to you,
or you gather the
signatures of the cabinet.
And that may have all been
a little confusing to you,
so let me summarize further
and tell you simply
that if the President dies,
I'll call you.
Until then, these men
are going to take you to a
secure, undisclosed location.
The hell they are.
I'm not going anywhere.
By being where you are
not supposed to be,
you are threatening the
security of this great nation.
These men are under orders
from the Department
of Homeland Security
and the Secretary of Defense
to take you
to a secure location.
Now you can walk out,
or they can carry you out.
And it makes no difference
to them, because guess what...
They serve at the pleasure
of the President,
and you...
Are not the President.
For the record...
(Kisses) The honor and privilege
of being here,
standing on such hallowed
ground, helping our President
set his agenda
for his first hundred days...
It never leaves me.
I'm so grateful,
madam Vice President,
because I'm gonna need your help
selling some big ideas.
I'm looking forward to it.
And I understand that part
of the first hundred days
will now be nominating
a supreme court justice.
That would be correct.
Who knew this chance
would come so quickly?
I know. It's so exciting.
I'll be giving you my names
by the end of the week.
Names?
That was the deal when Sally
signed on to our campaign.
I promised her first crack
at nominating a justice
if a vacancy occurred.
(Projector and camera shutter
clicking)
Thought perhaps you'd like to be
briefed on a few things, sir.
I am not a runner.
I hate running.
I'm only running so the leader
of China or Pakistan or whatever
can see photos of me running
and decide I'm too badass to pop.
I thought you might want to know
where the cameras are, sir.
Cameras?
The surveillance cameras...
(Panting) In the White House.
There are cameras?
Every morning, an agent reviews
the footage from those cameras
and either erases or archives
that video depending on...
- What you see?
- Yes, sir.
And I take it there's a camera
in the oval office.
- Yes, sir.
- And you reviewed
the footage the morning
after the inaugural ball.
I have not seen anything
worth archiving, sir,
not on my shift. But it won't
always be on my shift.
You understand, sir?
(Birds chirping)
What are my options?
Sir?
You just told me there are
surveillance cameras
all over the White House.
I'm asking where
aren't there cameras?
(Projector and camera
shutter clicking)
The state of the union
address is about the future.
It should be a showcase
of everything you believe.
A comprehensive, nonpunitive
immigration policy
is something I believe in.
That can't be your highlight.
It's not strong enough to...
It's what we ran on.
Immigration is noble,
but it doesn't light a fire.
If you can't see...
(Laughing)
We can't touch defense
or social issues.
It might upset the base.
I'm just saying.
And I'm saying
we need to be bold,
look forward, make a statement
with lasting impact.
(Grunts and pants)
Immigration policy
will get us a generation
of voters, maybe two.
(Grunts)
Fitz, stop running
for President
and start being President.
(Moans)
(Laughs)
Youth is the future.
Youth is the next generation.
You get young people involved
in volunteering.
You give them a stake
in the country's future...
And a credit
towards college tuition,
and you announce it
at the state of the union,
and any member of congress who
doesn't stand and applaud you
loses every parent
in their constituency.
That is...
That's gold.
What is that smell?
Fresh air,
sunshine,
the great outdoors.
Fresh air makes me
very nervous.
I'm an indoor person.
That's what the person
I was dating says.
Said.
(Birds chirping)
You should call James.
I bet he misses you.
Worst-kept secret
in Washington.
(Exhales deeply)
I am a leader
of the republican party.
It's complicated.
It's not. You want to be
with the man you love.
Be with him.
I'm an indoor person,
Liv.
(Knock on door)
Mellie, what are you...
(Laughs)
Surprise! (Laughs)
Honestly, I had to come.
The kids just left to go back
to boarding school,
and I'm not used to being all
alone in the White House yet,
so I just thought,
why not come up here,
see how the state of the union
speech is going?
It's going great.
Yeah, I told Mellie our sessions
have been very productive.
Yes.
Well, I would love to hear
all about it over dinner,
which is why
I'm at your door.
Fitz said you wouldn't want
to have dinner,
but I said,
of course you would.
Of course.
In a few moments, we're gonna
take you live to the White House
where former White House
communications director
Olivia Pope
will hold a briefing.
Pope, of course, was
part of the storied team
that ran President Grant's
election campaign.
When she left
the administration,
it was a move
that surprised many.
The choice to hand the podium
to Pope is unusual,
but I am told that there's been
a lot of chatter of support
for Pope's display of patriotism...
(Camera shutters clicking)
In stepping up at this time
of extraordinary crisis.
President Grant is in surgery.
His condition is described
as critical,
as is the press secretary.
The first lady was unharmed.
Any further updates
about the medical condition
of the President
and press secretary Britta Kagen
will come from the chief
of surgery at the hospital,
not from this podium.
Specific questions
about the attack
are being handled by the FBI.
Ashley.
Is the Vice President
acting as President?
The President is
still the President.
There are reports the first lady
is being treated for...
The first lady is
not being treated.
Why haven't we seen her then?
The first lady is staying
at the President's side.
She was not harmed.
The Vice President just landed
on the South lawn.
Why isn't she briefing us
instead of you?
The Vice President
isn't briefing you
because
our national security protocols
demand that her safety
be secured above all.
- Where's Huck?
-I think he had a date.
I wonder if he told her
he used to be a spy.
(Ashley) So the secret service
took her from the oval office
and just threw her
in the basement?
Nobody threw anybody
anywhere, Ashley.
If I'm ever shot, I want her
running the press conference.
Makes you wonder why she ever
left the White House.
...And equipped with
state-of-the-art communications
and a highly trained staff.
Livvie.
(Indistinct conversations,
phone ringing)
I haven't seen you.
I'm busy.
I'm busy, too, however,
I'm not sending my aides
to meetings
in an attempt to avoid you.
I'm busy.
(Lowered voice)
Olivia, I miss you.
You walked her
to my cabin door.
I didn't have a choice.
I don't know
what you expect.
I don't want to be in this.
This is...
- I am not this person.
- Look...
(Lowered voice)
I know this is difficult.
Difficult? Are you...
Ahem.
Somehow,
I've become this person who...
I have no words.
We are together.
(Whispers)
That's all that matters.
Really? Because I'm feeling
a little, I don't know,
Sally hemings/thomas Jefferson
about all this.
I have to go.
Livvie.
I have a meeting with Cyrus.
I'm afraid we're just
backed into a corner
on this one, verna.
When Sally signed
on to the campaign,
- Fitz had to promise that...
- I don't care what he promised.
Justice Williams has a year,
maybe two left in him, tops,
before he retires, so we'll get
another shot at this.
You're a slam dunk for
the next spot on the court,
- but we can't just...
- Have you two lost your minds?
I whored every ounce
of my integrity
to get that man elected,
and here you are,
sitting on mount Olympus,
telling me to go be
a good mortal,
and we'll send down some nectar
when we find the time.
No, sir.
No how.
Make it happen.
(Door closes)
The Detroit teachers union
seems to have decided
that now would be a good time
to go on strike.
Kim jong-il is engaging
in some fairly serious saber
rattling in the yellow sea,
and there have been six more
allegations of sexual misconduct
at the n.A.T.O. Base
in east Sudan.
So it's an easy day.
Oh, I also got a call
from some reporter
about some kind of
voting irregularities in Ohio,
- but it's nothing I can't handle.
- What was their name?
Oh, Richard something.
I'll take care of it.
No, I got it.
Give me his number.
Huck, it's Olivia Pope.
Can you do me a favor?
Morris.
Ms. Pope.
- I gave him some funyuns...
- Thank you.
But I couldn't let him
on the grounds.
I understand. Huck?
The reporter you asked about
got his information
from a Jesse Tyler.
He's an employee
of Cytron software
in palo alto, California.
Where have you been living?
A halfway house
on 6th street.
Huck, you live with me now.
But some clippers, give yourself
a haircut, take a shower.
- And, Huck?
- Yeah?
Take that shower before you
touch anything in my apartment.
Mm-hmm.
A Jesse Tyler is
calling some reporter,
hinting at voter fraud
in Ohio.
That boy's proving to be
a right pain in my oysters.
You know him.
Been calling my office,
looking to shake me down.
Appears he's trying
to call my bluff.
You need to handle this.
Don't you worry a bit
about it.
Young Mr. Tyler's punching
way above his weight.
I got this, darlin'.
(Projector and camera shutter
clicking)
(Crickets chirping)
What's wrong?
(Sighs)
You pace in circles
when something's wrong.
When you're just thinking,
it's back and forth,
but when something's wrong...
Circles.
Did you need something,
Mr. President?
See, you used to sound sexy
when you called me
"Mr. President."
Now it just sounds like
I'm a gym teacher.
Did you need something?
The Sally hemings-
Thomas Jefferson comment
- was below the belt.
- Because it's so untrue?
You're playing the race card
on the fact
that I'm in love with you?
(Scoffs)
(Laughs)
Come on. Don't belittle us.
It's insulting
and beneath you
and designed to drive me away.
I'm not going away.
I don't have to
drive you away.
You're married,
you have children,
you're the leader
of the free world.
You are away.
By definition, you're away.
You're unavailable.
So this is about Mellie?
N-no! This is...
(Crying)
I smile at her and I take off
my clothes for you.
I wait for you.
I watch for you.
My whole life is you.
I can't breathe
because I'm waiting for you.
You own me. You control me.
I-I belong to you. I...
You own me!
You control me.
I belong to you.
You think I don't want to be
a better man?
You think that I don't want to
dedicate myself to my marriage?
You don't think
I want to be honorable,
to be the man
that you voted for?
I love you.
I'm in love with you.
You're the love of my life.
My every feeling is controlled
by the look on your face.
I can't breathe without you.
I can't sleep without you.
I wait for you.
I watch for you.
I exist for you.
If I could escape
all of this
and run away with you...
There's no Sally
or Thomas here.
You're nobody's victim,
Liv.
I belong to you.
We're in this together.
(Footsteps depart)
We're gonna be here
all night with you.
Once again,
some three hours ago,
President Grant was shot
entering his birthday gala a...
I'm being told right now
that White House press secretary
Britta Kagen
succumbed to her injuries
in surgery
and was pronounced dead
only moments ago.
Britta Kagen was 32 years old.
She has 2 daughters,
ages 5 and 3.
She started her career here
at BNC.
(Paper rustles)
Let's go to Vanessa Leone
who's live at the vigil
in Lafayette Square.
(Cell phone rings)
- You all right?
- They just let us out of the bunker.
What the hell is going on
over there?
What do you mean?
The Vice President
is making a play.
She spent the last two hours
lobbying cabinet members
about signing over
the presidency to her.
She what?
All she needs is a majority...
Eight signatures,
and she's home.
She's two away.
Traitorous bastards. Jeannine,
get the cabinet in here.
- The whole...
- Yes! The whole cabinet.
Cyrus, there's another way.
Sally set the narrative
that Fitz is dying,
on top of which
there's all sorts of rumors
about Mellie and the baby.
People are scared.
There's only one person
who can turn this around,
who can assure the public,
and stop Sally in her tracks.
(Whispers) Mellie.
(Gasps) Is he dead?
(Normal voice) What?
They told me when they
took him into surgery
there was a chance
he might die on the table.
They seemed
kind of scared of me,
so I thought
they'd ask you to come in
and tell me that he was dead,
which would be...
Is he?
I don't...
I don't know anything. No.
(Exhales deeply)
Mellie, I'm sorry, but I need
to talk to you a...
Don't sit down next to me
like we are friends.
Sally Langston
is knocking on the door
of the oval office.
You need to make sure
the American people don't open
the door and let her in.
(Gasps)
(Sighs)
I'll need something to wear.
(Projector and camera
shutter clicking)
Apparently,
everything is color-coded.
There are tags
on each dress
indicating the date
and the event.
- Shoes have corr...
- Thank you.
But there's more.
Thank you.
(Door closes)
(Crying)
(Sniffs)
That's the constitution,
the actual constitution.
You want to touch it?
I'm not touching it.
- Touch it.
- No.
There are, like, six people
in the last hundred years
who touched the constitution.
- Be the seventh.
- You be the seventh.
I'm the sixth.
I touched it four seconds ago.
You didn't wait for me.
It's the constitution.
(Whispers) Wow.
"We the people."
That's just...
That's...
Just...
That's everything.
(Whispers) It's a new world.
It's a new world.
(Whispering)
I love you, too.
I'm in love with you, too.
(Sniffles)
(Whispers)
So we're in this together?
We're in this together.
(Crying)
(Sobbing)
(Stops crying)
(Sniffles)
(Clears throat)
(Sighs)
(Inhales and exhales deeply)
Let's talk about the first lady.
If, God forbid,
her husband were to die,
things would happen rapidly
for her.
Jackie Kennedy was forced
to discuss housekeeping details
with lady bird Johnson
four days after
the assassination
of President Kennedy,
and she was
out of the White House
within two weeks of his death.
One hopes that Mellie Grant,
pregnant with America's baby,
would be afforded
a far different outcome.
First of all, I'd like
to offer my condolences
to the family of Britta Kagen.
(Camera shutters clicking)
She served this country
honorably,
and we all owe her
an enormous debt.
I'd like to thank Hal Rimbeau,
the secret service agent
who took a bullet last night
but continues to stand watch
over my family.
I would also like to thank
those of you who have put
my husband in your prayers.
Not only is my husband
a religious man,
he's a man who believes
that hope has power.
So...
Having America pulling
for him...
(Sighs)
Well, that just means
the world to him.
Now...
About my husband's health...
There have been rumors...
Rumors that are not only
hurtful to my family,
they are hurtful
to this country,
so let me put them to rest.
America has a President...
A living President,
and his name is
Fitzgerald Grant.
He hasn't given up on you,
so please don't give up on him.
(Camera shutters clicking)
Thank you.
(Camera shutter clicks)
(Mellie) Get his good side,
gentlemen.
Focus on her.
She's better-looking.
(Laughs)
- Oh, your flag pin.
- What?
- Your flag pin's missing.
- Oh, I must have lost it somewhere.
(Chuckles)
(Clicking continues)
It's called 50/50.
You go out into the community
for two years,
tutor inner-city kids,
build homes, help with
environmental cleanup,
work for next to nothing,
and in return, we give you
money for college.
And your boss proves once again
that he's a conservative
in name only.
We need you to help sell it.
It's a boondoggle,
but I'll sell it.
Super.
But let me remind you again
that there is a vacancy
in the supreme court,
and I've made my decision.
My choice is
Bradley Hargrove.
I want him trotted out
in grand style,
confirmed by congress,
without so much as a scratch.
I'll inform the President
of your choice.
Glad to be a team player, Cyrus.
(Door opens)
(Door closes)
Do I have to do it,
or can you?
It has to be you.
I need to talk to you
privately.
No. We are not
getting back together.
I want
to give you something.
Besides the last year
of my life back?
James.
You won
what I'm giving you.
A story?
A name.
A nomination. Come on.
They're saying hargrove,
my nominee,
- had a juvenile record.
- Well, does he?
He was 15. It was
supposed to be sealed.
We can counter this.
It's not too late.
No supreme court nominee
recovers from a hit like this.
Pay your maid
with the wrong checkbook,
and you're toast.
But a criminal record?
His nomination's
as good as dead...
- Sally...
- And I think you killed it!
I think you made promises
you never intended to keep
because you needed me
on the ticket.
Well, let me make a promise
to you.
I am in this for me now!
Based on the gaggle,
you can expect the usual
"what'll be
in the state of the union?"
And the S.C.O.T.U.S. put
Verna's name out there,
so you'll get questions
about that.
Oh, and you may get asked about
this explosion in California.
What explosion?
In Palo Alto,
a software company blew up.
- Seven people killed.
- Terror connection?
Uh, too soon to say.
Could be an angry girlfriend.
Anyway, the company's name
is Cytron, if it comes up.
(Projector and camera shutter
clicking)
What did you do?
Did you blow up that office?
Did you kill seven people?
You said to take care of it.
I took care of it.
I didn't say to commit
cold-blooded murder.
We all done what we done.
Can't get your cherry back.
(Exhales)
(Whispers) Seven people.
Collateral damage.
Jesse Tyler could've ended
this presidency before it began.
We're in this thing.
There's no turning away
if things get a tad messy.
You don't get that,
you're living in a fantasy.
(Camera shutters clicking)
He came through the surgery
well.
We were able to remove
all three bullets,
and his intracranial pressure
is coming down,
but he's still unresponsive.
Okay.
So what do we do now?
We wait.
How long?
We don't know.
Truthfully, it could be a day.
It could be a week.
You have got to give me
something more, Dr. Carroll.
You have got to,
because "I don't know"
is not an acceptable answer.
There was a lot of damage,
Mrs. Grant.
At this point,
he's lucky to be alive.
(Crying)
Even with
the cabinet members' votes,
there might still be a way
to avoid this.
Cyrus. We find any
technicalities, even small ones,
exploit them to their fullest.
Cyrus, stop!
It's over.
(Pants)
(Kisses)
Oh. Excuse me.
Sorry.
We're celebrating.
What's the occasion?
I-I...
He asked me to marry
him, and I said yes.
And we're gonna have
a wedding and a baby
- and a house in Georgetown
with a garden. - Eh.
Oh, do you need
to talk to him?
Because I'm engaged.
I could go plan things.
Okay.
(Chuckles)
(Door opens and closes)
What is it?
That explosion in California...
Cytron...
That was Hollis.
(Gasps and exhales deeply)
Thought it might be.
He killed seven people, Cy,
and he's setting some
poor innocent girl up for it.
Her name's Lindsay Dwyer.
How shall we handle this?
What'll we do?
There isn't anything
we can do.
What? There's always
something we can do.
Olivia, we're an hour and a half
from the state of the union.
We're an hour and a half
from giving kids
a chance to go to college,
an hour and a half from changing
this nation for the better,
so what exactly would you have
us do? Expose what we did?
Have Fitz resign?
Make Sally Langston
the President
of the United States?
Hollis is
a dangerous person.
We won.
Hollis isn't a threat to us.
No one's a threat to us,
because we won.
And it is sad what happened
to those seven people,
it is heartbreaking,
but they gave their lives
in service to their country.
Lindsay dwyer
will give up her freedom
in service to her country,
and that makes them
American heroes.
That makes them patriots.
And the best way that I can
honor their sacrifice
is to move on.
Buckle down.
Liv, how are you?
Excited for the state
of the union speech tonight?
- Yes. (Chuckles)
- I'm excited, too.
I read a final draft
of the speech.
You and Fitz
did an amazing job.
Thank you, Mrs. Grant.
Well, I have something
of yours.
The secret service found it.
You know Hal, right?
He's on p.O.T.U.S. Detail.
He found it the night
the President went
to the national archives
to view the constitution,
which surprised me,
because...
If he'd gone to
the national archives to view
the original constitution
of the United States,
he would've invited his wife,
but Hal said you were there.
So...
Mellie, I...
We all want the same thing.
You and me, Cyrus...
We are a team.
We got him
in the White House,
and we are going
to keep him here.
We are doing
our patriotic duty,
serving our country,
working
for the greater good.
We just...
Go about it differently,
I suppose.
You'll make sure
Fitz gets this?
(Whispers) Yes.
Thank you, Olivia.
(Applause)
We gather this evening with
a new mandate for America.
The American people
have made it clear
that they want an end
to partisan rancor,
and every new President
stands here
vowing that things
will be different,
and nothing changes,
so listen to me carefully now.
This time will be different.
(Cheers and applause)
(Indistinct shouting)
I dedicate this presidency
to bringing integrity back,
responsibility back,
governing back.
And I will remind
both my own party
and those across the aisle
every day,
that we have the sworn duty,
the sacred obligation to not
just pay lip service,
but to actually, finally,
and definitively do better.
(Cheers and applause)
And so I leave you
with this pledge.
At this time, in this place,
with this presidency,
it... will... be... different.
(Cheers and applause)
(Projector and camera shutter
clicking)
I, Sally Margaret Langston,
do solemnly swear...
(Reed) President Sally Langston
makes history today
as not only the first President
to take office
under section 4
of the 25th amendment,
but also as the first female
commander in chief.
And will,
to the best of my ability...
And will, to the best
of my ability...
The President remains in...
And I call him "President"
because technically, he is
still President as well...
President Grant remains
in critical condition.
There is no more information
on his status at this time.
(Verna) So help you God?
So help me God.
Congratulations,
madam President.
Thank you.
All we can do as a nation
is pray.
(Monitor beeping rhythmically)
The FBI is issuing
what's called a high alert,
and they... they do have
a description of a suspect.
The suspect is dark-haired,
average height and build,
possibly with a buzz cut,
seen entering
the Stanworth Hotel
wearing a red hoodie.
This is
America's most wanted man.
Average height, average build,
wearing a red hoodie...
In Washington, D.C.,
home of the Redskins,
that narrows it down
to about 100,000 people.
Don't.
(Sighs)
We're gonna be here all night
with you.
Once again,
at 8:05 Eastern standard time,
some 14 hours ago,
President Grant was shot
entering his birthday gala.
(Cheers and applause)
(People screaming)
(Gunshot)
(Projector and camera
shutter clicking)
sync and corrections by bellows
www.addic7ed.com