If that letter from
President Grant was forged,
there will be joint
congressional hearings
- and letters of impeachment.
- Good-bye, Edison.
Previously on "Scandal"...
Which one of you
forged his signature?
- I did.
- It's a federal crime. It's treason.
I have a sworn affidavit
saying that your husband
has failed to so much
as open his eyes.
(Cell phone rings)
Hello?
Hi.
(Voice breaks) Hi.
(Projector and camera
shutter clicking)
Oh, hi.
"Oh. Hi"?
(Keys jangle)
Hello, Edison.
Olivia.
- What?
- What's going on? With us.
(Files rustling)
Nothing.
- Nothing's going on with us?
- Edison.
This serious boyfriend
that you had,
the one that you broke up with...
Look, I have a lot to do
tomorrow,
and I haven't had much sleep
and I'm not in the mood to...
This serious boyfriend...
Was it Fitzgerald Grant?
(Chuckles)
You're asking me
if I was in a relationship
- with the President?
- Yes.
- He's married.
- He's the President.
- Yes.
Is this a joke?
Are you kidding?
I'm waiting for you
to answer the question.
You're mad because
I wouldn't let you
into the President's
hospital room?
Not mad. Concerned.
Wary. Suspicious.
- Don't be. - Because the
President's not your boyfriend?
You really want to stop
asking me that.
I've been racking my brain
trying to find a reason
why you'd be stupid enough
to willingly attempt
to defraud the American people,
and the only reason
I can come up with
for why you'd be in so deep
is because you were his mistress.
Five...
that's sexist and insulting.
You'd never suggest
Scooter Libby
was screwing Dick Cheney.
Four... the lengths you're going
to try to twist this
into a conspiracy are
cause for concern.
You should speak to
someone about that.
Three... the President
is awake and talking,
and the suggestion that he isn't
is partisan political crap
that I thought you had
enough integrity to rise above.
Two...
in the past three minutes,
you've called me a criminal,
a whore,
an idiot, and a liar,
so this is pretty much the
last time we'll be speaking,
so one...who I am or
am not screwing,
what am or am not doing,
is no longer any of
your damn business.
You forget how well
I know you.
You this angry?
You have something to hide.
I have been summoned
to a meeting
at the white house tomorrow
with acting President Langston
about the letter
of reinstatement,
which she says is a forgery.
(Scoffs)
And she's going to tell that
to the entire cabinet
first thing in the morning.
So if there's something
that you want to tell me,
do it now, when I still
have time to help you.
(Beep)
Cyrus, we have a problem.
(Projector
and camera shutter clicking)
sync and corrections by bellows
www.addic7ed.com
Increasing our military
presence in Asia
costs money, Governor.
Which is why we'd have to
shift our defense spend...
Can't just run to daddy
and ask for the dough
on this one.
(Laughter)
(Lowered voice) Use the attack line.
Attack line.
Go to my web site.
Look at my spending plans.
- Do the math.
- Oh, no.
Now he's giving
the voters homework.
Fiscal budget, we can afford to
make this common reallocation.
I'm sorry, Governor.
We have to move on.
I deserve a chance
to respond.
You think you deserve
everything, don't you, Governor?
(Laughter)
No... (Chuckles)
No. If we could get
back to medicare.
Look. Look.
Governor Reston...
- I can't.
- Tell me when it's over.
You need 270 electoral
college votes to win, right?
And you've got 188 locked up
from the deep red states.
So you need a pickup
of 82 votes,
most likely from a
combination of Ohio,
Florida, Virginia, Colorado,
Nevada, North Carolina.
So, basically, you can't afford
to lose more than one of them.
- And if I do?
- You're toast.
Did the debate
move the needle at all?
Not in your favor.
I'm sorry, Governor.
Numbers don't lie.
(Projector and
camera shutter clicks)
As the individual helping
finance this little enterprise,
I'd like to start feeling like
I'm getting my money's worth.
We've still got a month left.
Plenty of time
to turn things around.
That's just whistlin'
past the graveyard.
- We need to do something.
- You have a suggestion?
Stack the deck.
I found a computer nerd
of my own,
says he can rig the election
for Grant, easy as pie.
- Very funny.
- Am I laughing?
(Lowered voice) Okay.
You saying "rig the election"
on a campaign plane is like
joking that you have a bomb
in the security line
at the airport.
You don't do it unless
you want to end up
having your body cavities
searched by big men with guns.
Whoa.
Just trying to help.
We got a problem.
I am a solution man.
Your solution is a felony.
Well, then,
you're the fix-it gal.
Quit bitchin'
and start pitchin'.
(Clears throat)
Those numbers are fatal.
What this campaign needs
is a big pointy boot
to kick it square in the ass.
I was thinking... (Sighs)
Maybe it's time
we brought in help.
- He's not gonna like it.
- He will learn to like it.
We talking about Jerry?
Fitz's father?
That's... that's brilliant.
I wondered why
he wasn't on the trail.
I figured maybe his health
wasn't good.
(Cyrus) Oh, it's good.
The good senator
Fitzgerald Thomas Grant II's
gonna bury us all.
Fitz has been very clear
about his father.
He'll never agree to it.
That was then.
This is 10 points down.
(Projector and camera
shutter clicking)
No! You know better!
You know!
We are losing!
We are lost!
I can win this on my own!
You have political capital!
You need to start spending it!
(Lowered voice) I need to
point out voices carry.
(Sighs) You might want to
either lower the volume
or continue this
conversation in a room.
You talk to him.
He actually listens to you.
(Beep, door opens and slams)
(Panting)
Fitz...
Mm?
We're all concerned that
the campaign needs a spark.
Your father could be it.
And I really don't want to
discuss my father right now.
(Exhales) Mm.
Your father...
Is a national treasure.
Self-made man,
two terms as...
Governor, 4-time senator.
I know.
The image of him passing on
the torch to his son...
That will ignite the base.
The press loves him.
Everyone loves him.
I don't want him here.
He can help.
You need help right now.
You really think
we're at that place?
We're at that place.
If I say yes,
will you stop talking
about the campaign
for the next 20 minutes?
Why?
Hmm...
(Gasps)
The bullet tore
through your frontal lobe.
We managed the swelling,
and with any luck,
the effects you see
will be minimal.
Effects such as?
Dizziness, fatigue, irritability.
The symptoms we commonly
associate with concussions.
And if they're not?
Our frontal lobes
control executive function.
So sometimes in patients
we've seen
an inability to make decisions,
a shorter attention span.
We've had patients who
haven't been able to write,
patients who suffer
from aphasia.
- Aphasia?
- Speech impairment?
Either you can't speak
at all, or if you can,
it's hard to find your words.
We'll also be on the lookout
for changes in personality.
It all depends on the patient.
That's why I want to get
a neurology team in here pronto
- and see where we are.
- So when can I get back to work?
Assuming there's no permanent
damage, three weeks.
(Sighs)
Walking across a room
will feel like a marathon.
(Knock on door)
Am I interrupting?
Thank you, doctor.
(Woman speaking
indistinctly over P.A.)
(Door closes)
What is it?
I'm afraid we have
a Sally Langston problem.
(Projector and camera
shutter clicking)
The letter of reinstatement
submitted on behalf
of President Grant
was entirely premature.
Regrettably, he is not
in any sort of condition
to resume the powers
and responsibilities
of this office at this time.
Understanding, as always,
that our first and only duty
is to the American people,
I have prepared a document
for your signatures
declaring that we are left no choice
but to challenge President
Grant's fitness...(Door opens)
To again assume...
Morning, everyone.
Sorry I'm late.
Are we sure this was
a good idea?
He's just gonna show his face,
shake a few hands,
hear ten minutes
of the briefing,
and go back to bed,
and Sally disappears forever
into that political black hole
called the vice presidency.
- He's looking great!
- Guy's a medical miracle.
Madame vice President,
how are you today?
(Laughs)
That was small of me.
I need to work on that. (Chuckles)
I need a fresh shirt.
Ask Izzie to send one down for me.
Why don't you we get you up to bed?
I have to get down
to the sit room.
Fitz, you did it.
You're back.
You're President.
You have nothing to prove.
Until Sally Langston
puts a letter on my desk
accepting my reinstatement,
I have everything to prove.
Have I thanked you for that,
by the way?
For forging my signature
and forcing me
out of the hospital
before my stitches
had healed
to save you from jail
and keep my job?
Thank you.
(Sighs)
I can't show any weakness.
This is not
a show of weakness.
You were shot. You've made
a miraculous recovery.
No one is expecting you
to spend five hours
in a military briefing.
Sally Langston
is dancing around the fire.
She's not gonna stop
until my head's on a stick.
They need to see me,
not her,
being commander-in-chief
of the armed forces.
I need a clean shirt.
And that's the difference
between Governor Reston and me.
My plan provides for $2 trillion
in discretionary spending.
Just say "spending cuts."
"Discretionary" confuses people.
$2 trillion in spending cuts,
which will save
Americans money
and stimulate growth.
Ah, to hell with spending cuts!
I want my taxes lowered!
(People murmuring) We titans
of industry built this nation.
We deserve to get a little relief
in these difficult economic times.
Everybody seems to forget
that the rich need help, too.
Boy, that sounded better in my head
than it did out loud, didn't it?
(Laughter)
Jerry! (Laughing)
(Laughing)
We are so glad that you came.
Anything for you.
Oh.
Mwah!
(Laughs)
Good to see you, Jer.
- Hello, Fitzgerald.
- Dad.
Everybody,
why don't we take a break?
No, no, no. Keep working.
I'm just furniture.
(People murmuring)
Hello.
(Man) - Good to see you, Jerry.
- Hi.
Where was I?
(Olivia) Uh, save Americans
money, stimulate growth.
Save Americans money
and stimulate growth
while reducing the national debt
by $5 trillion over the next 10 years
from a deficit that
right now increases
by an average of
$3.68 billion a d...
Wait, wait, this isn't
a funeral, son.
Perk up! You got the looks.
Add the charm. (Chuckles)
- As I was saying...
(Jerry) - Okay, go on.
$5 trillion from a deficit
that right now increases
by an average
of $3.68 billion a day.
A day.
When I am President,
I would...
Uh, no, no, no. Nobody wants
to hear all that math.
Here.
Let me show you how it's done.
Up, up, up!
(People murmuring)
Pleasure. (Sighs)
All right, sweetheart.
Feed it to me.
- A lot of people think this election
is about the economy. - Mm-hmm.
Tell us what differentiates
your economic plan
from Governor Reston's.
A mother is standing
on the sidewalk, choking.
She's, uh, swallowed
a penny accidentally,
and it's lodged in her throat.
A man in a suit comes by,
gives her the heimlich,
and out pops the penny.
Well, the... the woman says...
(Mouths words)
"Gosh darn,
I can't thank you enough."
And the guy in the suit said...
(Chuckles) "Oh...
Oh, no, I'm not a doctor.
I'm from the I.R.S.
and he snatched the penny
and he ran off.
That's what's gonna happen
if this guy wins the election.
Next question.
(Laughter and applause)
(People laughing hysterically)
(Jerry) No! No!
That's not the best part.
I come back from Nevada
after watching them test
a hydrogen bomb, and I see
these bruises on my chest.
So I go to an oncologist,
and I say,
"look at these bruises!
"I think I've been exposed
to radiation.
What should I do?"
And he looks at me
and he looks at my bruises,
and he says, "Nevada?"
And I go, "yeah."
He goes, "Jerry, that's
from leaning too hard
against the craps table."
(Laughter)
No, Verna was there.
She remembers.
- Well, I was more of a poker girl.
(Jerry) - Ah!
I bet she was.
(Laughter)
So when do you hit Florida?
Thursday.
You think you can join us, Jer?
- Hey...
(Fitz) - No.
You stump in Oregon.
I'll handle Florida myself.
(Laughs) Son...
Oh, no. You need me
in Florida.
No, I don't.
These young boys today.
They think they invented politics.
(Chuckling) We definitely
want you in Florida.
Did I say I want him in Florida?
(Mouths words) Look, I realize
you don't think I know anything,
but I've done more
in the past 20 years
than you'll do
in an entire lifetime.
You'll want me in Florida.
Unless you want to lose.
Do you want to lose, son?
(Scoffs)
(Swallows and sighs)
We'd be glad to have you.
So can I ask about
your campaign strategy?
No.
Honey. Why didn't you dig enough
dirt on Reston? (Liquid pouring)
We've had a clean campaign so far.
Fitz wants to keep it that way.
I think it's admirable.
Well, I think it's weak.
You want to win the presidency,
you have to attack, be strong.
Finish off your competition!
- You know this from experience?
- Fitz.
No, dad's giving me advice.
I'm just wondering
if it's from his vast experience
running for President.
Oh, yeah, you never ran, did you?
'Cause men who get caught
sleeping with prostitutes
don't get to be leader
of the free world.
Right?
Who wants coffee?
What was her name? Charity?
No, it was Hope.
Hard to forget that name.
You really kept hope alive,
didn't you, dad?
- Fitz.
- No, Hope is alive.
Mom's dead, though.
(Mellie) - Enough.
(Fitz sighs)
(Sets down glass)
Jerry, I'm so sorry.
It's fine.
We have all had a long day. Hmm?
And I think I'm gonna turn in.
Mwah! (Kisses)
Mm.
Mm. Mm.
(Chuckles and kisses)
(Lowered voice) We'll talk
about this in the morning.
(Elevator bell dings)
(Sighs and mutters)
(Indistinct conversations)
(Clears throat)
You didn't wait for me.
It's late.
We can talk in the morning.
Or we can go to your room, talk there.
Or...
Not talk.
(Sighs)
Fitz, you're drunk.
And you're sad.
You should get to bed.
(Slurring) - I'm trying to get to bed.
- Stop it.
Come on.
Really, no. No.
You want to talk, we can talk.
We can get a cup of coffee, you can
sober up, but... mnh-mnh. Mnh.
(Stammering) No...
Come on.
(Elevator bell dings)
Stop it.
Fitzgerald.
(Head thuds)
Oh...
(Sighs)
Um...
I'm sorry. I'm...
Sorry.
(Sighs)
Mellie...
I wanted to apologize for Fitz.
That's not like him, but he
has had too much to drink.
And he has always had
problems with his father,
and I just...
He respects you.
He needs you.
We both do, and...
I just don't want
what happened here tonight...
I'm so sorry.
I am.
I know how you must feel,
and I am so sorry.
It's okay.
Really.
I'm fine.
You don't have to apologize to me.
I don't know what he'd do without you.
I don't know what I
would do without you. (Chuckles)
(Breathes deeply)
(Projector and camera
shutter clicking)
The trouble with precision air
strikes is they're not precise.
There's too much
collateral damage.
Again, I think we should
have a S.E.A.L. team go in
and either capture or kill...
Kinyazi.
The east Sudan leader.
Send in a S.E.A.L. team
to capture or kill Kinyazi.
Yes, exactly.
Thank you all.
Mr. President.
(Projector
and camera shutter clicking)
There's no such thing as a
clean campaign! (Sighs)
It's an oxymoron!
From now on, you're...
There's still time
to call Hollis.
It's the only way
that you're gonna win this!
We don't have to put up with this.
(Shouting continues)
So we rig an election
instead, Cyrus?
I'm just saying it's an option.
I'm kidding.
(Door opens)
My son and I have had a talk.
We're gonna need oppo
on Reston. Everything...
S.A.T. scores,
parking tickets.
If he didn't put
the seat down once,
- we want to hear about it.
- Sir, with all due respect...
As I said before, we've been
running a clean campaign
since the primary.
Well, now I'm telling you
to get me some dirt
that we can pin on Reston.
- Sir, we don't work for you.
- We work for the Governor.
(Scoffs)
- Do we bring pillows to a
knife fight, son? - No, sir.
- Do we wanna run a real campaign?
- Yes, sir.
There you go.
Do what he says.
(Projector
and camera shutter clicking)
Harrison Wright, Abby Whelan.
The pleasure's all mine.
Hi.
Hi. Listen, we gotta
make this quick.
I got a meeting with the parole
officer in half an hour.
(Breathes deeply)
(Door opens)
Oh, God.
Oh.
I think he's coming
over here.
(Murmuring)
I'm Huck.
I brought you all here
to dig up some dirt
on the Reston campaign...
Disgruntled ex-girlfriends,
old coworkers...
Whatever we can find.
The dirtier, the better.
(Projector and camera shutter clicking)
- So this is politics, huh?
(Olivia) - What about
Mrs. Reston's accounts?
(Huck) Clean.
(Abby) So have you known
the restons a long time?
(Harrison) Talk to me.
What haven't they uncovered?
He was a rager. Crashed his car into
a tree after a Christmas party.
Excellent.
The only witness is a loyal,
and there's
no public record, so...
So dead intel.
Abby?
He was a man-whore.
With a temper.
- How bad? - He had a bevy of
pi-phis at his Beck and call.
Lots of them are still bitter
about his less-than-chivalrous
dating style.
But then he met Joan
and mellowed out.
(Projector and camera shutter clicking)
Stayed true, as far as I can tell.
- When did he meet Joan?
- '87.
Around the same time
he quit drinking.
You know, perhaps we need
more experienced and...
House-trained people
on this.
Sir, these people...
No more excuses.
If we don't get something on Reston,
something that sticks,
we may just as well
pull all of our ads, pack up camp.
Fitzgerald can't pull this
off on his own.
You know it and I know it.
(Projector and
camera shutter clicks)
We put all the lipstick
we can on this pig.
It's time to pony up
and seriously consider
all the options.
There are no options, Hollis.
Yes, there are.
I'm not saying I agree with it,
but we should discuss it.
(Lowered voice) Election rigging
is not an option.
(Lowered voice) I'm talking
about doing a patriotic thing.
You're not serious.
I may be a son of a bitch,
but Fitz is clean as a whistle.
Am I right, Cyrus?
He's the real deal.
A patriot.
A believer.
How rare is that?
How often does that come along?
Once in a generation,
if you're lucky.
I'm just saying,
this is our chance
to put a man with integrity
inside that big white house.
So you want to do this
because Fitz is so good? Really?
Doesn't matter why I want to do it.
It matters why you'd want to.
What are we talking about?
(Normal voice) Nothing.
(Normal voice)
Pull up a chair, Mellie.
Let's have a discussion.
Fitz is out on his feet.
He's weak,
has trouble concentrating,
plain as day.
Presiding over a national
security crisis...
It's damn near treason.
- He's nixed the air strikes.
- Ooh. He's what?
Do I bring him
before congress,
expose his unfitness
to the American people?
No. No.
You do nothing.
Just let him hang himself
with his own lasso.
Mulish pridefulness
about provin' himself
has always been
that boy's Achilles' heel
goin' back to him
and his daddy.
All you got to do
is lay back, be set,
step in once he crashes
and burns.
Your dad is helping.
The numbers are giving you
good news.
- Although...
- Although?
You're still 7 points down
overall.
(Groans)
Come on!
How was this not fixed earlier?
You!
You have done this before, right?
This is not your first time
plugging in a microphone?
We did hire someone who knows
how to do this job, right?!
Governor.
That's Jason.
And he's almost done fixing
the sound system.
- He just needs a minute.
- This is a town hall forum.
You got people spread
all around the room,
and I cannot hear
what they are saying!
What's the point of a debate
prep if I can't debate?
Everyone, good work.
But let's call it a night.
(Sighs)
Go home, get some sleep.
We'll start here again
at 7:00 A.M.
Not you.
Those people are working
their butts off for you.
- Then we need better people.
- Or we need a better candidate.
Screw you.
I am getting killed
in these debates.
I lose votes in these debates.
I need to be prepared.
Which is what we were doing when
you started yelling at people.
I am yelling because no
one is doing their job.
- Your job is to make sure I win.
- Good.
I was worried you thought
my job is to get felt up
in elevators
by my drunken candidate.
I'm sorry about that.
You know I'm sorry about that.
- Do you even want this?
- What?
Do you even want
to be President?
Obviously.
Is it obvious?
I'm running.
You're running like
you're being chased.
You're not running like you want
to cross the finish line first,
and so I'm asking you,
do you want it?
Or are you just wasting
everyone's time
and money and energy and
faith and hopes and dreams?!
- I want it.
- Why?
- Liv. - Why do you want
to be the President?
Okay, Olivia.
Why?!
I don't know what you
want me to say!
That's your problem.
You're always trying to say
what you think
everyone wants to hear,
be what you think everyone
wants you to be,
and I should have caught it before.
I would have if we weren't...
(Sighs)
I know you...
Because you let me know you.
But America has no idea
who you are,
because you've never let them
know who you are.
Nobody can tell you
how to do that.
I can't fix that, because
I'm not running for President.
Neither is Cyrus,
neither is your father,
so who are you,
and why do you
want to be President?
Mellie came to me.
I tried to stop it, but...
(Sighs) He's Fitz.
He'll look okay on tv, but...
- What? - The man is supposed
to be in the hospital,
and instead he's been
working all day.
(Lowered voice) I don't think
he'll last on his feet
more than 30 seconds.
You have to shut this down.
(Indistinct conversations)
(Door closes)
I hear someone
is being stubborn.
Cyrus sent you.
It might not be wise to
answer questions on live tv
in your condition.
It might not be wise,
but that's what I'm gonna do.
Mind telling me why?
What you said.
I'm stubborn.
(Exhales)
(Exhales and chuckles)
- You almost died.
- Yes.
- Don't do it again.
- Okay.
(Kisses)
(Sighs)
You can't do
this press conference.
You're not strong enough...
Not yet.
I'm doing the press conference.
Tell me why. Tell me why
it's so important to you.
(Groans softly)
This is my office.
I'm the President.
They can shoot me
if they want to,
but I'm not going anywhere,
because the people
of this country elected
me to this office,
and the people deserve to see me
and to know that I'm in charge.
(Knock on door)
(Door opens and closes)
Well?
He's doing the press conference...
Live.
And he's going to take
questions.
And it's gonna be great.
(Exhales)
Reston's narrative is that
he was an angry young man
until meeting his wife Joan,
who turned him into
the upstanding
public servant he is today.
Turns out it wasn't love
that fixed him.
- It was Prozac.
- Hmm.
(Projector and camera shutter clicks)
- But this isn't Reston's.
- We pulled it from his trash.
His doctors hide it
under a bunch of fake names,
but they all lead back
to Samuel Montrose Reston.
Fluoxetine.
60 milligrams a day.
For the past 20 years.
That's a pretty heavy habit.
My suggestion, if we choose
to go forward with this,
is to leak rumors
of prescription drug abuse
to the press
before the final debate.
It will take over
the news cycle
and prevent Reston from
being able to prepare properly.
That's a fine suggestion, honey,
but that's not what
we're gonna do.
We're gonna sit on it
until the debate itself.
And then you're gonna work it
into one of your answers
and blindside Reston
and send him up a creek
without a paddle
and demolish him in the process.
(Olivia) - Ahh.
(Jerry chuckles) - Huh?
If you need a rest or don't
know the answer to a question,
take a sip of water.
This is a press conference.
This is a town hall-style debate...
Real Americans
with real questions
looking to you for real answers.
Put them...
at ease. This isn't about
military strategy.
It's about convincing
the American people
that their commander-in-chief
is not just back,
but up to the job.
So I wait for a question
about the military?
That's when you drop the bomb.
Give them a choice
between a candidate
who's flown combat missions
and a candidate who takes
antidepressants.
Got it?
Fitz?
I got it.
Good.
Now show them who you are.
(Indistinct conversations)
(Applause)
(Camera shutters clicking)
At 5:00 this evening
eastern standard time,
a U.S. Navy S.E.A.L.team
parachuted into east Sudan
and captured its President,
Nijam Kinyazi.
(Reston)
The Governor's posturing, Carl.
He wants you to believe
that he's trustworthy,
that he's his father.
He's not his father.
His father was a self-made man.
The Governor...
he was made
on a boarding school assembly line.
He can't relate to you.
(Camera shutter clicks)
(Reporters shouting questions)
(Under breath) Here we go.
- Yes, Carol?
- What were the casualties?
- None on our side.
- And theirs?
I don't have numbers
for you yet,
but I'm told there were
several, all non-civilian.
(Reporters shouting questions)
Yeah. Peter?
Having just survived
an assassination attempt,
is there any concern
about P.T.S.D.
or impaired brain functioning that
could affect your judgment?
(Shutters clicking)
(Reporters murmuring)
Oh, boy.
(Clicking continues)
(Moderator) The next question
is for Governor Grant,
and it's from Jessica Moran.
- Jessica.
- Governor Grant...
Hi, Jessica.
As the mother
of an 18-year-old boy
who's about to enlist
in the army,
why should I trust you
as our next commander-in-chief?
(Under breath) This is it.
You know, people talk
about a lack of patriotism
in our country.
They're wrong.
And your son is proof of that.
Now, as for whether
you should trust me
as commander-in-chief...
Say it.
(Chuckles)
What I should say
is that I've served
in the military,
and I've flown combat missions,
and the courage that I exhibited
makes me fit
to lead this country.
That's what I should say,
because my pollsters
and aides and advisors
tell me that's what you
want to hear.
What the hell's he doing?
But the truth is, Jessica...
Those years I spent
in the Navy...
It wasn't courage I felt.
It was fear.
Fear that I'd crash.
Fear that the life
that I wanted to live
would end in a ball of flames
a million Miles from home.
It literally made me sick.
Now does that mean
that I am not fit
to be commander-in-chief?
(Camera shutter clicks)
(Projector clicks)
(Camera shutters clicking)
No.
In fact, I've never felt
more ready.
Weakness is our strength.
(Camera shutters clicking)
It's what makes us human.
- It's where our compassion
comes from. - I don't believe this.
Our humility.
All qualities that make for
a great commander-in-chief.
You can't have someone
protect you
if they don't know
what you're afraid of.
I know what you're afraid of.
I know what
your son's afraid of.
Why?
Because I'm afraid of it, too.
(Applause)
(Jessica) Thank you.
Works for me.
- Grant the protector.
- Yeah.
Pull the file on Reston's stint
as Baltimore D.A.
- We're painting him as soft on crime.
- Yeah.
(Applause,
camera shutters clicking)
(Fitz) Good night.
You knocked it
out of the park, sir.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
(Laughs)
So that's how you're gonna
win this thing, huh?
By taking out a hankie
and crying?
She teed it up for you
and you whiffed.
(Scoffs)
I know that I've won
fewer elections than you.
But not because you were
better than me,
because you are not.
You are a petty man.
You are an underhanded man.
You are a small man,
and I don't want to be you,
not now, not ever.
You're gonna lose
this election,
and it's gonna be
the end of this
so-called career of yours.
You're not cut out to lead.
You never were.
And I may be petty or whatever
else you want to call me,
but I'm a winner.
And that's something
you'll never be.
(Chuckles)
(Gate clatters)
Mr. President,
if I could have a word.
You're gonna need to move
this stuff out of here, Sally.
Of course. I'll send someone
right away.
What do you need?
I just wanted
to congratulate you
on kinyazi.
I didn't think a S.E.A.L. team
was the way to go. I was wrong.
These things don't always
break your way.
This time it did.
I always wanted
to give you this.
It's a copy of my letter
accepting your reinstatement.
When I questioned
your readiness to serve,
I was just thinking
about our country,
where it would leave us,
how it would make us look
to the world.
I wasn't rooting for you
to fail or die.
The truth is,
your getting shot
was the scariest thing
that ever happened to me.
I haven't slept a night
during this whole time.
It is not easy
being President.
Thank you, Sally.
You are welcome,
Mr. President.
Got my boy sleeping
with his phone under his pillow.
One call from me,
this election's ours.
- No. - We don't use him,
we're gonna lose this thing.
Or maybe you thought that
little math girlie was wrong
about how everything's gonna
shake out in Ohio.
I can't believe
we are having this conversation.
- Olivia, let's be practical.
- Mm.
- What do you want?
- What?
- What do you want out of this?
- I don't know.
Verna here is gonna be
supreme court justice
first time there's a vacancy.
Cyrus is gonna be
chief of staff.
Mellie... well, First Lady.
And what are you, Hollis?
I'm a guy everyone
sitting here owes a favor to.
Olivia, you need to think
about your future and decide...
What do you want?
- It has to be unanimous.
- Cyrus...
No, the only way we trust each other
is if everybody's ass is on the line.
If it's not unanimous,
we don't do it.
Then we don't do it.
(Sighs)
Governor?
Fitz, you all right?
My father had a heart attack
and died 20 minutes ago.
(Projector
and camera shutter clicks)
It was a very nice funeral.
I liked what you said
about your father.
It was a lie.
The story about the dog
he got me for my 10th birthday,
I made it up.
'Cause you can't get up
at your father's funeral
and tell the story about how
you sat outside his office door
on your 10th birthday and...
listened to him
bang his secretary.
(Grunts)
(Exhales)
I'm not sad.
I'm relieved.
I'm free.
(Wood clatters)
(Grunts)
And I want it, Liv.
(Axe clatters)
I want to win this election.
I'm going to win.
It's mine.
Do you think I'll make
a good President?
I think you'll make
a great President.
Put down the axe.
Put it down!
(Wood clatters)
Come here.
(Stifled crying)
(Sobs)
(Sobbing)
(Continues sobbing)
I'm changing my locks.
I wanted to talk to you,
and I didn't want
to wait in the hall.
We're done talking.
(Keys clatter)
I've been thinking about this.
Everything.
And you were right.
It was sexist to suggest
that you were in a relationship
with the President.
I was to wrong to think
that there was a conspiracy,
that someone forged
the President's signature.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
You forget that
I know you too well.
And so I know
when you are lying, Edison.
I love you.
I am in love with you,
and I don't care
what you've done,
who you've loved...
I don't care.
And if you will have me,
I would very much
like to marry you.
(Groans)
You were incredible today.
I've never seen anything
like it.
That press conference was flawless.
(Groans)
Struck just the right tone.
Presidential. Strong.
Everything. Back to normal.
(Sighs) I was worried,
I have to admit.
I was very worried.
Something like this happens...
a shooting or an accident...
You remember senator Hutchins.
He was in that car accident.
Now he's quadriplegic,
and his poor wife...
She has to change his diapers.
(Groans softly)
I can't even imagine.
Your life can change in an instant.
We were lucky.
You're back. You're you.
That is...
To have our life go back
to the way it was...
Is a gift.
Everything's good.
I'm grateful.
I'm so grateful.
And... honestly?
Your approval rating
has never been higher.
You can have anything
you want right now.
Anything.
We should think about that.
We should take advantage
of this moment politically.
But we have to be
smart about it.
What do you think?
What do you want?
If you could have anything...
I want a divorce.
You're telling me
that even though
there are 120 million people
voting in this thing,
all we care about is Ohio?
Our problem isn't Ohio.
Our problem is Franklin,
Summit, and Defiance.
You're right.
Take out those three counties,
and this election
is a statistical dead heat.
It could go either way.
Painting Reston as soft
on crime has been a godsend.
There isn't any crime
in Defiance?
I just do the math.
(Papers thud)
(Telephone ringing in distance)
I don't know how you can
even consider...
It isn't my idea. Hollis...
Hollis is your guy.
Hollis is Fitz's guy.
Let's not play innocent here.
Fitz is clean.
Fitz walks on water.
Fitz makes the fishes
and the loaves.
And people like Hollis
and me and you...
(Scoffs)
Don't roll your eyes.
You're one of us, Olivia.
We march behind him.
We sing his happy tune.
And then we pick up
our hatchets,
and we chop up the judases
into bloody little pieces
and dance around their corpses,
because that is our job.
That is what we do.
We take care of Fitz.
And we don't do it
because we are believers,
which we are.
We don't do it for the rush
or the high or the power,
which we are most
certainly junkies for.
We do it because Fitz can't.
He can't do it.
If he could do it, we wouldn't
worship at his altar.
People like Fitz...
They go down in history.
People like us, we create the history.
(Breath quavering)
We run this world
so he can lead it.
In order to lead it, the people
have to elect him, Cyrus.
The people have to find him worthy.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
The way this world works,
the people is you and me
and Hollis and Mellie and Verna.
(Breathing heavily)
- We're the people.
- Cy...
No. It comes down
to two questions, Olivia...
does he deserve to be President?
And if you believe he does,
do you think he can win it on his own?
If you can say "yes" to both,
then we'll never discuss
election rigging...
Ever again.
Do you think I'll make
a good President?
He's the real deal.
- Once in a generation.
- You're gonna lose this election.
Do you think I'll make
a good President?
Fitzgerald can't pull this
off on his own.
- I gotta win this election.
- What do you want?
- It's mine.
- Think about your future.
- I'm going to win...
- I'm a winner.
- ...this election.
- That's something you'll never be.
It's mine.
(Cyrus) It's a finite number
of people, Mellie.
- That's all I'm saying.
- Cyrus, we are all working
as hard as we can work.
I know.
I know that.
So we tell them they just...
(Speaks indistinctly)
Yes.
Yes?
So you're...
In.
(Beep)
(Clears throat)
It's a go.
sync and corrections by bellows
www.addic7ed.com