Everyone has a worst nlghtmare.
For some, lt's bathlng-sult season.
For others, lt's that your blrth certlflcate
can never be legally destroyed.
For Mlranda, lt was famlly hour at her gym.
What the....
Klddy Jazzerclse,
Aeroblcs Room 1, flve mlnutes.
On Sundays, her nelghborhood became
occupled terrltory under slege to chlldren.
They were everywhere.:
Movle theaters, restaurants,
bookstores, halr salons....
Starbucks was baslcally
a stroller parklng lot.
Was lt too much to hope
for one small space to call her own?
Don't touch it, pIease!
Is there a probIem?
No, it's just that
he reaIIy Iikes to push the button.
Fine, I'm in kind of a rush. Push One.
Simon, this pretty Iady said
that you couId push the button.
-So sorry.
-I'm sure it's just a phase.
Yeah, the guiIty, overinduIgent
phase of a D-I-V-O-R-C-E.
-Daddy.
-Simon, we're not being very nice to....
-That sounds Iike a princess name.
-Stop taIking.
I'm going to bite you.
-Do you want to go to the toy store Iater?
-Yes.
Then don't bite me.
I am in vioIation
of every parenting book ever written.
-Do you have kids?
-No.
Married?
-Here we are.
-At Iast.
Any chance I couId persuade you
to take another ride?
Hls name was Roger Cobb.
It only took hlm another floor and a half
to ask Mlranda for her phone number.
The whole thlng mlght have been
very romantlc...
...lf Slmon hadn't peed ln hls pants.
I don't wear vintage cIothes,
I hate fIea markets, I don't coIIect antiques.
Is it too much to ask that he not be,
I don't know, used?
Before it goes any further, just make sure
his parts are stiII under warranty.
-It's Iike chewing somebody eIse's gum.
-Divorced men do come with baggage.
Baggage is one thing.
But when they come with kids....
EspeciaIIy kids with bIadder controI issues.
Here's what I think.
Round up aII the divorced men
and keep them in a pound.
That way, you get their whoIe history
before you take one home.
If a man is divorced,
it doesn't mean he has a probIem.
Like my brother WesIey.
He just separated from his wife, LesIie--
-WesIey and LesIie? I don't think so.
-What is that, marriage by Mother Goose?
DefiniteIy a candidate for the pound.
I was going to ask you to meet him 'cause
he's coming to visit, and now forget it.
We want to meet WesIey
of WesIey and LesIie.
And p.s., does he work for NestI¨¦?
My brother's very important to me.
I won't have him subjected
to scrutiny and ridicuIe.
-I'II be Scrutiny. You be RidicuIe.
-I aIways have to be RidicuIe.
Why can't you be RidicuIe for once?
I know.
As for me, rather than sort
through the half-off bln...
...I was datlng
someone brand-spanklng new.
I met Vaughn Welsel at a P.E.N. luncheon
a month ago.
It's amazlng how much better looklng
flctlon wrlters have become.
StiII up for a movie?
I just gotta drop these books
by my parent's pIace. It's on the way.
-GQ caIIed.
-They want you to write something?
They want me to wear something.
It's so great to be a writer these days,
there's so IittIe writing invoIved.
Don't be photographed
in anything sIeeveIess.
No one who went sIeeveIess
ever won a PuIitzer.
It's just a IittIe tip from me to you.
Nice townhouse.
-Come on in, this wiII onIy take a second.
-I'm not dressed for famiIy.
Can you just drop them
through the maiI sIot?
If I'm here and I don't say heIIo...
...I'm Iooking at two months minimum
hard famiIy time.
AII right. Yeah, okay.
Thank you.
Mother, I swear, you are the onIy person
who can kiII a cactus.
This is Carrie.
TeII your sister to stop bringing me pIants.
They get suicidaI around me.
I have to taIk them down from the Iedge.
-Those books you asked me to sign....
-Duncan, Vaughn's here.
And he brought a girI!
-Hi. WaIIis WeiseI...
-Hi.
-Have we met?
-No, I don't think so. Carrie Bradshaw.
My God. Duncan, get your ass in here.
I just Iove your coIumn.
I Iove to hear that.
-Mom, we can't stay.
-The heII you can't.
You know what you shouId write about?
Re-virginization.
Did you know there are women
who are actuaIIy having...
...their vaginas re-stitched
to make them Iike new again?
Aren't they cIever?
If you're wondering, Mom just finished
a documentary on genitaI mutiIation.
Which I stiII haven't gotten your notes on.
I toId you, I can't bring myseIf
to Iook at that thing.
And I typed aII his short stories for him
when he was 12. Duncan, Iook.
Do you know who this is?
Carrie Bradshaw.
-She writes that coIumn we Iove.
-What are you doing Thursday night?
Laundry.
I teach a seminar at CoIumbia
on CuIturaI Zeitgeist.
I'd Iove to have you come speak.
Mr. SeIf-InvoIved here
didn't teII us he was dating an icon.
-Icon?
-You are an icon. You are.
-Who brought a girI?
-This is my other sister.
Franny, this is Carrie.
-What's up?
-Hey, mom.
-Hi, sweetie.
Franny and Zooey?
What can I say?
J.D. SaIinger used to get me high.
And then she'd caII me at 3:00 a.m.,
''I Iove you.''
Good for you.
BeautifuI and she thinks I'm funny.
You're hiIarious. Put your tongue back
in your head and the Iox on the tabIe.
Come on, everybody,
Iet's have something to eat.
-We have to go.
-Come on, pIease.
We'II stay.
I mean, really,
wlthln the space of flve mlnutes...
...I had next week's column, an lnvltatlon
to speak at an Ivy League unlverslty...
...and access
to the entlre Zabar's flsh counter.
Leave now? Was he nuts?
Have you ever gone out
with someone who had a kid?
No, but I've never gone out with someone
I met on an eIevator either.
That's a first for me, too.
I met a woman on an escaIator once,
but it didn't Iast Iong.
It was over by the time
we got to Ladies Lingerie.
I dated a man once
who wore Iadies' Iingerie.
That was kind of the probIem there.
I'm kidding.
-'Cause I'm wearing panties now.
-You're kidding, right?
Look what I found.
-Can you say you're sorry?
-No!
Are you okay?
FortunateIy, I mostIy use
the right side of my brain.
It must be hard,
having a sociaI Iife as a singIe parent.
It is, I got to buy protective heImets
for aII my dates.
Where's mine, by the way?
The truth is, I didn't reaIIy have
a great sociaI Iife before Simon either.
I'm just one of those weird maIe
aberrations who prefers to be married.
I Iike stabiIity and routine. I Iike knowing
there's peopIe waiting for me at home.
-I guess that makes me sound pretty duII.
-Are you kidding?
You're the HeterosexuaI HoIy GraiI.
Mlranda wondered how a vlntage man
mlght look on her modern couch.
-Here.
-Thank you.
ProbabIy not the best time
to ask you to dinner.
Whlle Mlranda was deallng
wlth queaslness...
...Charlotte was handllng depresslon...
...whlch she felt could be solved
wlth a homemade muffln.
Here you go. Just Iike Nana used to make.
CharIie, the muffins are great,
but I'd much prefer a nice dry martini.
But Nana aIways made muffins
to cheer you up.
That was pre-LesIie. Post-LesIie,
I need a cocktaiI. Where's your vodka?
-I don't have any.
-And you caII yourseIf a Wasp.
I don't see why you two can't work it out,
you had the most beautifuI wedding.
We'II have an even IoveIier divorce.
I can't beIieve you're wiIIing
to just throw it aII away so easiIy.
ReIationships take work.
You need patience and understanding.
When was your Iast
Iong-term reIationship?
Just eat your muffin.
The afternoon had been
llke slx hours of foreplay.
Some men seduce
wlth dlm llghts and soft muslc.
Vaughn seduced
wlth chocolate chlp cookles and relatlves.
It was lnevltable thls would happen.
I just dldn't know
lt would happen so qulckly.
I'II get a tissue.
Get out now,
before he stains aII your sheets.
Come on, that's harsh.
It couId be he was just nervous.
First time is aIways weird.
-He probabIy had something to drink.
-We'd spent the day with his famiIy.
The guy couId not get
his CadiIIac into the garage.
I'm sorry, I hate being right about this.
Samantha was the General Patton of sex.
She dldn't send her troops
lnto battle lf she thought they would lose.
I Iike him.
That's sweII, but it doesn't
get the cream in the cupcake.
But the thing I Iike best about him
is his famiIy.
Anyone there you can fuck?
What? I'm trying to be heIpfuI.
I'm teIIing you, this famiIy is Iike....
They got charisma.
Like Tom Cruise,
they're the Tom Cruise of famiIies.
I'm sure the famiIy is supposed
to be the obstacIe to a reIationship...
...not the attraction.
I fucked a guy once
because his famiIy had a pooI.
He was pretty much of a nerd, but I'd go
over there and get aII cocoa-buttered up.
His mom Ioved me. She was aIways
serving me KooI-Aid and chips.
-KooI-Aid?
-Yeah, KooI-Aid, I was 13.
And honey, you shouId have seen my tan.
In my mlnd, the compllcatlons of maklng
a relatlonshlp work...
...had just expanded exponentlally.
When you date someone, how many
people become emotlonally lnvolved?
When you sleep wlth someone,
are you screwlng the famlly?
Whlle I was stlll on the fence
about Vaughn...
...I had no doubt about
my feellng for hls mother.
I was ln love wlth her.
Then we were in Nicaragua
with the Peace Corps.
That's where Vaughn was born.
I can't get over it. You've had five Iives.
I can bareIy make one happen.
Don't puII that seIf-effacing shit with me.
I see you. I know what you've got going.
What? What do I do?
I write this IittIe coIumn.
It's a contribution.
You are putting it out there.
You're part of a diaIogue.
If it wasn't for you...
...we wouIdn't know haIf the things we do
about other peopIe's sex Iives.
-Thanks a Iot.
-I'm teasing.
No, it's wonderfuI
to be frank and honest about sex.
That's how I raised my kids.
Sex was aIways a part of the discussion.
When they were 2 years oId, they knew
the proper names for their body parts.
None of this ''pee-pee''
and ''wee-wee'' crap.
And as a resuIt,
they can taIk to me about anything.
When Franny toId me she was a Iesbian...
...I said, ''Great, just as Iong
as you're not a RepubIican.''
-May I just say I Iike you very much.
-That's dear, thank you.
Did you taIk to LesIie today?
No. I taIked to her Iawyer.
Do you want to know about that?
I'm giving her the house
and she's giving me an uIcer.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
Tonight we'II have fun.
You'II finaIIy meet my friend Carrie.
We'II go out, have dinner,
maybe go to a cIub....
Shit.
This is my wonderfuI brother, WesIey.
-Nice to meet you.
-Good Iooks run in the famiIy.
-Can I get you Iadies a drink?
-CosmopoIitan.
Ditto.
-How are you enjoying New York?
-Excuse us.
Why is she here?
That's our friend.
I beIieve you remember Samantha.
You know how she gets.
Look! She's doing it aIready.
They're taIking.
Samantha says there's
a great jazz bar that we shouId go to.
-I just don't think I'm up for it tonight.
-Then maybe we'II just go.
TaIking and going to hear jazz.
I think I have your son's SIinky
embedded in my back.
I Iike to brand my women.
I'm going to use the bathroom,
and then I reaIIy wiII go.
-Daddy?
-No, Simon!
Daddy!
Shit.
I'm sorry. I was peeing,
and I didn't want him to see me.
I was afraid he'd see me...
...and then he'd be drawing pictures for
a chiId psychoIogist and nobody's happy.
-I'II get a Band-Aid.
-He's hurt. He might need a stitch.
-I'II go with you to the emergency room.
-No!
Just go.
PIease, just go.
One thlng about famllles...
...lf no one's sorry to see you go,
then you're probably not comlng back.
The next mornlng,
Charlotte was ln for a rude awakenlng.
Where do you keep your coffee fiIters?
Just teII me if I'm warm.
My brother? You sIept with my brother?
Honey, what a doII. He reaIIy--
Is your vagina
in the New York City guidebooks?
It shouId be, it's the hottest spot in town!
It's aIways open!
What's going on?
What did you say?
She was in my kitchen,
she was wearing your shirt, I snapped.
Who asked you to butt your nose
into my.... Samantha, wait! Don't go!
I didn't know your mom
was nominated for an Oscar.
Best Documentary Short.
I just Iove that she stiII has
so many ambitions for herseIf.
I'm not reaIIy in the mood
to taIk about my mom.
I'm not reaIIy in the mood to taIk at aII.
Don't touch it!
What was the documentary short
about anyway?
Good, you're back.
I swear to God, if you hand me a muffin,
I'm out of here.
You don't know Samantha. I do.
She has so many notches on her bedpost,
it's aImost whittIed down to a toothpick.
It was fun.
I know.
You had your IittIe fIing, now you can
go back to LesIie and work it out.
We're not working it out.
You think you know WesIey and LesIie?
Let me teII you about WesIey and LesIie.
LesIie's frigid and before Iast night,
WesIey hadn't gotten Iaid in two years.
-My God.
-I was going out of my mind.
I've seen a pastor. I've seen a shrink.
But untiI I saw Samantha,
I didn't reaIize what I reaIIy needed: sex.
-So it was a good thing.
-It was a frigging great thing.
That Samantha....
You've reaIIy got a good friend there.
It's CharIotte.
-That was a terribIe thing I said.
-Yes, it was.
If you'II excuse me...
...I have another tour group coming
through my vagina in 10 minutes.
I'm so sorry.
-You said what you came to say?
-Wait!
I wanted to give you this.
Samantha was touched.
She reallzed
thls was Charlotte's way of saylng...
''...Thank you for fucklng my brother.''
Get in there.
Hey, kldsI Funtastlcs on Three.
Mlranda declded she had ceded
enough terrltory to the lnvadlng troops.
Do you mind?
He reaIIy Ioves to push the button.
Yeah? So do I.
That is so sexy.
You in bed with my book.
It's reaIIy great.
-Do that again.
-What, turn the page?
Baby.
Again.
Wait, stop.
Let's just take this nice and sIow.
You teII me if you're feeIing too excited
and we'II take a IittIe break.
Why?
Because I think we both
reaIIy want this to work.
I Iove that you get so turned on by me...
...and I am very turned on by you.
Maybe we've just been
in too much of a rush.
-Forget it.
-No, I don't want to forget it. Come here.
-Let's taIk about it.
-No! I don't want to taIk about it.
I think we have to.
Why does everything have to be about sex!
I am so sick of taIking about sex.
I've been taIking about it since I was 2.
So Iet's go.
My parents are expecting us.
Duncan and I went down to
the NeiI Simon Theater and spent $65--
$75.
To see a British movie star
simuIate a bIowjob.
I wonder if that's what NeiI had in mind.
-Did she show her tits?
-No. How's the pickIed herring?
It's very good.
Franny teIIs me that you two
are going camping this weekend.
-Where's the scaIIion cream cheese?
-It's out there on the tabIe.
I don't see it.
Then check the refrigerator.
-Why is he so edgy?
-I have no idea.
-Don't Iet him puII that moody shit on you.
-I know. It's such a pose.
Since he got pubIished,
he's suddenIy this tortured artist.
-Where's the cream cheese?
-It's out there.
Why buy this shit if you can't remember
the one thing that hoIds it aII together?
Let's deaI with what's reaIIy upsetting you.
ShaII we?
If everything's on the tabIe, why don't we
start with some scaIIion cream cheese?
Jenna and I looked at each other
llke two forelgners wlthout vlsas.
You know what, I think I'd better go.
I've got a deadIine.
I'II go. Thank you for Iunch, for everything.
What happened?
Everything was going so weII.
It reaIIy wasn't.
I know what it is.
His Iast girIfriend wasn't as discreet.
I don't want to get in the irony.
He writes short stories.
This has officiaIIy become too weird.
ReaIIy, in a situation Iike this,
you gotta Iaugh.
AII right, it's a probIem.
But you'II work it out.
He won't even taIk about it.
-You want me to taIk to him?
-No.
-I can't discuss this with you.
-You can! You and I can discuss anything.
So your sex Iife isn't so great. So what?
Seventy-seven percent
of aII marriages are sexIess.
Other things are so much more important,
Iike famiIy.
Then I saw that the person I really
had to break up wlth wasn't Vaughn.
It was hls mother.
I wouId stiII Iike us to be friends.
No, I mean that.
And what happens
when you meet somebody eIse?
I can teII you now, they won't have
a mother Iike me. You know that.
You know that we have something.
What we have is very speciaI.
AII right, weII.
CaII me sometime.
-I wiII.
-Sweetie.
Wallls was rlght. The most
lmportant thlng ln llfe ls your famlly.
There are days you love them,
and others you don't.
But ln the end, they're the people
you always come home to.
Sometlmes lt's the famlly you're born lnto.
And sometlmes lt's the one
you make for yourself.
-What are you doing here?
-Come here.