Llfe ls all about maklng cholces.
Some cholces, llke who you marry,
are blg...
...whlle others are even blgger.
What do you think?
The $5 ones that Iast three days,
or the $10 ones that Iast five?
Either one.
Three days.
$5.
Another cholce ls how to deal
wlth an ex-boyfrlend.
Some women handle lt
coolly, calmly, whlle others....
Fuck!
Steve.
Go!
$5! Come back here!
He Iooked so hurt.
Like a kid in one of those
big-eyed veIvet paintings.
Poor Steve.
I'm sorry, I panicked.
What was I to do, chat about the weather?
-The man's been inside me.
-CouId I have more Sweet 'N Low?
I've never been abIe
to be friends with an ex.
I meet those coupIes who stay friends
and I think, ''How do they do that?''
I've never been friends with men. Women
are for friendships, men are for fucking.
You must Iearn to form an opinion.
Friendship is the bonus of a reIationship.
No reIationship, no friendship.
If your coupIe doesn't work,
you withhoId friendship as a punishment?
You make it sound so bad.
BIack widow spiders bite
their mate's heads off when it's over.
WithhoIding friendship
is Ietting them off easy.
Imagine, instead of
the awfuI break-up scene...
...you say, ''Come here''...
...and chomp their head off.
I wouId Iove to be
one of those peopIe who's aII:
''We Ioved, thank you.
You enriched my Iife. Now, go, prosper.''
I'm much more: ''We didn't work out,
you need to not exist.''
What?
It's just so chiIdish.
Not you, the whoIe situation.
We keep dresses we'II never wear
but throw away our ex-boyfriends.
I'm not saying that I'm any better.
I haven't been abIe
to be friends with Big, but....
If you Ioved someone and you break up...
...where does the Iove go?
To their next girIfriend.
No. That is a different Iove.
The Iove that Big and I had cannot
be same thing he has with Natasha.
Natasha? When'd you stop caIIing her
the Idiot Stick Figure With No SouI?
About three weeks ago
when I saw them at Cafe M.
He was hoIding her hand and smiIing and...
...I finaIIy got it.
They're happy, sIash, we're over.
It was okay.
-Natasha, what a buIIshit name.
-TotaIIy.
-Stupid.
-CompIete buIIshit.
Later that nlght,
I got to thlnklng about the ex factor.
In mathematlcs, we learned
that ''x'' stands for the unknown.
''a'' plus ''b'' equals ''x.''
But what's really unknown ls.: what
plus what equals frlendshlp wlth an ex?
Is thls an unsolvable equatlon?
Or ls lt posslble to transform
a once-passlonate love...
...lnto somethlng that flts
nlce and easlly onto the frlendshlp shelf?
I couldn't help but wonder...
...can you be frlends wlth an ex?
That Sunday afternoon, Mlranda was
enjoylng a blscottl and the paper when....
There lt was...
...her ex's head.
I hear you breathing.
Yeah. Hi!
That was a shitty thing you did,
running away from me on the street.
I didn't run.
You ran.
I wasn't expecting to see you--
It reaIIy hurt my feeIings.
I don't do very weII
with ex-boyfriends and....
This is me.
Steve.
I heId your head whiIe you were sIeeping.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I hadn't seen you in so Iong
and I missed you...
...and then I did that shitty thing.
-It wasn't that shitty.
-It was.
It was a shitty thing. I'm a shitty person.
-You are not a shitty person.
-I am! I am shitty!
You'd never do anything that shitty.
How about showing up at your apartment
and caIIing you shitty?
Yeah, that was pretty shitty.
You've got a ''bat in the cave.''
I miss you.
Whenever something funny happens,
I aIways want to teII you about it.
So teII me.
Just 'cause we broke up doesn't mean
we can't have a friendIy meaI, does it?
I guess not.
What are you doing Friday?
I have a date.
Looking forward to it, are you?
As Mlranda made plans
to have dlnner wlth her last love...
...Charlotte came face to face
wlth the memory of her flrst...
...her horse, Taddy.
Charlotte's relatlonshlp wlth Taddy ended...
...when he threw her
durlng a teen equestrlan competltlon...
...causlng her to break her collarbone
and lose the blue rlbbon.
Her father promptly sold Taddy
and she hadn't been on a horse slnce.
Charlotte wondered lf lt was tlme
to get back ln the saddle.
Meanwhlle, across town...
...Samantha was about to see
a stalllon of her own.
I gotta say, you Iook amazing.
Excuse me, but do I know you?
Not yet.
I was thinking maybe you'd
have dinner with me sometime.
What makes you think that?
The way you were just checking me out.
You get 10 points for directness.
Do I aIso get your phone number?
I'm not sure yet.
I'II teII you what....
Here's my business card.
You caII me.
BIatantIy picking a woman up
on the street.
How'd you get to be so cocky?
I was born that way, I guess.
At Ieast consider meeting me
for a friendIy IittIe drink.
I'II think about it, Mr. Cocky.
PIease do.
Later that week, when I spotted
a Laura Ashley dress, clrca 1988...
...stlll hanglng ln my closet...
...I declded lt was tlme
to glve my ex a frlendly phone call.
I hadn't planned on the Idlot Stlck Flgure
Wlth No Soul answerlng.
Then, I remembered Blg had caller ID.
Shit!
HeIIo yourseIf.
-Did you just caII?
-No--
Yes, but I didn't get to taIk because...
...I accidentaIIy hit the thing...
...so, you know, it hung up.
So, yes.
And I...
...I heard Natasha, so, apoIogize to her.
How is Natasha?
Great.
She's great.
How are you?
I'm A-OK.
You sound a IittIe nuts.
Can't you Iet one go by?
This is weird.
The first caII.
Right.
Maybe I'd...
...do better if I went with
my IittIe prepared speech.
You have a speech?
I was wondering what you thought of...
...instead of pretending
each other doesn't exist...
...we try to be friends or something?
I'd Iike that.
I've been meanlng to call, but I dldn't
know lf you wanted to hear from me--
-Want to have a lunch or somethlng?
-Let's.
Thank you.
I have a 1:00 reservation. Bradshaw.
I used to make our lunch reservatlons
ln Blg's name.
But today, I put lt ln mlne,
because that's what frlends do.
The other party is aIready here.
Thank you.
Are you hungry? Because I am.
I got up at 6:00, worked out,
hardIy had any breakfast.
They have a great Cobb saIad here.
ShaII we eat?
-Let's eat.
-We'II eat.
And that's when I reallzed,
Blg was nervous.
It was odd. The new ''frlend'' part of me
felt lncredlbly compasslonate...
...whlle the old ''glrlfrlend'' part of me
felt lncredlbly smug.
-You okay?
-Fine.
You Iook good.
Thank you, so do you.
Good afternoon.
The Cobb saIad is very good here.
Can I get you something to drink?
Iced tea.
A mineraI water.
-Scotch.
-CosmopoIitan.
An hour later, I had solved
the unsolvable frlendshlp equatlon.
It seems the answer ls thls.:
Cosmopolltans plus scotch
equals frlendshlp wlth an ex.
And what about your music?
If I had to Iisten to freakin'
BIood, Sweat & Tears one more time....
-BIood, Sweat & Tears is great stuff.
-10 minutes after we're awake?
TeII me about the girI.
-ReaIIy?
-Friends taIk about their reIationships.
Go ahead, friend, teII me about the girI.
-She's very sweet--
-Okay, enough!
Don't teII me about the girI. No can do.
Maybe we shouId make a pact:
We don't taIk about our reIationships
untiI they get reaIIy serious.
It is serious.
We're engaged.
I wanted you to hear it from me.
I just got a spIitting headache.
I didn't know how to teII you....
-When you caIIed for Iunch--
-Engaged?
How can you be engaged? You have
a probIem with commitment, remember?
In fact, you toId me you never wanted
to get married again, ever.
Things change.
You just didn't want to marry me.
-Natasha and I--
-Don't say her name!
Don't you dare say her name to me!
You string me aIong for two years...
...then you marry some 25-year-oId girI
after onIy five months?
-I did not string you aIong.
-Fine, you didn't.
You know what? I have to go.
I have a headache.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
Don't heIp me! Don't you heIp me!
Carrie, hoId on, wait.
What is it?
-Don't end it Iike this--
-You did it Iike this. I was being friendIy.
This seems Iike a much better way
to end things.
Go. Be engaged, get married to...
...Nijinsky or whatever her name is.
Have a nice Iife.
Don't worry about me, I'm fine.
These steps are very dangerous.
The next day, I had promlsed to hold
Charlotte's hand whlle she trled rldlng.
It turned out,
she needed to hold mlne as well.
How are you doing?
Aside from the fact that my ex
is engaged to a teenager...
...and I've got horseshit
on my goddamn $300 shoes...
...I'm doing okay.
I think you're amazing.
I wouId be in a hospitaI or something.
What the fuck is his probIem?
He's got a stubborn streak.
Some horses never reaIIy Iike to be ridden.
Taddy was Iike that when I first got him,
but once I broke him in, he Ioved it.
You know what?
I broke in Big.
I broke him in and the Idiot Stick Figure
With No SouI gets to ride him.
I'm reaIIy sorry.
I know you are. Thanks.
Damn!
You see, this is what happens.
You try to be friendIy with an ex
and you wind up knee-deep in shit!
Perfect.
This is PaI. He's a good boy.
He's brown.
Taddy was brown,
but he had white spots on his fIank.
Just stay tiII I'm on the horse,
then you can go, okay?
I'm here, it's aII IoveIy. Go have fun.
Hey, PaI.
Foot in and up you go.
As Charlotte put her boot ln the stlrrup...
...all her bad memorles of Taddy,
broken bones and rlbbons flooded over her.
No!
Can't.
-No, I can't. Let's go.
-You just paid.
-I said, I can't!
-He's aII saddIed up.
After a few
''get to know each other'' phone calls...
...Samantha took up Mr. Cocky
on hls offer of a frlendly drlnk.
Turns out, lt was a very frlendly drlnk.
I want you to know,
I never pick up guys on the street...
...unIess they're very cute.
Get over here, you cutie.
Before we go any further...
...I gotta warn you about something.
Warn me about what?
I'm very weII-endowed.
Jackpot.
No. I'm serious.
It's huge.
Most women can't handIe it.
I'm not most women.
Unzip and get over here.
Samantha suddenly understood
what made Mr. Cocky so cocky.
I'm teIIing you,
it was Iike a waII of fIesh coming at me.
Nothing is scarier
than a reaIIy big one coming at you.
I didn't even want my mouth near it,
I was afraid I'd get Iockjaw.
It was quite a shock.
His hands are reIativeIy tiny.
-Don't teII me you beIieve that.
-Not anymore.
I'm going to have to psych myseIf up
before I try it again.
You're going to try it again? Why?
-Because it's there.
-It's a penis, not Mount Everest.
If it was Mount Everest...
...Iast night I couId onIy make it
to Base Camp One.
You dated Mr. Big, I'm dating Mr. Too Big.
You're unbeIievabIe.
You broke up with James because
he was too smaII, this guy is too big.
Who are you, GoIdicocks?
Yep.
I'm Iooking for one that's just right.
That nlght, after a frlendly dlnner...
...Steve and Mlranda began to explore
thelr newfound frlendshlp.
If you were a reaI friend,
you'd Iet me keep it.
Sorry, it's part of a break-up.
You gotta return my fire department shirt.
-It fits me perfectIy.
-TeII it to the judge.
-PIease?
-Nope.
Thanks for coming out for dinner.
Thanks for Ietting me pay, finaIIy.
That's what friends do, isn't it?
Goodnight.
I got another question for you.
Do friends kiss...
...here?
No.
Do friends kiss here?
Do friends kiss....
Yeah.
We had good reasons
for breaking up, right?
Yeah.
Money, scheduIes, goaIs.
Good reasons.
What now?
Are we stiII just friends?
Yeah, we're stiII just friends.
Friends who have sex.
And ln a bed across town....
Ready?
Wait.
After two yoga classes and a hlt
of the best Hawallan gold she could flnd...
...Samantha was ready to take
another run at Mount Everest.
Okay, here we go.
Nice and easy.
That's it.
Easy--
Easy.
Good.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go?
Yeah.
We're not there yet?
-No.
-Okay, stop.
Whoa, boy.
Can we just be friends?
And just llke that,
Samantha made her very flrst male frlend.
The next day ln Central Park,
Charlotte was maklng a new frlend as well.
Good, PaI.
She had declded she and Pal
were movlng too fast.
Before golng any further, they needed
to get to know each other better.
You're a good boy, PaI.
Does that feeI good?
You Iike that? My Taddy Iiked that, too.
I Ioved my Taddy so much.
Oh, good boy.
And wlth that gentle nudge
from her new pal...
...all Charlotte's bad feellngs
about Taddy llfted...
...and she remembered just how much
she had loved hls cute whlte spots.
Easy.
Okay. Go, boy, go!
Hey, lt's Carrle, I'm shoe shopplng.
It's me, are you there?
Pick up if you're there.
You're not there.
I'm caIIing to say
I feeI bad about Iast week.
I didn't mean for it to happen Iike that...
...I thought you needed to know.
I hated to think someone eIse
might teII you.
Chrlst.
I feel llke a real shlt. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry...
...I would never hurt you dellberately--
I know you wouIdn't.
-You're there?
-I'm here.
Like I was saying, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I shouIdn't have reacted Iike that.
It was such a shock.
I guess it was a shock
I needed to hear to move on.
Yeah.
I wish you aII the best. I do.
I hope you and Natasha wiII be very happy.
Do you mean that?
No.
But I wlll.
Really. I hope...
...some day very soon...
...we can aII meet for a drink
and be great friends.
Llke they do ln the movles.
Bye.
And I actually managed to hold
onto those frlendly feellngs, untll....
I can't beIieve my ex-boyfriend
is at the PIaza...
...having an engagement brunch.
And he had the nerve to invite you.
It's my own fauIt.
I had to make the big
''Iet's be friends'' speech.
Who am I kidding?
Big and I were never friends, we were...
...something eIse.
Something that did not end
with an engagement party at the PIaza.
-Do we want another round?
-What do you think?
Four more, pIease.
I think I can actuaIIy feeI them
over there eating shrimp.
It's just--why her?
I mean reaIIy....
Why her?
One word: HubbeII.
HubbeII.
Oh, my god. HubbeII.
It is so HubbeII.
Who's HubbeII?
HubbeII!
Robert ''HubbeII'' Redford
in The Way We Were.
I Iove that movie.
I Iove, Iove, Iove, that movie.
-Never saw it.
-Oh, my god!
What are you, an aIien?
How couId you have not seen it?
Chick fiIm.
Robert Redford
is madIy in Iove with Barbara Streisand.
-Katie.
-K-k-k-katie.
K-k-k-katie, right!
But he can't be with her
because she's too compIicated...
...and she has wiId, curIy hair.
HeIIo? C-c-c-curIy.
He Ieaves her and marries this...
...simpIe girI with straight hair.
Ladies, I am having an epiphany.
The worId is made of two types of women:
The ''simpIe'' girIs and the ''Katie'' girIs.
I'm a ''Katie'' girI and where are our drinks?
I aIways cry at the Iast scene
in that movie...
-...when she sees him with his new wife--
-The simpIe girI.
-And she reaches up--
-And smoothes his hair away.
She says to him:
''Your girI is IoveIy, HubbeII.''
Then the music comes in.
''Memories''
Oh my, God, it's so good.
''Light the corners of my mind
''Misty water-coIored memories
''Of the way we were''
Let me do my favorite part.
-''Can it be''
-Yes!
''Can it be that it was aII so simpIe then
''Or has time re-written every Iine?
''If we had the chance to do it aII again
''TeII me
''WouId we?
''CouId we?
''Memories''
I miss James.
Excuse me?
After I left my frlends, I found myself
pulled to the slte of the engagement party.
I had no lntentlon of golng ln,
but lt was on my way home.
One second.
I had a cholce.
I could run or I could stand
and ask hlm the questlon...
...that lf I dldn't ask,
would haunt me the rest of my llfe.
I thought by the time I got here,
I'd know what to say.
And?
You're Iate.
The party's over.
I'II say it is.
Funny.
I was just on my way home and....
I have a question for you.
Why wasn't it me?
-Carrie--
-No, seriousIy.
I reaIIy need to hear you say it.
Come on, be a friend.
I don't know.
It just got so hard...
...and she's....
Yeah.
''Your girI is IoveIy, HubbeII.''
I don't get it.
And you never did.
Easy, girI.
Then I had a thought,
maybe I dldn't break Blg.
Maybe the problem was
he couldn't break me.
Maybe some women
aren't meant to be tamed.
Maybe they need to run free
untll they flnd someone...
...just as wlld to run wlth.