My frlend Charlotte
was datlng Dr. Bram Walker...
...a very hardworklng orthopedlc surgeon.
Bram?
What?
Were you asIeep?
No, I was just resting my eyes.
My God.
I feII asIeep for one second.
I was up at 5:00, I had three carpaI tunneIs.
It's very exhaustive reconstructive work.
He feII asIeep when
he was making Iove to me.
He feII asIeep!
He was tired.
This has nothing to do with you.
Has a man ever faIIen asIeep
making Iove to you?
No, but I'm sure many of them wanted to.
I can't beIieve this happened to me!
You want some herb tea?
I must be reaIIy bad in bed.
You are not bad in bed.
I've got Constant Comment and....
Do you want some Tummy Tamer?
Of course it's her.
I have to say, I'm not surprised.
Ever seen her on a Stairmaster?
Nothing happening beIow the waist.
Nada. No saIe.
How can you say that?
Even if she was bad in bed,
which she isn't, is it reaIIy that important?
AbsoIuteIy. Who we are in bed
is who we are in Iife.
I never met a man who was bad in bed
who was good at Iife.
Just for the record, in bed, you are....
Don't make me state the obvious.
How can you be so sure?
No one ever took a nap whiIe fucking me...
...and I get affirmations aII the time.
Just Iast week....
Last week, Samantha had dlnner
wlth a gay couple she'd known for years.
Davld and Davld.
Thanks for a IoveIy dinner. It was fun.
I have to admit,
we have an uIterior motive.
What?
We're wondering if you're seeing
anyone speciaI right now?
ActuaIIy, no.
Do you have a hot guy for me?
Two.
-No!
-Yes!
We want to have sex with a woman.
-Are you serious?
-TotaIIy.
I'm curious about it.
We've never done it
and we thought it might be fun.
We were Iike:
''If we were gonna do it with a woman,
who wouId it be?''
-Then we were Iike, Samantha.
-TotaIIy.
We decided of aII the beautifuI women
we know, you are probabIy the best in bed.
TotaIIy.
Look at that!
I'm thinking about doing it.
They're cute, they're heaIthy.
They're gay!
For a sex coIumnist,
you have a Iimited view of sexuaIity.
Gay as pink suede.
Wake up. It's 2000.
The new miIIennium won't be about sexuaI
IabeIs, it'II be about sexuaI expression.
It won't matter if you're sIeeping
with men or women.
It'II be about sIeeping with individuaIs.
Or in your case, twos or threes.
Soon everyone wiII be pansexuaI.
It won't matter if you're gay or straight.
-Just if you're good or bad in bed.
-ExactIy.
That nlght I got to thlnklng about bed.
Are we secretly belng graded every tlme
we lnvlte someone to joln us ln lt?
A plus, B, D, lncomplete.
Is maklng love really nothlng
more than a pop qulz?
If sex ls a test, how do we know
lf we're passlng or falllng?
How do you know lf you're good ln bed?
Later on, I was walklng home thlnklng
about my sexual report card when....
What the heII--
Christ, I'm sorry. I didn't see you.
I threw my cigarette.
I thought I was stung by a bee. Jesus!
I'm sorry. Did it Ieave a mark?
You can't smoke in the restaurant.
I'm a smoker.
I'm a smoker too,
but watch where you throw those things?
No, it didn't Ieave a mark.
As the paln subslded,
my mlnd was free to notlce...
...how lncredlbly cute thls guy was.
I am sorry. My name's Patrick Casey.
Carrie Bradshaw, burn victim.
How weird was that? That was intense.
You gotta admit,
it's a cIever way to meet the Iadies.
You got a IittIe comedy routine
going there?
LittIe bit.
Listen, I reaIIy feeI bad.
At Ieast Iet me buy you a coffee,
or some burn saIve?
-Not funny yet.
-Sorry.
But it might be after a cappuccino.
There's a pIace right around the corner.
We can smoke there.
Three Marlboros and two
Marlboro Llghts later I had learned...
...Patrlck was a composer,
wrltlng muslc for movles.
What type of movies do you compose for?
ReaIIy bad ones.
The I Screamed When I Knew What You
Dld Last Summer On Elm Street types.
As Iong as you're chaIIenged
by what you do.
Dammit. Patrick Casey, whoever you are.
I'm Iate. I have to go.
Thank you for the coffee.
Maybe one day
you'II give me scar tissue again.
-You're great.
-Thanks.
As I walked away, I started to thlnk.:
How many cute, smart, slngle smokers
are there left ln the world? Seven?
I declded to do somethlng
I almost never do...
...glve a man my phone number.
This whoIe burn Iawsuit I pIan to initiate...
...it might get a IittIe crazy,
so here is my phone number.
You wiII need that for your attorney...
...or if you want to have
coffee again sometime.
I left feellng great. It was such a cute
approach. How could he not call?
How couId he not caII?
It's been three days.
Give him 12 more hours and then
send him off to the isIand of Iost men.
I don't wanna send him there, I Iike him.
CouId you beIieve that someone actuaIIy
had the nerve to caII this FIorentine Peach?
I can't beIieve you spent
this much on sheets.
It's an experiment.
I'm trying to change my bed karma.
I figure if I can make my bed
a pIace I reaIIy want to be...
...others wiII feeI the same way.
The fieId of dreams.
ExactIy. ''If you buiId it, he wiII come.''
The thing that gets me is, I'm not usuaIIy
wrong about the phone number size-up.
I don't put it out there
unIess I'm sure it's coming back.
I'm either reaIIy Ioving or hating the coIor.
He thinks I'm ugIy.
My God. Get a grip.
A guy doesn't caII you for three days
and you're ugIy?
-What's your point?
-PiIIowcase.
It's amazing.
We can feeI totaIIy good about ourseIves...
...and then it aII goes out the window
if the guy doesn't mirror it back to us.
This has a IittIe weird thing here.
Dammit. Does everything I bring into
this bedroom have to have a fIaw?
The next day I was ln the Vlllage looklng
for the perfect $7 dress...
...to go wlth my $300 shoes, when....
I had a cholce.
I could turn around and run away...
...or I could smlle, be brave
and walk on over.
Hi.
So what? Saturday's the day you stand on
the street and smoke in the ViIIage?
Hi, I'm Carrie.
-We're kind of in the middIe of something.
-Right, sure.
Bye. I was on my way to Perry Street.
This is Perry Street.
BIeecker, I meant BIeecker.
Okay, bye. Goodbye to you, too.
-Let me expIain.
-No, I'm embarrassed.
You're obviousIy in the middIe
of a thing with your Iover...
...or whoever and I'm there....
I'm not gay.
I'm an aIcohoIic.
We were waiting for a meeting to start.
I wanted to introduce you
but it's supposed to be anonymous.
I reaIIy wasn't getting the gay vibe
from you.
It's just, he was so cute and....
-I never caIIed.
-Right.
I was freaked. I've onIy been
in the program 11 months...
...and my sponsor said I reaIIy shouIdn't
get invoIved with someone for a year.
Okay, maybe you'II caII me in a month.
It doesn't bother you that I'm an aIcohoIic?
God, no. I Iove aIcohoIics.
HeII, I hope to be one someday.
-That was a joke.
-That's not funny, yet.
But it might be after a cappuccino.
What the fuck, it's onIy a coupIe of weeks.
WouId you Iike to go on a date sometime?
I can't think why not.
You caII me.
I accepted hls klnd lnvltatlon
because when you thlnk about lt...
...aren't we all ln recovery from somethlng?
Drlnklng? Drugglng?
Our last relatlonshlp?
On our flrst date,
Patrlck and I went for coffee.
I'm reaIIy compuIsive. If I open up a bag
of Chips Ahoy, I gotta eat the whoIe thing.
I'm Iike that with Reese's Pieces.
Reese's Pieces and shoes.
WouIdn't the shoes
be a IittIe tough on digestion?
This is me.
Thank you, Mr. Casey. I had a great time.
No, Miss Burn Victim.
I had the great time.
Then I gave hlm my very best
lean-ln-and-klss-me-goodnlght move.
Our next date, over dlnner,
he told me about worklng hls 12 steps.
After dlnner, I stood on my thlrd step
trylng to work hlm.
That smeII is amazing. What is that?
Me.
I'II caII you.
I couldn't flgure lt out.
I knew he wanted me, because durlng my
lean-ln-and-klss-me-goodnlght move...
...I'd accldentally, on purpose felt
hls pop-up-and-say-hello.
What was golng on?
By the thlrd date, I wanted hlm even more
than a flstful of Reese's Pleces.
WeII then, goodnight.
That was that. I'd hlt my humlllatlon llmlt.
Then I thought, how many cute,
smart, sexy, slngle, smoklng alcohollcs...
...are there left ln the world? Flve?
Do you want to come up?
But you see, the thing is,
I've never had sex sober.
I've aIways been drunk or high.
I don't know if I'II be any good.
What the heII?
Let's take it one step at a time.
Sex is amazing.
It feeIs so fucking amazing.
Do other peopIe know about this?
AII right! I did it! Sex without beer!
Easy, cowboy.
You!
What about you! You are the best.
You weren't haIf bad yourseIf.
You are the best.
-You're the best.
-I aim to pIease.
After we have a cigarette...
...can we do it again?
I'II have a Spanish omeIet, hash browns,
more coffee and orange juice.
Can I have some rice pudding
for Iater? Thanks.
Storing up for winter?
No, I'm starving. Patrick and I....
AII Iast night and I'm just....
No, don't stop, it's okay.
Just because I'm bad in bed
doesn't mean everybody is.
One more time.
You are not bad in bed.
ReaIIy? Has a man ever faIIen asIeep
making Iove to you?
No, but I once feII asIeep when a guy was
doing me. It was the Iudes.
It's okay.
I'm mature enough to reaIize that whiIe
I may be good at some things Iike...
...accessories, that I might need heIp
in others Iike....
-Fucking?
-Making Iove.
So, I'm taking a cIass.
A fucking cIass?
No, a tantric sex workshop.
Just don't drink any suspicious KooI-Aid
or put on new Nikes.
It's not Iike that. It's taught by a
weII-respected woman psychoIogist.
It's caIIed ''How To PIease A Man.''
I know how to pIease a man.
Just give away most of your power.
I have a trainer for the gym.
I can have a trainer for--
-Fucking?
-PIease stop saying that.
Are you actuaIIy going to do this?
Seating was Iimited,
so I signed you guys up.
PIease? I can't go aIone.
If Bram ever faIIs asIeep on me again,
I wiII die.
Pretty pIease, with sugar on it?
Christ, I'm in.
What the heII, I don't exactIy
have them hanging from the rafters.
''How To PIease A Man.''
I couId teach the damn cIass.
AII right.
That nlght,
whlle Davld and Davld got undressed...
...and walted for her ln the bedroom.
Samantha began to wonder
lf maybe she was about to go too far.
Was she actually capable
of belng thls sexually free?
Or was she gettlng ln over her head?
She declded before there were regrets,
they should all talk about lt a llttle more.
Listen, David and David, maybe....
You Iook amazing.
Just Iike Jean HarIow in Red Dust.
Samantha loved the Samantha mlrrored
through the eyes of the Davlds.
What the heII?
-They're so soft.
-I know.
-I can't do this.
-Neither can I.
But I....
-We're just getting start--
-No, can't.
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry.
It's very pretty, but no.
It's not you, it's us.
I have an idea. Let's aII put on our cIothes
and go out for geIati!
-Cheesecake.
-Whatever.
Suddenly, Samantha wasn't feellng
so good about herself ln bed.
I gotta go or I'm going to be Iate
for the tantric workshop thing.
Baby, you don't need a workshop.
You are amazing.
Come on, one more time.
We did it Iast night and aII this morning.
I couId have sex with you
morning, noon and night.
That's when I reallzed lt.
Mr. Compulslve wasn't ln bed wlth me...
More, c'mon.
...he was ln bed wlth a blg bag
of Chlps Ahoy.
More.
The intent of tantric...
...we say ''sacred sexuaIity...''
...is to experience
and merge with the Divine.
I think Patrick's addicted to me.
It's Iike he's repIaced drinking with me.
Program guys are tough.
I dated a guy who was
in Over-Eaters Anonymous.
Every time we had a fight,
he'd binge-eat hot fudge sundaes.
In other words, Iadies,
to drive your man crazy.
He wants to have sex aII the time.
It's getting a IittIe out of hand.
At Ieast he wants to fuck you.
-They were gay.
-So?
One minute they were interested and then,
suddenIy they weren't.
What did I do to turn them off?
Not having a dick wouId be the thing
that you did to turn them off.
You guys, I'm serious. This is rude.
Use it to bring any man to his knees.
With Iove, of course.
Where was this bitch Iast night
when I needed her?
Be quiet and you might Iearn something.
This Iady is supposed to be a genius.
If she's so good, why is she having
this workshop in her apartment?
I don't know.
Tantric sex is not about taIk,
it's about action.
DeIayed action.
So, without further deIay...
...Iet me introduce my husband.
Dr. Ronny Shapiro.
I wiII demonstrate the very effective...
...Lingham Massage.
I think I know why we're in an apartment.
The receiver Iies on his back...
...before the giver, naked.
GenitaIs cIearIy exposed for the massage.
You're not writing.
Take your time doing this.
An hour and a half later, crlppled by our
lnablllty to look away from a car crash...
...we watched as the Dr. Shaplro
lllustrated tantrlc sex.
Massage the head of the Lingham...
...as if you are using an orange juicer.
There go my good feeIings about breakfast.
Stop it! You're embarrassing me.
We're the embarrassing part?
PIace your right hand...
...on the receiver's Root chakra.
Root!
The Root chakra is Iocated between
the anus and the genitaIs.
I think that I just got my 50 bucks worth.
GentIy rock your hand
to awaken this chakra.
CIinicaIIy referred to as perineum.
Perineum: Latin for
''not without an engagement ring.''
WiII the women who are Iaughing
compose themseIves?
Thank you.
Orgasm is not the goaI
of Lingham Massage...
...but can be a pIeasant
and very weIcome side effect.
Watch what I'm doing here.
If you can master this...
...your man wiII aIways be faithfuI.
Because once they go tantric...
...they don't go back.
You go, girI.
See that? Can you aII see this?
My God!
He's gonna....
And just llke that,
Mlranda got hlt by Old Falthful.
What's funny?
After we talked Mlranda ln from
the ledge, I met Patrlck for a movle.
I was teIIing my sponsor today
how I feIt about you...
...and suddenIy I reaIized
maybe I shouId just teII you.
I Iove you.
There lt was, the llttle phrase
every glrl ls dylng to hear...
...a week and a half lnto a relatlonshlp.
Thanks and that's so....
What? Too soon?
Is that what you're thinking?
We have been going out for, Iike, a minute.
Fuck that shit. I don't want to pIay games.
I'm just trying to own my feeIings.
I Iove you. I said it.
Mr. Casey, you do not Iove me...
...you Iove you, not drinking, with me.
No, I Iove you.
I'm so fIattered...
...but I think maybe we shouId
sIow down a IittIe here.
What does that mean?
It means that things
are going very fast and....
You have these new feeIings
because you're not drinking--
No, don't give me that program buIIshit.
This has nothing to do with drinking.
I Iove you.
Maybe we shouId spend a IittIe time apart.
I'II caII you tomorrow.
-I'm not coming up?
-Just a coupIe of nights.
Are you breaking up with me? 'Cause if--
I'm not breaking up with you.
I'm just going inside.
CaII me tomorrow.
We'II do something next week, okay?
What am I going to do now?
You shouId go to a meeting.
And then go home, and caII me tomorrow.
Goodnight.
I'II see you next week.
Go.
Get yourseIf some cookies.
Meanwhlle, across town at Charlotte's....
My God, what are you doing?
My God.
You are good. Sweet Christ!
You are good!
Charlotte consldered lt the best 50 bucks
she'd ever spent.
It cost Mlranda a llttle more, but across
town ln her bed, thlngs were good as well.
CarrleI
What are you doing?
Fuck you, you bitch!
Shit!
I Ioved you and you didn't Iove me.
You fucking made me date you...
...before the month and now I'm drunk.
And I don't care!
I Iove you!
Make Iove to me!
What are you doing?
Don't take your cIothes off.
My flrst lmpulse was to go down
and rescue hlm...
...but as I learned on our second date,
that would be codependent.
Stlll, I felt I had to do somethlng.
Here, put this on, you'II get a coId.
I hope I fucking die!
Quiet, asshoIe, I'II caII the cops!
Shut the fuck up, dickweed!
Carrie!
You were the best fuck I ever had!
Three weeks later,
I got a letter from Patrlck...
...saylng he was back ln the program
and wanted to make amends.
I never saw hlm agaln
but I always wondered two thlngs.:
Was he able to stay sober?
Am I really that good ln bed?