Previously on...
Suits
When I was 11,
my parents were involved
in a really horrible accident.
My grandmother took me in.
It's your grandma.
She passed away.
Either Jessica will retain
her position,
or I will resume control
of Pearson Hardman.
I'm entitled to name
one new senior partner a year.
If you are on the wrong side,
there'll be no coming back.
The managing partner
is Daniel Hardman.
Jessica lost!
You lost!
Are you looking for another
way to make my life miserable?
Zoe, I'm still not convinced
I should hire you.
Well, Harvey never tried
to sleep with Ted Phillips.
Ms. Sheila Sazs.
I think Louis is attracted
to female Louis.
- I'm Tess.
- You guys must go way back.
First beer, prom, sex.
Your grandmother just died.
When something
like that happens,
people don't make
smart choices.
- You're married.
- And you called me anyway.
What if Hardman planted
the CM memo
in the first place?
All those in favor
of Daniel Hardman's dismissal...
[Knock on door]
I don't care
about being smart.
[Laughs]
Fyi, we're out of pizza.
You're telling me this now?
I didn't know
you were gonna get high.
You mean you didn't know
we were gonna get high.
Oh, does this mean you're
not going back to work tomorrow?
No, it means I'm celebrating
going back to work tomorrow.
Fine.
But don't think I don't know
what you're really doing.
What, getting you high,
so I can get into your pants
or under your sheet
or whatever?
I meant you're afraid.
Afraid? Nope.
I'm not afraid,
I can't wait to get back.
You can't wait to get back
to talk to Rachel?
I am not afraid
to talk to Rachel.
And I'm not afraid
of the big, bad wolf.
Look, I told you,
she's a friend.
She was just coming
to check up on me, that's all.
And I told you
I believed you.
You're welcome.
So why can't you just keep
pretending you believe me now?
Because you have
to go back to work tomorrow.
And your husband gets back
in town tomorrow.
- You want more pizza?
- Let's order more pizza.
- Yeah.
- Great.
Somebody give you
a promotion?
Somebody should.
Lopez buyout delayed,
Phillips merger closed.
Oh, and Zoe Lawford called,
which is odd,
because I don't remember us
having a trial
we needed
consulting services on.
So that's why you're sitting
at my desk.
I wanted to be
in a position of power
when I toyed with you.
Let's get one thing clear.
I'm not Charlie Brown,
you're not Lucy,
and that's not a football.
Let's get
two things clear.
I don't remember
ever placing a call to Zoe,
but her message said
she was calling back.
I called her.
For business.
What kind of business?
A merger?
Okay, what are you,
12 years old?
I'm not the one
robbing the cradle here.
I'm not robbing anything.
Zoe and I are the same age.
So you admit it.
You called to ask her
on a date.
Behind my back.
It wasn't behind your back.
You'd gone home already.
Because you waited
for me to go home.
Like I said,
it was behind your back.
Harvey,
just out of curiosity,
what took you so long
to call her?
I had my hands full
with Hardman.
Well, now you're hands full
of her.
Look, now it's over,
I want to celebrate.
And she's the person
I want to do it with.
Are you gonna tell her that?
I assume you heard
that the Lopez buyout
was delayed?
So I'm gonna need some--
Louis, I don't give a shit
what you need.
All right, Harvey,
you know what?
Look, it's been a week.
You won, you know,
get over it.
Get out.
You know,
for your information,
I wasn't the only senior partner
who voted for Hardman.
And I don't see you giving
anyone else shit
the way you give me.
And by the way,
when the chips were down,
I backed you,
I ousted him.
You mean
when you did this?
Tell yourself
whatever you want, Louis,
but tell it to yourself.
You here
to rip the band-aid off?
It's what grammy always said
to do when you have a boo-boo.
Really?
You're gonna use her
to get out of this?
Look, Rachel, I understand
that you're mad at me.
No, I'm not.
What's that expression?
"Fool me once,
shame on you.
Fool me twice--"
nobody's fooling anybody.
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry for what?
For what I saw
or what you did?
Rachel, come on.
I'm just trying to--
let me just ask you this.
Does she know that six hours
before you screwed her,
you tried to screw me?
Okay, let's not pretend
that this is about her, okay?
So she knows,
or she doesn't?
I mean, is it fair to her
that she was your second choice
that night?
Because if I were her, Mike--
She's married.
I don't think
she's really worried
about being
my second choice.
Welcome back.
Who's ready
for a great first day?
Harvey, can you give us
a minute, please?
I can't.
We actually have a crisis.
We gotta go.
Come on.
[Clears throat]
You once told me
you could fix anything, Harvey.
This is my son, Liam.
Your mother says
you have a problem.
Um, I was driving home
from Greenwich last night.
A friend's party.
I hit someone.
I-I didn't see him.
He came out of nowhere.
Were you drunk?
Don't answer that.
If this comes to trial,
I can't put him on the stand.
But I wasn't drinking.
And if we asked everybody else
at the party,
would they tell
the same story?
If it comes out,
we need to know.
Talk to anyone
who was there.
What if I checked your car
for beer bottles right now?
Go ahead.
Check anything you want.
I'm telling the truth.
Okay, it was an accident.
We can deal with this.
Tell me, what happened
to the guy you hit?
I don't know.
- That's why we called you.
- What do you mean?
He drove away.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ all right
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
♪ Suits 2x11 ♪
Blind-Sided
Original Air Date on January 17, 2013
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
I know exactly
what you're gonna say.
We have to find out
what happened to the guy he hit.
So I'm gonna call
all the hospitals...
I think you need
to sit this one out.
Look,
I know I jumped the gun,
but one wrong question
and I'm out?
You weren't jumping the gun,
it set you off.
Harvey, I'm fine.
Look, I'm not blaming you,
I'm understanding you.
Your parents were killed
by a drunk driver.
- And Liam said he wasn't drunk.
- Doesn't matter.
Your emotions get
the better of you on a merger.
Gillian's a longtime client.
It's her only son,
I can't have that.
I can do this.
Your grandmother
just died.
I said I'm onboard.
I'm onboard.
So what do you think?
The damage helps us.
It's minimal.
More importantly,
if the impact was central,
guy would have been directly
in your field of vision,
so this backs the story up.
He came out of nowhere.
Albert Chung was rushed
to the E.R. last night,
after a 911 call.
- You called 911?
- Yeah.
You should have
told us that.
He has a concussion,
contusions, four cracked ribs,
but he's stable.
Thank God,
so it's okay.
Gillian,
Liam needs to turn himself in.
It was an accident.
Exactly,
so if he comes forward,
he's a 20-year-old kid
who freaked out,
but now he's doing
the right thing.
Harvey's right.
If they come to us,
which I know they will,
we'll be on the defensive,
we'll never recover.
- Shit.
- You can't know that.
They might never find him.
You really want to risk
your son's life on that?
I'm sorry,
but isn't this Liam's decision?
- What's gonna happen to me?
- I don't know.
But if you're worried
about prison movies,
that's not
what's gonna happen.
How do you know that?
Because I know Harvey.
I don't know.
Hey, believe it or not,
I've been where you are
right now.
What?
Yeah.
I was 16.
Got busted for possession,
1/2 ounce.
[Chuckles]
I was so scared.
You smoke?
I did.
I do.
But you
didn't hurt anybody.
I know it feels
like there's no way out.
But I'm telling you,
you're going to be home
in time for dinner.
I must say,
I'm so glad you called.
- I'm so glad you answered.
- I'm glad you're glad.
When were you gonna tell me
about your promotion?
You know
about my promotion?
Senior partnerships
rocket to my ears
with the speed
of a late-night bullet.
- Really?
- I read it on Twitter.
From the moment
I laid eyes on you,
I could tell
you were a baller.
Oh, I ball,
which is why I called you.
One of the perks
of my new title--
Say it.
[Whispering]
Senior partner.
Go on.
I get to hire
an associate of my own.
A Boy Wonder
to my Batman.
Well, I am with you,
Dark Knight.
I want you
to send me the best of the best.
I've already
lined up interviews
with my top five
recent graduates.
- Have you?
- Figure of speech.
But, I have to say,
I was hoping you didn't call
exclusively for business.
I was hoping
you were hoping that.
I'm gonna be honest
with you, Louis.
Senior partner has
a certain sex appeal
junior partner doesn't.
I thought that
to myself about myself.
Room 405.
9:00 p.m. tomorrow.
Bring coconut oil,
a ski mask, and duct tape.
[Whispering]
Fear never felt so good.
Katrina Bennett.
- Harvey Specter.
- Nice to meet you.
Your record is something
of a legend around here.
Excellent.
I hope we can extend each other
some professional courtesy.
I'm not extending you
anything.
Of course.
What better thing to do
than to take down a legend?
Well, I'm glad
we understand each other.
We do,
but here's the problem.
This isn't the case for it.
It's a misdemeanor,
leaving the scene,
and now
he's turned himself in.
Because you knew
we'd trace the 911 call.
That's not why.
He feels terrible.
He feels afraid.
Not the same thing.
Katrina, I understand
you want to take me out,
but this is an accident.
Liam made a mistake,
and he's rectifying it.
We'll accept
maximum community service
and whatever fine
you deem appropriate.
And what
about funeral costs?
Wait. What?
He died?
Which makes it
felony hit-and-run.
He was stable.
His concussion led
to a brain bleed.
That man's death
doesn't change the fact
that it was an accident.
Felony hit-and-run,
under these circumstances,
is 12 to 15 years.
You wanted courtesy?
Here it is.
I'll go ten.
That's crazy.
It was dark.
He wasn't drinking.
Tell me it's not
what you would have offered.
Maria Monroe.
Secretary of your class
at Harvard Law.
Clerked
for Chief Justice Roberts.
Glowing letters
of recommendation.
You think this impresses me?
Negative.
Which means you have
exactly five minutes
to convince me
that you're the one.
I don't need five minutes.
I am the one.
It's you who's on the clock,
Louis.
I have standing offers from
the top three firms in the city.
Pearson Hardman
is a top-three firm.
Well,
I used to think so.
But if it's taking you this long
to meet with me,
maybe you're slipping.
Oh, no, I'm not--
[Stammers] We're not slipping.
You need to submit
a formal offer by noon tomorrow
if you want me
to even consider working here.
Wh-- Maria,
hold on a second.
Just wait right there,
wait right there.
You four, beat it.
Position has been filled.
I'll beat any salary by 50%.
25,000 signing bonus.
- Put it in writing.
- W-w-w--
don't you want me
to give you a tour of the firm?
Show you
where you'll be working?
Well, I don't care
where I'd be working
because I'm a machine.
I have to have you.
That's what they all say.
Police report,
photos of the intersection,
coroner's report.
This isn't sixth-grade math.
Don't show me your work,
just give me the answer.
God, I wish I had you
in the sixth grade.
Except, no--
Miss Jenson, very hot.
You need a minute alone?
There was a reason that Liam
did not see Albert Chung.
He was wearing a hooded
sweatshirt, jeans, and sneakers.
All black.
Guy couldn't have been harder
to see if he was trying.
Maybe he was trying.
Albert Chung was
an art school dropout.
Look at that graffiti
on the wall.
"A.C."
Albert Chung.
He was trying
to be invisible
because he was tagging
that building.
And he was running away
when he got hit.
Which means
Liam didn't cause the accident,
Albert Chung did.
I think you missed
your calling as a fake cop.
Going back to that well again?
Okay.
So what are you gonna do?
Stick it to Katrina?
No, you're gonna stick it
to Katrina.
You heard her.
Her agenda isn't
just prosecuting Liam,
it's beating me.
See, I'm taking
the personal out of it.
Your problem is,
you put the personal into it.
Okay,
I thought my problem
was showing you my work
unnecessarily.
Who said
there's only one problem?
Well played.
Felony hit-and-run hinges
on a lack
of contributory negligence.
Albert Chung was fleeing
a crime scene.
He put himself
in harm's way.
So your client
can't be held responsible?
We'll plead to misdemeanor
leaving the scene,
but that's all.
I'm going to do you a favor
and take this deal.
You're not doing me a favor,
you're doing yourself a favor.
We've got you.
Got me or not,
it's no secret
the D.A. and Harvey had
a run-in.
He finds out
this is Harvey's case,
it goes to trial.
And anything can happen
at trial,
so let me be clear,
I am doing you a favor.
What do you want?
To make the same career jump
Harvey did.
To corporate litigation?
To Pearson Hardman.
Wait, I thought you--
That I wanted
to kick Harvey's ass?
I said that
because you don't impress
a lawyer like Harvey
with flowers.
Look, this is a fair plea.
And it's one
that should go through.
I'll make sure
that it does.
And if you were
to put a word in with Harvey,
I would appreciate it.
You got
to be kidding me.
She actually said that?
Yeah.
I don't know if I settled a case
or agreed to a bribe.
- Did she sign the plea offer?
- Yeah.
Then, "A," because she
can't rescind that thing
unless new evidence
comes to light,
and I don't have
to interview her for shit.
- Good.
- Yeah, good.
I don't want to hire
another associate ever again.
The one I picked
causes me enough headaches.
Oh, right,
like winning cases?
Graffiti, man in black--
is that ringing any bells?
It does indeed,
which leads us
to our next assignment,
should you choose
to accept it.
Please tell me
you're about to self-destruct.
We need to settle
with the Chung family.
Harvey,
their son just died.
I know, and I also know
that grief comes in stages,
and the best time to settle
is before it gets to anger.
You mean the best time
to take advantage of them
is before it
gets to anger.
- That's not--
- Our concern?
I know we got Liam
out of prison,
but he still hit a guy,
and that guy is still dead.
And we still
represent Liam.
Harvey...
I know it's not
the same situation, but...
I remember the day
the lawyer came to our place.
Nick Rinaldi.
I...
I remember his dirty shoes.
I remember
how they scraped the floor
when he walked
into the living room
to tell my grandmother
how much my parents' lives
were worth.
I've been
where these people are.
Let me be the one
to tell them.
You sure
you can handle it?
I'm sure as hell
not going
to leave them
to the likes of you.
Okay,
you can handle it.
You're authorized
to go as high as $100,000.
Divorce is on 43.
Look, I know
that you're mad at me,
and I never meant
to put you in this situation,
but I would
really appreciate it
if you kept what I told you
to yourself.
[Laughs]
Let me get this straight.
You hit on me,
then you run into the arms
of some married woman,
you come waltzing
into my office
trying to cutesy your way
out of it,
and now you have the nerve
to think I'm gonna go
and tell other people?
[Box hittable]
I have no idea what
you're gonna tell other people,
but you sure seem
to have the ability
to judge everything
that I do.
Do you think that you have
the lock on bad decisions?
All I know
is I'm not little miss perfect.
I've had
an affair before too.
You see the look
on your face?
Who's judging who now,
Mike?
And, no, it was not
some 50-year-old man
trying to take advantage
of poor, young me.
We were the same age,
and I went after him.
I am not the goody-goody
you think I am.
You have no idea
what you passed on.
And I'll tell you something,
Mike.
What you're doing,
it only ends one way.
Ms. Chung,
I just want you to know
that Liam Colson is devastated
by this accident,
regardless of who caused it.
Thank you.
I know that there's
no amount of money
that can ever
make up for it...
and that this is
probably the last thing
you want to be talking about.
My brother wasn't exactly
a model citizen, Mr. Ross.
We know he's not entitled
to much.
All my parents want is
to pay off Albert's debts
and cover
the funeral costs.
And how much would that be?
$20,000.
Well, I'd like
to offer you $100,000.
In fact, I insist on it.
[Speaking in Cantonese]
Where do we sign?
Um...
Right here and here.
[Pen scribbles]
Will you stay for some tea?
I'd be honored.
9:00 p.m.
to the second.
Punctuality is
the best aphrodisiac.
Who are you?
I'm Batman.
Did you bring
the accoutrement?
Oui.
I'm on pins and needles.
[Giggles]
Uh-uh.
Before we begin,
I need to know...
Who's your front-runner?
Maria Monroe.
Wasn't even close.
I know.
There were no five best.
- You were testing me?
- Mm-hmm.
I wasn't about to serve up
my best candidate
on a silver platter.
God, I love that.
After all,
Maria is very desirable.
But the thing is,
I'm gonna need you...
to help me close her.
Louis, come closer.
Stop.
I'm gonna close the shit
out of Maria for you.
And you're gonna close
the shit out of me.
All aboard.
Wait a minute,
if I didn't pick her,
we wouldn't be doing this?
Oh, I'm saying
no such thing.
But the nature
of what we're about to do
would be
radically different.
I dominated,
so I get to dominate.
- You get to be dominated.
- Yes, I do.
Do you need
a safe word?
Safe words are for pussies.
Start with my slippers.
Oh, thank you.
[Gasps]
[Knocks on door]
- Hello.
- Where are your flowers?
My flowers?
You go on a date, you're
supposed to bring flowers.
- Am I?
- Yes, Harvey.
Everyone knows that.
How many dates
have you been on?
- Six.
- Six?
Mm, sounds serious.
Who's the lucky guy?
Jason.
He's not a guy,
he's a boy.
And he brings flowers.
[Laughs]
Well, maybe next time
we can have a double date.
You that sure
it's gonna go well tonight?
Olivia,
why don't you go upstairs
and finish watching
your show?
Is there maybe something
you forgot to tell me?
You mean
about your daughter?
See, that's funny
because we never slept together.
I don't find it funny
in the least,
and by "it," I mean
that we never slept together.
Seriously, Harvey,
I'm really sorry about this.
Olivia's my niece.
My brother just dropped her off.
He didn't have
anybody else.
Then I guess
we'll have to sit down,
watch Bugs Bunny,
and order a pizza.
[Laughs]
Bugs Bunny?
Yeah, no one
watches that anymore.
I thought Apocalypse Now
would be a little much for her.
Can I come in?
Hey.
Thanks for starting without me.
- Couldn't wait.
- That bad a day?
Mm, nope,
that good of one.
So your little chat
with Rachel went well.
Not what I meant.
I negotiated a settlement
with the sister
of the man who was killed
in a car accident today.
Oh, my God.
No, no.
It's not what you think.
I, um,
I gave this family dignity.
And as hard as it was...
It was the best day of work
I've ever had.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Hey.
Liam's plea deal
came through.
It's on its way
to Gillian's.
I need you to go over there
and walk 'em through it,
so we can wrap this up.
Uh, I'm on my way.
Sh.
What?
I have to go see a client.
Mike, you're high.
What if they can tell?
Tess, I was high every day
of my life for years,
and nobody knew, okay?
[Hands clap]
I can handle it.
- She asleep?
- Not exactly.
She wants you to go up there
and kiss her good night.
[Laughs]
You don't have to do this.
- No, I can do that.
- Harvey.
Afterwards, I want you
to come down here
and kiss me good night.
So...
I sign this,
and we're done?
Um...yeah.
Uh, the A.D.A. agreed to it,
so you sign it,
and then, um...
and then the judge will sign it.
[Voice breaks] And then--
then we're done.
[Sighs]
Community service
and a fine.
You sound disappointed.
No, no,
I appreciate it.
It's just...
It could have been
so much worse.
I thought
my life was over.
I'm such an asshole.
Hey, Liam,
it's okay to feel relief.
The Chung family
doesn't blame you.
Nobody blames you.
Do you remember
what you said the other day
about getting high?
[Laughs]
Um, why are you asking me that?
I was high.
What?
[Sighs]
How could you
not tell us that?
'Cause Harvey
said not to.
But you said
you weren't drunk.
You said, "ask everyone."
You could have.
I was alone.
I get high all the time,
and no one ever knows.
- Oh, my God.
- What's the matter?
You said
this was a done deal.
It is, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a done deal.
- We got a huge problem.
- Don't worry, Mike.
I'm sure 'Nsync
will tour again someday.
We can't submit this deal
because it wasn't an accident.
It was a DUI.
- What?
- He was stoned.
This changes everything.
It changes nothing.
I misrepresented the facts
to Katrina.
No, you didn't,
because you didn't know
because we didn't ask.
And I didn't ask now,
but he told me now.
And that's privileged,
and the deal is done.
Wait a minute,
so you're not gonna do anything?
I'm gonna have Donna messenger
this to the D.A.'s office.
Harvey, this family thinks
their son is to blame.
Because he was fleeing
the scene of a crime,
which put him in harm's way.
Okay, maybe.
But if I don't tell them
this part,
then I'm no different
than Nick Rinaldi.
- You're already different.
- What do you mean?
I mean, they were ready
to take the $20,000,
but you gave 'em $100,000.
Did you think I wasn't going
to find out about that?
Harvey, please, come on.
You asked me
to be on this case
after I warned you
about something like this.
You said, "I'm onboard."
Do you have any idea
what would happen
if Gillian found out
what you did?
What if she found out
about her son?
She'd probably give them
a bigger settlement.
But, hey, you already did that,
and I let it go.
You need to let this go.
Say whatever you want.
That's no different
than Nick Rinaldi,
that's just more money
and cleaner shoes.
Oh, my God.
You were waiting.
I heard you were here,
so I rushed right out.
I formally accept
your offer
of employment
at Pearson Hardman.
Oh, this is
the best week ever.
I won't let you down.
I'm sorry.
I have no idea
what this is regarding,
but, yes, he will.
He always does.
- Water off a snail's back.
- See what I mean?
Donna Paulsen, Maria Monroe,
my personal first-year.
- Oh.
- She's a machine.
And let me
just tell you something,
she's gonna run circles
around Mike Ross.
You wait right here,
and I'll get us some bundt cake.
I'm sorry, Mike who?
- Mike Ross.
- Is he a first-year?
Why do you ask?
I thought you only hired
from Harvard.
- We do.
- I was secretary of my class.
I knew every name.
There was no Mike Ross
my year at Harvard.
But you weren't
the same year.
No, I clerked
for a year.
He's a year
ahead of me here,
but he would have been
in my class.
Oh, well, Mike clerked
for three years,
which means
he wasn't in your class.
Well, I look forward
to meeting him.
Uh...last night.
I was, uh...
I was driving home,
I'd had a lot to drink.
I hit someone.
And I'm pretty sure
that they're dead.
So, uh,
I need your help.
Sorry,
I don't take cases like that.
You don't take cases
like that?
What about your case
from 1992?
Driver plows into a car,
after drinking
about a thousand jack and cokes,
killing
a happily married couple?
James and Nina Ross?
I'm afraid
I have no recollection of that.
Oh, yeah? Let me ring
a bell for you, then.
Two days later, you walk
into their living room,
you find their little boy
and his grandmother
just sitting there,
and then you stick it to them.
They hadn't even had time
to hold a wake yet.
Are you still
gonna deny it?
I didn't deny it,
just have
no recollection of it
because I did it
so many times.
I'm sorry, is that
supposed to move me, huh?
Am I supposed to think
that you're somehow
above all that now?
It's not supposed
to do anything.
But let me point out,
you walked in here
two minutes ago,
told me you'd hit somebody,
and I turned you away.
[Sighs]
- What's your name?
- Like you give a shit.
Okay.
What are you looking for
from me?
I want to know
how you live with yourself.
how you wake up every morning
and not put a bullet
in your brain,
knowing what a piece of shit
you are!
You might not want
to hear this.
But just because I
don't remember who you are
doesn't mean I don't regret
what I did to you.
Now the sad fact is
that once a deal is done,
it can't be undone.
James and Nina Ross.
If I ever see you again,
you better remember
who they are.
Thank you.
Did you know Louis
is hiring his own associate?
Not specifically,
but he is entitled to it.
We got to stop him.
Harvey,
I know you're mad at Louis.
So am I,
but it's over.
We won, and the man
has a job to do.
That's not
what I meant.
We let him hire the person
he just hired,
Mike's gonna be exposed.
How do you know this?
She was secretary
of his class.
And there's 600 kids
in that class.
Nobody knows everybody.
She says she does.
- How can you be so sure?
- Donna met her.
She's sure.
Goddamn Mike Ross.
He's the gift
that keeps on giving.
How many more headaches is
this kid gonna cause me, Harvey?
You wanted
to see me?
Did you make an offer
to a Maria Monroe
to be
a first-year associate?
Yes, and let me
just tell you something,
you're gonna love her.
Rescind it.
- What?
- Firm's been through a lot.
We have to regroup.
Therefore, I'm instituting
a hiring freeze,
which you
would have known about
had you come
and asked my permission first.
Okay, you can't do this.
I'm a senior partner,
and that's the rule.
Strictly speaking,
it's not a rule,
it's a tradition.
I get it.
Strictly speaking, this
isn't about a hiring freeze,
this is punishment.
You can be punitive,
I can be punitive.
The offer already went out,
Jessica.
You're a lawyer,
make it go away.
What am I gonna tell
the world?
I'm gonna look
like a freaking fool.
Well, tell them
there's a hiring freeze.
I don't care.
Make it go away.
You're dismissed.
The message you left
was a little cryptic.
What do you want?
I want to help you get
what you want.
And what is that?
Liam Colson was driving
under the influence
when he hit Albert Chung.
How exactly did you come
to know that?
I can't tell you that.
- Thank you, Mike.
- Yeah.
All rise
for the honorable judge
Nicholas Palermo.
Be seated.
"State of New York
versus Liam Colson."
I am happy to report
the state entered
into a plea agreement
with the defendant
last night.
You have a copy
of the terms, Your Honor.
Everything appears
to be in order.
The agreement
is approved.
Community service
starts Monday.
That's it?
You're just walking away?
As fast as I can.
Because you know what "I can't
tell you how I know that" means?
It means
you just violated privilege.
Wait, so you don't care
that he was driving
under the influence?
I can't prove
he was under the influence.
You don't know
what you could prove
if you got that kid
in a room.
If I were to use
what you just told me,
all I would be doing is making
myself look like an idiot.
Are you really gonna be able
to sleep at night?
Are you?
You're the one
who walked in there
and tried
to sell out a 20-year-old kid.
He took someone's life,
right?
That someone had a mother
and a father and a sister.
That family
is never gonna be the same.
Listen to me,
you think I haven't had a case
where I could have crossed
a line to put someone away?
[Laughs] I wouldn't
be surprised if you did,
after that bribe
you offered me.
I didn't offer you shit.
I did you a favor.
And then I asked for a favor,
which you could do or not.
Is that really
what you tell yourself
when you look
in the mirror?
If you're willing
to break privilege,
you're the one who needs
to look in the mirror.
Katrina Bennett called.
The deal's done.
Get the paperwork started.
Harvey,
what did you do?
I did
what I had to do.
Your first hire
was Mike.
Are you sure you want this
to be your second?
I don't want
to hear it.
She starts on Monday.
Chateauneuf-du-pape,
1985.
I guess they were out
of the '83.
Louis,
you look like I just kicked you
in the stomach
but in a bad way.
I'm sorry.
I, uh...
my mind's on something else.
What is it?
Promise
you won't be mad?
You're not about to tell me
I have to get tested, are you?
What? No.
Nothing like that.
I...
I had to rescind the offer...
to Maria.
You're mad?
No.
I'm disappointed.
Sheila...
You're not the man
I thought you were.
I--I didn't have
a choice.
It was
Jessica Pearson's decision.
Okay, well,
then I must have read you wrong
'cause I thought you were
a strong, powerful
senior partner.
I am.
The evidence suggests
otherwise.
I think you should go.
Sheila, please.
I mean, can't this snafu
just be something we laugh at,
like, in an hour and a half,
hour and 45 minutes?
Your sexual prowess
isn't gonna get you out of this.
- You are mad.
- Yeah.
I put my reputation on the line
to close Maria.
Look, it's not my fault.
The firm instituted
a hiring freeze.
If there's
a hiring freeze going on,
then why do I know
for a fact
that Harvey Specter hired
a fifth-year associate today?
You offered Katrina Bennett
a job?
I looked into her.
Turns out
she's a stellar candidate.
[Scoffs]
You bribed her.
A bribe requires
a clear exchange
of something
for something else.
That didn't happen here.
Bullshit.
She said she'd put
the deal through
if you offered her a job.
She said she'd put
the deal through,
then I offered her a job.
Oh, right, because you needed
an insurance policy.
Because I could see exactly
what you were gonna do.
So you offered her a job to
get her to do what you wanted.
That's something
for something else.
You bribed her.
You bet your ass I did.
But what you're too stupid
to understand is
I did it to save you.
Get it
through your goddamn head.
You're not like
other lawyers.
You break
attorney-client privilege,
nothing different happens
with Liam,
but they're sure as shit
gonna look into you.
And you and I both know what
they're gonna find when they do.
What difference does it make
what they find?
There's such a thing
as right and wrong.
And we're wrong!
You know what?
I have had it up to here
with you blaming me
for every hard choice
that comes with this job.
- Harvey, come on.
- Shut up!
Is your life better or worse
than before I hired you?
It's both.
Well, maybe you should focus
on the better,
because the next time
I have the option
to cross a line
to save you,
I'll send you packing
and not think twice.
Now get your shit together.
[Elevator bell dings]
Is it done?
It's done.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
A man is dead.
You killed him,
and I have to live with it.
And you think
I don't know that?
I get to go back to my life
like nothing happened,
but something did happen.
It makes me sick.
It should.
Is that why you came here,
to make me feel worse?
You've been given a gift
that you don't deserve.
So you better
clean yourself up
and figure out a way
to make up for Albert Chung.
[Knock at door]
You brought flowers.
You're learning.
They're for Olivia.
What about me?
That's for you.
You bought me a...car?
Yeah, I was thinking
we'd drive up to the Berkshires.
There's a little cabin
I know.
It's got its own sauna,
private chef.
Oh, wow.
I can't go away
with you, Harvey.
Why not?
My brother's
got cancer.
He's--
he's not gonna make it.
Oh, my God.
Her dad.
I mean, we knew
that it was coming.
We just didn't know
it would be this fast.
- Is she here?
- No.
But I'm going
to my parents',
and I'm gonna--
I'm gonna take her with me.
I'm gonna raise her.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I thought,
you know, when...
[Sniffles]
you saw Olivia was here,
that we'd reschedule
or something, you know?
And then...
I saw you with her,
and it...
It was...
You wanted
to have a night.
Okay, I didn't think
it would lead to that.
But I'm really happy
that it did.
When are you going?
Soon.
I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
Surprise.
Hey, I never heard from you.
How did the case go?
I don't want
to talk about it.
That bad, huh?
Yeah, that bad.
Well, why don't you
come over here,
and I'll make you
feel better?
I already started
without you.
I can't do this anymore,
Tess.
Get high?
- It's so disgusting.
- What got into you?
This whole thing
is disgusting.
Are you breaking up
with me?
- Do you love your husband?
- What?
It's a simple question, Tess,
answer it.
Do you love your husband?
- Uh, I don't know.
- See, I don't even know that.
Because we never even talk
about it.
Well, we can talk
about it now.
I don't want
to talk about it now!
Tess, there is such a thing
as right and wrong.
And what we're doing here...
It's just wrong, and...
you're married.
And I don't want
a part of it anymore.
What if I wasn't?
Mike.
You need to go.
And I need
to get my shit together.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==