1
00:06:20,210 --> 00:06:23,210
{\pos(70,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:06:20,210 --> 00:06:23,210
{\pos(70,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:06:20,210 --> 00:06:23,210
{\pos(60,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:06:20,210 --> 00:06:23,210
{\pos(86,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:06:20,210 --> 00:06:23,210
{\pos(100,254)}人人影视
YYeTs.com

6
00:06:20,210 --> 00:06:23,210
{\pos(101,267)}原创翻译  双语字幕

7
00:06:20,210 --> 00:06:23,210
{\pos(240,267)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

8
00:06:23,210 --> 00:06:26,210
{\an8}翻译：某豚 一不二 爱卿遛小鸟 月月 CiciXT allenlovestar 叽咕

9
00:06:26,210 --> 00:06:29,210
{\an8}校对：油炸电风扇 月月     总监：月月

10
00:06:29,210 --> 00:06:32,210
{\an8}后期：仓鼠sama     时间轴：迟迟 凭陵新月

11
00:06:46,610 --> 00:06:48,780
{\pos(185,208)}第二季 第十一集

12
00:06:46,610 --> 00:06:48,780
{\pos(185,193)}诉 讼 双 雄

13
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:01,270
{\an8}《诉讼双雄》前情提要

14
00:00:01,390 --> 00:00:02,560
我十一岁那年
When I was 11,

15
00:00:02,570 --> 00:00:05,290
我父母遇到了一起严重事故
my parents were involved in a really horrible accident.

16
00:00:05,290 --> 00:00:06,440
我的奶奶收留了我
My grandmother took me in.

17
00:00:06,570 --> 00:00:08,780
是你奶奶  她去世了
It's your grandma. She passed away.

18
00:00:08,920 --> 00:00:11,200
一种结果是杰西卡继续留任
Either Jessica will retain her position,

19
00:00:11,200 --> 00:00:13,980
另一种就是我重新掌管皮尔逊·哈德曼律所
or I will resume control of Pearson Hardman.

20
00:00:13,980 --> 00:00:16,670
我有权每年任命一位新的资深合伙人
I'm entitled to name one new senior partner a year.

21
00:00:16,670 --> 00:00:20,320
若你站错了队伍  可没有后悔药
if you are on the wrong side, there'll be no coming back.

22
00:00:20,440 --> 00:00:23,210
新执行合伙人是丹尼尔·哈德曼
The managing partner is Daniel Hardman.

23
00:00:23,210 --> 00:00:25,250
杰西卡输了  你输了
Jessica lost! You lost!

24
00:00:25,250 --> 00:00:27,320
你又想到什么新法子来折磨我了吗
You looking for another way to make my life miserable?

25
00:00:27,320 --> 00:00:29,380
佐伊  我还是不确定我是否该雇你
Zoe, I'm still not convinced I should hire you.

26
00:00:29,380 --> 00:00:31,360
毕竟  哈维可没想睡泰德·菲利普斯
Well, Harvey never tried to sleep with Ted Phillips.

27
00:00:31,360 --> 00:00:32,440
希拉·赛斯女士
Ms. Sheila Zass.

28
00:00:32,580 --> 00:00:34,810
我看路易迷上女版的自己了
I think Louis is attracted to female Louis.

29
00:00:34,980 --> 00:00:36,840
-我叫苔丝  -那你们一定交情颇深了
- I'm Tess. - You guys must go way back.

30
00:00:36,840 --> 00:00:39,120
第一罐啤酒  第一次毕业舞会  第一次做爱
First beer, prom, sex.

31
00:00:39,970 --> 00:00:41,090
你祖母才刚去世
Your grandmother just died.

32
00:00:41,090 --> 00:00:42,100
就是在这种时候
When something like that happens, 

33
00:00:42,100 --> 00:00:43,870
人往往没法做出明智的决定
people don't make smart choices.

34
00:00:43,870 --> 00:00:46,110
-你结婚了  -不过你还是打给我了
- You're married. - And you called me anyway.

35
00:00:46,110 --> 00:00:47,360
也许当初就是哈德曼捏造了
What if Hardman planted 

36
00:00:47,360 --> 00:00:48,510
那份科斯特尔汽车的备忘
the CM memo in the first place?

37
00:00:48,520 --> 00:00:51,510
有人赞成丹尼尔·哈德曼离职吗
All those in favor of Daniel Hardman's dismissal?

38
00:00:53,290 --> 00:00:55,140
我不在乎是否明智
I don't care about being smart.

39
00:01:14,700 --> 00:01:16,950
提醒一句  披萨吃完了
FYI, we're out of pizza.

40
00:01:17,130 --> 00:01:18,770
你居然现在告诉我
You're telling me this now?

41
00:01:19,260 --> 00:01:20,920
我怎么知道你在嗑药
I didn't know you were gonna get high.

42
00:01:20,920 --> 00:01:22,820
你是说  你不知道我俩会嗑药
You mean you didn't know we were gonna get high.

43
00:01:23,080 --> 00:01:25,570
这就是说  你明天不打算去上班了吗
Oh, does this mean you're not going back to work tomorrow?

44
00:01:25,570 --> 00:01:27,850
不是  这是说我正庆祝明天能回去上班
No, it means I'm celebrating going back to work tomorrow.

45
00:01:27,850 --> 00:01:28,780
随你怎么说
Fine.

46
00:01:28,970 --> 00:01:30,950
别以为我不知道你在干什么
But don't think I don't know what you're really doing.

47
00:01:30,950 --> 00:01:32,840
怎么  我还需要让你嗑药  
What, getting you high, 

48
00:01:32,840 --> 00:01:34,180
才能脱掉你的裤子  
so I can get into your pants 

49
00:01:34,180 --> 00:01:35,400
或者让你躺在床上吗
or under your sheet or whatever?

50
00:01:35,400 --> 00:01:36,730
我是说  你害怕了
I meant you're afraid.

51
00:01:37,680 --> 00:01:39,650
害怕  怎么可能
Afraid? Nope.

52
00:01:39,650 --> 00:01:41,410
我才不害怕呢  迫不及待想回去
I'm not afraid, I can't wait to get back.

53
00:01:41,410 --> 00:01:43,240
迫不及待想回去和瑞秋谈谈吗
You can't wait to get back to talk to Rachel?

54
00:01:45,930 --> 00:01:47,550
我才不怕和瑞秋聊呢
I am not afraid to talk to Rachel.

55
00:01:47,550 --> 00:01:48,850
我还不怕大灰狼呢
And I'm not afraid of the big, bad wolf.

56
00:01:48,850 --> 00:01:50,550
我告诉过你  她就是个朋友
Look, I told you, she's a friend.

57
00:01:50,550 --> 00:01:52,710
过来看看我而已  就这么简单
She was just coming to check up on me, that's all.

58
00:01:52,850 --> 00:01:54,190
我也告诉过你  我相信过你
And I told you I believed you.

59
00:01:54,330 --> 00:01:55,360
不用谢啊
You're welcome.

60
00:01:56,780 --> 00:01:59,230
为什么不能假装相信我呢
So why can't you just keep pretending you believe me now?

61
00:01:59,430 --> 00:02:01,790
因为你明天要回去上班
Because you have to go back to work tomorrow.

62
00:02:03,610 --> 00:02:05,690
你丈夫明天也要回来了
And your husband gets back in town tomorrow.

63
00:02:08,520 --> 00:02:09,580
-还要披萨吗  -那就再订点吧
- You want more pizza? - Let's order more pizza.

64
00:02:09,580 --> 00:02:10,760
-好  -就这样
- Yeah. - Great.

65
00:02:29,290 --> 00:02:30,730
有人给你升职啦
Somebody give you a promotion?

66
00:02:30,730 --> 00:02:32,090
某人是该给我升职
Somebody should.

67
00:02:32,680 --> 00:02:35,920
洛佩兹并购推迟  菲利普合并完结
Lopez buyout delayed, Phillips merger closed.

68
00:02:35,930 --> 00:02:38,900
佐伊·劳福德打电话来了  很奇怪啊
Oh, and Zoe Lawford called, which is odd,

69
00:02:38,910 --> 00:02:40,510
我可不记得有哪个案子
because I don't remember us having a trial

70
00:02:40,510 --> 00:02:42,190
需要咨询服务的
we needed consulting services on.

71
00:02:42,190 --> 00:02:43,590
所以你才坐在我桌前
So that's why you're sitting at my desk.

72
00:02:43,590 --> 00:02:45,940
我希望捉弄你的时候  我能站在高处
I wanted to be in a position of power when I toyed with you.

73
00:02:49,210 --> 00:02:50,490
有件事可讲清楚了
Let's get one thing clear.

74
00:02:50,630 --> 00:02:51,880
我不是查理·布朗
I'm not Charlie Brown,

75
00:02:50,630 --> 00:02:53,820
{\an8}动画片史努比中情节  露西总是让查理信任自己
又在查理踢球前把球抽走

76
00:02:52,010 --> 00:02:53,820
你也不是露西  这件事也不是橄榄球
You're not Lucy, and that's not a football.

77
00:02:54,480 --> 00:02:55,660
有两件事可讲清楚了
Let's get two things clear.

78
00:02:56,040 --> 00:02:58,230
我不记得给佐伊打过电话
I don't remember ever placing a call to Zoe,

79
00:02:58,440 --> 00:03:00,740
但她的留言说  她是回电
but her message said she was calling back.

80
00:03:00,940 --> 00:03:03,030
我打给她了  出于公事
I called her. For business.

81
00:03:03,030 --> 00:03:05,660
什么样的公事  合并吗
What kind of business? A merger?

82
00:03:05,820 --> 00:03:07,130
够了  你多大了  十二岁吗
Okay, what are you, 12 years old?

83
00:03:07,130 --> 00:03:08,380
玩老少恋的可不是我
I'm not the one robbing the cradle here.

84
00:03:08,380 --> 00:03:09,450
我可没玩老少恋
I'm not robbing anything.

85
00:03:09,450 --> 00:03:11,370
-佐伊和我年纪一样大  -是承认了吗
- Zoe and I are the same age. - So you admit it.

86
00:03:11,370 --> 00:03:12,670
是你打电话约她出来
You called to ask her on a date.

87
00:03:12,810 --> 00:03:14,420
-还背着我  -这不是背着你
- Behind my back. - It wasn't behind your back.

88
00:03:14,420 --> 00:03:15,350
你那时已经回家了
You'd gone home already.

89
00:03:15,350 --> 00:03:16,590
因为你特地等到我回家
Because you waited for me to go home.

90
00:03:16,590 --> 00:03:18,160
正如我所说  背着你
Like I said, it was behind your back.

91
00:03:21,130 --> 00:03:23,750
哈维  我只是好奇
Harvey, just out of curiosity,

92
00:03:23,760 --> 00:03:25,450
你怎么过了这么久才联系她
what took you so long to call her?

93
00:03:25,760 --> 00:03:27,290
我对付哈德曼还忙不过来呢
I had my hands full with Hardman.

94
00:03:27,290 --> 00:03:28,660
现在你该为她焦头烂额了
Well, now you're hands full of her.

95
00:03:28,660 --> 00:03:30,830
现在一切都结束了  我想庆祝庆祝
Look, now it's over, I want to celebrate.

96
00:03:30,960 --> 00:03:32,370
而她是庆祝的不二人选
And she's the person I want to do it with.

97
00:03:33,380 --> 00:03:34,410
这话你会对她说吗
Are you gonna tell her that?

98
00:03:35,200 --> 00:03:37,560
你应该听说洛佩兹并购推迟的消息了吧
I assume you heard that the Lopez buyout was delayed?

99
00:03:37,560 --> 00:03:38,270
我需要...
So I'm gonna need some--

100
00:03:38,270 --> 00:03:39,920
路易  我才不管你要什么
Louis, I don't give a shit what you need.

101
00:03:40,200 --> 00:03:41,090
哈维  知道吗
All right, Harvey, you know what?

102
00:03:41,090 --> 00:03:42,430
都一周了
Look, it's been a week.

103
00:03:42,950 --> 00:03:44,770
你赢了  这件事就过去吧
You won, you know, get over it.

104
00:03:44,770 --> 00:03:45,480
出去
Get out.

105
00:03:46,080 --> 00:03:47,320
告诉你一句
You know, for your information,

106
00:03:47,320 --> 00:03:49,390
我可不是唯一投给哈德曼的高级合伙人
I wasn't the only senior partner who voted for Hardman.

107
00:03:49,390 --> 00:03:51,630
我怎么没见你给别人这样的白眼
and I don't see you giving anyone else shit the way you give me.

108
00:03:51,730 --> 00:03:53,190
还有  在紧要关头
And by the way, when the chips were down,

109
00:03:53,190 --> 00:03:54,720
我支持了你  赶走了他
I backed you, I ousted him.

110
00:03:55,220 --> 00:03:56,290
你是说你这样投票的时候吗
You mean when you did this?

111
00:03:59,450 --> 00:04:00,740
路易  你想怎么说都行
Tell yourself whatever you want, Louis,

112
00:04:00,740 --> 00:04:01,890
对着镜子说去
but tell it to yourself.

113
00:04:17,820 --> 00:04:19,500
你是来火上浇油吗
You here to rip the band-aid off?

114
00:04:19,630 --> 00:04:21,990
奶奶总是说  做错了事就该这样
It's what grammy always said to do when you have a boo-boo.

115
00:04:23,450 --> 00:04:24,350
真的吗
Really?

116
00:04:24,520 --> 00:04:26,190
你要拿她当借口  来摆脱这件事吗
You're gonna use her to get out of this?

117
00:04:28,430 --> 00:04:30,450
瑞秋  我知道你生我的气
Look, Rachel, I understand that you're mad at me.

118
00:04:30,460 --> 00:04:31,370
不  我没有
No, I'm not.

119
00:04:32,890 --> 00:04:33,930
那句话怎么说来着
What's that expression?

120
00:04:33,930 --> 00:04:35,420
愚弄我一次  羞愧的是你
"Fool me once, shame on you.

121
00:04:35,550 --> 00:04:36,720
愚弄我两次
Fool me twice--"

122
00:04:36,720 --> 00:04:37,940
没有人想愚弄谁
Nobody's fooling anybody.

123
00:04:38,280 --> 00:04:39,780
-我很抱歉  -抱歉什么
- I'm sorry. - Sorry for what?

124
00:04:40,760 --> 00:04:42,580
为我看到的事  还是你做的事
For what I saw or what you did?

125
00:04:42,580 --> 00:04:43,380
瑞秋  别这样
Rachel, come on.

126
00:04:43,380 --> 00:04:44,400
-我只想...  -我想问问你
- I'm just trying to-- - Let me just ask you this.

127
00:04:44,400 --> 00:04:46,690
她知道  你搞上她六小时前
Does she know that six hours before you screwed her,

128
00:04:46,690 --> 00:04:47,820
你想搞我吗
you tried to screw me?

129
00:04:49,880 --> 00:04:51,550
别假装拿她当做重点  好吗
Okay, let's not pretend that this is about her, okay?

130
00:04:51,550 --> 00:04:53,140
那她是知道还是不知道
So she knows, or she doesn't?

131
00:04:53,550 --> 00:04:54,700
我是说  你拿她
I mean, is it fair to her

132
00:04:54,700 --> 00:04:56,040
当那晚的备胎  对她公平吗
that she was your second choice that night?

133
00:04:56,040 --> 00:04:58,290
-因为如果我是她  麦克  -她结婚了
- Because if I were her, Mike-- - She's married.

134
00:04:59,830 --> 00:05:00,600
我觉得她并不在乎
I don't think she's really worried

135
00:05:00,600 --> 00:05:02,590
做我的备胎
about being my second choice.

136
00:05:06,270 --> 00:05:07,200
欢迎回来
Welcome back.

137
00:05:07,830 --> 00:05:09,220
准备好迎接精彩的第一天了吗
Who's ready for a great first day?

138
00:05:09,370 --> 00:05:10,830
哈维  拜托能回避一分钟吗
Harvey, can you give us a minute, please?

139
00:05:10,990 --> 00:05:13,510
不能  我们出现危机了  该走了
I can't. We actually have a crisis. We gotta go.

140
00:05:25,470 --> 00:05:27,590
你曾经告诉我  能摆平一切的  哈维
You once told me you could fix anything, Harvey.

141
00:05:28,040 --> 00:05:29,400
这是我儿子  利亚姆
This is my son, Liam.

142
00:05:30,670 --> 00:05:32,130
你妈妈说你有麻烦了
Your mother says you have a problem.

143
00:05:34,610 --> 00:05:37,990
我昨晚从格林威治开车回家
Um, I was driving home from Greenwich last night.

144
00:05:38,400 --> 00:05:39,330
一个朋友的聚会
A friend's party.

145
00:05:41,340 --> 00:05:42,340
我撞了人
I hit someone.

146
00:05:44,250 --> 00:05:45,410
我  我没看到他
I-I didn't see him.

147
00:05:45,410 --> 00:05:46,800
-他不知从哪儿钻出来  -你喝酒了吗
- He came out of nowhere. - Were you drunk?

148
00:05:47,500 --> 00:05:48,440
别回答那个问题
Don't answer that.

149
00:05:48,940 --> 00:05:51,170
如果庭审的话  我不能让他上庭
If this comes to trial, I can't put him on the stand.

150
00:05:51,170 --> 00:05:52,150
但我没喝酒
But I wasn't drinking.

151
00:05:52,150 --> 00:05:53,080
如果我们问聚会上的其他人
And if we asked everybody else at the party,

152
00:05:53,080 --> 00:05:54,740
他们会也这么说吗
would they tell the same story?

153
00:05:55,530 --> 00:05:57,210
如果走到那一步  我们得知道
If it comes out, we need to know.

154
00:05:58,130 --> 00:05:59,650
你可以去问在场的人
Talk to anyone who was there.

155
00:05:59,650 --> 00:06:01,870
如果我现在就去你车里  会不会找到酒瓶子
What if I checked your car for beer bottles right now?

156
00:06:02,050 --> 00:06:03,950
你去找啊  随便你找
Go ahead. Check anything you want.

157
00:06:04,470 --> 00:06:05,620
我没撒谎
I'm telling the truth.

158
00:06:06,000 --> 00:06:08,310
好了  这是个意外  我们能处理
Okay, it was an accident. We can deal with this.

159
00:06:08,880 --> 00:06:11,910
告诉我  你撞到的那个人怎么样了
Tell me, what happened to the guy you hit?

160
00:06:13,720 --> 00:06:14,560
我不知道
I don't know.

161
00:06:15,590 --> 00:06:17,990
-这就是叫你们来的原因  -什么意思
- That's why we called you. - What do you mean?

162
00:06:18,810 --> 00:06:19,930
他逃逸了
He drove away.

163
00:06:52,830 --> 00:06:53,920
我知道你要说什么
I know exactly what you're gonna say.

164
00:06:53,920 --> 00:06:55,480
我们要了解被撞的人的现状
We have to find out what happened to the guy he hit.

165
00:06:55,480 --> 00:06:56,660
我打电话给各个医院问...
So I'm gonna call all the hospitals...

166
00:06:56,660 --> 00:06:58,540
我觉得你不能再跟这个案子了
I think you need to sit this one out.

167
00:06:59,230 --> 00:07:00,740
我知道我操之过急了
Look, I know I jumped the gun,

168
00:07:00,740 --> 00:07:02,060
但问错一个问题我就出局了吗
but one wrong question and I'm out?

169
00:07:02,060 --> 00:07:04,240
你不是操之过急  是没控制自己的怒气
You weren't jumping the gun, it set you off.

170
00:07:04,250 --> 00:07:05,080
哈维  我没事
Harvey, I'm fine.

171
00:07:05,080 --> 00:07:07,130
我不是在责怪你  我理解
Look, I'm not blaming you, I'm understanding you.

172
00:07:07,130 --> 00:07:08,710
你父母就是因为醉驾交通事故去世的
Your parents were killed by a drunk driver.

173
00:07:08,860 --> 00:07:10,860
-利亚姆说了他没喝酒  -这不重要
- And Liam said he wasn't drunk. - Doesn't matter.

174
00:07:10,860 --> 00:07:13,050
如果是并购案  你的情绪会令你振作
Your emotions get the better of you on a merger.

175
00:07:13,220 --> 00:07:14,680
吉莉安是律所的长期客户
Gillian's a longtime client.

176
00:07:14,680 --> 00:07:16,180
这是她的独子  我不能冒险
It's her only son, I can't have that.

177
00:07:16,190 --> 00:07:17,420
我没问题的
I can do this.

178
00:07:17,620 --> 00:07:19,200
你祖母刚刚去世
Your grandmother just died.

179
00:07:20,930 --> 00:07:22,310
我说了我能行
I said I'm onboard.

180
00:07:23,100 --> 00:07:24,070
我就能行
I'm onboard.

181
00:07:30,300 --> 00:07:31,630
你觉得如何
So what do you think?

182
00:07:32,230 --> 00:07:34,250
车损帮了我们  损害很小
The damage helps us. It's minimal.

183
00:07:34,370 --> 00:07:37,560
更重要的是  如果车损在车前中央
More importantly, if the impact was central,

184
00:07:37,560 --> 00:07:39,260
被撞的人会在你视线范围内
guy would have been directly in your field of vision,

185
00:07:39,260 --> 00:07:41,950
这说明你说的是事实  他是突然冲过来的
so this backs the story up. He came out of nowhere.

186
00:07:42,350 --> 00:07:44,760
警方接到报警之后
Albert Chung was rushed to the E.R. last night,

187
00:07:44,760 --> 00:07:46,180
把艾伯特·钟送进了急诊
after a 911 call.

188
00:07:47,440 --> 00:07:49,040
-你报警了  -对
- You called 911? - Yeah.

189
00:07:49,190 --> 00:07:50,390
你应该告诉我们的
You should have told us that.

190
00:07:50,510 --> 00:07:53,250
他现在脑震荡  挫伤  四根肋骨骨折
He has a concussion, contusions, four cracked ribs,

191
00:07:53,260 --> 00:07:54,300
不过情况很稳定
but he's stable.

192
00:07:54,300 --> 00:07:56,000
谢天谢地  所以没事了
Thank God, so it's okay.

193
00:07:56,210 --> 00:07:58,360
吉莉安  利亚姆需要去自首
Gillian, Liam needs to turn himself in.

194
00:07:58,360 --> 00:07:59,960
那是个意外
It was an accident.

195
00:08:00,110 --> 00:08:01,830
正是如此  他只是个吓坏了的二十岁的孩子
Exactly, so if he comes forward,

196
00:08:01,830 --> 00:08:03,400
如果他能站出来
he's a 20-year-old kid who freaked out,

197
00:08:03,400 --> 00:08:04,630
去自首才是他该做的
but now he's doing the right thing.

198
00:08:04,630 --> 00:08:05,440
哈维说得对
Harvey's right.

199
00:08:05,440 --> 00:08:07,040
如果他们找上门  我肯定他们会的
If they come to us, which I know they will,

200
00:08:07,040 --> 00:08:09,080
我们就被动了  毫无胜算
we'll be on the defensive, we'll never recover.

201
00:08:09,270 --> 00:08:10,950
-该死  -你怎么能确定
- Shit. - You can't know that.

202
00:08:11,240 --> 00:08:12,410
他们也许永远都找不到我们
They might never find him.

203
00:08:12,570 --> 00:08:14,300
你愿意赌上你儿子的前途吗
You really want to risk your son's life on that?

204
00:08:14,300 --> 00:08:17,640
抱歉  这难道不应该由利亚姆自己决定吗
I'm sorry, but isn't this Liam's decision?

205
00:08:24,920 --> 00:08:27,410
-我会怎么样  -我不知道
- What's gonna happen to me? - I don't know.

206
00:08:27,520 --> 00:08:29,240
不过如果你在担心电影里监狱情节的话
But if you're worried about prison movies,

207
00:08:29,240 --> 00:08:30,930
你就放心吧
that's not what's gonna happen.

208
00:08:31,280 --> 00:08:32,180
你怎么知道
How do you know that?

209
00:08:32,360 --> 00:08:33,630
因为我了解哈维
Because I know Harvey.

210
00:08:34,720 --> 00:08:35,490
我不知道
I don't know.

211
00:08:36,260 --> 00:08:37,320
我不知道
I don't know.

212
00:08:38,550 --> 00:08:40,640
信不信由你
Hey, believe it or not,

213
00:08:41,030 --> 00:08:42,460
我也经历过这些
I've been where you are right now.

214
00:08:43,240 --> 00:08:44,050
什么
What?

215
00:08:44,440 --> 00:08:46,530
那年我16岁
Yeah. I was 16.

216
00:08:47,170 --> 00:08:49,620
藏了半盎司的毒品  被抓到警局
Got busted for possession, 1/2 ounce.

217
00:08:51,050 --> 00:08:52,290
我当时害怕极了
I was so scared.

218
00:08:52,290 --> 00:08:53,240
你抽大麻
You smoke?

219
00:08:54,130 --> 00:08:55,110
抽过
I did.

220
00:08:58,170 --> 00:08:59,160
现在也抽
I do.

221
00:09:00,390 --> 00:09:02,070
但你没有伤害别人
But you didn't hurt anybody.

222
00:09:02,660 --> 00:09:04,560
我知道你感觉无路可走了
I know it feels like there's no way out.

223
00:09:04,560 --> 00:09:05,580
但告诉你
But I'm telling you,

224
00:09:05,720 --> 00:09:07,340
你今天一定能够回家吃晚饭
you're going to be home in time for dinner.

225
00:09:14,170 --> 00:09:16,610
我必须说  很高兴你能给我打电话
I must say, I'm so glad you called.

226
00:09:17,100 --> 00:09:18,930
-很高兴你能赏脸  -很高兴你能高兴
- I'm so glad you answered. - I'm glad you're glad.

227
00:09:19,330 --> 00:09:20,970
你准备什么时候告诉我你升职了
When were you gonna tell me about your promotion?

228
00:09:21,120 --> 00:09:22,140
你知道我升职了
You know about my promotion?

229
00:09:22,140 --> 00:09:23,820
资深合伙人的消息
Senior partnerships rocket to my ears

230
00:09:23,820 --> 00:09:25,300
我一向都能火速知道
with the speed of a late-night bullet.

231
00:09:25,300 --> 00:09:27,060
-是吗  -我在推特上看到了
- Really? - I read it on twitter.

232
00:09:27,310 --> 00:09:28,690
看到你的第一眼
From the moment I laid eyes on you,

233
00:09:28,700 --> 00:09:30,130
我就知道你有胆识
I could tell you were a baller.

234
00:09:30,130 --> 00:09:32,440
我有胆识  所以我才打给你
Oh, I ball, which is why I called you.

235
00:09:33,530 --> 00:09:34,970
我新职务的特权之一就是
One of the perks of my new title--

236
00:09:34,970 --> 00:09:35,860
说出来
Say it.

237
00:09:36,370 --> 00:09:37,440
资深合伙人
Senior partner.

238
00:09:38,320 --> 00:09:39,350
接着说
Go on.

239
00:09:39,510 --> 00:09:41,170
我可以雇一个自己的助理律师
I get to hire an associate of my own.

240
00:09:42,000 --> 00:09:43,770
蝙蝠侠的神奇小子
A boy wonder to my batman.

241
00:09:43,910 --> 00:09:45,520
与你同在  黑暗骑士
Well, I am with you, dark knight.

242
00:09:45,660 --> 00:09:47,300
把最好的介绍给我
I want you to send me the best of the best.

243
00:09:47,300 --> 00:09:48,240
我已经让我最好的五个毕业生
I've already lined up interviews

244
00:09:48,240 --> 00:09:50,050
排好了队等你面试
with my top five recent graduates.

245
00:09:50,050 --> 00:09:52,400
-是吗  -打个比方罢了
- Have you? - Figure of speech.

246
00:09:52,600 --> 00:09:54,160
但我必须得说  希望你给我打电话
But, I have to say, I was hoping you didn't call

247
00:09:54,160 --> 00:09:56,130
并不是只为公事
exclusively for business.

248
00:09:56,290 --> 00:09:57,660
我正期待你这么想
I was hoping you were hoping that.

249
00:09:57,660 --> 00:09:59,160
跟你说实话吧  路易
I'm gonna be honest with you, Louis.

250
00:09:59,370 --> 00:10:01,200
资深合伙人就是一种性吸引力
Senior partner has a certain sex appeal.

251
00:10:01,200 --> 00:10:02,580
初级合伙人没有
Junior partner doesn't.

252
00:10:03,160 --> 00:10:05,160
我也是这么看自己的
I thought that to myself about myself.

253
00:10:07,500 --> 00:10:10,900
明晚九点  405房间
Room 405. 9:00 PM, tomorrow.

254
00:10:11,090 --> 00:10:13,570
带上椰子油  滑雪面罩和胶带
Bring coconut oil, a ski mask, and duct tape.

255
00:10:20,480 --> 00:10:21,860
恐惧从未感觉如此美好
Fear never felt so good.

256
00:10:27,200 --> 00:10:28,340
我叫卡特里娜·班尼特
Katrina Bennett.

257
00:10:28,890 --> 00:10:31,300
-哈维·斯佩克特  -很高兴见到你
- Harvey Specter. - Nice to meet you.

258
00:10:31,910 --> 00:10:34,350
你的胜诉率简直是业界传奇
Your record is something of a legend around here.

259
00:10:34,350 --> 00:10:35,280
太好了
Excellent.

260
00:10:35,290 --> 00:10:37,910
希望我们在庭上能够相互学习
I hope we can extend each other some professional courtesy.

261
00:10:37,910 --> 00:10:39,520
我没想过要让着你
I'm not extending you anything.

262
00:10:39,820 --> 00:10:40,710
当然了
Of course.

263
00:10:40,710 --> 00:10:42,770
还有什么能比打败一个传奇更光彩呢
What better thing to do than to take down a legend?

264
00:10:42,770 --> 00:10:44,500
很高兴我们有同样的想法
Well, I'm glad we understand each other.

265
00:10:44,650 --> 00:10:47,070
的确是  但有一个问题
We do, but here's the problem.

266
00:10:47,170 --> 00:10:48,260
这件案子没那么大
This isn't the case for it.

267
00:10:48,920 --> 00:10:50,690
是轻罪  不过是当时离开了事故现场
It's a misdemeanor, leaving the scene,

268
00:10:50,830 --> 00:10:52,230
现在他已经自首了
and now he's turned himself in.

269
00:10:52,330 --> 00:10:54,400
那是因为你知道我会发现他报过警
Because you knew we'd trace the 911 call.

270
00:10:54,400 --> 00:10:56,460
不是  他很过意不去
That's not why. He feels terrible.

271
00:10:56,680 --> 00:10:57,910
他不过是害怕
He feels afraid.

272
00:10:58,020 --> 00:10:59,220
不能混为一谈
Not the same thing.

273
00:10:59,220 --> 00:11:01,180
卡特里娜  我明白你想打赢我
Katrina, I understand you want to take me out,

274
00:11:01,180 --> 00:11:02,400
但这是个意外
but this is an accident.

275
00:11:02,500 --> 00:11:04,490
利亚姆犯了错  他在悔改
Liam made a mistake, and he's rectifying it.

276
00:11:04,670 --> 00:11:06,540
我们可以接受最重的社区服务惩罚
We'll accept maximum community service

277
00:11:06,540 --> 00:11:08,240
和你提议的罚款
and whatever fine you deem appropriate.

278
00:11:08,390 --> 00:11:10,230
葬礼花费呢
And what about funeral costs?

279
00:11:10,620 --> 00:11:11,670
等一下  你说什么
Wait. What?

280
00:11:12,190 --> 00:11:13,150
他死了
He died?

281
00:11:13,360 --> 00:11:15,130
这个案子就是肇事逃逸的重罪了
Which makes it felony hit-and-run.

282
00:11:15,130 --> 00:11:16,160
他之前情况很稳定啊
He was stable.

283
00:11:16,170 --> 00:11:18,120
脑震荡引起了脑出血
His concussion led to a brain bleed.

284
00:11:18,120 --> 00:11:20,050
就算他死了也不能改变
That man's death doesn't change the fact

285
00:11:20,050 --> 00:11:21,130
这只是个意外的事实
that it was an accident.

286
00:11:21,130 --> 00:11:23,020
肇事逃逸是重罪  按现在的情况
Felony hit-and-run, under these circumstances,

287
00:11:23,020 --> 00:11:24,570
大概要判12到15年
is 12 to 15 years.

288
00:11:25,530 --> 00:11:28,200
想要礼节吗  这就是我的礼节
You wanted courtesy? Here it is.

289
00:11:28,720 --> 00:11:29,690
我可以接受十年
I'll go ten.

290
00:11:30,020 --> 00:11:31,990
你的提议太疯狂了  当时天色已晚
That's crazy. It was dark.

291
00:11:32,000 --> 00:11:32,930
他也没喝酒
He wasn't drinking.

292
00:11:33,860 --> 00:11:36,170
换成你  难道不会提出同样的提议吗
Tell me it's not what you would have offered.

293
00:11:44,450 --> 00:11:45,760
玛丽亚·门罗
Maria Monroe.

294
00:11:45,870 --> 00:11:47,820
哈佛法学院  班长
Secretary of your class at Harvard Law.

295
00:11:47,980 --> 00:11:49,920
为首席法官罗伯茨做过书记员
Clerked for Chief Justice Roberts.

296
00:11:49,920 --> 00:11:51,770
金光闪闪的推荐信
Glowing letters of recommendation.

297
00:11:51,930 --> 00:11:53,350
你觉得这就能打动我
You think this impresses me?

298
00:11:55,720 --> 00:11:56,870
那就错了
Negative.

299
00:11:56,990 --> 00:11:58,650
给你五分钟时间来说服我
Which means you have exactly five minutes

300
00:11:58,660 --> 00:11:59,970
你就是我要的人
to convince me that you're the one.

301
00:11:59,980 --> 00:12:02,200
不用五分钟  我是无人能及的
I don't need five minutes. I am the one.

302
00:12:02,310 --> 00:12:03,970
该着急的是你  路易
It's you who's on the clock, Louis.

303
00:12:03,970 --> 00:12:06,490
我收到了纽约最顶尖三家律所的持续邀约
I have standing offers from the top three firms in the city.

304
00:12:06,610 --> 00:12:08,550
皮尔逊·哈德曼律所就是顶尖的
Pearson Hardman is a top-three firm.

305
00:12:08,550 --> 00:12:09,940
我本来也这么以为
Well, I used to think so.

306
00:12:09,940 --> 00:12:11,790
但如果你要花这么久来面试我
But if it's taking you this long to meet with me,

307
00:12:11,790 --> 00:12:12,880
也许你们水平在下滑
maybe you're slipping.

308
00:12:12,880 --> 00:12:14,760
不  我没有  我们才没有
Oh, no, I'm not-- we're not slipping.

309
00:12:14,770 --> 00:12:17,220
明天中午之前给我一份正式工作邀请
You need to submit a formal offer by noon tomorrow

310
00:12:17,220 --> 00:12:19,630
如果你想让我考虑在这儿工作的话
if you want me to even consider working here.

311
00:12:20,040 --> 00:12:21,880
玛丽亚  等一下
Wh-- Maria, hold on a second.

312
00:12:21,880 --> 00:12:23,470
在这儿等着
Just wait right there, wait right there.

313
00:12:25,500 --> 00:12:27,580
你们四个  走吧  招到人了
You four, beat it. Position has been filled.

314
00:12:29,570 --> 00:12:32,490
他们出多少薪资  我加一半  签约金两万五
I'll beat any salary by 50%. 25,000 signing bonus.

315
00:12:32,760 --> 00:12:34,350
-写下来  -等等
- Put it in writing. - W-w-wait--

316
00:12:34,350 --> 00:12:36,450
要我带你参观一下律所吗
Don't you want me to give you a tour of the firm?

317
00:12:36,600 --> 00:12:37,730
看看你将来的工作环境
Show you where you'll be working?

318
00:12:37,740 --> 00:12:39,460
我不介意工作环境
Well, I don't care where I'd be working

319
00:12:39,460 --> 00:12:40,540
我就是台工作机器
because I'm a machine.

320
00:12:41,130 --> 00:12:42,600
我一定要聘请你
I have to have you.

321
00:12:43,040 --> 00:12:44,010
大家都这么说
That's what they all say.

322
00:12:45,260 --> 00:12:47,450
警方报告  十字路口的照片
Police report, photos of the intersection,

323
00:12:47,860 --> 00:12:48,860
法医报告
coroner's report.

324
00:12:48,860 --> 00:12:50,290
又不是六年级数学
This isn't sixth-grade math.

325
00:12:50,290 --> 00:12:51,760
我不用知道过程  只要知道结果
Don't show me your work, just give me the answer.

326
00:12:51,760 --> 00:12:53,680
天呐  真希望我的六年级有你作伴
God, I wish I had you in the sixth grade.

327
00:12:53,680 --> 00:12:56,340
可惜没有  詹森老师  超性感
Except, no-- Miss Jenson, very hot.

328
00:12:56,500 --> 00:12:57,690
你需要自己待一会儿吗
You need a minute alone?

329
00:12:58,080 --> 00:13:02,240
利亚姆没看到艾伯特·钟是有原因的
There was a reason that Liam did not see Albert Chung.

330
00:13:02,240 --> 00:13:05,410
他穿着连帽运动衫  牛仔裤  运动鞋
He was wearing a hooded sweatshirt, jeans, and sneakers.

331
00:13:05,410 --> 00:13:06,340
一身黑色
All black.

332
00:13:06,550 --> 00:13:08,880
他是故意不想引人注意
Guy couldn't have been harder to see if he was trying.

333
00:13:08,880 --> 00:13:09,930
也许他真是故意的
Maybe he was trying.

334
00:13:09,940 --> 00:13:12,170
艾伯特·钟从艺校辍学了
Albert chung was an art school dropout.

335
00:13:12,290 --> 00:13:14,000
看看墙上的涂鸦
Look at that graffiti on the wall.

336
00:13:14,130 --> 00:13:15,870
A.C.就代表艾伯特·钟
"A.C." Albert Chung.

337
00:13:15,870 --> 00:13:17,010
他不想引人注意
He was trying to be invisible

338
00:13:17,010 --> 00:13:18,560
因为他在墙上涂鸦
because he was tagging that building.

339
00:13:18,560 --> 00:13:19,950
他在逃跑时被撞了
And he was running away when he got hit.

340
00:13:19,950 --> 00:13:21,590
也就是说  造成这场意外的不是利亚姆
Which means Liam didn't cause the accident,

341
00:13:21,590 --> 00:13:22,900
而是艾伯特·钟
Albert Chung did.

342
00:13:23,180 --> 00:13:25,260
你应该去假扮警察
I think you missed your calling as a fake cop.

343
00:13:25,260 --> 00:13:27,460
又说这茬是吧
Going back to that well again? Okay.

344
00:13:27,940 --> 00:13:29,690
你准备怎么做  跟卡特里娜谈判
So what are you gonna do? Stick it to Katrina?

345
00:13:29,690 --> 00:13:31,050
不  你去和卡特里娜谈判
No, you're gonna stick it to Katrina.

346
00:13:31,210 --> 00:13:32,170
你听到她说的了
You heard her.

347
00:13:32,360 --> 00:13:34,490
她的目的不是单单起诉利亚姆
Her agenda isn't just prosecuting Liam,

348
00:13:34,490 --> 00:13:35,610
而是打败我
it's beating me.

349
00:13:35,780 --> 00:13:37,370
我要把个人情感抽离这案子
See, I'm taking the personal out of it.

350
00:13:37,560 --> 00:13:39,800
你的问题是把个人情感带进案子里
Your problem is, you put the personal into it.

351
00:13:39,800 --> 00:13:40,890
我还以为
Okay, I thought my problem

352
00:13:40,890 --> 00:13:42,640
我的问题是爱卖弄
was showing you my work unnecessarily.

353
00:13:42,650 --> 00:13:44,060
谁说只有一个问题了
Who said there's only one problem?

354
00:13:44,890 --> 00:13:45,730
这招狠
Well-played.

355
00:13:50,320 --> 00:13:51,370
重大肇事逃逸罪
Felony hit-and-run hinges

356
00:13:51,370 --> 00:13:53,940
前提在于是否有共同过失
on a lack of contributory negligence.

357
00:13:53,940 --> 00:13:55,780
艾伯特·钟当时正逃离犯罪现场
Albert Chung was fleeing a crime scene.

358
00:13:55,780 --> 00:13:56,980
他将自己置于险境
He put himself in harm's way.

359
00:13:56,980 --> 00:13:58,840
你的委托人就完全没有责任了
So your client can't be held responsible?

360
00:13:58,840 --> 00:14:00,850
我们准备以驾车逃逸来作辩护
We'll plead to misdemeanor leaving the scene,

361
00:14:00,850 --> 00:14:01,770
仅此而已
but that's all.

362
00:14:02,400 --> 00:14:04,680
我就帮你这个忙  接受这份协议
I'm going to do you a favor and take this deal.

363
00:14:04,780 --> 00:14:07,300
你不是帮我  是帮你自己
You're not doing me a favor, you're doing yourself a favor.

364
00:14:07,430 --> 00:14:08,350
我们赢了
We've got you.

365
00:14:08,350 --> 00:14:10,160
不管怎样  大家都知道
Got me or not, it's no secret

366
00:14:10,160 --> 00:14:12,010
地方检察官跟哈维有过不和
the D.A. And Harvey had a run-in.

367
00:14:12,010 --> 00:14:13,690
他要知道这是哈维的案子
He finds out this is Harvey's case,

368
00:14:13,690 --> 00:14:14,540
就会让你们庭审
it goes to trial.

369
00:14:14,540 --> 00:14:16,600
审讯时什么都可能发生
And anything can happen at trial,

370
00:14:16,600 --> 00:14:17,780
恕我直言
so let me be clear,

371
00:14:18,520 --> 00:14:19,820
是我帮你一个忙
I am doing you a favor.

372
00:14:20,860 --> 00:14:21,910
你要什么
What do you want?

373
00:14:22,460 --> 00:14:24,470
跟哈维一样跳槽
To make the same career jump Harvey did.

374
00:14:24,470 --> 00:14:25,810
做商业律师
To corporate litigation?

375
00:14:26,090 --> 00:14:27,280
去皮尔逊·哈德曼律所
To Pearson Hardman.

376
00:14:27,800 --> 00:14:28,770
等等  我以为你
Wait, I thought you--

377
00:14:28,770 --> 00:14:30,210
我要把哈维打得落花流水
That I wanted to kick Harvey's ass?

378
00:14:30,220 --> 00:14:31,750
我这么说是因为献殷勤
I said that because you don't impress

379
00:14:31,750 --> 00:14:33,880
无法给哈维这样的律师留下印象
a lawyer like Harvey with flowers.

380
00:14:34,700 --> 00:14:36,660
这份认罪协议很公平
Look, this is a fair plea.

381
00:14:37,220 --> 00:14:38,360
应该能通过
And it's one that should go through.

382
00:14:38,360 --> 00:14:39,550
我会保证它能通过
I'll make sure that it does.

383
00:14:40,200 --> 00:14:42,090
你要能帮我在哈维面前说说好话
And if you were to put a word in with Harvey,

384
00:14:42,670 --> 00:14:43,950
我将感激不尽
I would appreciate it.

385
00:14:47,550 --> 00:14:48,370
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding me.

386
00:14:48,380 --> 00:14:49,360
-她真这么说  -是的
- She actually said that? - Yeah.

387
00:14:49,360 --> 00:14:52,320
我都搞不清是解决了案子还是接受了贿赂
I don't know if I settled a case or agreed to a bribe.

388
00:14:52,320 --> 00:14:54,030
-认罪协议她签了吗  -签了
- Did she sign the plea offer? - Yeah.

389
00:14:54,030 --> 00:14:56,800
那就满分通过  她又不能撤销协议
Then, "A," Because she can't rescind that thing

390
00:14:56,800 --> 00:14:58,730
除非出现新证据
unless new evidence comes to light,

391
00:14:58,730 --> 00:15:00,330
而我也就不必面试她了
and I don't have to interview her for shit.

392
00:15:00,340 --> 00:15:02,020
-很好  -很好
- Good. - Yeah, good.

393
00:15:02,020 --> 00:15:04,280
我不想再请一个助理了
I don't want to hire another associate ever again.

394
00:15:04,670 --> 00:15:06,450
我选的那个已经够让我头痛了
The one I picked causes me enough headaches.

395
00:15:06,450 --> 00:15:08,020
是吗  比如说帮你赢官司
Oh, right, like winning cases?

396
00:15:08,470 --> 00:15:10,840
涂鸦  穿了一身黑的男人  想起什么了吗
Graffiti, man in black-- is that ringing any bells?

397
00:15:10,960 --> 00:15:12,080
想起来了
It does indeed,

398
00:15:12,450 --> 00:15:14,360
也就带出了下一个任务
which leads us to our next assignment,

399
00:15:14,360 --> 00:15:15,680
你接不接受
should you choose to accept it.

400
00:15:15,680 --> 00:15:17,630
拜托告诉我你要自杀
Please tell me you're about to self-destruct.

401
00:15:17,630 --> 00:15:19,260
我们要和钟家和解
We need to settle with the Chung family.

402
00:15:21,650 --> 00:15:23,230
哈维  他们的儿子刚刚过世
Harvey, their son just died.

403
00:15:23,350 --> 00:15:26,100
我知道  我也知道悲伤是有阶段的
I know, and I also know that grief comes in stages,

404
00:15:26,100 --> 00:15:28,250
和解的最佳时间就是赶在愤怒阶段之前
and the best time to settle is before it gets to anger.

405
00:15:28,250 --> 00:15:29,640
你的意思是  占便宜的最佳时间
You mean the best time to take advantage of them

406
00:15:29,650 --> 00:15:31,400
是赶在他们愤怒之前吧
is before it gets to anger.

407
00:15:31,510 --> 00:15:32,860
-这就  -不关我们的事了
- That's not-- - Our concern?

408
00:15:33,720 --> 00:15:34,990
我知道我们帮利亚姆逃离了牢狱之灾
I know we got Liam out of prison,

409
00:15:34,990 --> 00:15:37,620
但他毕竟撞了人  那人毕竟死了
but he still hit a guy, and that guy is still dead.

410
00:15:37,770 --> 00:15:39,180
我们也毕竟是利亚姆的代表律师
And we still represent Liam.

411
00:15:39,530 --> 00:15:40,320
哈维
Harvey...

412
00:15:41,160 --> 00:15:43,250
我知道情况不一样  但是
I know it's not the same situation, but...

413
00:15:44,640 --> 00:15:46,780
我记得律师来我家的那天
I remember the day the lawyer came to our place.

414
00:15:48,190 --> 00:15:49,630
尼克·里纳尔迪  我
Nick Rinaldi. I...

415
00:15:50,360 --> 00:15:52,100
我记得他肮脏的鞋  我
I remember his dirty shoes. I...

416
00:15:52,850 --> 00:15:54,490
我记得他走进客厅
I remember how they scraped the floor

417
00:15:54,490 --> 00:15:55,660
告诉我奶奶
when he walked into the living room

418
00:15:55,660 --> 00:15:56,670
我父母的命值多少钱时
to tell my grandmother

419
00:15:56,670 --> 00:15:58,840
那双鞋发出的声音
how much my parents' lives were worth.

420
00:16:01,050 --> 00:16:02,460
我也经历过他们的悲剧
I've been where these people are.

421
00:16:03,940 --> 00:16:05,220
让我去告诉他们吧
Let me be the one to tell them.

422
00:16:07,080 --> 00:16:08,420
你确定没问题吗
You sure you can handle it?

423
00:16:08,550 --> 00:16:09,370
我很肯定不会
I'm sure as hell not going

424
00:16:09,370 --> 00:16:10,350
把他们留给你这样的人
to leave them to the likes of you.

425
00:16:10,350 --> 00:16:12,520
好吧  交给你吧
Okay, you can handle it.

426
00:16:14,320 --> 00:16:16,740
最高出价十万
You're authorized to go as high as $100,000.

427
00:16:31,850 --> 00:16:33,730
离婚案在43号架子上
Divorce is on 43.

428
00:16:35,890 --> 00:16:37,850
我知道你生我气
Look, I know that you're mad at me,

429
00:16:38,340 --> 00:16:40,070
我无意这样对你的
and I never meant to put you in this situation,

430
00:16:40,080 --> 00:16:41,890
我真的很感激
but I would really appreciate it

431
00:16:41,890 --> 00:16:44,050
如果你别告诉其他人  我感激不尽
if you kept what I told you to yourself.

432
00:16:45,460 --> 00:16:46,560
让我来理理
Let me get this straight.

433
00:16:47,160 --> 00:16:48,170
你先找上我
You hit on me,

434
00:16:48,170 --> 00:16:50,160
然后又投入某个已婚女人的怀抱
then you run into the arms of some married woman.

435
00:16:50,310 --> 00:16:52,290
再故作潇洒地走进我办公室
You come waltzing into my office

436
00:16:52,290 --> 00:16:53,580
想要粉饰一切
trying to cutesy your way out of it.

437
00:16:53,580 --> 00:16:54,960
现在你还有脸认为
And now you have the nerve

438
00:16:54,960 --> 00:16:57,110
我会到处宣扬吗
to think I'm gonna go and tell other people?

439
00:17:02,010 --> 00:17:03,800
我当然不知道你会不会宣扬
I have no idea what you're gonna tell other people,

440
00:17:03,810 --> 00:17:04,960
但你明显就是
but you sure seem to have the ability

441
00:17:04,960 --> 00:17:06,540
带着有色眼镜看我
to judge everything that I do.

442
00:17:06,540 --> 00:17:08,690
你觉得你干过的蠢事还少吗
Do you think that you have the lock on bad decisions?

443
00:17:08,690 --> 00:17:10,240
我确实不像你  从没犯过错
All I know is I'm not little Miss Perfect.

444
00:17:10,250 --> 00:17:12,230
我以前也当过小三
I've had an affair before too.

445
00:17:13,770 --> 00:17:15,110
你真该看看你现在的表情
You see the look on your face?

446
00:17:15,630 --> 00:17:17,210
谁才是带着有色眼镜  迈克
Who's judging who now, Mike?

447
00:17:17,360 --> 00:17:19,960
而且不是什么50多岁的老男人
And, no, it was not some 50-year-old man

448
00:17:19,960 --> 00:17:22,170
因我年轻无知  试图占我便宜
trying to take advantage of poor, young me.

449
00:17:22,270 --> 00:17:25,330
我们年龄相似  还是我主动的
We were the same age, and I went after him.

450
00:17:27,480 --> 00:17:30,550
我可不是你所认为的乖乖女
I am not the goody-goody you think I am.

451
00:17:32,110 --> 00:17:35,340
你根本就不知道自己错过了什么
You have no idea what you passed on.

452
00:17:38,280 --> 00:17:39,690
而且我跟你说  迈克
And I'll tell you something, Mike.

453
00:17:39,690 --> 00:17:42,850
这种事情  肯定不会有好结果
What you're doing, it only ends one way.

454
00:17:50,140 --> 00:17:52,450
钟女士  我想告诉你
Ms. Chung, I just want you to know

455
00:17:52,450 --> 00:17:55,820
无论错在谁  利亚姆·柯顺因此事
that Liam Colson is devastated by this accident,

456
00:17:55,820 --> 00:17:57,440
心里备受煎熬
regardless of who caused it.

457
00:17:57,700 --> 00:17:58,700
谢谢
Thank you.

458
00:17:59,450 --> 00:18:01,130
我知道任何金额
I know that there's no amount of money

459
00:18:01,130 --> 00:18:02,510
都弥补不了
that can ever make up for it...

460
00:18:03,820 --> 00:18:06,700
而且眼下你们最不想提及的
And that this is probably the last thing

461
00:18:06,700 --> 00:18:08,250
也是赔偿一事
you want to be talking about.

462
00:18:08,330 --> 00:18:11,300
我弟弟并不是模范市民  罗斯先生
My brother wasn't exactly a model citizen, Mr. Ross.

463
00:18:11,470 --> 00:18:13,680
我们明白他不配
We know he's not entitled to much.

464
00:18:14,130 --> 00:18:16,800
我父母只想偿还艾伯特欠的债
All my parents want is to pay off Albert's debts

465
00:18:16,800 --> 00:18:18,410
再支付葬礼费用
and cover the funeral costs.

466
00:18:19,030 --> 00:18:20,260
总共需要多少
And how much would that be?

467
00:18:20,820 --> 00:18:22,810
两万
$20,000.

468
00:18:27,470 --> 00:18:29,990
我们愿意支付十万
Well, I'd like to offer you $100,000.

469
00:18:32,030 --> 00:18:33,600
事实上  我坚持如此
In fact, I insist on it.

470
00:18:36,740 --> 00:18:39,250
他们给  赔五倍

471
00:18:49,890 --> 00:18:54,410
你帮我告诉他  我们很感谢他

472
00:18:56,660 --> 00:18:57,800
在哪里签字
Where do we sign?

473
00:18:59,730 --> 00:19:00,980
这里和这里
Right here and here.

474
00:19:04,650 --> 00:19:06,140
要不要喝点茶
Will you stay for some tea?

475
00:19:07,490 --> 00:19:08,650
乐意至极
I'd be honored.

476
00:19:20,850 --> 00:19:23,170
晚上9点  一秒不差
9 P.M. To the second.

477
00:19:23,170 --> 00:19:24,940
准时最让人性奋了
Punctuality is the best aphrodisiac.

478
00:19:27,070 --> 00:19:28,270
真让人捉摸不透
Who are you?

479
00:19:30,330 --> 00:19:31,510
人家是蝙蝠侠么
I'm batman.

480
00:19:34,010 --> 00:19:35,410
全副武装吗
Did you bring the accoutrement?

481
00:19:35,410 --> 00:19:36,430
当然[法语]
Oui.

482
00:19:36,650 --> 00:19:39,220
我都迫不及待了
I'm on pins and needles.

483
00:19:40,710 --> 00:19:43,410
不过开始前  我要知道
Before we begin, I need to know...

484
00:19:43,770 --> 00:19:44,910
你挑中了谁
who's your front-runner?

485
00:19:45,390 --> 00:19:46,690
玛丽亚·门罗  其他人差远了
Maria Monroe. Wasn't even close.

486
00:19:46,690 --> 00:19:49,660
我知道  并非是五个最佳人选
I know. There were no five best.

487
00:19:49,660 --> 00:19:50,800
你是在考验我吗
You were testing me?

488
00:19:51,380 --> 00:19:53,330
上好的菜品  我可不会用
I wasn't about to serve up my best candidate

489
00:19:53,330 --> 00:19:54,270
次等餐具
on a silver platter.

490
00:19:54,270 --> 00:19:55,290
就喜欢你的品位
God, I love that.

491
00:19:56,380 --> 00:19:58,210
不过玛丽亚确实出类拔萃
After all, Maria is very desirable.

492
00:19:58,230 --> 00:19:59,980
不过  我需要你...
But the thing is, I'm gonna need you...

493
00:20:01,320 --> 00:20:02,820
帮我说服她
to help me close her.

494
00:20:02,820 --> 00:20:05,870
路易  走进点
Louis, come closer.

495
00:20:08,170 --> 00:20:09,340
停下
Stop.

496
00:20:10,710 --> 00:20:13,290
我肯定替你把玛丽亚搞定
I'm gonna close the shit out of Maria for you.

497
00:20:14,230 --> 00:20:16,620
你得先让我满意才行
And you're gonna close the shit out of me.

498
00:20:17,760 --> 00:20:19,090
没问题
All aboard.

499
00:20:22,390 --> 00:20:24,240
等下  若我没选她
Wait a minute, if I didn't pick her,

500
00:20:24,240 --> 00:20:26,230
我们是不是没戏了
we wouldn't be doing this?

501
00:20:26,230 --> 00:20:27,940
我可没这么说
Oh, I'm saying no such thing.

502
00:20:27,940 --> 00:20:30,090
但我们下面要做的事
But the nature of what we're about to do

503
00:20:30,090 --> 00:20:32,070
可就不在一个级别上了
would be radically different.

504
00:20:32,340 --> 00:20:35,470
我通过考验  就由我来主导
I dominated, so I get to dominate.

505
00:20:35,470 --> 00:20:37,670
-是被调教  -听你的
- You get to be dominated. - Yes, I do.

506
00:20:37,680 --> 00:20:39,350
要不要一个暂停口令
Do you need a safe word?

507
00:20:40,310 --> 00:20:42,500
没种的才要那个
Safe words are for pussies.

508
00:20:42,500 --> 00:20:43,690
从下面开始
Start with my slippers.

509
00:20:43,690 --> 00:20:45,120
你太了解我了
Oh, thank you.

510
00:20:57,470 --> 00:20:59,960
-你好啊  -花在哪呢
- Hello. - Where are your flowers?

511
00:20:59,960 --> 00:21:01,190
什么花
My flowers?

512
00:21:01,190 --> 00:21:03,620
约会要带花来的吖
You go on a date, you're supposed to bring flowers.

513
00:21:03,620 --> 00:21:06,300
-是吗  -是的  哈维
- Am I? - Yes, Harvey.

514
00:21:06,300 --> 00:21:08,070
大家都知道的
Everyone knows that.

515
00:21:08,070 --> 00:21:09,980
你有过几次约会啊
How many dates have you been on?

516
00:21:10,930 --> 00:21:12,860
-六次  -六次哦
- Six. - Six?

517
00:21:12,860 --> 00:21:15,700
挺认真的嘛  哪个男人这么幸运啊
Mm, sounds serious. Who's the lucky guy?

518
00:21:15,700 --> 00:21:17,150
杰森
Jason.

519
00:21:17,330 --> 00:21:19,150
不是男人  是男孩
He's not a guy, he's a boy.

520
00:21:19,150 --> 00:21:21,210
他都会带花
And he brings flowers.

521
00:21:22,260 --> 00:21:24,810
也许下次我们可以四人约会
Well, maybe next time we can have a double date.

522
00:21:24,810 --> 00:21:26,950
你就这么确信会有下次啊
You that sure it's gonna go well tonight?

523
00:21:26,950 --> 00:21:28,290
奥利维亚  你为何不上楼
Olivia, why don't you go upstairs

524
00:21:28,300 --> 00:21:30,150
继续看电视去
and finish watching your show?

525
00:21:30,150 --> 00:21:32,130
你是不是忘记跟我说什么了
Is there maybe something you forgot to tell me?

526
00:21:32,130 --> 00:21:33,750
你是指你女儿吗
You mean about your daughter?

527
00:21:33,750 --> 00:21:36,100
可说起来我们都还没上过床
See, that's funny because we never slept together.

528
00:21:36,100 --> 00:21:37,570
我可不觉得这事有趣
I don't find it funny in the least,

529
00:21:37,570 --> 00:21:39,890
我是指我们还没上过床
and by "it," I mean that we never slept together.

530
00:21:39,890 --> 00:21:43,170
说真的  哈维  我很抱歉
Seriously, Harvey, I'm really sorry about this.

531
00:21:43,660 --> 00:21:46,100
奥利维亚是我侄女  我哥哥丢给我的
Olivia's my niece. My brother just dropped her off.

532
00:21:46,100 --> 00:21:47,330
他没其他亲人了
He didn't have anybody else.

533
00:21:47,330 --> 00:21:48,970
那我们就排排坐
Then I guess we'll have to sit down,

534
00:21:48,970 --> 00:21:51,070
点份匹萨  看看卡通
watch Bugs Bunny, and order a pizza.

535
00:21:51,730 --> 00:21:53,350
兔八哥吗
Bugs Bunny?

536
00:21:53,980 --> 00:21:56,010
早就过时啦
Yeah, no one watches that anymore.

537
00:21:56,010 --> 00:21:58,680
她看《现代启示录》还太小了嘛
I thought Apocalypse Now would be a little much for her.

538
00:21:58,680 --> 00:22:00,050
我能进来吗
Can I come in?

539
00:22:02,910 --> 00:22:06,080
你怎么不等等我
Hey. Thanks for starting without me.

540
00:22:06,150 --> 00:22:08,450
-等不急了  -今天这么不顺啊
- Couldn't wait. - That bad a day?

541
00:22:08,450 --> 00:22:10,910
没  其实挺好的
Nope, that good of one.

542
00:22:11,760 --> 00:22:13,800
看样子你跟瑞秋谈得挺好
So your little chat with Rachel went well.

543
00:22:13,800 --> 00:22:15,360
我说的不是这方面
Not what I meant.

544
00:22:16,030 --> 00:22:17,880
有个死于车祸的男人
I negotiated a settlement with the sister

545
00:22:17,880 --> 00:22:20,370
我今天跟他姐姐谈好了协议
of the man who was killed in a car accident today.

546
00:22:21,040 --> 00:22:21,980
哦  我的天
Oh, my god.

547
00:22:21,980 --> 00:22:23,460
不  不是你想的那样
No, no. It's not what you think.

548
00:22:23,460 --> 00:22:24,830
我...
I, um,

549
00:22:24,850 --> 00:22:27,080
我给了他们尊严
I gave this family dignity.

550
00:22:27,310 --> 00:22:29,270
尽管很难
And as hard as it was...

551
00:22:31,360 --> 00:22:33,530
今天是我工作后最棒的一天
it was the best day of work I've ever had.

552
00:22:35,160 --> 00:22:36,350
那太好了
That's awesome.

553
00:22:41,260 --> 00:22:42,220
喂
Hey.

554
00:22:42,220 --> 00:22:44,240
利亚姆的认罪协议到了
Liam's plea deal came through.

555
00:22:44,240 --> 00:22:45,830
就要到吉莉安家了
It's on its way to Gillian's.

556
00:22:45,830 --> 00:22:47,920
我需要你过去  帮他们签好
I need you to go over there and walk 'em through it,

557
00:22:47,920 --> 00:22:49,420
把此案弄完
so we can wrap this up.

558
00:22:49,420 --> 00:22:50,980
我这就去
Uh, I'm on my way.

559
00:22:51,390 --> 00:22:52,600
-惨了  -怎么了
- Shit. - What?

560
00:22:52,850 --> 00:22:54,460
我要去见客户
I have to go see a client.

561
00:22:54,460 --> 00:22:56,690
迈克  你嗑药了啊
Mike, you're high.

562
00:22:57,110 --> 00:22:58,530
被看出来怎么办
What if they can tell?

563
00:22:59,750 --> 00:23:01,820
苔丝  我之前有几年天天都嗑
Tess, I was high every day of my life for years,

564
00:23:01,820 --> 00:23:03,510
可没人知道
and nobody knew, okay?

565
00:23:03,510 --> 00:23:05,060
我能搞定
I can handle it.

566
00:23:06,640 --> 00:23:08,400
-她睡着了吗  -还没
- She asleep? - Not exactly.

567
00:23:08,400 --> 00:23:11,170
她希望你上去  给她个晚安吻
She wants you to go up there and kiss her good night.

568
00:23:12,320 --> 00:23:13,650
你不用去的
You don't have to do this.

569
00:23:13,650 --> 00:23:16,190
-没事  我去  -哈维
- No, I can do that. - Harvey.

570
00:23:16,210 --> 00:23:18,630
我想让你一会儿下来
Afterwards, I want you to come down here,

571
00:23:18,630 --> 00:23:20,310
也和我吻安
and kiss me good night.

572
00:23:28,070 --> 00:23:29,260
所以...
So...

573
00:23:30,290 --> 00:23:32,160
我签了这个就没事了
I sign this, and we're done?

574
00:23:34,930 --> 00:23:37,130
对
Yeah.

575
00:23:37,130 --> 00:23:39,110
检察官助理已经同意了
Uh, the A.D.A. agreed to it,

576
00:23:39,110 --> 00:23:42,440
你签完字  然后...
so you sign it, and then, um...

577
00:23:42,440 --> 00:23:44,250
然后法官也会签字
and then the judge'll sign it.

578
00:23:44,610 --> 00:23:46,650
然后就完事了
And then-- then we're done.

579
00:23:55,410 --> 00:23:57,350
社区服务和交罚款
Community service and a fine.

580
00:23:58,310 --> 00:24:00,070
听起来你还挺失望的
You sound disappointed.

581
00:24:00,730 --> 00:24:03,410
不不  我很感激
No, no, I appreciate it.

582
00:24:03,410 --> 00:24:04,490
只是...
It's just...

583
00:24:05,620 --> 00:24:07,170
我本来以为会更糟糕呢
It could have been so much worse.

584
00:24:07,170 --> 00:24:08,760
我还以为这辈子完蛋了呢
I thought my life over.

585
00:24:09,840 --> 00:24:11,380
我真是个混蛋
I'm such an asshole.

586
00:24:11,480 --> 00:24:14,660
利亚姆  你可以觉得解脱的
Hey, Liam, it's okay to feel relief.

587
00:24:14,660 --> 00:24:16,490
钟的家人不怪你的
The Chung family doesn't blame you.

588
00:24:17,100 --> 00:24:18,440
没人怪你
Nobody blames you.

589
00:24:19,900 --> 00:24:21,790
你还记得那天你说
Do you remember what you said the other day

590
00:24:21,790 --> 00:24:23,190
你以前嗑药吗
about getting high?

591
00:24:25,120 --> 00:24:28,480
为什么问这个
Why are you asking me that?

592
00:24:29,380 --> 00:24:30,680
我那天嗑药了
I was high.

593
00:24:33,090 --> 00:24:34,280
什么
What?

594
00:24:40,030 --> 00:24:42,350
你怎么不早告诉我们
How could you not tell us that?

595
00:24:42,550 --> 00:24:43,780
哈维不让我说
'Cause Harvey said not to.

596
00:24:43,790 --> 00:24:44,890
但你说你没醉
But you said you weren't drunk.

597
00:24:44,890 --> 00:24:46,090
你说我们可以随便去问
You said, "Ask everyone."

598
00:24:46,090 --> 00:24:47,180
你可以问
You could have.

599
00:24:47,180 --> 00:24:48,480
我自己嗑的
I was alone.

600
00:24:48,790 --> 00:24:50,990
我总嗑药  但从来没人知道
I get high all the time, and no one ever knows.

601
00:24:51,240 --> 00:24:53,360
-天哪  -怎么了
- Oh, my God. - What's the matter?

602
00:24:54,960 --> 00:24:56,700
你说这事已经定了
You said this was a done deal.

603
00:24:57,220 --> 00:24:58,500
是吧
It is, right?

604
00:24:59,530 --> 00:25:00,680
是
Yeah.

605
00:25:03,440 --> 00:25:04,930
是  已经定了
Yeah, it's a done deal.

606
00:25:16,730 --> 00:25:18,730
-出大事了  -没事  迈克
- We got a huge problem. - Don't worry, Mike.

607
00:25:18,730 --> 00:25:21,390
超级男孩还会有巡演的
I'm sure 'NSync will tour again someday.

608
00:25:22,820 --> 00:25:25,120
这协议解不能交  那不是意外
We can't submit this deal because it wasn't an accident.

609
00:25:25,120 --> 00:25:26,180
那是醉驾
It was a DUI.

610
00:25:26,180 --> 00:25:27,540
-什么  -他嗑药了
- What? - He was stoned.

611
00:25:27,540 --> 00:25:30,730
-我们得重来  -没什么要变的
- This changes everything. - It changes nothing.

612
00:25:30,730 --> 00:25:32,770
可我跟卡特里娜歪曲了事实
I misrepresented the facts to Katrina.

613
00:25:32,770 --> 00:25:33,630
你没有
No, you didn't,

614
00:25:33,630 --> 00:25:35,280
因为当时我们没问  你也不知道
because you didn't know because we didn't ask.

615
00:25:35,280 --> 00:25:37,460
我也没问  但他刚告诉我了
And I didn't ask now, but he told me now.

616
00:25:37,460 --> 00:25:39,690
而我们要遵守保密特权  谈都谈完了
And that's privileged, and the deal is done.

617
00:25:39,690 --> 00:25:41,580
等等  你打算什么都不做吗
Wait a minute, so you're not gonna do anything?

618
00:25:41,620 --> 00:25:43,720
我得让唐娜把这个送去地检办公室
I'm gonna have Donna messenger this to the D.A.'s office.

619
00:25:43,720 --> 00:25:46,060
哈维  那家人觉得是自己儿子的错
Harvey, this family thinks their son is to blame.

620
00:25:46,060 --> 00:25:47,820
本来他就是在逃离犯罪现场
Because he was fleeing the scene of a crime,

621
00:25:47,820 --> 00:25:49,830
-所以才会被撞  -好吧  就算是
- which put him in harm's way. - Okay, maybe.

622
00:25:49,830 --> 00:25:51,450
但如果我不告诉他们事实
But if I don't tell them this part,

623
00:25:51,450 --> 00:25:53,200
那我和尼克·里纳尔迪有什么区别
then I'm no different than Nick Rinaldi.

624
00:25:53,200 --> 00:25:54,850
-你已经和他不一样了  -什么意思
- You're already different. - What do you mean?

625
00:25:54,850 --> 00:25:57,030
我意思是他们都同意拿两万了
I mean, they were ready to take the $20,000,

626
00:25:57,040 --> 00:25:58,530
你给了人家十万
but you gave 'em $100,000.

627
00:25:58,530 --> 00:25:59,840
你觉得能一直瞒着我吗
Did you think I wasn't going to find out about that?

628
00:25:59,840 --> 00:26:00,780
哈维  拜托  别这样
Harvey, please, come on.

629
00:26:00,780 --> 00:26:02,750
我都警告你会有这种事了
You asked me to be on this case

630
00:26:02,750 --> 00:26:04,700
你还非要参与这案子
after I warned you about something like this.

631
00:26:04,700 --> 00:26:06,370
你说我没事
You said, "I'm onboard."

632
00:26:06,370 --> 00:26:07,880
要是吉莉安发现了你干的好事
Do you have any idea what would happen

633
00:26:07,880 --> 00:26:09,130
你想过后果没有
if Gillian found out what you did?

634
00:26:09,130 --> 00:26:10,760
要是她发现她儿子嗑药了呢
What if she found out about her son?

635
00:26:10,760 --> 00:26:12,300
大概也就多给点调解费吧
She'd probably give them a bigger settlement.

636
00:26:12,300 --> 00:26:15,010
不过反正你也已经多给了  我也没管你
But, hey, you already did that, and I let it go.

637
00:26:15,530 --> 00:26:17,430
-这事就这样了  -随你怎么说
- You need to let this go. - Say whatever you want.

638
00:26:17,430 --> 00:26:18,850
我都跟尼克·里纳尔迪没什么区别
That's no different than Nick Rinaldi.

639
00:26:18,850 --> 00:26:21,210
不过钱多点儿  鞋干净点儿罢了
That's just more money and cleaner shoes.

640
00:26:28,980 --> 00:26:30,090
天呐  让你等了
Oh, my God. You were waiting.

641
00:26:30,090 --> 00:26:32,310
我听说你在  就赶紧出来了
I heard you were here, so I rushed right out.

642
00:26:32,310 --> 00:26:33,610
我正式接受你的聘用
I formally accept your offer

643
00:26:33,610 --> 00:26:35,660
加入皮尔森·哈德曼
of employment at Pearson Hardman.

644
00:26:35,660 --> 00:26:37,720
这周真是棒极了
Oh, this is the best week ever.

645
00:26:37,720 --> 00:26:39,240
我不会令你失望的
I won't let you down.

646
00:26:39,760 --> 00:26:40,680
抱歉
I'm sorry.

647
00:26:40,680 --> 00:26:42,100
我不知道他具体指什么
I have no idea what this is regarding,

648
00:26:42,100 --> 00:26:44,750
不过他肯定会让你失望的  一向如此
but, yes, he will. He always does.

649
00:26:44,750 --> 00:26:46,950
-就当耳边风  -看到了吧
- Water off a snail's back. - See what I mean?

650
00:26:46,950 --> 00:26:49,510
唐娜·鲍尔森  这是玛丽亚·门罗
Donna Paulsen, Maria Monroe,

651
00:26:49,510 --> 00:26:50,250
我的新私人助理
my personal first-year.

652
00:26:50,260 --> 00:26:52,020
她是个工作狂
She's a machine.

653
00:26:52,020 --> 00:26:52,930
而且我跟你说
And let me just tell you something,

654
00:26:52,930 --> 00:26:54,740
迈克·罗斯跟她没得比
she's gonna run circles around Mike Ross.

655
00:26:54,740 --> 00:26:56,770
你在这儿等会  我去拿蛋糕来
You wait right here, and I'll get us some bundt cake.

656
00:26:56,770 --> 00:26:58,700
抱歉  迈克什么
I'm sorry, Mike who?

657
00:26:58,700 --> 00:27:01,050
-迈克·罗斯  -他也刚来吗
- Mike Ross. - Is he a first-year?

658
00:27:01,050 --> 00:27:01,940
为什么这么问
Why do you ask?

659
00:27:01,940 --> 00:27:04,040
我还以为你们只招哈佛的呢
I thought you only hired from Harvard.

660
00:27:04,040 --> 00:27:06,160
-没错  -我是班长
- We do. - I was secretary of my class.

661
00:27:06,160 --> 00:27:07,420
我知道所有人的名字
I knew every name.

662
00:27:07,420 --> 00:27:10,130
我们这届哈佛没有叫迈克·罗斯的
There was no Mike Ross my year at Harvard.

663
00:27:10,710 --> 00:27:12,060
不过你们不是一年的啊
But you weren't the same year.

664
00:27:12,060 --> 00:27:14,130
不  我做了一年书记员
No, I clerked for a year.

665
00:27:14,130 --> 00:27:15,510
他在这里比我早一年
He's a year ahead of me here,

666
00:27:15,510 --> 00:27:17,140
不过在学校应该和我一届
but he would have been in my class.

667
00:27:17,140 --> 00:27:19,150
迈克做了三年书记员
Oh, well, Mike clerked for three years,

668
00:27:19,150 --> 00:27:21,160
所以他不跟你一届
which means he wasn't in your class.

669
00:27:21,980 --> 00:27:24,600
我很期待与他见面
Well, I look forward to meeting him.

670
00:27:31,410 --> 00:27:33,550
昨晚
Uh...last night.

671
00:27:34,070 --> 00:27:35,630
我...
I was, uh...

672
00:27:36,110 --> 00:27:37,560
我开车回家
I was driving home,

673
00:27:38,180 --> 00:27:39,720
喝了不少酒
I'd had a lot to drink.

674
00:27:39,960 --> 00:27:41,270
然后撞人了
I hit someone.

675
00:27:42,650 --> 00:27:44,570
我觉得我肯定把人撞死了
And I'm pretty sure that they're dead.

676
00:27:45,730 --> 00:27:48,260
所以我需要你的帮助
So, uh, I need your help.

677
00:27:50,990 --> 00:27:53,080
抱歉  我不接这种案子
Sorry, I don't take cases like that.

678
00:27:53,080 --> 00:27:54,920
你不接这种案子吗
You don't take cases like that?

679
00:27:55,200 --> 00:27:57,410
那你1992年接的案子呢
What about your case from 1992?

680
00:27:57,410 --> 00:27:58,600
肇事者直接撞进了别人车里
Driver plows into a car,

681
00:27:58,600 --> 00:28:00,740
之前喝了得有一桶威士忌加可乐
after drinking about a thousand jack and cokes,

682
00:28:00,740 --> 00:28:02,410
一对幸福的夫妻就这么死了
killing a happily married couple?

683
00:28:02,420 --> 00:28:03,950
叫詹姆斯·罗斯和妮娜·罗斯
James and Nina Ross?

684
00:28:04,240 --> 00:28:05,820
抱歉我不记得了
I'm afraid I have no recollection of that.

685
00:28:05,820 --> 00:28:08,040
是吗  那我给你提个醒
Oh, yeah? Let me ring a bell for you, then.

686
00:28:08,040 --> 00:28:10,100
车祸两天后  你走进他们家客厅
Two days later, you walk into their living room,

687
00:28:10,100 --> 00:28:12,760
发现只有个小男孩和他奶奶坐在那里
you find their little boy and his grandmother just sitting there,

688
00:28:12,760 --> 00:28:15,130
然后你就占尽了便宜
and then you stick it to them.

689
00:28:15,810 --> 00:28:18,400
他们都还没来得及办追悼会呢
They hadn't even had time to hold a wake yet.

690
00:28:18,910 --> 00:28:20,560
你还不承认吗
Are you still gonna deny it?

691
00:28:20,560 --> 00:28:21,890
我没有不承认
I didn't deny it.

692
00:28:22,030 --> 00:28:23,290
我只是想不起来了
Just have no recollection of it

693
00:28:23,290 --> 00:28:25,250
因为这种事太多了
because I did it so many times.

694
00:28:25,260 --> 00:28:28,220
抱歉  你这是想感动我吗
I'm sorry, is that supposed to move me, huh?

695
00:28:28,220 --> 00:28:29,250
我是不是该想
Am I supposed to think

696
00:28:29,250 --> 00:28:30,840
你都已经不在乎感情了
that you're somehow above all that now?

697
00:28:30,840 --> 00:28:33,030
我没想怎么样
It's not supposed to do anything.

698
00:28:33,040 --> 00:28:33,900
不过我提醒你下
But let me point out,

699
00:28:33,900 --> 00:28:35,340
两分钟前你进来
you walked in here two minutes ago,

700
00:28:35,340 --> 00:28:37,660
告诉我你撞人了  我没接你的案子
told me you'd hit somebody, and I turned you away.

701
00:28:42,820 --> 00:28:45,370
-你叫什么  -好像你在乎一样
- What's your name? - Like you give a shit.

702
00:28:46,130 --> 00:28:47,420
好吧
Okay.

703
00:28:47,790 --> 00:28:49,720
那你为什么来找我
What are you looking for from me?

704
00:28:49,720 --> 00:28:51,760
我想知道你怎么还能继续生活
I wanna know how you live with yourself.

705
00:28:52,160 --> 00:28:53,710
我想知道那之后你每天醒来
I wanna know how you wake up every morning

706
00:28:53,720 --> 00:28:54,950
怎么能忍住不开枪自杀
and not put a bullet in your brain,

707
00:28:54,950 --> 00:28:57,230
尽管明知自己干了些什么破事
knowing what a piece of shit you are!

708
00:28:57,710 --> 00:28:59,530
这话可能不好听
You might not want to hear this,

709
00:29:00,110 --> 00:29:01,520
我不记得你是谁
But just because I don't remember who you are

710
00:29:01,520 --> 00:29:03,740
并不代表对于我造成的伤害  我毫无悔意
doesn't mean I don't regret what I did to you.

711
00:29:04,150 --> 00:29:05,830
非常不幸的是  白纸黑字写清了
Now the sad fact is that once a deal is done,

712
00:29:05,830 --> 00:29:07,270
是无法改变的
it can't be undone.

713
00:29:07,270 --> 00:29:09,200
詹姆斯和尼娜·罗斯
James and Nina Ross.

714
00:29:11,450 --> 00:29:13,390
要是我再碰到你
If I ever see you again,

715
00:29:13,700 --> 00:29:16,080
你最好能记得这两个名字
you better remember who they are.

716
00:29:21,230 --> 00:29:22,750
谢谢
Thank you.

717
00:29:23,770 --> 00:29:26,180
你知道路易要雇佣私人助手吗
Did you know Louis is hiring his own associate?

718
00:29:26,180 --> 00:29:28,290
不是特别关心  他有这个权利
Not specifically, but he is entitled to it.

719
00:29:28,290 --> 00:29:29,630
我们得制止他
We got to stop him.

720
00:29:29,630 --> 00:29:31,340
哈维  我知道你在生路易的气
Harvey, I know you're mad at Louis.

721
00:29:31,340 --> 00:29:33,050
我也是  但事情过去了
So am I, but it's over.

722
00:29:33,050 --> 00:29:35,000
我们是赢家  他现在是为我们打工
We won, and the man has a job to do.

723
00:29:35,000 --> 00:29:36,510
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.

724
00:29:39,680 --> 00:29:42,350
他如果雇佣了现在这个人
We let him hire the person he just hired,

725
00:29:42,570 --> 00:29:44,100
迈克的身份就暴露了
Mike's gonna be exposed.

726
00:29:44,100 --> 00:29:45,090
你怎么知道
How do you know this?

727
00:29:45,090 --> 00:29:46,630
她是班长
She was secretary of his class.

728
00:29:46,630 --> 00:29:48,520
一个班得有600号人吧
And there's 600 kids in that class.

729
00:29:48,520 --> 00:29:51,240
-有谁能记住所有的人  -她号称她可以
- Nobody knows everybody. - She says she does.

730
00:29:52,020 --> 00:29:54,120
-你怎么就那么肯定呢  -唐娜和她打过照面
- How can you be so sure? - Donna met her.

731
00:29:54,120 --> 00:29:55,390
她非常肯定
She's sure.

732
00:29:55,390 --> 00:29:57,330
见鬼的迈克·罗斯
Goddamn Mike Ross.

733
00:29:57,590 --> 00:29:59,570
他老给我们添乱
He's the gift that keeps on giving.

734
00:30:00,840 --> 00:30:03,620
他还要拖我们多长时间后退  哈维
How many more headaches is this kid gonna cause me, Harvey?

735
00:30:09,940 --> 00:30:11,210
你要见我
You wanted to see me?

736
00:30:11,400 --> 00:30:14,070
你是不是要招一个叫玛丽亚·门罗的
Did you make an offer to a Maria Monroe

737
00:30:14,080 --> 00:30:15,410
来做初级助理
to be a first-year associate?

738
00:30:15,420 --> 00:30:16,950
是的  我和你说吧
Yes, and let me just tell you something,

739
00:30:16,950 --> 00:30:18,720
-你绝对会喜欢她的  -让她别来了
- you're gonna love her. - Rescind it.

740
00:30:18,720 --> 00:30:20,390
-什么  -公司最近变动很大
- What? - Firm's been through a lot.

741
00:30:20,390 --> 00:30:21,690
我们需要重组
We have to regroup.

742
00:30:21,690 --> 00:30:24,130
所以  我决定停招新人 
Therefore, I'm instituting a hiring freeze,

743
00:30:24,140 --> 00:30:25,810
要是你招人之前问我一声
which you would have known about

744
00:30:25,810 --> 00:30:27,430
也不用现在这么大费周章了
had you come and asked my permission first.

745
00:30:27,440 --> 00:30:28,360
你不能这么对我
Okay, you can't do this.

746
00:30:28,360 --> 00:30:29,730
我是高级合伙人  公司规章允许我招
I'm a senior partner, and that's the rule.

747
00:30:29,730 --> 00:30:31,420
严格来说  并未成规章
Strictly speaking, it's not a rule,

748
00:30:31,420 --> 00:30:32,640
只是传统罢了
it's a tradition.

749
00:30:32,640 --> 00:30:33,910
我懂了
I get it.

750
00:30:33,950 --> 00:30:36,310
严格来说  并不是什么停招
Strictly speaking, this isn't about a hiring freeze,

751
00:30:36,310 --> 00:30:37,570
就是给我穿小鞋
this is punishment.

752
00:30:37,580 --> 00:30:39,990
你能这么做  我也可以
You can be punitive, I can be punitive.

753
00:30:40,900 --> 00:30:42,260
聘书已经发出去了
The offer already went out, Jessica.

754
00:30:42,260 --> 00:30:44,170
你不是律师吗  自己想办法
You're a lawyer, make it go away.

755
00:30:44,180 --> 00:30:45,540
我怎么对别人说啊
What am I gonna tell the world?

756
00:30:45,540 --> 00:30:46,840
搞得我想白痴一样
I'm gonna look like a freaking fool.

757
00:30:46,840 --> 00:30:48,890
就和他们说  现在公司停招
Well, tell them there's a hiring freeze.

758
00:30:50,600 --> 00:30:51,960
随你怎么说
I don't care.

759
00:30:52,350 --> 00:30:53,870
摆平就行
Make it go away.

760
00:30:57,500 --> 00:30:58,930
你可以走了
You're dismissed.

761
00:31:05,340 --> 00:31:07,770
你的留言看着有点耐人寻味
The message you left was a little cryptic.

762
00:31:07,770 --> 00:31:08,920
你到底想要什么
What do you want?

763
00:31:09,600 --> 00:31:11,580
我想要帮你得到你想要的
I want to help you get what you want.

764
00:31:11,760 --> 00:31:13,000
我想要的是什么
And what is that?

765
00:31:13,630 --> 00:31:15,760
利亚姆·柯顺开车撞倒艾伯特·钟那晚
Liam Colson was driving under the influence

766
00:31:15,760 --> 00:31:17,310
他嗑了药
when he hit Albert Chung.

767
00:31:17,840 --> 00:31:19,330
你是怎么知道的
How exactly did you come to know that?

768
00:31:19,330 --> 00:31:20,800
这无法奉告
I can't tell you that.

769
00:31:22,700 --> 00:31:24,480
谢谢你  迈克
Thank you, Mike.

770
00:31:24,480 --> 00:31:25,750
全体起立
All rise.

771
00:31:25,750 --> 00:31:28,310
有请尊敬的尼古拉斯·巴勒莫法官阁下
For the honorable judge Nicholas Palermo.

772
00:31:29,560 --> 00:31:30,760
全体坐下
Be seated.

773
00:31:30,770 --> 00:31:34,080
纽约州状告利亚姆·柯顺一案现在开庭
"State of New York versus Liam Colson."

774
00:31:36,630 --> 00:31:37,930
报告法官大人
I am happy to report

775
00:31:37,930 --> 00:31:39,600
昨晚被告已经和检方
the state entered into a plea agreement

776
00:31:39,600 --> 00:31:40,720
达成了认罪协议
with the defendant last night.

777
00:31:40,720 --> 00:31:42,660
协议条款已经呈送给您
You have a copy of the terms, your honor.

778
00:31:45,600 --> 00:31:47,420
一切进行得井井有条
Everything appears to be in order.

779
00:31:47,420 --> 00:31:48,610
本院批准这个协议
The agreement is approved.

780
00:31:48,610 --> 00:31:50,650
被告从下周一开始社区服务
Community service starts Monday.

781
00:31:53,080 --> 00:31:54,650
这就完了吗  你就这么走了吗
That's it? You're just walking away?

782
00:31:54,650 --> 00:31:56,060
是的  快步离开
As fast as I can.

783
00:31:56,060 --> 00:31:59,460
你知道你的"无可奉告"意味着什么吗
Because you know what "I can't tell you how I know that" means?

784
00:31:59,460 --> 00:32:00,910
你违反了保密特权
It means you just violated privilege.

785
00:32:00,920 --> 00:32:02,010
等等  你对他
Wait, so you don't care

786
00:32:02,010 --> 00:32:03,570
嗑药开车无动于衷
that he was driving under the influence?

787
00:32:03,570 --> 00:32:05,130
我不能证明他嗑了药
I can't prove he was under the influence.

788
00:32:05,130 --> 00:32:06,230
不把那孩子放上被告席
You don't know what you could prove

789
00:32:06,240 --> 00:32:07,600
你根本就不知道能问出点什么
if you got that kid in a room.

790
00:32:07,610 --> 00:32:08,800
如果我把你告诉我的作为证据
If I were to use what you just told me,

791
00:32:08,800 --> 00:32:11,300
别人还不都把我当傻瓜看
all I would be doing is making myself look like an idiot.

792
00:32:11,300 --> 00:32:13,550
你这么做晚上竟然能安然入梦
Are you really gonna be able to sleep at night?

793
00:32:14,380 --> 00:32:15,610
你能吗
Are you?

794
00:32:16,080 --> 00:32:17,500
你大摇大摆走进去
You're the one who walked in there

795
00:32:17,500 --> 00:32:19,970
想要毁了一个20岁少年的生活
and tried to sell out a 20-year-old kid.

796
00:32:19,970 --> 00:32:22,130
那个少年撞死了人
He took someone's life, right?

797
00:32:22,130 --> 00:32:24,750
而死者也是有父母  有姐姐
That someone had a mother and a father and a sister.

798
00:32:24,750 --> 00:32:27,240
现在他们一家生活全乱套了
That family is never gonna be the same.

799
00:32:27,360 --> 00:32:29,880
你听好了  你认为我就从来没有
Listen to me, you think I haven't had a case

800
00:32:29,880 --> 00:32:31,990
想要通过非正规手段把人送进监狱吗
where I could have crossed a line to put someone away?

801
00:32:31,990 --> 00:32:33,760
你觉得你当然想过
I wouldn't be surprised if you did,

802
00:32:33,760 --> 00:32:35,460
你不还想着要贿赂我吗
after that bribe you offered me.

803
00:32:35,470 --> 00:32:37,880
我贿赂你什么了
I didn't offer you shit.

804
00:32:37,880 --> 00:32:39,600
我只是帮了你个忙
I did you a favor.

805
00:32:39,610 --> 00:32:41,170
同时我也请你帮个忙
And then I asked for a favor,

806
00:32:41,170 --> 00:32:42,550
做不做都随你
which you could do or not.

807
00:32:42,560 --> 00:32:43,780
当你审视镜子中的自己
Is that really what you tell yourself

808
00:32:43,780 --> 00:32:45,260
就这么安慰自己吗
when you look in the mirror?

809
00:32:45,460 --> 00:32:46,820
如果你不惜违反保密特权
If you're willing to break privilege,

810
00:32:46,820 --> 00:32:49,270
你才应该去审视下自己
you're the one who needs to look in the mirror.

811
00:33:04,450 --> 00:33:06,070
卡特里娜·班尼特来电
Katrina Bennett called.

812
00:33:06,150 --> 00:33:07,400
事情确定了
The deal's done.

813
00:33:08,470 --> 00:33:10,250
你去起草文件吧
Get the paperwork started.

814
00:33:12,430 --> 00:33:13,930
哈维  你这是干什么
Harvey, what did you do?

815
00:33:14,680 --> 00:33:16,450
这事儿我没得选
I did what I had to do.

816
00:33:19,290 --> 00:33:21,060
你第一个雇的是迈克
Your first hire was Mike.

817
00:33:21,060 --> 00:33:23,110
你真想让她成为你的第二个雇员吗
Are you sure you want this to be your second?

818
00:33:23,120 --> 00:33:24,600
你别说了
I don't want to hear it.

819
00:33:24,860 --> 00:33:26,550
她从周一开始上班
She starts on Monday.

820
00:33:45,410 --> 00:33:47,340
教皇新堡  1985年产
Chateauneuf-du-Pape, 1985.

821
00:33:47,340 --> 00:33:49,530
我想他们83年的酒都卖光了
I guess they were out of the '83.

822
00:33:51,610 --> 00:33:52,780
路易
Louis,

823
00:33:53,150 --> 00:33:54,920
你看着好像  我刚给你一拳
you look like I just kicked you in the stomach

824
00:33:54,920 --> 00:33:56,650
-可你都不享受  -对不起
- but in a bad way. - I'm sorry.

825
00:33:56,650 --> 00:33:59,740
我心思不在这儿
I, my mind's on something else.

826
00:33:59,740 --> 00:34:01,000
怎么了
What is it?

827
00:34:02,920 --> 00:34:04,350
答应我听了别发火
Promise you won't be mad?

828
00:34:05,440 --> 00:34:07,730
你不是想让我去做什么艾滋病检查吧
You're not about to tell me I have to get tested, are you?

829
00:34:07,730 --> 00:34:10,380
什么  不是这件事
What? No. Nothing like that.

830
00:34:10,380 --> 00:34:11,480
我
I...

831
00:34:11,480 --> 00:34:13,290
我不得不撤回聘书
I had to rescind the offer...

832
00:34:13,690 --> 00:34:14,950
不招玛丽亚了
To Maria.

833
00:34:16,550 --> 00:34:18,310
-你生气了  -没有
- You're mad? - No.

834
00:34:18,410 --> 00:34:21,440
-我很失望  -希拉
- I'm disappointed. - Sheila...

835
00:34:21,450 --> 00:34:23,450
你和我想象中的不一样
You're not the man I thought you were.

836
00:34:23,950 --> 00:34:25,630
我别无选择
I-I didn't have a choice.

837
00:34:25,810 --> 00:34:27,240
是杰西卡·皮尔逊做的决定
It was Jessica Pearson's decision.

838
00:34:27,240 --> 00:34:28,390
好吧  我对你是看走眼了
Okay, well, then I must have read you wrong

839
00:34:28,390 --> 00:34:31,520
本以为你是有能力  有权力的高级合伙人
'cause I thought you were a strong, powerful senior partner.

840
00:34:31,520 --> 00:34:32,450
我是啊
I am.

841
00:34:32,450 --> 00:34:34,290
现在看来完全不是
The evidence suggests otherwise.

842
00:34:35,170 --> 00:34:36,680
你还是走吧
I think you should go.

843
00:34:39,580 --> 00:34:41,020
希拉  别这样
Sheila, please.

844
00:34:41,360 --> 00:34:44,220
我们对这事儿不能一笑了之吗
I mean, can't this snaff just be something we laugh at?

845
00:34:44,220 --> 00:34:45,990
过一两个小时就别去想它了
Like, in an hour and a half, hour and 45 minutes?

846
00:34:46,000 --> 00:34:48,270
你床上功夫再好也没有用
Your sexual prowess isn't gonna get you out of this.

847
00:34:48,270 --> 00:34:49,690
-你生气了  -是的
- You are mad. - Yeah.

848
00:34:49,690 --> 00:34:51,800
我以自己的名誉向她替你说好话
I put my reputation on the line to close Maria.

849
00:34:51,800 --> 00:34:53,150
听着  这不是我的错
Look, it's not my fault.

850
00:34:53,150 --> 00:34:54,970
公司已经停止招聘了
The firm instituted a hiring freeze.

851
00:34:54,970 --> 00:34:56,280
若真是如此
If there's a hiring freeze going on,

852
00:34:56,280 --> 00:34:57,470
为何我却听说
then why do I know for a fact

853
00:34:57,480 --> 00:35:00,670
哈维·斯佩克特今天招了一个
that Harvey Specter hired a fifth-year associate today?

854
00:35:02,080 --> 00:35:03,940
你把卡特里娜·班尼特招进来了吗
You offered Katrina Bennett a job?

855
00:35:03,940 --> 00:35:04,840
我查了她的背景
I looked into her.

856
00:35:04,840 --> 00:35:06,820
她在应聘者中算是佼佼者
Turns out she's a stellar candidate.

857
00:35:07,080 --> 00:35:08,390
你这是贿赂她
You bribed her.

858
00:35:08,690 --> 00:35:10,820
贿赂是需要明确地用某物
A bribe requires a clear exchange

859
00:35:10,820 --> 00:35:12,540
与另外一物进行交换才算成立
of something for something else.

860
00:35:12,540 --> 00:35:14,130
-我可没做这事  -扯淡
- That didn't happen here. - Bullshit.

861
00:35:14,130 --> 00:35:16,520
她说了你若聘她  她就签协议
She said she'd put the deal through if you offered her a job.

862
00:35:16,520 --> 00:35:17,880
是她先签了协议
She said she'd put the deal through,

863
00:35:17,880 --> 00:35:19,240
我再去聘她的
then I offered her a job.

864
00:35:19,240 --> 00:35:21,450
还真是啊  因为你需要份保障书
Oh, right, because you needed an insurance policy.

865
00:35:21,450 --> 00:35:23,710
是因为我料到了你会怎么做
Because I could see exactly what you were gonna do.

866
00:35:23,710 --> 00:35:26,480
所以你才给她份工作  以得到你想要的
So you offered her a job to get her to do what you wanted.

867
00:35:26,480 --> 00:35:27,990
这就是一物换一物
That's something for something else.

868
00:35:27,990 --> 00:35:29,460
你贿赂了她
You bribed her.

869
00:35:29,560 --> 00:35:31,210
你一口咬定我贿赂
You bet your ass I did.

870
00:35:31,210 --> 00:35:32,990
但你蠢到连我这是为了你
But what you're too stupid to understand is

871
00:35:32,990 --> 00:35:34,980
都想不到
I did it to save you.

872
00:35:34,980 --> 00:35:37,010
你这楠木脑袋给我想清楚了
Get it through your goddamn head.

873
00:35:37,010 --> 00:35:38,700
你没按规矩来
You're not like other lawyers.

874
00:35:38,700 --> 00:35:40,440
侵犯了当事人特权
You break attorney-client privilege.

875
00:35:40,440 --> 00:35:42,470
利亚姆倒没什么事儿
Nothing different happens with Liam,

876
00:35:42,490 --> 00:35:44,270
但他们是肯定要来调查你了
but they're sure as sh-- gonna look into you.

877
00:35:44,270 --> 00:35:46,050
他们会发现什么就不必我明说了吧
And you and I both know what they're gonna find when they do.

878
00:35:46,050 --> 00:35:47,810
他们发现了又如何
What difference does it make what they find?

879
00:35:47,820 --> 00:35:49,480
是非黑白是有个度的
There's such a thing as right and wrong.

880
00:35:49,480 --> 00:35:50,190
这事是错在我们
And we're wrong!

881
00:35:50,200 --> 00:35:50,740
告诉你
You know what?

882
00:35:50,740 --> 00:35:52,920
每次碰到了灰色地带  要做决定
I have had it up to here with you blaming me

883
00:35:52,920 --> 00:35:55,190
你就跑来指责我  我受够了
for every hard choice that comes with this job.

884
00:35:55,200 --> 00:35:56,500
-哈维  别这样  -闭嘴
- Harvey, come on. - Shut up!

885
00:35:59,140 --> 00:36:02,020
我雇用你后  生活是变好了还是变差了
Is your life better or worse than before I hired you?

886
00:36:03,250 --> 00:36:04,060
都有
It's both.

887
00:36:04,070 --> 00:36:05,730
你还是记着那些好的吧
Well, maybe you should focus on the better,

888
00:36:05,730 --> 00:36:07,590
因为下次若我还要
Because the next time I have the option

889
00:36:07,590 --> 00:36:09,430
越界去救你
to cross a line to save you,

890
00:36:09,430 --> 00:36:12,270
我只会让你收拾包袱滚蛋
I'll send you packing and not think twice.

891
00:36:12,890 --> 00:36:14,850
给我好好想想吧
Now get your shit together.

892
00:37:15,490 --> 00:37:16,460
搞定了吗
Is it done?

893
00:37:16,470 --> 00:37:17,570
搞定了
It's done.

894
00:37:18,120 --> 00:37:21,370
太感谢了  这是干什么
Thank you. What's wrong?

895
00:37:21,370 --> 00:37:24,110
干什么  闹出条人命了
That's wrong? A man is dead.

896
00:37:24,120 --> 00:37:26,680
是你杀了他  而我无能为力
You killed him, and I have to live with it.

897
00:37:27,210 --> 00:37:28,750
你以为我不知道吗
And you think I don't know that?

898
00:37:29,400 --> 00:37:31,830
我还得装作没事继续我的生活
I get to go back to my life like nothing happened,

899
00:37:31,880 --> 00:37:33,550
但事情无可挽回了
but something did happen.

900
00:37:34,290 --> 00:37:35,980
-我很难受  -你活该
- It makes me sick. - It should.

901
00:37:35,980 --> 00:37:38,630
所以你过来是让我更难受吗
Is that why you came here, to make me feel worse?

902
00:37:38,630 --> 00:37:41,460
这份协议你根本不配有
You've been given a gift that you don't deserve.

903
00:37:41,460 --> 00:37:43,120
所以你最好反思一下自己
So you better clean yourself up

904
00:37:43,120 --> 00:37:45,700
该怎么补偿艾伯特·钟
and figure out a way to make up for Albert Chung.

905
00:37:53,510 --> 00:37:55,610
你带花来了  有长进噢
You brought flowers. You're learning.

906
00:37:55,610 --> 00:37:57,190
这是给奥利维亚的
They're for Olivia.

907
00:37:58,060 --> 00:37:59,310
那我怎么办
What about me?

908
00:38:00,840 --> 00:38:02,270
那个是给你的
That's for you.

909
00:38:02,320 --> 00:38:04,430
你给我买了辆...车吗
You bought me a...car?

910
00:38:04,430 --> 00:38:06,850
对啊  我想着可以一起去趟伯克夏兹
Yeah, I was thinking we'd drive up to the Berkshires.

911
00:38:06,970 --> 00:38:08,380
那边有个小木屋
There's a little cabin I know.

912
00:38:08,380 --> 00:38:09,990
自带桑拿浴
It's got its own sauna,

913
00:38:09,990 --> 00:38:11,360
私人厨师
private chef.

914
00:38:15,180 --> 00:38:17,400
我不能跟你去  哈维
I can't go away with you, Harvey.

915
00:38:18,710 --> 00:38:19,880
怎么了
Why not?

916
00:38:24,560 --> 00:38:25,970
我哥哥得了癌症
My brother's got cancer.

917
00:38:25,980 --> 00:38:28,290
不知道能熬多久
He's-- he's not gonna make it.

918
00:38:29,320 --> 00:38:30,660
我的天啊
Oh, my god.

919
00:38:32,440 --> 00:38:33,480
是她爸爸
Her dad.

920
00:38:33,480 --> 00:38:34,980
我们知道迟早会这样
I mean, we knew that it was coming.

921
00:38:34,980 --> 00:38:37,450
但没想到会来的这么快
We just didn't know it would be this fast.

922
00:38:40,920 --> 00:38:43,300
-她在这里吗  -没有
- Is she here? - No.

923
00:38:43,300 --> 00:38:45,140
不过我准备去我父母那
But I'm going to my parents',

924
00:38:45,200 --> 00:38:47,630
我会让她跟着我生活
and I'm gonna-- I'm gonna take her with me.

925
00:38:48,380 --> 00:38:50,020
我要抚养她长大
I'm gonna raise her.

926
00:38:52,000 --> 00:38:53,590
你怎么不告诉我呢
Why didn't you tell me?

927
00:38:53,590 --> 00:38:55,740
因为我觉得  要是...
Because I thought, you know, when...

928
00:38:55,750 --> 00:38:57,010
你看到奥利维亚在这里
you saw Olivia was here,

929
00:38:57,010 --> 00:38:59,130
我们会慢慢适应重新调整的
that we'd reschedule or something, you know?

930
00:38:59,130 --> 00:39:00,670
结果...
And then...

931
00:39:00,670 --> 00:39:04,460
看见你 跟她在一起  真是...
I saw you with her, and it...

932
00:39:04,470 --> 00:39:05,850
很...
it was...

933
00:39:06,260 --> 00:39:07,990
你想留份美好回忆
You wanted to have a night.

934
00:39:09,560 --> 00:39:12,430
那并不是我的本意
Okay, I didn't think it would lead to that.

935
00:39:14,820 --> 00:39:17,140
但最后发现那晚很美好
But I'm really happy that it did.

936
00:39:19,340 --> 00:39:20,770
你什么时候走
When are you going?

937
00:39:21,550 --> 00:39:22,820
很快
Soon.

938
00:39:28,190 --> 00:39:29,630
抱歉
I'm sorry.

939
00:39:31,950 --> 00:39:34,540
真的很遗憾
I'm so, so sorry.

940
00:39:38,200 --> 00:39:39,770
惊喜一下
Surprise.

941
00:39:41,670 --> 00:39:44,000
你都没跟我联系  案子怎么样
Hey, I never heard from you. How did the case go?

942
00:39:44,000 --> 00:39:45,590
我没心情说
I don't want to talk about it.

943
00:39:47,100 --> 00:39:48,280
输得挺惨吧
That bad, huh?

944
00:39:48,280 --> 00:39:49,820
是啊  很惨
Yeah, that bad.

945
00:39:50,330 --> 00:39:52,540
这样  那你干嘛不过来
Well, why don't you come over here,

946
00:39:52,540 --> 00:39:54,170
我会让你感觉好点儿的
And I'll make you feel better?

947
00:39:54,420 --> 00:39:56,540
我没等你来就开始了
I already started without you.

948
00:40:00,630 --> 00:40:02,720
我不能再这样了  苔丝
I can't do this anymore, tess.

949
00:40:03,410 --> 00:40:04,320
吸毒吗
Get high?

950
00:40:04,320 --> 00:40:08,060
-太恶心了  -你中什么邪了
- It's so disgusting. - What got into you?

951
00:40:08,060 --> 00:40:10,110
整件事就很恶心
This whole thing is disgusting.

952
00:40:14,860 --> 00:40:16,570
你这是在跟我分手吗
Are you breaking up with me?

953
00:40:21,970 --> 00:40:23,970
-你爱你的丈夫吗  -什么
- Do you love your husband? - What?

954
00:40:23,970 --> 00:40:25,760
答案很简单  苔丝  回答我
It's a simple question, Tess, Answer it.

955
00:40:25,760 --> 00:40:27,240
你爱你的丈夫吗
Do you love your husband?

956
00:40:29,290 --> 00:40:32,820
-我不知道  -你看  我连这个都不知道
- Uh, I don't know. - See, I don't even know that.

957
00:40:32,820 --> 00:40:34,330
因为我们从没谈论过
Because we never even talk about it.

958
00:40:34,330 --> 00:40:35,200
那我们现在可以来谈谈啊
Well, we can talk about it now.

959
00:40:35,210 --> 00:40:37,180
我现在没心情跟你说这个
I don't want to talk about it now!

960
00:40:37,640 --> 00:40:40,390
苔丝  是非黑白都有个度
Tess, there is such a thing as right and wrong.

961
00:40:40,390 --> 00:40:42,100
我们做的这些...
And what we're doing here...

962
00:40:43,420 --> 00:40:45,100
是错的  何况...
It's just wrong, and...

963
00:40:45,100 --> 00:40:46,350
你结婚了
You're married.

964
00:40:47,500 --> 00:40:49,350
我不想搅合在里面
And I don't want a part of it anymore.

965
00:40:53,280 --> 00:40:54,940
如果我没结婚呢
What if I wasn't?

966
00:40:58,250 --> 00:40:59,400
迈克
Mike.

967
00:41:01,360 --> 00:41:02,660
你走吧
You need to go.

968
00:41:03,870 --> 00:41:05,790
我自己要好好想想
And I need to get my shit together.

