1
00:07:25,000 --> 00:07:28,000
<font color="#00ff00">-=耐卡影音论坛=-
www.ncar.cc/bbs
欣赏更多精彩美剧</font>

8
00:07:28,000 --> 00:07:33,000
<font color="#ffff00">字幕源自INTERNET</font>

11
00:07:49,660 --> 00:07:51,830
{\pos(185,208)}第二季 第十二集

12
00:07:49,660 --> 00:07:51,830
{\pos(185,193)}诉 讼 双 雄

13
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:01,070
《诉讼双雄》前情提要

14
00:00:01,210 --> 00:00:03,790
苔丝  是非黑白都有个度
Tess, there is such a thing as right and wrong.

15
00:00:03,790 --> 00:00:06,150
-你结婚了  -如果我没结婚呢
- You're married. - What if I wasn't?

16
00:00:06,330 --> 00:00:09,220
这种事情  肯定不会有好结果
What you're doing, it only ends one way.

17
00:00:11,900 --> 00:00:14,110
我可不是唯一投给哈德曼的高级合伙人
I wasn't the only senior partner who voted for Hardman.

18
00:00:14,110 --> 00:00:15,440
我怎么没见你给别人
And I don't see you giving anyone else shit

19
00:00:15,440 --> 00:00:16,410
这样的白眼
the way you give me.

20
00:00:16,410 --> 00:00:17,870
还有  在紧要关头
And by the way, when the chips were down,

21
00:00:17,870 --> 00:00:19,790
我支持了你  赶走了他
I backed you, I ousted him.

22
00:00:19,830 --> 00:00:21,490
字幕路易  你想怎么说都行
Tell yourself whatever you want, Louis.

23
00:00:21,600 --> 00:00:22,740
对着镜子说去
But tell it to yourself.

24
00:00:23,260 --> 00:00:25,000
我不能跟你去  哈维
I can't go away with you, Harvey.

25
00:00:26,580 --> 00:00:27,600
怎么了
Why not?

26
00:00:29,550 --> 00:00:31,420
因为下次若我还要
The next time I have an option

27
00:00:31,420 --> 00:00:33,040
越界去救你
to cross a line to save you,

28
00:00:33,040 --> 00:00:35,510
我只会让你收拾包袱滚蛋
I'll send you packing and not think twice.

29
00:00:36,190 --> 00:00:37,980
给我好好想想吧
Now get your shit together.

30
00:00:40,490 --> 00:00:41,690
你走吧
You need to go,

31
00:00:41,870 --> 00:00:43,610
我自己要好好想想
and I need to get my shit together.

32
00:01:11,140 --> 00:01:13,180
真好  在电梯口迎接我
How nice, greeting me at the door.

33
00:01:13,180 --> 00:01:14,720
你说什么时候才会把那个摘下来
When do you think are they gonna take that down?

34
00:01:14,720 --> 00:01:17,730
皮尔逊  找不到押韵的
Pearson... just doesn't have the same ring.

35
00:01:18,010 --> 00:01:19,740
皮尔逊-保尔森就不错
Pearson Paulsen sounds pretty good.

36
00:01:20,860 --> 00:01:21,990
好吧  我收回
Okay. No, it doesn't.

37
00:01:21,990 --> 00:01:23,090
今天什么安排
How's my day?

38
00:01:23,090 --> 00:01:24,020
你昨晚怎么样
How was your night?

39
00:01:24,020 --> 00:01:25,390
说是昨晚  我是问周末
And by night, I mean weekend,

40
00:01:25,390 --> 00:01:27,090
说是周末  我是问佐伊
and by weekend, I mean Zoe.

41
00:01:27,140 --> 00:01:28,140
挺好
It was fine.

42
00:01:29,530 --> 00:01:30,300
这就没了
That's it?

43
00:01:30,310 --> 00:01:31,610
你都不开玩笑
No fun banter?

44
00:01:32,410 --> 00:01:33,770
也不大肆引用
No witty repartee?

45
00:01:33,770 --> 00:01:36,100
而且八点整就到办公室了
And you're in the office at exactly 8:00.

46
00:01:36,480 --> 00:01:38,210
要是约会很失败  你肯定会早来
Not early, which would mean it went badly.

47
00:01:38,210 --> 00:01:39,940
要是约会很惬意  你就会迟到
And not late, which would mean it went great.

48
00:01:39,940 --> 00:01:41,840
你却准时来上班  就是说...
But exactly on time, which means--

49
00:01:42,220 --> 00:01:44,260
你和佐伊周末就没出去
You and Zoe never went away for the weekend.

50
00:01:44,600 --> 00:01:46,300
怎么了啊  你要聊聊不
What happened? Do you want to talk about it?

51
00:01:46,300 --> 00:01:47,190
我有冰淇淋
I have ice cream.

52
00:01:47,190 --> 00:01:48,120
这才早上八点
It's 8:00 A.M.

53
00:01:48,120 --> 00:01:50,480
{\an8}知名冰淇淋品牌Ben&Jerry的一种冰淇淋口味

54
00:01:48,120 --> 00:01:50,480
所以才会有胖墩猴这种口味啊
Which is why god made chunky monkey.

55
00:01:50,500 --> 00:01:52,320
有巧克力和香蕉哦
It has chocolate and bananas.

56
00:01:52,510 --> 00:01:53,910
香蕉是健康早餐必备品
Bananas are part of a healthy breakfast.

57
00:01:53,910 --> 00:01:54,520
但这不是重点
And who cares about the bananas?

58
00:01:54,520 --> 00:01:55,830
重点是巧克力
It has chocolate.

59
00:01:56,700 --> 00:01:58,830
被你发现了  其实我不吃香蕉的
Okay, you caught me. I don't even eat the bananas.

60
00:01:58,830 --> 00:02:01,350
早上八点因为着工作日已经开始了
8:00 A.M. means the business day has already started.

61
00:02:01,350 --> 00:02:02,600
还是开始工作吧
I'd like to conduct some business.

62
00:02:02,600 --> 00:02:03,740
那样的话
Well, in that case,

63
00:02:03,740 --> 00:02:04,930
特伦特·德文想见你
Trent Devon would like to see you.

64
00:02:04,930 --> 00:02:06,240
那就安排一次会面
So schedule an appointment.

65
00:02:06,240 --> 00:02:08,460
你八点零二分要回见特伦特·德文
Okay, you have an 8:02 with Trent Devon.

66
00:02:09,140 --> 00:02:10,320
我去电梯门口迎你
Well, I didn't meet you at the elevator

67
00:02:10,320 --> 00:02:11,800
可不是光为了跟你聊周末
just to chat about your weekend.

68
00:02:11,800 --> 00:02:12,810
你行的  叫迈克来
Fine. Get Mike.

69
00:02:12,810 --> 00:02:14,520
从他家么
From home?

70
00:02:15,800 --> 00:02:16,880
你没开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.

71
00:02:17,080 --> 00:02:19,380
客户已经到了  我的助手还没到吗
My client is here, and my associate is not?

72
00:02:19,380 --> 00:02:19,990
我相信...
Well, I'm sure--

73
00:02:19,990 --> 00:02:21,650
唐娜  我不要听解释
Donna, I don't want to hear it.

74
00:02:22,190 --> 00:02:24,470
迈克·罗斯一踏进办公楼
The minute Mike Ross sets foot in this building,

75
00:02:24,470 --> 00:02:25,600
就给我叫过来
I want to know.

76
00:02:28,120 --> 00:02:29,800
我觉得这主意很糟  哈维
I think it's a bad idea, Harvey.

77
00:02:30,600 --> 00:02:31,600
到第一季度结束
We'll double the share price

78
00:02:31,600 --> 00:02:33,020
我们就能让股价翻倍
by the end of the first quarter.

79
00:02:33,020 --> 00:02:34,630
我不是指这个
That's not what I meant.

80
00:02:35,000 --> 00:02:36,640
我只是不确定在眼下
I'm just-- I'm not sure going public

81
00:02:36,640 --> 00:02:37,980
上市是最好的一步棋
is the best move right now.

82
00:02:37,980 --> 00:02:39,390
所以才要我啊
That's why I'm here.

83
00:02:39,390 --> 00:02:41,290
相信我  这不是正儿八经的合同
Trust me, these aren't valid reservations.

84
00:02:41,290 --> 00:02:42,550
你只是临阵怯场了
You're just getting cold feet.

85
00:02:42,650 --> 00:02:43,370
哈维
Harvey.

86
00:02:43,370 --> 00:02:45,220
我会让唐娜送你些棉窝窝[对应前面cold feet]
I'll have Donna send you some fuzzy slippers.

87
00:02:45,220 --> 00:02:46,170
一切都很好
You'll be just fine.

88
00:02:46,170 --> 00:02:46,990
那玩意能阻止
Are fuzzy slippers gonna stop

89
00:02:46,990 --> 00:02:49,100
周五即将出台的16号法令吗
the title 16 ruling that came down Friday?

90
00:02:51,230 --> 00:02:52,680
你都不知道那是什么吧
You don't even know what that is, do you?

91
00:02:52,680 --> 00:02:53,620
不  我是不知道
No, I don't.

92
00:02:53,620 --> 00:02:55,010
但我很确定的是
But what I do know is it's not gonna change

93
00:02:55,010 --> 00:02:56,610
这不会改变你网站的价值
the value of your site.

94
00:02:56,610 --> 00:02:58,720
在过去十个月  点击量翻了三倍
You've tripled your reach in the past ten months.

95
00:02:58,720 --> 00:03:00,960
大家都在谈论你
Everyone is talking about you.

96
00:03:01,130 --> 00:03:02,740
现在正是时候
Now is the time.

97
00:03:03,210 --> 00:03:04,730
我们之前说好了的
Come on, we agreed on this.

98
00:03:07,860 --> 00:03:09,110
你到底在担心什么
What's this really about?

99
00:03:10,260 --> 00:03:12,110
担心事务所的变动
It's about the changes around here.

100
00:03:12,270 --> 00:03:13,470
没有任何改变
Nothing's changed.

101
00:03:14,210 --> 00:03:15,880
-我就在这  -哈维
- I'm here. - Harvey.

102
00:03:16,070 --> 00:03:17,910
我也许是个技术宅  但并非一无所知
I may be a tech head, but I'm not oblivious.

103
00:03:17,910 --> 00:03:19,820
这家事务所刚经历一场权利斗争  我都知道
This firm just went through a battle, and I know it.

104
00:03:19,990 --> 00:03:21,270
你是说  你不相信我
Are you telling me that you don't trust me

105
00:03:21,270 --> 00:03:22,910
会把你的需求至于公司的之上吗
to put your needs above the firm's?

106
00:03:22,910 --> 00:03:24,770
不  我一直相信你  哈维
No, I've always trusted you, Harvey.

107
00:03:24,770 --> 00:03:27,350
我只是...
I'm just saying I don't--

108
00:03:28,890 --> 00:03:30,030
我认为你有太多事烦心
I think you might be too distracted

109
00:03:30,030 --> 00:03:31,560
没法提供给我最专业的服务
to give me the best advice.

110
00:03:31,560 --> 00:03:33,550
-特伦特  -我得考虑下备选方案
- Trent. - I have to consider my options.

111
00:03:33,890 --> 00:03:36,020
关于上市  还是我们事务所
About the IPO or Pearson Hardman?

112
00:03:37,090 --> 00:03:38,140
都要
Both.

113
00:03:39,230 --> 00:03:40,500
我们碰到问题了
We have a problem.

114
00:03:41,590 --> 00:03:42,660
怎么了
Yeah?

115
00:03:42,830 --> 00:03:44,770
伯尼·卡雷尔准备离开我们
Bernie Carillo is thinking of leaving us.

116
00:03:44,770 --> 00:03:46,680
肯定不是真的  是的话我早有信了
That's absolutely not true, and I would know.

117
00:03:46,680 --> 00:03:48,050
我的消息来源很可靠
I have it on good authority.

118
00:03:50,290 --> 00:03:51,800
让我猜猜  你是来怪我的
So let me guess. It's my fault.

119
00:03:51,800 --> 00:03:53,120
路易  我不是来责备你
Louis, I didn't come here to blame you.

120
00:03:53,120 --> 00:03:54,870
我是来提醒你
I came here to give you a heads up.

121
00:03:57,860 --> 00:03:59,380
你想说什么就直说
You want to spit out what you're chewing on?

122
00:03:59,380 --> 00:04:01,230
你跟我说  公司停招
Yeah, you order me to rescind an offer

123
00:04:01,230 --> 00:04:03,550
让我收回发出的聘书
due to a firm-wide hiring freeze.

124
00:04:03,610 --> 00:04:05,060
我可是用自己的名誉担保的
I stake my reputation on it.

125
00:04:05,070 --> 00:04:07,380
可一转眼  你就招了一个毕业五年的
Two minutes later, you hire a fifth-year.

126
00:04:08,180 --> 00:04:09,170
你食言了
You went back on your word.

127
00:04:09,170 --> 00:04:10,110
把我当傻瓜耍
And you made me look like a fool.

128
00:04:10,110 --> 00:04:11,330
我也跟你说过
I also gave you my word that

129
00:04:11,330 --> 00:04:13,270
若站错队  可没有后悔药
there'd be no coming back from your vote.

130
00:04:13,690 --> 00:04:15,810
我还想跟你算这笔账呢
And I'm ready to go back on that.

131
00:04:16,040 --> 00:04:19,360
客户在流失  路易  这是我不能接受的
We're losing clients, Louis, and I can't have that.

132
00:04:19,360 --> 00:04:21,930
今天就是路易·利特
So today is day one

133
00:04:21,930 --> 00:04:24,320
重振旗鼓的第一天
of the Louis Litt rehabilitation program.

134
00:04:24,920 --> 00:04:26,820
接受现实  向前看
Take it. Move on.

135
00:04:26,820 --> 00:04:29,270
是时候忘记过去的伤口
It is time to heal the wounds.

136
00:04:32,600 --> 00:04:34,050
我会搞点卡雷尔
I'll take care of Carillo.

137
00:04:38,580 --> 00:04:39,600
拜托
Come on!

138
00:04:41,920 --> 00:04:43,230
别管它了  你干了什么好事
Out with it. What'd you do?

139
00:04:43,280 --> 00:04:44,490
我想我墨水放多了
I think I put in too much toner.

140
00:04:44,490 --> 00:04:45,880
我是说卡雷尔  你个傻蛋
With Carillo, you imbecile.

141
00:04:45,880 --> 00:04:47,170
他在考虑换律师
He's considering a change of counsel.

142
00:04:47,180 --> 00:04:48,640
现在  我想知道你干了什么
Now, I want to know what you did

143
00:04:48,640 --> 00:04:50,700
或者说你忘了什么  把事情搞成这样
or more likely did not do to cause this.

144
00:04:52,540 --> 00:04:53,620
你要说啥
What?

145
00:04:53,620 --> 00:04:55,070
-我不知道  -就知道你不知道
- I don't know. - What a shocker.

146
00:04:55,070 --> 00:04:56,570
若你需要  我去翻翻  我再...
If you want, I can go back, and I'll retry--

147
00:04:56,570 --> 00:04:57,820
错  错  错
No, no, no, no.

148
00:04:57,970 --> 00:04:59,640
我需要的是
What I want is for you to finish

149
00:04:59,640 --> 00:05:00,730
你在明早八点前
drafting the contracts

150
00:05:00,730 --> 00:05:02,340
起草好合同
and deliver them to Rachel Zane

151
00:05:02,350 --> 00:05:04,040
再交给瑞秋·赞恩
by 8.00 A.M. tomorrow morning.

152
00:05:04,040 --> 00:05:05,260
然后听她发落
Then wait for further instructions,

153
00:05:05,260 --> 00:05:06,620
乖乖坐着
politely seated,

154
00:05:06,620 --> 00:05:08,360
双手老实放在腿上
with your hands crossed on your lap.

155
00:05:10,020 --> 00:05:11,790
若有任何闪失
And if anything goes wrong,

156
00:05:11,790 --> 00:05:13,720
我对天发誓
I swear to almighty god

157
00:05:13,720 --> 00:05:15,310
你肯定会后悔
that you are gonna rue the day

158
00:05:15,310 --> 00:05:16,390
当年自己怎么会
that you decided to become

159
00:05:16,390 --> 00:05:18,510
下决定做一个这么蹩脚的律师
the embarrassment of a lawyer that you are.

160
00:05:18,670 --> 00:05:22,500
路易·利特决不能丢客户
Louis Litt does not lose clients.

161
00:05:23,370 --> 00:05:24,720
听明白了吗
Is that clear?

162
00:05:26,010 --> 00:05:27,370
关于卡雷尔的合同
About the Carillo contracts

163
00:05:27,370 --> 00:05:29,070
还是你不会丢客户
or the fact that you don't lose clients?

164
00:05:29,080 --> 00:05:30,170
出去
Get out.

165
00:05:31,160 --> 00:05:32,330
抱歉
Oh, sorry.

166
00:05:35,870 --> 00:05:37,790
噢噢  等一下
Uh-oh. Wait a minute.

167
00:05:38,020 --> 00:05:39,790
这是什么
What is this?

168
00:05:40,620 --> 00:05:43,270
这不是杯三倍浓度无糖无脂的摩卡吗
Is that a triple nonfat sugar-free mocha latte?

169
00:05:43,270 --> 00:05:45,680
你真是太贴心了
Oh, you sweet, sweet-- 

170
00:05:45,680 --> 00:05:47,230
等下  你做了什么好事
Wait a minute. What did you do wrong?

171
00:05:47,360 --> 00:05:49,190
我好受伤啊  你竟然怀疑我动机不纯
Okay, I'm offended. You're questioning my motives?

172
00:05:49,190 --> 00:05:50,650
-实际上  迈克  -没关系
- Actually, Mike-- - It's okay.

173
00:05:50,650 --> 00:05:52,220
你今早第二杯咖啡还没喝呢
You haven't had your second triple latte yet.

174
00:05:52,220 --> 00:05:54,780
我原谅你啦  因为我心情很好
I forgive you because I'm in a forgiving mood.

175
00:05:54,790 --> 00:05:56,510
-是  但哈维的...  -我真喜欢一大早的
- Right, but Harvey's... - I love the smell

176
00:05:56,510 --> 00:05:57,470
-紧张气息  -很糟
- of litigation in the morning. - Not.

177
00:05:57,480 --> 00:05:58,870
都八点半了
It's 8:30.

178
00:05:59,650 --> 00:06:00,450
是  还是早上
Yeah, in the morning.

179
00:06:00,460 --> 00:06:01,720
离你该到的点
It's 30 minutes past

180
00:06:01,720 --> 00:06:03,140
已经过了30分钟了
when you were required to be here,

181
00:06:03,150 --> 00:06:04,610
就是说离你自觉上班的点
which means it's an hour past

182
00:06:04,620 --> 00:06:05,700
已经过了一个小时
when you should be here.

183
00:06:05,700 --> 00:06:07,560
知道了  我们什么时候讲究这个了啊
Okay, since when do we use a time clock?

184
00:06:10,280 --> 00:06:12,730
联邦贸易委员会发的16号法令有什么新要求
What are the new FTC title 16 requirements?

185
00:06:12,730 --> 00:06:14,330
没什么  无关紧要
Oh, they're nothing. It's a nuisance.

186
00:06:14,490 --> 00:06:16,090
特伦特·德文为此担心
Trent Devon's worried about them.

187
00:06:16,960 --> 00:06:18,860
只是又要多填一张表
Okay, well, all it is is another form to fill out.

188
00:06:18,860 --> 00:06:20,820
如果你是担心这个的话  没事的
So if that's what you're worried about, it's fine.

189
00:06:20,820 --> 00:06:22,430
我担心的是
What I'm worried about is the fact

190
00:06:22,430 --> 00:06:23,530
你要是今早八点
that I could've told him that

191
00:06:23,530 --> 00:06:24,680
准时上班  参与了会面
had you been at the meeting

192
00:06:24,680 --> 00:06:25,950
我就能这么告诉他了
this morning at 8:00.

193
00:06:25,960 --> 00:06:27,160
什么  我查看过日历
What? I checked the schedule.

194
00:06:27,160 --> 00:06:28,300
今早没有安排啊
There was nothing on it for this morning.

195
00:06:28,300 --> 00:06:30,830
临时安排的  我们经常如此
It happened spontaneously, as things do.

196
00:06:30,830 --> 00:06:31,930
我在
And I was there.

197
00:06:31,930 --> 00:06:33,540
而你却不在
You were not there.

198
00:06:35,270 --> 00:06:36,210
我告诉你
Did you not hear me

199
00:06:36,210 --> 00:06:37,900
让你好好想想  你有没有听进去啊
when I told you to get your shit together?

200
00:06:37,900 --> 00:06:39,000
我听了
No, I did hear you, and I did

201
00:06:39,000 --> 00:06:40,640
我确实有好好反省
get my shit together, by the way.

202
00:06:40,640 --> 00:06:42,110
所以今早才迟到了
That's why I'm late this morning.

203
00:06:42,110 --> 00:06:44,090
你这反省的方式还真特别
Deciding to be late to get your shit together

204
00:06:44,100 --> 00:06:45,910
都反省得迟到了
is not getting your shit together.

205
00:06:46,280 --> 00:06:47,260
你给我听清楚
Get it through your head.

206
00:06:47,260 --> 00:06:48,720
公司刚经历一场内战
We just went through a civil war,

207
00:06:48,720 --> 00:06:49,840
而大家都知道了
and the world knows it.

208
00:06:49,840 --> 00:06:50,740
我们处于劣势
We're weak.

209
00:06:50,740 --> 00:06:52,090
而这个残酷世界的法则就是
And the law of the jungle says

210
00:06:52,090 --> 00:06:53,240
弱肉强食
the weak get eaten.

211
00:06:53,240 --> 00:06:55,010
哈维  我很抱歉
Okay, Harvey, I'm sorry,

212
00:06:55,010 --> 00:06:56,270
但你要放松点
but you need to ease up here.

213
00:06:56,270 --> 00:06:57,520
放松个头
Ease up?

214
00:06:57,880 --> 00:06:59,310
客户都准备炒掉我们
You're telling me to ease up

215
00:06:59,310 --> 00:07:01,060
你还让我放松
when our clients are leaving?

216
00:07:01,260 --> 00:07:03,500
是的  特伦特·德文可能会走
That's right, Trent Devon might leave.

217
00:07:03,500 --> 00:07:04,750
没人会离开我
People don't leave me!

218
00:07:04,750 --> 00:07:06,080
-我...  -够了
- I-I-- - enough!

219
00:07:06,310 --> 00:07:08,930
你的工作是协助我  不是顶嘴
Your job is to help me, not to screw me.

220
00:07:08,930 --> 00:07:10,100
如果我说你错了
If I tell you you did that,

221
00:07:10,110 --> 00:07:12,030
我不想听你辩解说自己没错
I don't want to hear that you didn't.

222
00:07:12,200 --> 00:07:13,290
我上周真该炒掉你
I should've fired you last week.

223
00:07:13,290 --> 00:07:14,930
其实  我现在就改炒掉你
You know what, I should fire you right now.

224
00:07:14,960 --> 00:07:16,990
但我放过你一马  因为你祖母刚刚去世
But I cut you slack because your grandmother died.

225
00:07:16,990 --> 00:07:18,610
现在你的同情已经用光了
Well, you've used up the rope.

226
00:07:18,610 --> 00:07:20,960
你还这么搞下去  明天我就炒了你
You keep it up, I will fire you tomorrow.

227
00:08:04,650 --> 00:08:05,820
"没人会离开我"
"People don't leave me"?

228
00:08:05,820 --> 00:08:07,170
-唐娜  我不是  -我会
- Donna, I don't-- - I do.

229
00:08:07,170 --> 00:08:09,570
-他活该  -他应该被打两巴掌
- He deserved it. - He deserved a slap.

230
00:08:09,570 --> 00:08:11,470
你却把他打得头破血流
You knocked him across the room.

231
00:08:14,800 --> 00:08:16,140
佐伊怎么了
What happened with Zoe?

232
00:08:19,100 --> 00:08:20,900
她要离开纽约
She's leaving New York

233
00:08:21,060 --> 00:08:24,190
回去照顾她侄女  她爸爸要不行了
to take care of her niece whose father is dying.

234
00:08:25,140 --> 00:08:26,400
我的天
Oh, my God.

235
00:08:27,190 --> 00:08:28,650
哈维  真替你难过
Harvey, I'm sorry.

236
00:08:30,490 --> 00:08:31,660
有没有什么...
Is there anything...

237
00:08:31,690 --> 00:08:32,550
不用
No.

238
00:08:36,230 --> 00:08:37,550
最后一句
Just one thing.

239
00:08:38,380 --> 00:08:40,970
我觉得  四处发泄不会有什么帮助
I don't think kicking the dog is gonna help.

240
00:08:52,110 --> 00:08:54,010
你脸色真差
Wow, you look like hell.

241
00:08:56,970 --> 00:08:57,900
吉米
Jimmy.

242
00:08:58,420 --> 00:08:59,580
是来找我打架的吗
You here to pick a fight with me?

243
00:08:59,580 --> 00:09:00,470
我现在实在没心情
'Cause I'm really not in the mood.

244
00:09:00,470 --> 00:09:02,980
不是  迈克  不是你想的那样
No, no, Mike. It's not like that, man.

245
00:09:02,980 --> 00:09:04,650
你不生我的气了吗
Oh, yeah? You're not still pissed at me?

246
00:09:04,730 --> 00:09:05,960
你让我丢了工作
You gave me an out.

247
00:09:06,510 --> 00:09:07,750
一开始我可能不觉得是好事
I might not have respected it at the time,

248
00:09:07,750 --> 00:09:08,810
但现在不一样了
but I do now.

249
00:09:08,810 --> 00:09:09,620
在我看来
As far as I'm concerned,

250
00:09:09,620 --> 00:09:10,740
-我欠你一个人情  -好
- I owe you one. - Okay.

251
00:09:10,740 --> 00:09:12,130
我请你喝一杯
Yeah. Let me buy you a drink.

252
00:09:12,130 --> 00:09:12,930
两个条件
Two conditions.

253
00:09:12,930 --> 00:09:13,820
一  你仍然欠我个人情
One, you still owe me one.

254
00:09:13,820 --> 00:09:16,650
二  你还是欠我个人情
Two, you still owe me one.

255
00:09:17,870 --> 00:09:19,210
只要我不多欠你一个人情就行
As long as I still don't owe you one.

256
00:09:19,340 --> 00:09:22,020
-酒保  -真高兴能见到你
- Bartender. - It's good to see you, man.

257
00:09:22,020 --> 00:09:23,750
我也是  兄弟  你这是怎么了
You too, buddy. So what's going on?

258
00:09:23,750 --> 00:09:26,150
-今天很不顺心吗  -是啊
- You had a bad day? - Yeah.

259
00:09:26,190 --> 00:09:27,400
跟我说说
Okay. So give it to me.

260
00:09:27,410 --> 00:09:30,680
事实证明  八点半上班只能说明一件事
Well, evidently, getting in at 8:30 can only mean one thing.

261
00:09:30,730 --> 00:09:33,660
七点到八点一刻才刚睡了一会儿
Yeah, that you had your head up your ass from 7:00 to 8:15.

262
00:09:33,660 --> 00:09:34,570
你怎么知道
How'd you know?

263
00:09:34,570 --> 00:09:36,670
忘了吗  我也在路易手底下干过
Are you forgetting I used to work for Louis too?

264
00:09:36,680 --> 00:09:38,950
不过跟你不同  我没哈维保护着我
And unlike you, I didn't have Harvey there to protect me.

265
00:09:38,950 --> 00:09:40,370
不  这次就是哈维
No, this was Harvey.

266
00:09:40,760 --> 00:09:43,390
那真是太扯了
Whoa. Ain't that some shit.

267
00:09:43,390 --> 00:09:46,310
总之  敬这个助理律师的
Anyway, here's to the wonderful world 

268
00:09:46,310 --> 00:09:47,280
美好世界
of being an associate, right?

269
00:09:48,490 --> 00:09:49,970
敬皮尔逊·哈德曼
Yeah. Pearson Hardman.

270
00:09:51,120 --> 00:09:52,010
这话什么意思
What does that mean?

271
00:09:54,390 --> 00:09:55,910
我现在在布莱顿·古尔德了  伙计
I'm at Bratton Gould, my man.

272
00:09:56,070 --> 00:09:58,050
-我现在很开心  -不可能
- And I'm happy. - No!

273
00:09:58,050 --> 00:09:59,680
助理律师没资格幸福  吉米
Associates don't get to be happy, Jimmy.

274
00:09:59,680 --> 00:10:01,060
在布莱顿·古尔德就可以
No, you do at Bratton Gould.

275
00:10:02,370 --> 00:10:03,730
我有自己的办公室
I got an office.

276
00:10:06,090 --> 00:10:07,190
现在就杀了我吧
Shoot me now.

277
00:10:07,520 --> 00:10:08,640
真棒
That's great.

278
00:10:09,550 --> 00:10:10,560
听着  迈克
Listen, Mike.

279
00:10:10,720 --> 00:10:12,390
我说欠你一个人情是真心的
When I said that I owe you one, I mean it.

280
00:10:13,280 --> 00:10:15,090
当然你不是听我说的  我们正在招人
'Cause you didn't hear it from me, but we're expanding.

281
00:10:15,090 --> 00:10:16,440
如果你要跳槽  告诉我
So if you want to jump, just let me know.

282
00:10:16,440 --> 00:10:17,330
我会为你向上面美言
I'll put in a word for you.

283
00:10:17,330 --> 00:10:19,510
-我不能离开哈维  -让哈维去死
- I can't leave Harvey. - Screw Harvey.

284
00:10:19,880 --> 00:10:21,170
他为你做了什么
I mean, what's he done for you?

285
00:10:23,300 --> 00:10:24,610
比你知道的多得多
More than you know.

286
00:10:25,600 --> 00:10:26,940
或许吧
Okay, maybe.

287
00:10:27,700 --> 00:10:29,800
在哈维·斯佩克特手底下做过一年
But a year under Harvey Specter,

288
00:10:29,800 --> 00:10:30,890
他们会打破头抢着要你
they would kill to have you.

289
00:10:31,420 --> 00:10:32,770
而且你不是唯一一个
And you wouldn't be the only one.

290
00:10:36,490 --> 00:10:37,730
还有别人从皮尔逊·哈德曼
There are people from Pearson Hardman 

291
00:10:37,730 --> 00:10:39,600
去布莱顿·古尔德吗  是谁
going to Bratton Gould? Who?

292
00:10:39,600 --> 00:10:40,890
这我不能告诉你
I can't tell you that.

293
00:10:40,890 --> 00:10:42,370
吉米  你必须要告诉我
Jimmy, you have to tell me that.

294
00:10:42,370 --> 00:10:44,020
迈克  要是他们知道是我说出去的
Mike, come on. If they knew it came from me--

295
00:10:44,020 --> 00:10:45,280
他们不会发现的
They won't.

296
00:10:48,970 --> 00:10:52,180
我看见克拉克和欧文斯和我们的合伙人见面
I saw Clark and Owens meeting with our partners.

297
00:10:55,760 --> 00:10:57,700
如果你是来交辞职信的
If you're here to give me your letter of resignation,

298
00:10:57,700 --> 00:10:58,790
明天早上我会接受的
I'll accept it in the morning.

299
00:10:58,790 --> 00:11:01,090
真是够讽刺  我今晚刚接到工作邀请
Oh, that's ironic. I was offered a job tonight.

300
00:11:01,090 --> 00:11:02,700
-恭喜啊  -我拒绝了
- Congratulations. - I passed.

301
00:11:03,200 --> 00:11:04,210
想让我表扬你吗
You want credit for that?

302
00:11:04,210 --> 00:11:06,270
不是  我想接着做我的本职工作
No, I want to do the job I already have.

303
00:11:07,080 --> 00:11:08,430
接受你的道歉
Apology accepted.

304
00:11:09,400 --> 00:11:10,890
布莱顿·古尔德在挖我们的助理律师
Bratton Gould is poaching our associates,

305
00:11:10,890 --> 00:11:13,510
克拉克  欧文斯  而且还瞄准了我们的
Clark, Owens, but he's also coming after--

306
00:11:13,510 --> 00:11:15,890
客户  特伦特·德文
Our clients. Trent Devon.

307
00:11:15,890 --> 00:11:17,320
有人在他耳边吹风
Someone's whispering in his ear.

308
00:11:17,320 --> 00:11:18,470
艾莉森·霍特
Allison Holt.

309
00:11:18,480 --> 00:11:19,930
一个月前她来律所
She was brought in about a month ago.

310
00:11:19,930 --> 00:11:21,520
当时她准备把你当牺牲品
She was ready to throw you under the bus.

311
00:11:21,520 --> 00:11:23,000
杰西卡赶走了她
And Jessica threw her out.

312
00:11:23,000 --> 00:11:24,470
你觉得她是在报复
So you think she's in this for revenge?

313
00:11:24,470 --> 00:11:25,430
也许
Maybe.

314
00:11:25,450 --> 00:11:27,020
但我们都知道是谁带她进来的
But we both know who brought her in.

315
00:11:27,560 --> 00:11:28,640
哈德曼
Hardman.

316
00:11:29,510 --> 00:11:30,670
你觉得是他
You think this is him?

317
00:11:32,230 --> 00:11:33,400
绝佳视野
Hell of a view.

318
00:11:33,760 --> 00:11:36,000
克拉克和欧文斯不配得到这个
Clark and Owens don't deserve this.

319
00:11:36,270 --> 00:11:39,210
哪个是欧文斯来着  红头发那个吗
Which one is Owens, by the way, the redhead?

320
00:11:39,510 --> 00:11:41,190
你连自己的助理律师都不认识
You don't even know who your associates are,

321
00:11:41,200 --> 00:11:43,650
却来抱怨他们的离开
but you're here to complain about losing them?

322
00:11:43,650 --> 00:11:45,310
你因为被我们解雇怀恨在心吗
You bitter because you were fired?

323
00:11:45,310 --> 00:11:46,660
我没有  哈维
I'm not bitter, Harvey.

324
00:11:47,090 --> 00:11:48,890
我和你不一样  我不会感情用事
Unlike you, I don't take things personally.

325
00:11:48,890 --> 00:11:50,560
顺便说一句  我是对的
And by the way, I was right.

326
00:11:50,570 --> 00:11:53,050
我劝你和解  你和解了
I advised you to settle, and you settled.

327
00:11:53,050 --> 00:11:54,840
你是劝我们律所和解
Your advice was for us to settle,

328
00:11:55,240 --> 00:11:56,590
并让我被吊销执照
and I lose my law license.

329
00:11:56,590 --> 00:11:57,670
我的问题是
And my question is,

330
00:11:57,670 --> 00:12:00,830
那次到底是你的主意还是丹尼尔·哈德曼的
was taking that deal your idea or Daniel Hardman's?

331
00:12:01,190 --> 00:12:02,890
你觉得丹尼尔是幕后推手
You think Daniel's behind this?

332
00:12:02,890 --> 00:12:04,790
六天前你见过他
You met with him six days ago.

333
00:12:05,060 --> 00:12:07,080
我不会问你是怎么知道的
I'm not even gonna ask how you know that.

334
00:12:07,180 --> 00:12:08,610
我告诉过你  杰西卡
I told you before, Jessica.

335
00:12:08,610 --> 00:12:09,880
我是个坦白的人
I'm a straight shooter.

336
00:12:10,540 --> 00:12:12,050
丹尼尔以前没有指挥我
Daniel wasn't dictating my actions then,

337
00:12:12,050 --> 00:12:13,310
现在也没有
and he's not now.

338
00:12:13,740 --> 00:12:16,470
无论如何  我们会提出干扰侵权的控诉
Either way, we are filing a claim for tortious interference.

339
00:12:16,480 --> 00:12:19,610
你在用保密信息挖我们的客户
You're using privileged information to target our clients.

340
00:12:20,070 --> 00:12:21,800
你真的想击鼓鸣冤吗
You really want to cry foul to the ref?

341
00:12:21,990 --> 00:12:23,980
你知道谁最会喊冤吗
You know who went to the ref more than anyone?

342
00:12:23,980 --> 00:12:25,970
迈克尔·乔丹  他安安静静地找裁判
Michael Jordan. He did it quietly.

343
00:12:25,970 --> 00:12:27,700
得到了六个总冠军戒指  
And he got six rings, 

344
00:12:27,700 --> 00:12:30,650
还有  他是我的客户
and he's my client.

345
00:12:30,800 --> 00:12:32,580
那也许我也该打给他
Maybe I should call him too.

346
00:12:32,580 --> 00:12:34,260
你得不到特伦特·德文的
You're not getting Trent Devon.

347
00:12:34,260 --> 00:12:36,710
想走的人你留不住的  哈维
You can't keep people who want to leave, Harvey.

348
00:12:37,130 --> 00:12:39,320
谁都知道你们的内斗
Everybody knows about your civil war.

349
00:12:39,520 --> 00:12:41,590
皮尔逊·哈德曼现在四分五裂
Pearson Hardman is falling apart.

350
00:12:41,820 --> 00:12:43,210
我跟你说
And I'm telling you,

351
00:12:43,900 --> 00:12:45,610
雪崩已经开始
the avalanche has already started.

352
00:12:53,900 --> 00:12:55,330
卡雷尔的合同应该签好之后
The Carillo contracts, they should be signed 

353
00:12:55,330 --> 00:12:56,510
放在我桌子上的
and on my desk.

354
00:12:56,510 --> 00:12:57,370
-我知道  -既然你知道
- I know. - Well, since you're so in the know,

355
00:12:57,370 --> 00:12:59,210
也许你能告诉我  为什么我还没看到
perhaps you can tell me why I don't have them yet.

356
00:12:59,210 --> 00:13:01,810
-因为没签好  -没签好
- Because they're not signed. - Not signed?

357
00:13:01,810 --> 00:13:03,240
我之前打过电话让他们送过来
I called earlier to have them messengered--

358
00:13:03,240 --> 00:13:04,440
你说的这个故事太长了
The story's already taking too long.

359
00:13:04,440 --> 00:13:05,630
然后他们说没必要看合同
And they said they didn't need to see them.

360
00:13:05,630 --> 00:13:06,720
我在等结果
Still waiting.

361
00:13:07,680 --> 00:13:09,370
他们说不再是我们的客户了
They said they're no longer a client.

362
00:13:09,910 --> 00:13:10,760
哈罗德
Harold.

363
00:13:10,760 --> 00:13:12,520
不是  哈罗德没有
No. Harold didn't--

364
00:13:12,530 --> 00:13:14,360
路易  哈罗德没做什么
Louis, Harold didn't do anything.

365
00:13:14,520 --> 00:13:15,600
哈罗德就没做对过
Harold never does anything.

366
00:13:15,600 --> 00:13:17,520
今天一早他就把合同给我了
He got me the contracts first thing this morning.

367
00:13:17,520 --> 00:13:18,820
他通宵工作  那份合同真的很
He worked all night. They were really quite--

368
00:13:18,820 --> 00:13:19,850
不好意思  那份合同真的很
Excuse me. They were really quite--

369
00:13:19,850 --> 00:13:22,110
-很什么  -很好
- "Quite" what? - Good, actually.

370
00:13:22,110 --> 00:13:24,010
你修改过多少处注解
Uh-huh. And how many citations you correct?

371
00:13:24,010 --> 00:13:25,190
-没有  -撒谎
- None. - You're lying.

372
00:13:25,190 --> 00:13:26,670
-我没撒谎  -我不在乎
- No, I'm not. - I don't care.

373
00:13:27,170 --> 00:13:28,930
是个纹身
Wow. Yeah. That is a tattoo.

374
00:13:28,930 --> 00:13:30,610
-很酷吧  -是啊
- It's cool, right? - Yeah.

375
00:13:30,610 --> 00:13:34,390
海牛啊  真是海洋里缓慢温柔的奶牛
Manatee--the slow, gentle cow of the sea.

376
00:13:34,390 --> 00:13:36,800
其实那是鲨鱼
Uh, no. It's a shark actually.

377
00:13:37,520 --> 00:13:38,680
对对对  绝对是
Totally. No--yes.

378
00:13:38,680 --> 00:13:39,800
是鲨鱼
That's a shark.

379
00:13:39,800 --> 00:13:42,940
是个宽大肥的鲨鱼
That is a big, wide, fat shark.

380
00:13:42,940 --> 00:13:44,030
你被解雇了
You're fired.

381
00:13:44,860 --> 00:13:47,120
-你不能解雇迈克  -是你
- You can't fire Mike. - You.

382
00:13:47,120 --> 00:13:49,600
你个笨蛋  连被炒了都不知道
You moron. You can't even get your firing right.

383
00:13:50,630 --> 00:13:52,210
-我被解雇了  -路易  别这样
- I'm fired? - Louis, come on.

384
00:13:52,210 --> 00:13:53,870
打包走人  现在马上
Pack up your things and go. Now.

385
00:13:53,870 --> 00:13:55,300
但你要求的事我都做了啊
But I did everything you asked.

386
00:13:55,300 --> 00:13:56,480
我把合同交到卡雷尔的公司了
I delivered the Carillo contracts.

387
00:13:56,480 --> 00:13:57,510
我不管
I don't care.

388
00:13:57,510 --> 00:14:00,170
客户炒了我们  我就炒了你
The client fired us, and now I'm firing you.

389
00:14:00,420 --> 00:14:01,820
世道艰难啊
Times are tough, people.

390
00:14:01,820 --> 00:14:05,320
我们承受不了错误  承受不了能力不足
We can't afford mistakes. We can't afford incompetence.

391
00:14:05,320 --> 00:14:07,450
做不到的话  就滚吧
You can't cut it, get out.

392
00:14:07,450 --> 00:14:09,890
皮尔逊·哈德曼不需要平庸之辈
There is no place for mediocrity here at Pearson Hardman,

393
00:14:09,890 --> 00:14:12,700
更没有你这种人的立足之处
And there's certainly no place for someone like you.

394
00:14:14,470 --> 00:14:16,200
都回去工作
Everyone else get back to work.

395
00:14:26,650 --> 00:14:28,780
他交代的事我都做了
You know. I didn't just do what he asked for Carillo.

396
00:14:28,790 --> 00:14:29,930
我还多做了很多
I went way beyond.

397
00:14:30,230 --> 00:14:31,420
我什么错都没犯
I didn't make any mistakes,

398
00:14:31,420 --> 00:14:33,520
而且我知道不是因为我客户才离开的
and I know that they're not leaving because of me.

399
00:14:33,520 --> 00:14:34,920
你怎么没跟他说呢
So why didn't you say that to him?

400
00:14:34,920 --> 00:14:37,490
因为他把我吓得动弹不得
Because he makes me freeze.

401
00:14:39,420 --> 00:14:40,450
有时候我真希望
You know, sometimes I wish 

402
00:14:40,450 --> 00:14:42,070
在哈佛的时候我们就认识
we would've known each other at Harvard.

403
00:14:43,380 --> 00:14:46,040
是啊  在哈佛
Yeah. Yeah. Harvard.

404
00:14:46,040 --> 00:14:48,510
你估计都和邓肯那群牛人在一起
You probably hung out with Duncan and those guys.

405
00:14:48,510 --> 00:14:50,770
而我在图书馆奋斗
I hung out with the library.

406
00:14:51,420 --> 00:14:52,830
我真是个废物
I'm such a loser.

407
00:14:52,830 --> 00:14:54,370
你不是  哈罗德
No, you're not, Harold.

408
00:14:54,390 --> 00:14:56,240
郑重说明  邓肯是个二货
Look, for the record, Duncan was a douche.

409
00:14:56,240 --> 00:14:58,080
他是二货
He was a douche.

410
00:14:58,080 --> 00:14:59,840
-绝对的  -二货中的二货
- Totally. - Like a douchy-douche.

411
00:14:59,840 --> 00:15:01,430
你知道他以前
Do you remember that thing he used to do with the--

412
00:15:01,430 --> 00:15:05,000
-我知道  -知道我的意思吧
- I know. - You know what I mean?

413
00:15:06,140 --> 00:15:07,110
对啊  我要说的就是这个
See, that's what I mean.

414
00:15:07,110 --> 00:15:07,910
如果当时我们就认识
If you would've known me there,

415
00:15:07,910 --> 00:15:09,420
这里起码还有一个人知道
then at least someone here would know that

416
00:15:09,420 --> 00:15:10,920
我不是一直这样
I wasn't always like this.

417
00:15:10,920 --> 00:15:13,950
原来同学都会找我帮助他们写论文
People used to come to me for help on their essays.

418
00:15:13,950 --> 00:15:15,780
我们在我公寓里安安静静的
We'd sit in the quiet of my apartment

419
00:15:15,780 --> 00:15:17,170
没人对着我吼
where no one was yelling at me,

420
00:15:17,170 --> 00:15:20,140
我才能思考和写东西
and I could think and write.

421
00:15:20,140 --> 00:15:22,970
-是吗  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.

422
00:15:23,530 --> 00:15:24,530
给你
Here.

423
00:15:26,680 --> 00:15:28,930
这是我在法学院写的第一篇论文
This is the first essay I wrote in law school.

424
00:15:29,150 --> 00:15:30,820
看教授的评语
Look at the professor's comments.

425
00:15:31,790 --> 00:15:33,170
天啊
Holy shit.

426
00:15:33,220 --> 00:15:35,320
路易说得对  我不属于这里
Louis is right. I don't belong here.

427
00:15:36,850 --> 00:15:38,130
不  他错了
No, he's not.

428
00:15:38,290 --> 00:15:39,860
-托马斯  -波克诺山的周末
- Thomas. - Poconos weekend.

429
00:15:39,860 --> 00:15:41,230
-和女朋友  -哪个
- With the girlfriend. - Which one?

430
00:15:41,230 --> 00:15:43,890
-无所谓  -没问题  温特斯
- Doesn't matter. - Done. Winters?

431
00:15:43,890 --> 00:15:45,150
-和市长约个午饭  -坎佩斯
- Lunch with the mayor. - Campos.

432
00:15:45,150 --> 00:15:47,230
-和我吃午饭  -和我还差不多
- Lunch with me. - Lunch with me.

433
00:15:47,230 --> 00:15:48,950
-本森呢  -拳击赛
- Benson? - Box at the garden.

434
00:15:48,950 --> 00:15:50,660
让伦德奎斯特比赛前和他见一面
Have Lundqvist meet him pre-game.

435
00:15:50,660 --> 00:15:51,520
他会愿意吗
Does the king do that?

436
00:15:51,520 --> 00:15:53,360
为我当然愿意  塞尔博斯
He does for me. Siebertz.

437
00:15:53,360 --> 00:15:54,720
-门票  -超级碗的吗
- Tickets. - Super bowl.

438
00:15:54,720 --> 00:15:56,500
-百老汇  -不会吧
- Broadway. - Really?

439
00:15:56,500 --> 00:15:57,630
他那壮硕的胸腔里
Beneath that lumberjack chest

440
00:15:57,630 --> 00:15:59,090
跳的可是颗黄鹂鸟的心
beats the heart of a songbird.

441
00:15:59,090 --> 00:16:00,490
好吧  只要不是《猫》
Fine. Anything but Cats.

442
00:16:00,490 --> 00:16:01,870
《猫》十几年前就停演了
Cats closed over a decade ago.

443
00:16:01,870 --> 00:16:03,440
早该停演了
What took 'em so long?

444
00:16:03,770 --> 00:16:05,630
好了  就这些了
That's it then. We're done.

445
00:16:06,150 --> 00:16:07,160
都搞定了
Closed them all.

446
00:16:07,170 --> 00:16:09,460
前戏罢了  离搞定还早着呢
That's just foreplay. We didn't close shit.

447
00:16:09,460 --> 00:16:11,440
今天我打算和每一个客户
I want to have talked to every one of my clients

448
00:16:11,440 --> 00:16:12,750
都好好聊聊
by the end of the day.

449
00:16:12,750 --> 00:16:15,230
你就负责联系特伦特·德文  直到他接电话
You stay on Trent Devon until he takes the call.

450
00:16:15,230 --> 00:16:16,470
我会的
I will.

451
00:16:16,490 --> 00:16:17,730
哈维
And, Harvey...

452
00:16:18,700 --> 00:16:20,250
没人要离开你
No one is leaving you.

453
00:16:26,100 --> 00:16:26,920
好了
Okay.

454
00:16:26,920 --> 00:16:28,990
哈罗德都快被吓死了
Harold is totally freaked out.

455
00:16:28,990 --> 00:16:30,070
我觉得他快要急上火了
I think he's gonna have an ulcer,

456
00:16:30,070 --> 00:16:32,080
但好消息是他不会再让你失望了
but the good news is he'll never disappoint you again,

457
00:16:32,080 --> 00:16:36,240
你就过去不计前嫌地再雇他回来吧
so you can go and magnanimously hire him back now.

458
00:16:36,240 --> 00:16:37,600
我为什么要雇他回来
Why would I do that?

459
00:16:37,810 --> 00:16:40,170
我不知道  因为你已经达到目的了
Um, I don't know, because you made your point.

460
00:16:40,480 --> 00:16:41,980
你觉得我那是在演戏吗
You think that was a show?

461
00:16:42,520 --> 00:16:44,570
我知道哈罗德有时有点
Look, I know Harold can be...

462
00:16:45,840 --> 00:16:46,690
哈罗德
Harold.

463
00:16:46,690 --> 00:16:48,520
他就是个白痴学者还屁都不懂
He's an idiot savant minus the savant.

464
00:16:48,520 --> 00:16:50,220
他很努力  是个好人
He tries hard. He's a good person.

465
00:16:50,220 --> 00:16:52,030
是吧  那告诉他去加入和平军啊
Yeah, well, then tell him to join the peace corps.

466
00:16:52,480 --> 00:16:54,380
你为什么不能再给他一次机会
Why don't you just give him a second chance?

467
00:16:54,380 --> 00:16:56,890
我早给过了  迈克  他来这儿的第二天
I did, Mike. It was called his second day.

468
00:16:56,890 --> 00:16:58,440
你辞他总得有个理由吧
You realize you need cause, right?

469
00:16:58,440 --> 00:16:59,560
你想要理由
You want a cause?

470
00:16:59,810 --> 00:17:01,580
霍普金斯调解书里他少写了个零
He left a zero off the Hopkins settlement,

471
00:17:01,580 --> 00:17:04,160
害我们客户损失了36万
which cost the client $360,000.

472
00:17:04,160 --> 00:17:05,910
本该发给上级法院的动议
He filed a motion with the appeals court

473
00:17:05,910 --> 00:17:08,530
他发给了上诉法庭
instead of the superior court, 

474
00:17:08,530 --> 00:17:09,980
结果一不小心惹出了一场死刑审查
which accidentally triggered a death penalty review.

475
00:17:09,980 --> 00:17:11,260
然后我唯一一次
And then the one and only time

476
00:17:11,260 --> 00:17:14,010
带他去法庭  他就不在状态
that I take him to court with me, his fly was down,

477
00:17:14,010 --> 00:17:16,930
然后管法官叫"法官主人"
and he called the judge "Your owner."

478
00:17:19,860 --> 00:17:22,140
你知道他为什么会这样吧
You know why he does those things, right?

479
00:17:22,550 --> 00:17:24,190
因为你太吓人了
Because you intimidate him.

480
00:17:24,190 --> 00:17:25,740
你对他太残酷了
You brutalize him.

481
00:17:25,740 --> 00:17:28,090
你总是说你很会培养人才
You're always talking about how great you are at grooming us.

482
00:17:28,090 --> 00:17:29,690
你根本不是在培养他
Well, you were not great at grooming him.

483
00:17:29,690 --> 00:17:31,130
操练军士对他嚷嚷两句他都受不了
If he can't take a drill sergeant yelling at him,

484
00:17:31,130 --> 00:17:32,760
怎么受得了别人对他开枪
how can he handle people shooting at him?

485
00:17:32,760 --> 00:17:34,070
没人要对我们开枪  路易
People don't shoot at us, Louis.

486
00:17:34,070 --> 00:17:35,340
是吗
Don't they?

487
00:17:37,040 --> 00:17:38,650
好吧  不如这样
Okay. You know what?

488
00:17:38,830 --> 00:17:40,180
你想让他留下
You want him to stay...

489
00:17:43,140 --> 00:17:44,680
好  他可以留下
Fine. He can stay.

490
00:17:46,030 --> 00:17:47,080
谢谢
Thank you.

491
00:17:47,080 --> 00:17:48,420
有个条件
One condition.

492
00:17:48,540 --> 00:17:50,010
就像我以前做的
You personally guarantee

493
00:17:50,020 --> 00:17:51,500
哈罗德从这办公室里
every piece of work product

494
00:17:51,500 --> 00:17:52,900
发出的每份工作文件
that Harold sends out of this office

495
00:17:52,900 --> 00:17:54,160
都由你个人负责
just like I have.

496
00:17:54,380 --> 00:17:55,370
他的所有工作由你检查
You check everything he does.

497
00:17:55,370 --> 00:17:56,830
要细致入微
You cross every "t," dot every "i,"

498
00:17:56,830 --> 00:17:58,840
同时还得完成哈维给你的工作
and still do everything you have to for Harvey.

499
00:17:59,750 --> 00:18:02,610
可能没人冲我们开枪  但我们是在打仗
People may not be shooting at us, but we are at war.

500
00:18:03,170 --> 00:18:04,740
怎么样
So how does that work for you?

501
00:18:05,590 --> 00:18:06,620
成交吗
Do we have a deal?

502
00:18:15,520 --> 00:18:16,690
哈罗德
Harold.

503
00:18:19,420 --> 00:18:21,610
我就是来祝你一切顺利
I was just coming by to wish you well.

504
00:18:21,610 --> 00:18:23,910
多谢  瑞秋  不过我觉得应该没事的
Thanks, Rachel, but I think it's gonna be okay.

505
00:18:23,910 --> 00:18:25,760
迈克在和路易谈呢
Mike's talking to Louis right now.

506
00:18:25,760 --> 00:18:26,910
是吗
Really?

507
00:18:26,910 --> 00:18:28,150
太好了
That's great.

508
00:18:34,360 --> 00:18:35,270
怎么样
Well?

509
00:18:42,550 --> 00:18:44,010
我无能为力
There was nothing I could do.

510
00:18:45,700 --> 00:18:48,980
没关系  我知道你尽力了  迈克
It's okay. I know you tried, Mike.

511
00:18:49,570 --> 00:18:51,180
如果能让你感觉好点
If it'll make you feel better,

512
00:18:51,620 --> 00:18:54,030
其实这周不止辞了你一个
you're not the only person being let go this week.

513
00:18:54,040 --> 00:18:56,780
克拉克和欧文斯被辞退
Well, Clark and Owens are only getting let go

514
00:18:56,780 --> 00:18:58,170
是因为有人发现
because someone found out that they're moving

515
00:18:58,170 --> 00:19:00,260
他们要和麦肯尼和克莱恩跳槽到布莱顿·古尔德
to Bratton Gould with Mckinney and Kline.

516
00:19:00,260 --> 00:19:01,950
-真的吗  -是啊  我听到的
- They are? - Yeah, I overheard it.

517
00:19:01,950 --> 00:19:05,530
还真是大难临头各自飞啊
I guess some people will choose any port in a storm.

518
00:19:06,180 --> 00:19:09,240
哈罗德  祝你好运
Harold, good luck.

519
00:19:10,450 --> 00:19:11,530
你也是
You too.

520
00:19:24,500 --> 00:19:26,700
-真糟糕  -是啊
- This sucks. - It does.

521
00:19:26,930 --> 00:19:28,740
不该这样的
He didn't deserve that.

522
00:19:33,910 --> 00:19:35,270
艾莉森还在挖人
Allison's not done.

523
00:19:35,270 --> 00:19:37,150
我知道  我们在联系客户了
We know. We're working all the clients.

524
00:19:37,150 --> 00:19:39,390
不  不止客户  她把麦肯尼和克莱恩都挖走了
No, it's more than that. She's taking Mckinney and Kline.

525
00:19:39,390 --> 00:19:40,600
不过两个助理罢了
It's just two more associates.

526
00:19:40,600 --> 00:19:42,040
不  没那么简单
No, it's more than that.

527
00:19:45,050 --> 00:19:46,470
我跟你说人都开溜了
I tell you the rats are jumping ship,

528
00:19:46,470 --> 00:19:47,910
你还跟没事人似的  唐娜点个头
and you say it's fine, but Donna nods,

529
00:19:47,910 --> 00:19:49,420
你就一副大难临头的样子了
and you're busting out life jackets?

530
00:19:49,420 --> 00:19:50,670
你没事也爱瞎恐慌
You have a history of panicking.

531
00:19:50,670 --> 00:19:52,030
他不是瞎恐慌
He's not panicking.

532
00:19:52,030 --> 00:19:53,730
克拉克  欧文斯  麦肯尼  克莱恩
Clark, Owens, Mckinney, Kline--

533
00:19:53,730 --> 00:19:55,120
他们不止是入职五年的助理
These aren't just associates.

534
00:19:55,130 --> 00:19:56,050
入职五年的助理里他们是最好的
They're the best fifth-years.

535
00:19:56,050 --> 00:19:57,920
他们是路易最早管的一班助理了
They're Louis's first class of associates.

536
00:19:57,920 --> 00:19:59,740
他给她通风报信了
He gave her a report card?

537
00:19:59,940 --> 00:20:01,920
哈维  你别乱想
Harvey, you do not know that.

538
00:20:01,920 --> 00:20:03,840
那我现在就去搞明白
Well, I'm gonna goddamn find out.

539
00:20:06,520 --> 00:20:07,210
别
Stop.

540
00:20:07,210 --> 00:20:08,890
别说了
Just cut it out.

541
00:20:08,890 --> 00:20:10,310
我回头跟你说
All right, I'll talk to you later.

542
00:20:10,310 --> 00:20:11,360
再见
Bye.

543
00:20:11,360 --> 00:20:13,170
我一直不喜欢你  路易
I never liked you, Louis.

544
00:20:13,170 --> 00:20:15,050
你就是一只吱吱乱叫总想着报复的死耗子
You're a vindictive, sniveling rat,

545
00:20:15,050 --> 00:20:17,590
但我从没料到你会背叛你自己的公司
but I never thought you'd betray your own firm.

546
00:20:18,090 --> 00:20:19,300
我从来没背叛过公司
I never betrayed this firm.

547
00:20:19,300 --> 00:20:21,040
那你帮艾莉森·霍特挖我们的助理
What do you call helping Allison Holt

548
00:20:21,040 --> 00:20:22,220
算怎么回事
poach our associates?

549
00:20:22,220 --> 00:20:24,270
我可没做这种事
I had nothing to do with that.

550
00:20:24,270 --> 00:20:25,640
我爱这家公司  哈维
I love this firm, Harvey.

551
00:20:25,640 --> 00:20:27,290
你投票给哈德曼的时候就是个叛徒
You were a traitor when you voted for Hardman,

552
00:20:27,290 --> 00:20:28,560
现在也是个叛徒
And you're a traitor now.

553
00:20:28,560 --> 00:20:29,640
我跟你说过
Like I've told you before,

554
00:20:29,640 --> 00:20:31,410
这家公司里投给哈德曼的不止我一个
I'm not the only one in this firm who voted for Hardman.

555
00:20:31,410 --> 00:20:33,280
我知道后也把他投出去了
And I voted to oust him once I knew.

556
00:20:33,280 --> 00:20:35,170
知道你要自顾不暇了
Once you knew you had to save your own ass.

557
00:20:35,170 --> 00:20:36,750
够了  哈维  出去
All right, you know what, Harvey, just get out.

558
00:20:37,830 --> 00:20:39,050
出去
Get out.

559
00:20:40,180 --> 00:20:42,890
我没做错什么
Ri-- I did nothing wrong.

560
00:20:44,140 --> 00:20:45,360
天哪
Jesus!

561
00:20:45,790 --> 00:20:47,300
你监听我的办公室
You bugged my office.

562
00:20:47,300 --> 00:20:49,720
你跑去跟哈德曼说了科斯特尔汽车公司案
You ran to Hardman about the CM lawsuit.

563
00:20:49,720 --> 00:20:51,900
你为了成为资深合伙人不惜一切
You sold your soul for senior partnership.

564
00:20:51,900 --> 00:20:54,650
上位后立马搞了个药检规定
And once you got it, you created a drug policy

565
00:20:54,650 --> 00:20:57,340
就为了把我赶出去
with the sole purpose of firing me!

566
00:20:57,340 --> 00:20:58,290
我那是替哈德曼做的
I did it for Hardman.

567
00:20:58,300 --> 00:20:59,670
就算是哈德曼要整死我
Maybe Hardman wanted me dead,

568
00:20:59,670 --> 00:21:02,050
但是你跑出去买了把枪
but you're the one who went out, got the gun, 

569
00:21:02,050 --> 00:21:05,020
瞄准了我  冲我开枪的
aimed it, and fired it at my head.

570
00:21:05,020 --> 00:21:06,250
我最后不是自食其果了吗
And it blew up in my face!

571
00:21:06,250 --> 00:21:08,530
那要是没那样呢
And what would have happened if it didn't?

572
00:21:10,330 --> 00:21:11,590
我那是奉命而为
I was under orders.

573
00:21:11,590 --> 00:21:13,140
你跑去跟哈德曼说莫妮卡·伊顿时
Were you also under orders when you ran

574
00:21:13,140 --> 00:21:14,890
也是奉命而为吗
to Hardman about Monica Eton?

575
00:21:16,140 --> 00:21:17,120
你怎么知道那是我干的
How do you know it was me?

576
00:21:17,130 --> 00:21:19,140
因为那是我设的局
Because I set it up!

577
00:21:20,210 --> 00:21:22,270
因为我知道你是个什么人
Because I know who you are!

578
00:21:23,650 --> 00:21:25,270
你还打算继续跟我说
Are you still gonna tell me

579
00:21:25,270 --> 00:21:26,670
你没有帮艾莉森吗
you're not helping Allison?

580
00:21:26,670 --> 00:21:29,020
哈维  我向上帝发誓
Harvey, I swear to god

581
00:21:29,020 --> 00:21:30,410
我没帮她
I did not do this.

582
00:21:31,820 --> 00:21:32,720
也许吧
Maybe not.

583
00:21:32,720 --> 00:21:34,810
但事已至此
But now that you've done what you've done,

584
00:21:34,810 --> 00:21:36,920
我不会再相信你了
I will never trust you.

585
00:21:41,040 --> 00:21:42,790
皮尔逊·哈德曼是我的一切
Pearson Hardman is my life.

586
00:21:43,230 --> 00:21:45,430
从现在起  事实摆在这里
Well, here's what's gonna happen from now on.

587
00:21:46,380 --> 00:21:49,640
你和我  我们玩完了
You and I, we're done.

588
00:21:50,510 --> 00:21:52,250
不用来我办公室了
Don't drop by my office.

589
00:21:52,760 --> 00:21:54,720
也别想唐娜那里套情报
Don't ask Donna for information.

590
00:21:54,720 --> 00:21:56,150
没人想留你
You're the guy that nobody wants

591
00:21:56,150 --> 00:21:57,750
但又赶不走
but we can't get rid of.

592
00:22:00,340 --> 00:22:02,190
我是资深合伙人
I'm a senior partner.

593
00:22:03,070 --> 00:22:04,890
所以我赶不走你
So I can't make you leave.

594
00:22:04,890 --> 00:22:06,670
但对我来讲
But as far as I'm concerned,

595
00:22:07,200 --> 00:22:09,180
你不在这工作了
you don't even work here anymore.

596
00:22:30,420 --> 00:22:32,600
你看着好消沉啊
That glass does not look half-full.

597
00:22:39,440 --> 00:22:41,410
你在挑我们最好的助理
You're cherry-picking Pearson Hardman associates.

598
00:22:41,410 --> 00:22:42,720
我当然只要最好的
I only want the best cherries.

599
00:22:42,720 --> 00:22:44,830
那为什么不挑他们的培养者呢
Then why not go after the gardener who grew 'em?

600
00:22:46,920 --> 00:22:48,810
你想离开皮尔逊·哈德曼了
You want to leave Pearson Hardman.

601
00:22:48,810 --> 00:22:51,620
众所周知我很能赚钱
I'm a proven commodity who delivers outstanding billables.

602
00:22:51,620 --> 00:22:53,270
还有无人能比的金融知识
With an unparalleled knowledge of finance.

603
00:22:53,280 --> 00:22:55,550
我清楚你是什么人  路易
Yeah, I'm well aware of who you are, Louis.

604
00:22:56,430 --> 00:22:57,940
但我怎么知道你不是
But how do I know that Harvey Specter

605
00:22:57,940 --> 00:22:59,230
哈维·斯佩克派来的呢
didn't just send you here?

606
00:22:59,230 --> 00:23:01,310
因为哈维·斯佩克绝不会信任我
'Cause I'm the last person that Harvey Specter would trust.

607
00:23:01,310 --> 00:23:02,460
你可以去问丹尼尔·哈德曼
Just ask Daniel Hardman.

608
00:23:02,460 --> 00:23:04,460
我问了  他说你背叛了他
I did. He said you betrayed him.

609
00:23:05,220 --> 00:23:07,560
我说了  我清楚你是什么人
Like I said, I am well aware of who you are.

610
00:23:07,560 --> 00:23:09,190
你要是和丹尼尔聊过了  你还应该知道
Well, if you spoke to Daniel, then you would know

611
00:23:09,190 --> 00:23:11,570
他失去事务所不是因为我背叛了他
that he lost Pearson Hardman not because of my betrayal

612
00:23:11,570 --> 00:23:12,880
而是他自己的错
but because of his own.

613
00:23:12,880 --> 00:23:15,420
我不是见风使舵的人
My loyalty does not sway with the wind.

614
00:23:17,220 --> 00:23:18,430
我想离开皮尔逊·哈德曼
I'm leaving Pearson Hardman

615
00:23:18,430 --> 00:23:20,260
是因为那里我待不下去了
because there's no room for me there anymore.

616
00:23:20,640 --> 00:23:21,620
你去哪儿都行啊
You could go anywhere.

617
00:23:21,620 --> 00:23:23,150
我可做足了功课
Well, I've done my homework.

618
00:23:23,150 --> 00:23:26,780
你们正在扩张  雇用条件也不错
You guys are expanding. You are hiring well.

619
00:23:26,790 --> 00:23:29,340
你们招的新人
You're gonna have a young staff

620
00:23:29,340 --> 00:23:30,720
也需要指导
that needs guidance.

621
00:23:30,790 --> 00:23:32,530
你知道我最合适
You know that I'm the right fit.

622
00:23:32,530 --> 00:23:34,030
而且我现在就想走
And I want to move now.

623
00:23:34,040 --> 00:23:35,570
你还有非竞争条款呢
You have a non-compete clause.

624
00:23:35,570 --> 00:23:37,080
杰西卡会放弃非竞争条款
Jessica is gonna waive the non-compete

625
00:23:37,080 --> 00:23:38,460
只要我不带客户走
as long as I don't take clients.

626
00:23:38,460 --> 00:23:40,640
-要是我就不会放弃  -你又不是她
- I wouldn't if I were her. - Well, you're not.

627
00:23:41,740 --> 00:23:42,830
哈维想把我赶走
Harvey wants me gone,

628
00:23:42,830 --> 00:23:45,850
一般他要什么有什么  所以
and he has a way of getting what he wants, so--

629
00:23:49,170 --> 00:23:51,800
可能有个合伙人的位置给你
There might be a partnership position for you.

630
00:23:53,670 --> 00:23:55,600
资深合伙人
Senior partnership.

631
00:23:56,040 --> 00:23:57,600
那就得靠你努力了
That, you're gonna have to earn.

632
00:23:57,600 --> 00:23:58,800
我已经努力过了
I have earned it.

633
00:23:58,800 --> 00:24:01,530
我可不会放弃我一生的追求
And I'm not giving up what I've worked for my whole life.

634
00:24:01,800 --> 00:24:04,250
路易  你犯了个战术错误
Louis, you have made a tactical error.

635
00:24:04,600 --> 00:24:05,910
你已经把底牌亮给我了
You've shown me all your cards,

636
00:24:05,910 --> 00:24:07,550
你不能带来任何客户
you can't offer any clients,

637
00:24:07,550 --> 00:24:09,020
你被迫离开一个
And you're being forced to leave a place

638
00:24:09,020 --> 00:24:10,040
不想要你的地方
that doesn't want you.

639
00:24:10,040 --> 00:24:13,360
你很适合我们律所
You are a very good fit for us.

640
00:24:13,470 --> 00:24:15,040
若你想要加入我们
But if you want to join us,

641
00:24:15,830 --> 00:24:18,920
就得证明你有多渴望
you're gonna have to prove how much you want it.

642
00:24:18,920 --> 00:24:19,990
别这样
Please don't do this.

643
00:24:19,990 --> 00:24:22,550
哪样  我只是在跟你商量
Do what? I'm just negotiating.

644
00:24:22,880 --> 00:24:24,470
你在那里徒具虚名
You have an empty title.

645
00:24:26,220 --> 00:24:28,900
来我们这儿的话  我保证
If you come with us, I promise

646
00:24:29,780 --> 00:24:32,810
你将受到重视
that you will be truly valued.

647
00:24:42,450 --> 00:24:43,280
搞定了
Well, that's it.

648
00:24:43,280 --> 00:24:45,370
除了特伦特·德文  其他客户我都谈过了
I've talked to every client except Trent Devon.

649
00:24:45,370 --> 00:24:46,600
我知道为什么他回艾莉森电话
Well, I know why he's returning

650
00:24:46,610 --> 00:24:47,930
却不理你了
Allison's calls instead of yours.

651
00:24:47,930 --> 00:24:49,270
因为他觉得我们不够专攻
Because he thinks we're not focused.

652
00:24:49,270 --> 00:24:50,360
还不止
That's not enough.

653
00:24:50,360 --> 00:24:52,520
快点  你叫我常问...
Come on. You taught me to always ask...

654
00:24:52,560 --> 00:24:53,620
对他有什么好处
What's in it for him?

655
00:24:53,620 --> 00:24:55,250
"如果我们要扩大市场
"If we're looking to expand our reach,

656
00:24:55,250 --> 00:24:56,780
那特伦特·德文公司的数据平台
then Trent Devon's data platform

657
00:24:56,780 --> 00:24:59,980
和我们的搜索算法简直是天作之合"
provides the perfect symbiosis with our search algorithms."

658
00:24:59,980 --> 00:25:03,880
第23页  闪光起点总裁说的
Page 23, the CEO of Flash-Start.

659
00:25:04,000 --> 00:25:05,450
艾莉森不是他们的代表律师
Allison doesn't represent them.

660
00:25:05,450 --> 00:25:07,680
{\an8}网上即时通讯软件

661
00:25:05,450 --> 00:25:07,680
谷歌用一亿美元收购了米博
Google bought Meebo for $100 million.

662
00:25:07,680 --> 00:25:10,500
艾莉森在对闪光起点做相同的事
Allison is trying to do the same thing with Flash-Start.

663
00:25:10,500 --> 00:25:12,070
艾莉森不是他们的代表律师
Allison doesn't represent them.

664
00:25:12,070 --> 00:25:13,760
假设她是
Pretend she does.

665
00:25:15,020 --> 00:25:16,990
特伦特拿到一亿美元
Trent gets $100 million,

666
00:25:17,000 --> 00:25:18,330
但他的公司却被人生吞活剥了
but his company gets swallowed up,

667
00:25:18,330 --> 00:25:19,250
这可不是他想要的
and that's not what he wants.

668
00:25:19,250 --> 00:25:20,620
要是他们让他同时运营两家公司呢
Well, what if they let him run both companies?

669
00:25:20,620 --> 00:25:21,670
那这笔交易也好得太不真实了
That's too good to be true.

670
00:25:21,670 --> 00:25:23,190
有过先例
It's happened before.

671
00:25:23,730 --> 00:25:25,080
如果是真的  我们只要
So if that's true, all we need to do

672
00:25:25,080 --> 00:25:26,630
想办法找出更好的交易
is figure out a way to beat that deal.

673
00:25:26,630 --> 00:25:28,350
我们没法找到
We can't beat that deal.

674
00:25:29,650 --> 00:25:31,070
好吧  那怎么办
Okay. So what do we do?

675
00:25:39,670 --> 00:25:40,840
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you just tell me?

676
00:25:40,840 --> 00:25:42,270
艾莉森说你俩有过节
Allison said you had a history

677
00:25:42,280 --> 00:25:45,010
也许你会对这笔交易从中作梗
and that it might get in the way of what she was offering.

678
00:25:45,130 --> 00:25:47,120
-闪光起点  -不错
- Flash-Start. - Very good.

679
00:25:47,120 --> 00:25:48,690
但艾莉森不是他们的代表律师
But Allison doesn't represent them.

680
00:25:48,690 --> 00:25:50,780
的确  但她是某一对冲基金的代理人
No, but she does represent a hedge fund

681
00:25:50,780 --> 00:25:53,180
而这个基金将会控股闪光
that's about to buy a controlling interest.

682
00:25:53,180 --> 00:25:54,120
让我猜猜
And let me guess.

683
00:25:54,120 --> 00:25:55,950
他们要你来管理两家公司
They want you to run the whole thing.

684
00:25:56,400 --> 00:25:57,890
我们将和谷歌一较高下
We'll take on Google.

685
00:25:58,270 --> 00:25:59,760
让我猜猜
And let me guess.

686
00:25:59,800 --> 00:26:01,110
你们想来破坏这笔交易
You're here to try and beat it.

687
00:26:01,110 --> 00:26:03,560
不  我来让你接受这笔交易
No, I'm here to tell you to take it.

688
00:26:03,560 --> 00:26:04,540
换作我是你  我就会接受
If I were you, I would,

689
00:26:04,540 --> 00:26:06,460
我还会聘请那个向我提出这笔交易的律师
and I would hire the lawyer who brought it to me.

690
00:26:07,860 --> 00:26:08,710
谢了  哈维
Thanks, Harvey.

691
00:26:08,710 --> 00:26:10,030
不客气
You're welcome.

692
00:26:10,280 --> 00:26:11,860
就一个问题
There's just one thing.

693
00:26:14,190 --> 00:26:16,060
我在想  这事对她有什么好处
I wonder, what's in it for her?

694
00:26:16,060 --> 00:26:16,960
你什么意思
What are you implying?

695
00:26:16,960 --> 00:26:19,220
容我用业余时间看一下这笔交易
Let me look over the deal. My own time.

696
00:26:19,360 --> 00:26:21,580
要真如她所说这么好  我会告诉你
If it is what she says it is, I'll tell you.

697
00:26:21,590 --> 00:26:23,430
不是的话  你也会想知道的
If it's not, you'll want to know.

698
00:26:23,430 --> 00:26:24,720
-哈维  我跟你说过了  -听着
- Harvey, I already told you-- - Look.

699
00:26:24,720 --> 00:26:26,240
你说我们不够专攻
You said we weren't focused,

700
00:26:26,240 --> 00:26:28,430
我来也不是为了说服你这点
and I'm not here to try to convince you that we were.

701
00:26:28,430 --> 00:26:30,610
但你也说过你一直很信任我
But you also said you've always trusted me,

702
00:26:30,610 --> 00:26:33,680
那就请你再信我一次
and I'm telling you, trust me one more time.

703
00:26:39,960 --> 00:26:42,770
路易  有什么事吗
Louis. Do you need something?

704
00:26:42,770 --> 00:26:44,080
事实上  有
Actually, yes.

705
00:26:48,610 --> 00:26:50,140
我要你免除我的非竞争条款
I need you to waive my non-compete,

706
00:26:50,140 --> 00:26:52,480
这样我就能另谋高就了
so I can take a position at another firm.

707
00:26:54,560 --> 00:26:55,440
布莱顿·古尔德
Bratton Gould.

708
00:26:55,450 --> 00:26:58,750
我跟艾莉森·霍特挖墙脚的事完全没关系
I had nothing to do with Allison Holt's poaching.

709
00:26:58,750 --> 00:27:00,270
她开给你什么条件
What did she offer you?

710
00:27:03,310 --> 00:27:04,570
是我去找她的
I went to her.

711
00:27:05,360 --> 00:27:06,330
为什么
Why?

712
00:27:06,330 --> 00:27:09,950
我明白哈维的意思
I got Harvey's message.

713
00:27:10,090 --> 00:27:11,350
什么意思
What message?

714
00:27:12,710 --> 00:27:16,060
你不知道吗  也无所谓了
You don't know? It doesn't matter.

715
00:27:16,060 --> 00:27:17,340
这就是他想要的
This is what he wants.

716
00:27:17,340 --> 00:27:19,050
这也是你想要的吗
And this is what you want?

717
00:27:22,740 --> 00:27:24,160
你知道不能带走客户的
You know you can't take clients.

718
00:27:24,160 --> 00:27:27,730
就算能我也不会带走
Oh, I wouldn't even if I could.

719
00:27:28,800 --> 00:27:30,340
我无意损害我们律所的利益
I have no desire to hurt our firm--

720
00:27:30,340 --> 00:27:32,490
你的律所
your firm.

721
00:27:33,310 --> 00:27:35,480
你知道我为什么要制定
Do you know why I instituted

722
00:27:35,480 --> 00:27:38,200
路易·利特重整旗鼓吗
the Louis Litt Rehabilitation Program?

723
00:27:38,740 --> 00:27:41,890
因为我也曾受到丹尼尔·哈德曼的利诱
Because I was seduced by Daniel Hardman once too.

724
00:27:42,150 --> 00:27:45,100
他让我觉得自己聪明又特别
He made me feel special and smart

725
00:27:46,440 --> 00:27:47,150
而且受人重视
and valued.

726
00:27:48,370 --> 00:27:49,700
问题在于
The problem was

727
00:27:49,860 --> 00:27:52,290
他其实根本不在乎我
he really didn't give a sh-- about me.

728
00:27:53,110 --> 00:27:55,420
但有一点我同意他
But I will give him one thing.

729
00:27:56,080 --> 00:27:57,700
他对你的看法
He was right about you.

730
00:27:59,890 --> 00:28:01,970
你值得高级合伙人的资格
You deserve a senior partnership.

731
00:28:07,660 --> 00:28:09,880
我会放你走  路易
I'm gonna let you go, Louis.

732
00:28:11,070 --> 00:28:12,560
声明一下
Just for the record,

733
00:28:12,610 --> 00:28:15,430
我不同意哈维的意见
I am not on the same page as Harvey.

734
00:28:17,050 --> 00:28:18,520
我不希望你走
I don't want you to go.

735
00:28:34,800 --> 00:28:35,680
怎么
What?

736
00:28:35,680 --> 00:28:37,060
我们真要放弃
Were we really quitting,

737
00:28:37,060 --> 00:28:38,950
还是只是为了拿到合同才这么做的
or was that just a move to get to the contract?

738
00:28:38,950 --> 00:28:40,880
你觉得我其实不在乎什么对他最有利吗
You don't think I have his best interests at heart?

739
00:28:40,880 --> 00:28:41,970
我没问这个
That's not what I asked.

740
00:28:41,980 --> 00:28:43,500
要真是笔好交易  他应该接受
If it's a good deal, he should take it.

741
00:28:43,500 --> 00:28:44,940
但你说这笔交易好得不真实
But you said it's too good to be true.

742
00:28:44,950 --> 00:28:46,360
我还说什么了
What else did I say?

743
00:28:46,930 --> 00:28:48,240
我的工作就是协助你
That it's my job to help you.

744
00:28:48,240 --> 00:28:49,290
那你要做什么呢
So what are you gonna do?

745
00:28:49,290 --> 00:28:50,680
我要去查清楚到底有什么猫腻
I'm gonna go find out what's too good about it.

746
00:28:50,690 --> 00:28:51,580
再见  迈克
Good-bye, Mike.

747
00:28:51,580 --> 00:28:52,790
你想怎么放弃都行
Hey, you can quit all you want,

748
00:28:52,790 --> 00:28:54,570
但特伦特·德文是不会离开的
but Trent Devon is not leaving.

749
00:28:54,570 --> 00:28:56,970
真是场愉快的谈话
Okay. Good talk.

750
00:29:09,390 --> 00:29:12,090
你认得我是谁  混蛋
Yeah. You know who I am, asshole.

751
00:29:12,100 --> 00:29:13,520
-我很抱歉  -抱歉什么
- I'm sorry. Okay? - For what?

752
00:29:13,520 --> 00:29:14,820
上了我老婆吗
Sleeping with my wife?

753
00:29:15,190 --> 00:29:17,090
怎么  你要说不是故意的吗
What, you didn't do it on purpose?

754
00:29:17,090 --> 00:29:18,220
已经结束了
It's over. Okay?

755
00:29:18,220 --> 00:29:20,200
-我向天发誓  -你以为就这么简单吗
- I swear to God. - You think it's that easy?

756
00:29:23,390 --> 00:29:25,250
我不接受你的道歉
Keep your goddamn apology,

757
00:29:25,500 --> 00:29:27,390
给我离苔丝远一点
and stay the hell away from Tess!

758
00:30:16,240 --> 00:30:17,820
天哪  你怎么了
Oh, my God. What the hell happened to you?

759
00:30:17,820 --> 00:30:20,010
我不想说
Oh, I don't want to talk about it.

760
00:30:20,480 --> 00:30:22,300
跟我来  立刻
With me. Now.

761
00:30:24,030 --> 00:30:26,830
这不是厨房里的急救箱
This isn't the first-aid kit from the kitchen.

762
00:30:26,830 --> 00:30:28,770
用别人的抗菌药膏吗
Use other people's antibacterial cream?

763
00:30:28,770 --> 00:30:31,100
我还不如直接让自己染上葡萄球菌呢
Please, I might as well give myself a staph infection.

764
00:30:31,430 --> 00:30:33,210
这是抗菌的
It's antibacterial.

765
00:30:33,520 --> 00:30:34,740
他们就想让你这么想
That's what they want you to believe.

766
00:30:34,740 --> 00:30:36,980
-但你也还在用啊  -闭嘴
- But you're using it. - Shh.

767
00:30:37,790 --> 00:30:39,130
看来还是会瘀青
Looks like it's gonna bruise.

768
00:30:39,130 --> 00:30:42,220
没事的  这不过是
Oh, look, I'm sure it's gonna be fine, it's--

769
00:30:44,360 --> 00:30:45,870
你怎么知道如何处理伤口
How do you know how to do this?

770
00:30:47,770 --> 00:30:49,300
布鲁诺以前常跟37楼的
Bruno used to get into these fights

771
00:30:49,310 --> 00:30:51,990
那只缅因猫打架
with this Maine Coon on the 37th floor.

772
00:30:53,780 --> 00:30:54,830
名字叫南瓜
Pumpkin.

773
00:31:00,320 --> 00:31:01,580
-我不需要  -给你
- No, I don't need it. - Here you go.

774
00:31:01,580 --> 00:31:03,000
-我不要纸巾  -你确定吗
- I don't need tissues. - Are you sure?

775
00:31:03,000 --> 00:31:04,270
把纸巾放下
Put them down.

776
00:31:07,040 --> 00:31:08,510
你准备告诉我发生什么事了吗
Are you gonna tell me what happened?

777
00:31:09,810 --> 00:31:11,250
这儿可是纽约  我被人偷袭了
It's New York. I got jumped.

778
00:31:11,250 --> 00:31:12,230
没报警吗
Didn't you call 911?

779
00:31:12,230 --> 00:31:14,040
让警察过来问一大堆问题
To have the police come and ask a million questions

780
00:31:14,050 --> 00:31:15,750
却永远都抓不到那人吗
about a guy who they're never gonna catch?

781
00:31:15,750 --> 00:31:17,000
不了  谢谢
No, thanks.

782
00:31:17,560 --> 00:31:18,680
你认识他
You knew him.

783
00:31:22,200 --> 00:31:25,430
这么说吧  做事要承担后果
Let's just say that actions have consequences.

784
00:31:26,120 --> 00:31:27,110
好吧
Okay.

785
00:31:27,890 --> 00:31:31,390
我明白
I get it. Yeah, I get that.

786
00:31:32,010 --> 00:31:34,380
要谈谈你拿着的那个盒子吗
We gonna talk about that box you were carrying?

787
00:31:34,610 --> 00:31:36,250
天呐  什么盒子
Oh, man. What box?

788
00:31:36,250 --> 00:31:39,230
装满你办公室里个人物品的盒子
The box full of personal things from your office?

789
00:31:39,230 --> 00:31:42,020
正如你所说  做事要承担后果
Like you said, actions have consequences.

790
00:31:43,310 --> 00:31:46,230
杰西卡把你开除了
Jessica fired you.

791
00:31:46,230 --> 00:31:48,860
-她请我留下  -是吗
- She asked me to stay. - She did?

792
00:31:48,860 --> 00:31:49,640
是的  因为她知道
Yeah, because she knows

793
00:31:49,640 --> 00:31:51,110
我绝不会出卖这家律所
that I would never sell out this firm.

794
00:31:51,120 --> 00:31:52,410
那我就不明白了  你在
Well, then I don't understand, what are you--

795
00:31:52,410 --> 00:31:54,150
迈克  还要我说出来吗
Mike, do I have to spell it out for you?

796
00:31:54,430 --> 00:31:56,720
你可是哈维的左右手  他讨厌我
You're Harvey's right hand. He hates me.

797
00:31:56,720 --> 00:31:58,700
那又如何  杰西卡才是老板
So? Jessica's the boss.

798
00:31:59,080 --> 00:32:00,570
而且哈维向来都很讨厌你
Come on, Harvey's always hated you.

799
00:32:00,570 --> 00:32:02,360
其实不是的
No, actually.

800
00:32:02,410 --> 00:32:04,510
哈维并非一直很讨厌我
Harvey hasn't always hated me.

801
00:32:05,280 --> 00:32:07,130
我俩从来都不是兔八哥和埃尔默
We were never Elmer and Bugs.

802
00:32:07,950 --> 00:32:11,960
我们是  拉尔夫和山姆
We were... Ralph and Sam.

803
00:32:12,060 --> 00:32:12,790
谁
Who?

804
00:32:12,790 --> 00:32:14,480
大灰狼拉尔夫和牧羊犬山姆
Ralph Wolf and Sam Sheepdog.

805
00:32:14,480 --> 00:32:15,790
卡通人物吗
The cartoon characters?

806
00:32:15,790 --> 00:32:16,990
是的
Yeah.

807
00:32:17,140 --> 00:32:20,560
他们每天都开开心心一起到牧场上班
They came to the meadow every day to work, friendly.

808
00:32:20,560 --> 00:32:22,670
但是上班打完卡之后
But then when they punched in the time clock,

809
00:32:22,670 --> 00:32:24,260
大灰狼就会去偷羊
Ralph would try to steal the sheep,

810
00:32:24,260 --> 00:32:25,710
牧羊犬就会阻止它
and Sam would stop him.

811
00:32:25,710 --> 00:32:28,770
的确很残忍
I mean, it was brutal.

812
00:32:29,710 --> 00:32:31,380
接着他们又下班打卡  恩怨尽消
And then they'd punch out again.

813
00:32:32,230 --> 00:32:33,300
还是朋友
Friends.

814
00:32:34,420 --> 00:32:36,000
我和哈维就是如此
And that was me and Harvey.

815
00:32:37,590 --> 00:32:39,570
哈维不再打卡下班了
Harvey's not punching out anymore.

816
00:32:39,860 --> 00:32:42,620
我无法每天走进律所
And I can't walk in here every day

817
00:32:42,620 --> 00:32:46,190
明知要跟一个鄙视自己的人
knowing that I'm gonna be working side by side

818
00:32:46,190 --> 00:32:47,370
一起上班
next to somebody who despises me.

819
00:32:47,370 --> 00:32:49,000
我就是  不行  迈克
I just-- Mike, I can't.

820
00:32:51,430 --> 00:32:54,520
路易  如果做事要承担后果
Louis, if actions have consequences,

821
00:32:54,520 --> 00:32:57,940
那也许你能做些事来补偿
then maybe actions can redeem you.

822
00:32:57,940 --> 00:33:00,010
不  太晚了
No, it's too late for that.

823
00:33:01,400 --> 00:33:03,320
他已经将我打入地狱了
Die's been already cast.

824
00:33:03,930 --> 00:33:05,860
{\an8}外伤用药

825
00:33:03,930 --> 00:33:05,860
给你  你方便的时候可以还我
Here. You can send me a new tube of arnica

826
00:33:05,860 --> 00:33:07,210
一管新的山金车酊
at your convenience.

827
00:33:07,210 --> 00:33:08,490
我不会强留你
You don't have to stay,

828
00:33:08,490 --> 00:33:11,640
但我要为哈维看个
but I have some merger projections

829
00:33:11,640 --> 00:33:12,980
企业并购案
that I have to go through for Harvey.

830
00:33:12,980 --> 00:33:16,550
我很肯定我办不好这事
And I'm pretty sure I'm gonna be out of my depth.

831
00:33:21,240 --> 00:33:22,100
早上好
Morning.

832
00:33:22,100 --> 00:33:24,480
我想早点来打败艾莉森·霍特
Thought I'd get in early and destroy Allison Holt.

833
00:33:24,480 --> 00:33:25,740
怎么样了
How's that going?

834
00:33:25,740 --> 00:33:28,140
还在进行中
It's a work in progress.

835
00:33:28,140 --> 00:33:30,410
路易的辞职信
Louis's letter of resignation.

836
00:33:30,410 --> 00:33:32,010
今早在我桌上看到的
Found it on my desk this morning.

837
00:33:32,010 --> 00:33:33,010
-很好  -不好
- Good. - No.

838
00:33:33,010 --> 00:33:34,390
并不好  哈维
Not good, Harvey.

839
00:33:35,590 --> 00:33:36,960
我们就求同存异吧
We can agree to disagree.

840
00:33:36,960 --> 00:33:38,800
没有同  只有异
We're not agreeing on anything.

841
00:33:38,800 --> 00:33:40,760
你赶走了路易
You pushed Louis out the door.

842
00:33:40,760 --> 00:33:42,250
你没这个资格
It was not your call to make.

843
00:33:42,250 --> 00:33:44,900
不管路易有没有帮艾莉森
Louis may or may not have helped Allison,

844
00:33:44,900 --> 00:33:48,680
他都背叛了你和我  还有整家律所
but he has betrayed you, me, and this entire firm.

845
00:33:48,680 --> 00:33:49,720
没了他更好
We're better off.

846
00:33:49,730 --> 00:33:50,630
你要真这么觉得
If you really believe that,

847
00:33:50,630 --> 00:33:52,010
一定有其他什么事害你表现如此糟糕
then something's got you off your game.

848
00:33:52,010 --> 00:33:53,770
-杰西卡  我表现得  -别说了
- Jessica, I'm not off my-- - No.

849
00:33:54,030 --> 00:33:56,320
不是你  是我
Not you. Me.

850
00:33:56,530 --> 00:33:58,730
你的工作就是协助我
Your job is to help me.

851
00:33:58,730 --> 00:34:00,760
如果我说你表现得不好
And when I say you are off your game,

852
00:34:00,760 --> 00:34:03,110
你就该问  我要如何弥补
you say, "How do I get it back?"

853
00:34:03,640 --> 00:34:06,470
我去找路易  请他重新入伙
I went to Louis to get him back on board,

854
00:34:06,470 --> 00:34:08,720
结果你害我无计可施
and you made an end run around me.

855
00:34:08,820 --> 00:34:10,210
这种状况何时才能结束
When does it stop?

856
00:34:10,400 --> 00:34:11,820
我们不能让特伦特和艾莉森合作
We can't let Trent go with Allison.

857
00:34:11,820 --> 00:34:14,280
他会  搞砸的
He's gonna...get screwed.

858
00:34:14,430 --> 00:34:16,310
我  我很抱歉
I'm--I'm sorry.

859
00:34:18,260 --> 00:34:19,030
这不是什么大事
It's nothing.

860
00:34:19,030 --> 00:34:21,530
只是几级台阶
It's just some stairs.

861
00:34:24,260 --> 00:34:25,400
天呐
Oh, god.

862
00:34:26,440 --> 00:34:28,470
很抱歉  我没看到她在这里
I'm so sorry. I didn't see her there.

863
00:34:28,480 --> 00:34:29,460
是谁干的
Who did this to you?

864
00:34:29,460 --> 00:34:31,170
-我很好  -你不好
- I'm fine. - You're not.

865
00:34:31,170 --> 00:34:32,740
等我把揍你的家伙痛扁一顿
And after I'm done kicking his ass,

866
00:34:32,740 --> 00:34:34,330
他也就不会很好了
the guy who did it isn't gonna be either.

867
00:34:34,330 --> 00:34:35,980
-哈维  别管了  -这可不是我的风格
- Harvey, just let it go. - That's not who I am.

868
00:34:35,980 --> 00:34:37,340
是我活该
I deserved it.

869
00:34:38,580 --> 00:34:41,450
-你干了什么  -我不想告诉你
- What did you do? - I don't want to tell you.

870
00:34:41,450 --> 00:34:43,310
你这可不像是想好好干的样子
I wouldn't call this getting your shit together.

871
00:34:43,310 --> 00:34:44,930
我不想告诉你是因为你跟我讲过
I don't want to tell you because of the story

872
00:34:44,930 --> 00:34:46,870
关于你父母的故事
you told me about your mom and your dad.

873
00:34:50,860 --> 00:34:52,360
你倒是学得挺快
You got off easy.

874
00:34:52,900 --> 00:34:53,950
我知道
I know.

875
00:34:57,180 --> 00:34:58,370
这项交易非常不妥
It's a bad deal.

876
00:34:58,370 --> 00:34:59,720
什么  你读懂了其中的弦外之音吗
What, you're reading between the lines?

877
00:34:59,720 --> 00:35:02,200
我在这份合同里都找不到任何蛛丝马迹
'cause I couldn't find anything in the contract.

878
00:35:02,200 --> 00:35:04,240
因为问题不在这份合同里
Because the problem's not in the contract.

879
00:35:04,240 --> 00:35:05,910
你自己也说了  这项交易好得不真实
You said it yourself. The deal's too good to be true.

880
00:35:05,910 --> 00:35:07,290
资金根本不够运作
The financials don't support it.

881
00:35:07,290 --> 00:35:09,360
怎么  你一夜之间就成了工商管理硕士吗
What, you get your MBA overnight?

882
00:35:09,670 --> 00:35:10,830
不是
No.

883
00:35:10,990 --> 00:35:12,090
你去找路易了
You went to Louis?

884
00:35:12,090 --> 00:35:12,900
我们整晚都在工作
We worked all night.

885
00:35:12,900 --> 00:35:15,070
他没有背叛我们  哈维  他发现的问题
He didn't betray us, Harvey. He found the problem.

886
00:35:15,070 --> 00:35:17,160
他们根本就没想打特伦特公司的主意
They never wanted anything to do with Trent's company.

887
00:35:17,160 --> 00:35:19,430
交易完成后  他们就会分期抛售股份
After the deal, they're just gonna sell it off for spare parts.

888
00:35:19,430 --> 00:35:20,900
这样他们会亏损的
That won't get them what they paid for it.

889
00:35:20,910 --> 00:35:22,710
但能得到他们想要的
But it'll get them what they wanted.

890
00:35:22,710 --> 00:35:24,440
-特伦特  -正是
- Trent. - Exactly.

891
00:35:24,810 --> 00:35:26,100
路易发现的吗
Louis figured this out?

892
00:35:26,100 --> 00:35:28,100
特伦特和路易的合同有相同的问题
Trent's contract has the same problem as Louis's.

893
00:35:28,100 --> 00:35:29,150
都有非竞争条款
He's got a non-compete.

894
00:35:29,150 --> 00:35:30,240
只有买下他的公司
They couldn't get him to run the company

895
00:35:30,250 --> 00:35:31,620
他才会帮他们管理公司
unless they bought his.

896
00:35:31,620 --> 00:35:33,010
路易又想回来了吧
Now Louis wants back in.

897
00:35:33,010 --> 00:35:34,270
没有  他不想
No, he doesn't.

898
00:35:34,270 --> 00:35:36,510
这只是他表达歉意的方式
This is just his way of saying he's sorry.

899
00:35:44,860 --> 00:35:46,710
这菜不在菜单上  不过请允许我推荐
It's not on the menu, but might I suggest

900
00:35:46,710 --> 00:35:48,400
"我被痛扁"马提尼
the "I got my ass kicked" Martini?

901
00:35:48,400 --> 00:35:50,890
跟"二流律所"土豆皮可是绝配
It goes well with the "Second-tier law firm" Potato skins.

902
00:35:50,890 --> 00:35:52,230
再配上点培根
Those come with bacon?

903
00:35:52,230 --> 00:35:54,670
不清楚  从没尝过
I don't know, never had 'em.

904
00:35:54,930 --> 00:35:56,400
我想我的客户是不会来了
I take it my client's not coming.

905
00:35:56,400 --> 00:35:57,870
他曾是你的客户
He was your client,

906
00:35:57,870 --> 00:36:00,370
但你为他提供了一项梦幻交易
but then you offered him a deal too good to be true.

907
00:36:01,260 --> 00:36:02,460
你拿到文件了
You got the paperwork.

908
00:36:02,460 --> 00:36:04,250
因为他信任的人是我
Because he trusted me.

909
00:36:05,620 --> 00:36:07,210
干得漂亮  哈维
Well played, Harvey.

910
00:36:07,210 --> 00:36:08,920
不  应该是这样
No. Here's the play.

911
00:36:08,970 --> 00:36:10,610
正如我两个月前告诉他的那样
He's gonna take his company public,

912
00:36:10,610 --> 00:36:12,500
他的公司会上市
like I told him two months ago.

913
00:36:12,510 --> 00:36:15,610
我的新客户刚刚同意
A deal my new client, a certain hedge fund,

914
00:36:15,610 --> 00:36:17,280
认购一定数额的对冲基金
just agreed to underwrite.

915
00:36:17,580 --> 00:36:19,180
你知道埃德尔森投资公司吧
You know Edelson investments, don't you?

916
00:36:19,180 --> 00:36:20,160
我知道
I do.

917
00:36:20,160 --> 00:36:21,920
当然  我曾代理过他们公司
Apparently, I used to represent them.

918
00:36:21,920 --> 00:36:23,950
你倒是接受得很淡定嘛
Ah, you're taking this well.

919
00:36:23,950 --> 00:36:25,650
你要我怎么做  哭吗
What do you want me to do, cry?

920
00:36:25,940 --> 00:36:27,060
哈维  人在江湖
Harvey, we play the game.

921
00:36:27,060 --> 00:36:29,300
胜负乃兵家常事
Sometimes we win, sometimes we lose.

922
00:36:29,300 --> 00:36:30,610
我就不这样
Not me.

923
00:36:30,920 --> 00:36:34,050
这倒是让我想起了一条建议
Which brings me to a suggestion of my own.

924
00:36:34,670 --> 00:36:36,210
来为布莱顿·古尔德效力吧
Come work for Bratton Gould.

925
00:36:36,210 --> 00:36:37,780
给你打工吗
Come work for you?

926
00:36:37,990 --> 00:36:38,860
与我合作
With me.

927
00:36:38,860 --> 00:36:41,250
你没听到我是怎么说土豆皮的吗
Did you not hear what I said about the potato skins?

928
00:36:41,250 --> 00:36:42,500
你们是二流的
You're second-tier.

929
00:36:42,500 --> 00:36:43,900
那你们呢
What about you?

930
00:36:43,970 --> 00:36:45,780
树大招风  哈维
There's blood in the water, Harvey.

931
00:36:45,780 --> 00:36:47,000
你们也许成功抵挡了这次攻击
You may have fended off this attack,

932
00:36:47,000 --> 00:36:48,420
但我们不是这圈子里的唯一一家
but we're not the only ones circling.

933
00:36:48,420 --> 00:36:50,930
我们抵挡了你的攻击  就能抵挡别人的
We fended you off, we'll fendff the rest.

934
00:36:50,930 --> 00:36:51,970
和谁一起
With who?

935
00:36:51,970 --> 00:36:54,480
我挖走了你最好的高级助手
I got all your best senior associates,

936
00:36:54,480 --> 00:36:56,450
你的未来  而且我不会就此罢休的
your future, and I'm not done.

937
00:36:56,580 --> 00:36:58,100
咱们等着瞧吧
We'll see about that.

938
00:36:58,570 --> 00:37:00,050
午饭算我们的
Lunch is on us.

939
00:37:01,220 --> 00:37:03,610
毕竟我们刚收获了一位大客户
After all, we just landed a huge, new client.

940
00:37:03,610 --> 00:37:06,050
你总说我们  但我可没看到
You say "we", but I don't see

941
00:37:06,050 --> 00:37:07,660
门上有你的名字
your name on the door.

942
00:37:09,190 --> 00:37:11,280
迈克  迈克  我听到你的留言了
Mike, Mike, Mike. I got your call.

943
00:37:11,290 --> 00:37:12,580
你说你欠我一份情  对吧
You said you owed me one, right?

944
00:37:12,580 --> 00:37:13,850
没错  我是认真的
Yeah, and I meant it too.

945
00:37:13,850 --> 00:37:14,840
那现在就来还吧
Well, you're gonna pay me back.

946
00:37:14,840 --> 00:37:17,470
乐意之至  听我说
I'm happy to, 'cause listen to me,

947
00:37:17,470 --> 00:37:18,750
等我带你进公司
when I bring you in,

948
00:37:18,750 --> 00:37:20,980
你大展拳脚  我就在一旁助阵
and you kick ass, I look kick-ass.

949
00:37:20,980 --> 00:37:23,400
-带简历了吗  -在这
- Got your resume? - Right there.

950
00:37:26,530 --> 00:37:27,640
你拿我开玩笑呢吧
You gotta be kidding me.

951
00:37:27,640 --> 00:37:30,090
你不会觉得还我人情会很容易吧
Oh, you didn't think it was gonna be easy to pay me back, did you?

952
00:37:30,090 --> 00:37:31,400
哈罗德
Harold?

953
00:37:31,790 --> 00:37:32,950
我别想看到大展拳脚了
I'm not gonna look kick-ass.

954
00:37:32,950 --> 00:37:34,300
只能看到拳打脚踢了
I'm gonna look ass-kicked.

955
00:37:34,340 --> 00:37:35,560
你看看他的业绩
Look at how he did.

956
00:37:37,420 --> 00:37:38,220
你拿我开玩笑呢吧
Are you kidding me?

957
00:37:38,220 --> 00:37:39,380
干嘛一直重复这句
You keep saying that.

958
00:37:39,380 --> 00:37:40,480
老兄  咱俩说的是同一个哈罗德吗
Man, we talking about the same Harold?

959
00:37:40,480 --> 00:37:41,450
我知道
I know.

960
00:37:42,860 --> 00:37:43,660
说真的  迈克  老兄
Seriously, Mike, man,

961
00:37:43,660 --> 00:37:45,390
如果这个不行  我就要遭殃了
If this doesn't work, I'm gonna look like shit.

962
00:37:45,390 --> 00:37:47,920
吉米 他需要一次翻身的机会
Jimmy, he needs a second chance

963
00:37:47,920 --> 00:37:49,220
像你一样
just like you did.

964
00:37:50,090 --> 00:37:51,700
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.

965
00:37:51,950 --> 00:37:53,100
你不会后悔的
You won't regret it.

966
00:37:53,110 --> 00:37:53,840
哈罗德很棒
Harold's great.

967
00:37:53,840 --> 00:37:55,390
你会喜欢他的新纹身的
You're gonna love his new tattoo.

968
00:37:56,970 --> 00:37:58,020
他在这  是吧
He's here, isn't he?

969
00:37:58,020 --> 00:37:59,430
就在那
Right over there.

970
00:38:10,660 --> 00:38:12,510
你不仅留下了一位客户
Not only do you retain one client,

971
00:38:12,520 --> 00:38:13,800
还收获了一位新客户
you landed another.

972
00:38:13,800 --> 00:38:15,760
我就知道我留下你是有原因的
I knew there was a reason why I kept you around.

973
00:38:15,760 --> 00:38:18,770
也是艾莉森·霍特试图挖我过去的原因
And a reason Allison Holt's trying to steal me away.

974
00:38:18,770 --> 00:38:21,460
恭喜  我想你一定很高兴
Congratulations. I'm sure you'll be very happy.

975
00:38:21,460 --> 00:38:23,350
能出什么岔子呢
What could possibly go wrong?

976
00:38:23,350 --> 00:38:25,620
恭喜  我也是这样对迈克说的
Congratulations. That's what I said to Mike.

977
00:38:25,640 --> 00:38:27,590
他也被邀请了  她真是全面开炮啊
Him too? She's after everyone.

978
00:38:27,600 --> 00:38:29,470
别担心  他不会走的
Don't worry. He's staying.

979
00:38:29,590 --> 00:38:30,810
像巴吉度猎犬一样忠诚
Loyal as a basset hound.

980
00:38:30,810 --> 00:38:32,770
这种狗特别忠诚吗
Oh. Are they particularly loyal?

981
00:38:33,750 --> 00:38:35,080
我拒绝她了
I turned her down.

982
00:38:37,660 --> 00:38:38,650
但是呢
But?

983
00:38:39,050 --> 00:38:40,630
我的名字要挂在门口
I want my name on the door.

984
00:38:41,830 --> 00:38:44,110
我不想再给你当副手了
I don't want to end around you anymore.

985
00:38:46,080 --> 00:38:49,380
我想跟你平起平坐
I want to discuss things with you as an equal.

986
00:38:49,380 --> 00:38:51,330
有点太迟了  你不觉得吗
It's a little late for that, don't you think?

987
00:38:51,330 --> 00:38:54,630
他的名字还得在墙上呆多久
How long are we gonna walk by his name on the wall, huh?

988
00:38:54,630 --> 00:38:55,780
他们步步紧逼
They're coming after us,

989
00:38:55,780 --> 00:38:58,180
除非我们向他们表明  我们是一个整体
and they're not gonna stop until we send them a message

990
00:38:58,190 --> 00:38:59,530
他们是不会罢休的
that we are whole.

991
00:38:59,530 --> 00:39:00,830
我不会随便
I'm not gonna just slap

992
00:39:00,830 --> 00:39:02,650
把某个人的名字贴上去的  哈维
someone else's name up there, Harvey.

993
00:39:02,660 --> 00:39:05,010
-某个人  -我曾经跟你说过
- "Someone"? - I told you once.

994
00:39:05,020 --> 00:39:07,800
你一受到失败的影响  就无法做决定
You don't make decisions when you're reeling from a loss.

995
00:39:07,800 --> 00:39:10,970
而你的回答却是  咱们今天退出吧
And your response was, "Let's quit today."

996
00:39:10,970 --> 00:39:12,360
不是退出  是去奋战
Not quit. Fight.

997
00:39:12,360 --> 00:39:14,290
完全不计后果
Without any thought for the consequences.

998
00:39:14,290 --> 00:39:16,380
运用我的胆量  如虎添翼
With my gut, which serves me well.

999
00:39:16,390 --> 00:39:18,170
作为一个律师  而非领导者
As a closer, not a leader.

1000
00:39:18,170 --> 00:39:19,440
杰西卡
Jessica.

1001
00:39:19,440 --> 00:39:20,870
华生  克莱曼
Watson, Glyman,

1002
00:39:20,870 --> 00:39:22,780
加洛  高德伯格  斯佩克特
Gallo, Goldberg, Specter.

1003
00:39:22,780 --> 00:39:24,710
你提名的第一批高级合伙人
The first five senior partners you named.

1004
00:39:24,710 --> 00:39:27,420
是我所下的五步好棋
The first five major moves I made.

1005
00:39:27,430 --> 00:39:29,120
都非常成功
All success stories.

1006
00:39:29,130 --> 00:39:31,260
上礼拜  你莫名其妙地要我
Last week, you had me steal someone

1007
00:39:31,260 --> 00:39:33,790
去地方检察官的办公室里要人
from the D.A.'s office for reasons you won't say.

1008
00:39:33,790 --> 00:39:35,870
我们就不深究你对路易做了什么了
We won't even go into what you did to Louis.

1009
00:39:35,870 --> 00:39:37,980
后来锦上添花的就来了
And then there's the cherry on top.

1010
00:39:37,980 --> 00:39:39,510
-迈克  -他今早来的时候
- Mike. - Who showed up this morning

1011
00:39:39,510 --> 00:39:41,040
像是被痛扁了一顿
beaten to a pulp.

1012
00:39:41,040 --> 00:39:42,650
他也把哈德曼痛扁了一顿
He also beat Hardman to a pulp.

1013
00:39:42,650 --> 00:39:45,630
总有一天  他的优点
One day, what he is isn't going to be enough

1014
00:39:45,630 --> 00:39:47,290
将无法弥补他的缺点
to make up for what he isn't.

1015
00:39:47,290 --> 00:39:49,310
这也是你对我的感觉吧
Which is how you feel about me.

1016
00:39:52,220 --> 00:39:54,400
哈维  迈克尔·乔丹在公牛队的记录如何
Harvey, what was Michael Jordan's record on the Bulls?

1017
00:39:54,400 --> 00:39:57,550
664胜  285败
664 wins, 285 losses.

1018
00:39:57,810 --> 00:40:00,580
胜绩是败绩的两倍还多
More than twice as many wins than losses.

1019
00:40:01,010 --> 00:40:03,400
你知道他管理公牛时的记录是多少吗
Do you know what his record was in the front office?

1020
00:40:03,400 --> 00:40:06,120
-不知道  -185比291
- No. - 185 to 291.

1021
00:40:06,750 --> 00:40:09,490
败绩几乎是胜绩的两倍
Almost twice as many losses as wins.

1022
00:40:09,490 --> 00:40:10,720
你知道我是怎么知道吗
You know how I know that?

1023
00:40:10,720 --> 00:40:12,660
因为你知道有一天  我会进来
Because you knew one day, I'd come in here

1024
00:40:12,660 --> 00:40:13,980
问你要这些
asking for this.

1025
00:40:15,950 --> 00:40:17,900
因为我用成年人的眼光
Because I look at the future

1026
00:40:18,350 --> 00:40:19,730
来展望未来
like an adult.

1027
00:40:21,260 --> 00:40:22,820
你是在拒绝我吗
Are you saying it's a no?

1028
00:40:22,820 --> 00:40:26,950
我是说我不会匆忙做决定
I'm saying I'm not rushing this decision

1029
00:40:27,850 --> 00:40:30,400
而且你那天的判断也是错的
and that your judgment that day was wrong.

1030
00:40:37,560 --> 00:40:38,570
谢谢
Thank you.

1031
00:40:46,850 --> 00:40:47,930
我想你应该很乐意知道
I thought you'd like to know

1032
00:40:47,930 --> 00:40:52,650
哈罗德在另一家公司找到了工作
that Harold got a job at another firm.

1033
00:40:52,990 --> 00:40:54,130
很好
Good.

1034
00:40:57,120 --> 00:40:58,190
听着 瑞秋
Look, Rachel--

1035
00:40:58,190 --> 00:41:00,560
他发现了  对吗
He found out, didn't he?

1036
00:41:02,000 --> 00:41:03,280
我只是想告诉你这一切
I just want you to know that it was

1037
00:41:03,280 --> 00:41:05,550
发生在我与苔丝了断以后
after I ended things with Tess.

1038
00:41:06,860 --> 00:41:09,820
我也想告诉你  我一点都不在乎
I want you to know that I just don't give a shit.

