Previously on "Switched at Birth"...
I never felt at home at Buckner.
Going to Carlton doesn't make any sense.
They do have this new pilot program
for kids with deaf
parents or deaf siblings.
We need somebody that
everybody's familiar with.
Like a brand.
John, you're a leader.
You deserve a third act.
Think about it.
No turning back now.
I thought maybe you wanted to know
that you had another one on the way.
_
She hates me for no
reason, other than the fact
that I'm hearing.
Look, I don't know what your deal is.
If this is something about Emmett or...
_
So I re-read "The Scarlet Letter"
and I learned all of the relevant signs.
"Adultery, "hypocrisy,"
"who thought it was a good
idea to cast Demi Moore
as Hester Prynne?" And I have not
slowed down the class
once in the last week.
_
(Sighs) Well, uh,
next up, Shakespeare.
I may have to use up my sick days.
_
Yeah. Hey, um, maybe we can
even sit with your old crew.
Or not.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Nice work.
Noah. Pilot program.
We have like every class together.
Noah, I know who you are.
There's only like seven of us.
I'm sorry. Look, I'm distracted right now.
Trying to fix this. Someone wrote
something really nasty on my locker.
Oh, yeah.
They shoved a note in mine too.
There's Ms. Bledsoe.
Maybe we should tell her.
Uh, yeah. And add "rat"
to my list of crimes against deaf humanity?
No, thank you.
_
Uhh...
just personalizing my locker.
_
Uh, "let" may be too strong of a word.
Where's a volleyball
when you need one, huh?
You heard about that?
(Chuckles)
Daphne: Something happened.
But Bay won't say what.
Some of the deaf kids don't
like the pilot program.
You'd think that people who
had been bullied themselves
would be the last ones
to do it to someone else.
But Bay's all right?
She seems to be.
Can you finish up?
My telenovela is on.
Mom, wait. I need to talk to you.
Both of you.
I know that tone.
- Angelo.
- Yes.
It's Angelo.
He's gonna be a father again.
- What?!
- You're pregnant?!
No. Not me.
He got someone else pregnant?
Yeah.
Of course he did.
Do we know who she is?
Her name is Lana.
And she's a medical student at U.M.K.C.
Young. Of course.
They met on the plane going back to Italy.
(Chuckling) Oh, that's just perfect.
Mom! Please. Can I get through this?
Is she African-American?
- Pretty?
- Yeah.
You know her?
She came to the court looking for Angelo,
and both Bay and Daphne met her.
They just didn't know who she was.
Bay knows?
Everyone knows.
I'm sorry I didn't tell
you when I found out.
But I knew what you would say.
And it seemed as if you and Angelo
had finally buried the hatchet.
I know where I'd like to bury a hatchet.
Isn't your novela starting?
Yes, but they're bound to be a letdown.
Nothing they write in the telenovelas
can hold a candle to Angelo's real life.
(Door closes)
I'm sorry, honey.
Honestly, it really doesn't affect me.
Are you okay?
I really thought he had changed.
Hey, do you remember that day spa
that you and I went to when I
hurt my shoulder playing basketball?
Yeah.
Let's go there again. This weekend.
Just you and me.
It'll be a "suck it, Angelo" spa party.
And he can pay for it.
I'll use the money from the food truck.
That sounds fantastic.
Perfect.
Ivan: For the first few events,
- you'll be preaching totally to the choir.
- John: Uh-huh.
Give you a chance to work out
- your stump speech.
- Okay.
Oh, and Kathryn, we've got you booked
on Dara Walker's radio show.
So you can share your favorite recipe
- with all of her listeners.
- Great.
Sorry to interrupt. Uh, mom, can I borrow
your car again?
I gotta go to rehearsal.
Oh, sure, honey. When
is yours gonna be fixed?
Not till Saturday.
Thanks, though.
Okay, see you.
Mm. Ivan, here's the thing.
I'm not interested in
memorizing talking points.
It's one of the things that drives me crazy
when I watch these national guys campaign.
- It's just the same canned crap...
- (Ivan chuckles)
over and over and over.
And John's great at speaking off-the-cuff.
We've been getting very
familiar with the issues.
I'd like to focus on
education and immigration.
And you will.
When you get elected.
During the campaign, the
trick is to keep it general.
Pro-middle class, anti-big government.
But I think what
John has to say on
education and immigration
will really resonate with
people in our district.
You're running in a conservative district
in a solidly G.O.P. state. People love you.
All you have to do to get
elected is to be yourself,
talk about your business successes
and tell that great story
about the home run you hit
in the '92 all-star game.
You can't lose.
Hey, this is the recipe you should share.
These are delicious.
I bought 'em.
Hmm.
I am gonna make stickers.
If Natalie wants to fight
it out with graffiti,
she picked the wrong girl.
_
She is the one who is throwing gasoline.
And I've tried to make peace.
And I'm trying to keep up,
but she just keeps hating me
because I can hear.
And that's like hating me
because I have brown hair or brown eyes.
There's nothing that I can do about it.
_
Wow, that sucks.
But we didn't ask for any cuts.
And if Natalie and her posse
keep taking it out on the hearing kids,
we're just gonna fight back.
_
Hi. Uh, Noah.
- Bay: Very funny.
- (Chuckles)
Are you ready for the A.S.L. test?
Uh, yes. You?
I think I understand everything.
Mm, except for "understand."
This is "understand."
You signed "horny."
Mm. Crap.
I haven't gotten one full sentence right.
Great, what do you think they've cut now?
Hey, what's going on?
_
"Student tolerance retreat this weekend.
- Attendance mandatory."
- (Bay sighs)
I'm guessing I'm on the list.
Bet I am too.
I'm guessing so is she.
_
Thanks.
"Crybaby."
_
So it's all of the pilot program kids
and some of the deaf kids?
Yup.
At a tolerance retreat?
Mm-hmm.
But there isn't a problem?
Okay, maybe there were
a few misunderstandings.
But that's just because the
whole thing is new to everyone.
Bay, I know you feel like you have to
make it sound like everything is fine
because you pushed so hard, but...
Mom, everything is fine.
And I promise if I need you guys,
I will tell you, okay?
- Okay.
Have fun.
(Door opens and closes)
I knew this school wasn't a good idea.
At Buckner,
when there were problems
with groups of kids,
we would have assemblies...
we'd do trust falls in the gym
or pass around like a talking stick.
We were not sent into the woods
to reenact "The Hunger Games."
Maybe you should have thought about that
before you hit Natalie with a volleyball.
(Scoffs) I apologized for that.
And then she was the
one who bombed my locker.
Oh, so you're just an
innocent victim in all of this.
I told I was sorry you
and the leadership kids
got dragged into this,
but maybe if you weren't
such an upstanding student...
Wait, now it's my fault that I
have to spend my weekend doing this?
No, I'm just saying it's not my fault.
Okay, I was supposed to bring my mom
to the spa this weekend,
because she was feeling so bad about Angelo
and his new baby.
Something that you didn't
bother telling me about.
Why didn't you tell me?
I should have, I know.
But when I found out, Regina didn't know.
And then Angelo and I
got into this big fight.
I'm sorry.
I have to go get the rest of my stuff.
(Sighs)
Okay, I guess I'm ready to go.
Try not to be too mad at Bay.
I'm sure she feels bad
about all of this too.
I know. I just...
I was really looking forward
to spending time with you.
Me too.
(Sighs) But we can just do next weekend.
And while you're gone I can
catch up on "Breaking Bad"
and count the amount of times
grandma says "I told you so."
Hey.
Why don't you come with us?
- On the retreat?
- Yeah.
Why not?
You can hang out with Melody,
eat s'mores,
avoid grandma.
I do make a mean s'more.
You really do.
You know what? I think that's a great idea.
I have a doctor's
appointment in the afternoon,
but I can meet you up there.
Are you having more
problems with your hands?
Actually, no.
Um, this is somebody new
and she's run lots of tests
and seems optimistic.
I'm hoping for good news.
- That's so great!
- I know.
Come as soon as you can.
Okay.
Lana: And you didn't
know two weeks ago that
the parts needed to come from Germany?
We hoped we could get them locally.
Well, my insurance won't
cover any more rental car days.
I'm really sorry.
I am a pregnant woman walking eight blocks
to and from the bus stop every day.
My wife has had four kids.
She says exercise is
good for you and the baby.
Helps with the delivery.
Oh, really? Dr. Larry.
Is there any other medical
advice you would like
to give me or my unborn child?
- Hi.
- We are not done here.
No, sorry. Um...
- Don't know if you remember me, but...
- Yeah.
From Angelo's place.
Right. Yeah. Can I help?
I swear her car will be ready tomorrow.
Well, mine's done now. I could give you
a ride home today and bring you
back tomorrow, if that would help.
Tomorrow.
As God as my witness.
Um, okay, I... I really
don't wanna put you out.
You're not.
Okay. Thanks.
Sure.
_
Noah, right?
No, Jeremy.
(Chuckles)
There better not be
contraband in there, camper.
And if there is? But I'm willing to share.
Ah, I really don't see a problem then.
(Chuckles)
Whoa, how much contraband
have you consumed?
(Exhales)
Noah, whoa! Are you okay?
(Exhales deeply)
I just need a minute.
(Clears throat)
What's going on?
Um...
I have this thing
called Meniere's disease.
(Sniffs)
It messes with my... my
balance and my hearing and stuff.
What do you mean "messes with"?
Uh, I just get dizzy spells.
They last for a few minutes or all day.
I've lost 60% of the
hearing in my right ear.
And eventually...
I could lose it all.
When we went around in
the circle that first day,
I thought you said you were at Carlton
because you had deaf relatives.
Yeah, my Uncle.
He's got Meniere's too.
- (Chuckles)
- Right.
My parents figured that it'd be good
to get a head start on
the whole hand thing.
It's incredible, you know?
One day you're fine, and the next...
whole life changes.
Yeah.
It's crazy how that can happen.
Why didn't you just tell everybody
that you have Meniere's?
I don't really like to talk about it.
Well...
you wanna hear my "your whole
life changes in a day" story?
(Chuckling) You've got one too?
Get comfortable.
(Noah chuckles)
Bay: Um, so we took this blood
test in bio class and, well...
Jane: Welcome. I can see you're
all very excited to be here.
Well, you have been selected to participate
in this team-building weekend because...
you are either a role model at Carlton,
a troublemaker...
or a target.
Your first assignment
will be to replicate
the object that's under this tarp.
You will be split up into groups of five...
one looker, two runners
and two builders.
You'll get the hang of it.
Now before you start out,
please remember: You must always sign.
Okay.
First group:
Daphne.
Natalie.
Jane: Bay.
Noah.
And Emmett.
Second group:
Jennifer.
Tony.
Amy.
Howard.
And Liz.
So Kathryn, what do you call this dish?
Just what it is...
pork chops, black beans
- and salsa.
- That is so good!
Now I taste the cinnamon. But what else?
Cumin, a little chili powder, ginger.
It's a rub.
And can you tell our listeners
how you came up with this
delectable combination?
Actually, um...
I got this recipe a long time ago
from this guy who works for John
at the car wash... Hector Gonzales.
I believe it's a variation
on a Guatemalan dish.
- Interesting.
- Yeah.
Hector started out on the
line at John's first car wash.
And when he opened two more,
he promoted him to manager.
He did a great job.
Is that when he gave you this recipe?
I... I...
I don't quite remember.
But it's so great because
John never forgets that we
are a nation of immigrants.
And he believes that we should be finding
legal ways to welcome people
who want to be part of
this great American dream.
Not putting up barriers to push them out.
That is very admirable.
Does your family eat a lot
of Latin-inspired dishes?
We're very inclusive.
We eat all kinds of food.
(Exhales)
So can I burn this thing now?
I'm afraid the news isn't good.
But I'm feeling better.
That's because you haven't been doing
anything to irritate the problem.
Cutting hair, signing, painting.
The M.R.I. shows the beginnings
of osteonecrosis in your wrists.
And that's bad?
It can be.
If you don't make some changes soon,
it'll be hard to turn a doorknob,
hold a hairbrush, drive a car.
Okay, so what do I need
to do to make it better?
At this point,
it's about not making it worse.
(Sighs)
I'll just find someone else.
Regina.
You've seen over a dozen specialists.
At some point it's not about giving up.
It's just simply about
accepting your new reality.
(Pop music playing)
* I waited for your call
* and for the moon
* to release me from the
longest afternoon... *
All right, an art project.
We are so gonna win this.
_
Okay, I didn't get all of that,
- but I'm pretty sure it was insulting.
- _
_
What's Noah doing?
- _
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Um, I just wanted to ask, um...
Daphne, uh, for more...
uh... (Exhales)
Uh, paper, pen?
- Your palm's itchy?
- No no no, um...
- How do you sign "information"?
- Oh, uh,
- "information."
- Information. Okay, sorry.
Ms. Bledsoe
said that, uh,
the, um...
Uhh, Daphne?
Oh, uh, the lookers!
The lookers, yes.
The can come to the, uh...
Uh, the fence!
Thank you.
Um, so we don't
have to run so far if we need
information.
Yes!
Yes, I knew them all. Knew all those signs.
Ha ha! First sentence!
(Chuckles)
(Wood rattles)
And I'm back to being
completely in the dark again.
Okay, now, she's asking
what we are supposed
to do with all this stuff.
Okay okay.
_
You and me?
Okay. Um, maybe.
_
Because he's my friend.
And he's not feeling well.
_
No no, it's not like that.
Look, it's hard to explain.
_
Noah: I think we know what to do now.
Lana: Does everybody know?
In your family?
Uh, about you and Angelo?
Yeah, kinda.
Ah, but don't worry, we've
all been fooled by Angelo
at some time or another.
He's a charming guy.
I wouldn't really know.
I barely know him.
I don't normally
meet somebody and then...
I mean, I... I... I'm saying
I... I'm not some kind of...
Oh, yeah. I'm sure you're not.
So you're not like ready
to have the baby, are you?
I don't think so.
Good. I didn't pay attention
to those birthing videos in health class,
so I wouldn't be much help.
Well, you don't have to worry.
- I'm a medical student.
- They teach you how to...
deliver your own baby in medical school?
- (Inhaling and exhaling deeply)
- Are you okay?
- Look out!
- Oh!
- (Tires screech)
- (Car crashes)
(Both panting)
- Thanks, man. Sorry.
- Yeah.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine. I just...
I feel terrible about your car.
I mean, if you weren't taking me home...
I could be in a worse
accident on the freeway.
(Moaning) Oh.
(Inhales deeply and exhales)
- Ooh, okay.
- Okay, we're going to the hospital.
No, it's just Braxton-Hicks.
It's... they're practice contractions.
They're perfectly harmless...
(Groans)
I think.
Yep, definitely going to the hospital.
Here we go.
(Groans)
Jane: So how do you all think that went?
Matthew?
How'd it go for you and your group?
_
Maybe you should
try talking and see how
good you are at that?
- Bay...
- Whoa whoa!
_
- That's not okay!
- (Overlapping arguing)
- Daphne: You should not be here!
- Noah: Calm down! Hey!
(Indistinct shouting)
Jane: Enough! Enough.
That's what I thought.
I want you to make a list
of all the things that you think you know
about your partner.
And when you're done,
you'll share your insights
with the group.
Sign only. No interpreter.
And remember:
You can't say anything related
to being hearing or deaf.
All right.
Now I'm gonna break you into pairs.
Bay
and Natalie.
Noah
and Matthew.
I do have insurance, I promise.
It's just in my other purse,
which is moronic of me.
Don't worry, we'll figure it out later.
You don't have to stay.
How else are you gonna get home?
I'll figure something out.
Are you sure you don't
want me to call somebody?
Angelo, maybe?
Okay, not Angelo.
Um...
someone from your family? Anybody?
My family lives in Boston.
And they don't even know I'm pregnant.
Nurse: Dr. Kornreich
thinks everything is fine.
But she wanted us to get an
ultrasound just to be sure.
Are you the dad?
Me? No. God, no.
I mean...
well, not because she's...
we've never...
I mean, we're not, you know...
You know, we're just... we're friends.
Yes. (Exhales)
Um, I... I'll give you a minute.
You can stay.
You know,
if you want to.
Okay. Sure.
There she is.
Toby: Wow.
That's incredible.
Yeah. It's pretty amazing.
I try not to look.
It just makes it harder.
Makes what harder?
Giving her up for adoption.
Oh.
(Sighs)
Jane: All right, enough.
Bay
and Natalie, you're up.
_
Look, if I have to...
Okay. Fine, I'll start.
Um, Natalie Pierce is a bully.
(Pen and paper clatter)
_
You don't know anything about me,
but you hate me anyway,
which makes you a bigot
and a bully.
_
Because every hearing person in the world
is the same, right?
We're all out to get you.
Jane: All right, settle down.
Now that you've let off some steam,
try again.
But this time, say something positive
about the other.
Proud.
(Sighs and smacks lips)
_
Tough.
Honest.
_
Jane: Excellent!
And not so hard, right?
I think we've all earned our s'mores.
Well, you missed all the fireworks.
I caught a few.
I'm gonna go get some s'mores.
Hey!
You're not wearing your brace.
That means good news, right?
Not exactly.
Oh.
_
(Chuckling)
Yeah, did the doctor say
when you'd get better?
She said the same thing
that all the rest of them have said.
That with the combination
of learning to sign as an adult,
the amount of signing that I've done
and the painting and the
years of cutting hair,
the damage is irreparable.
And if I go back to doing what I was,
it'll get worse.
Chronic numbness, pain,
severe arthritis.
What about sign language?
I can't.
Ever?
You can still sign to me.
And I can understand it.
You never know with medicine.
New things are happening all the time.
I... I need to go check on my group.
_
Yes.
What?
_
Meaning?
You think I'm faking this?
_
If I could, why wouldn't I?
You are not in my body.
You do not know how I feel.
And if you really think that
I am not trying hard enough,
you are most certainly not my friend.
(Exhales and chuckles)
I'm sorry.
I, uh... I haven't figured out
how to do that
without, uh, scaring someone
who can't hear me coming.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Can I help?
Not unless you're a wizard or a magician.
I don't think so.
But, um,
Harry Potter didn't find out
that he was a wizard until he was like...
15.
So...
there's always a chance.
- 11.
- Hmm?
Harry Potter was 11 when he
found out he was a wizard.
Oh, right.
My bad.
I just found out that my mom
can't sign to me ever again.
She has some
weird physical thing
messing up her hands.
I'm sorry.
You're not deaf. You don't get it.
You have no idea how exhausting it is
to have to read lips all the time.
Imagine you found out that your parents
could never talk to you
with their voice ever again.
You had to sign with them
for the rest of your life.
I'm imagining.
If it you makes you, um,
feel any better...
she's probably a million
times madder than you are.
It sucks to feel like
your body's betraying you.
I'll see you back at camp.
- (Soft pop music playing)
- * thinking nothing is right
* baby, come on
* ooh
* baby, come on.
(Sighs)
- Hey.
- I just got off the phone with Ivan
who told me that I need
to reign in my wife.
- Excuse me?
- Yeah.
Guy's really got a way with
words, but the radio show...
you were just supposed
to talk about recipes.
The only non-food thing
I said was that you
believe that new immigrants
should get a shot at the American dream.
Is that so bad?
Apparently Sawyer is already spinning it...
saying that I encourage
illegal immigration.
But that's absurd. Hector's legal.
All your guys are legal.
But you didn't say that.
(Scoffs)
Fine, we'll go the press
tomorrow with the facts.
No, the point is that it
is easy to make mistakes.
That is why Ivan wants to
keep the message general.
You know, we don't want to waste
time going on the defensive,
doing damage control.
So that's how you wanna win this thing?
By saying nothing of substance?
I have spent a lot of my life
thinking I was just a dumb jock.
That is your father talking.
But if I am elected,
I can really do something meaningful.
I can make a difference in
how our kids are educated,
in whether or not people get jobs,
can own their own homes.
But I can't do that
if I don't win.
Then tell people your ideas.
Let them vote for something.
I'm sorry,
but I think Ivan is right.
If you're in the stronger position,
you don't get aggressive,
you hold steady and you let the other team
make the mistakes.
No more talking politics.
Fine.
Then consider your wife reigned in.
Noah: (Off-key) * as the sun shines on
♪ my face
♪ it's true...
Whoa! (Chuckles)
Wow, payback's a bitch.
Payback?
Yeah, I snuck up on somebody earlier.
(Chuckling) Never mind.
How'd you find me here?
Used my superpowers.
I heard the singing. Don't tell anyone.
Oh.
Well, with my A.S.L. skills,
I don't think you have to worry about me
telling anybody anything.
True.
I just wanted some space.
And I think your boyfriend wanted
to see a little less of me too.
Come on.
He was giving me the stink eye all day.
I kind of put it together.
Emmett's not my boyfriend.
He was.
What are you listening to anyway?
Mm.
Nice playlist.
Yeah.
I'm trying to commit them all to memory.
You know, for when the...
(Sighs)
yeah, it sucks 'cause I really love music.
So do Emmett and Daphne.
Emmett's even in my brother's band.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Am I an idiot?
'Cause I don't really get that.
I'm just saying going deaf may
not be what you think it is.
I hope not.
You wanna listen to something?
Ooh, no signing and listening to music?
Dangerous stuff.
Living on the wild side here at
- the Carlton deaf school retreat.
- (Music playing)
* I'm feeling your heart in mine *
* ooh, yeah.
Poison Ivy.
Yeah, uh,
I got it too.
Here.
This stuff is like magic.
Look, um, I really don't
wanna go on another retreat.
_
Okay.
So why don't we call a truce?
The other kids can follow our example.
No more retreats.
_
No problem.
Okay, the car's coming around, so, uh...
thanks for the ride.
No problem.
Hey, I can't stop thinking about
what you said last night at the hospital.
About putting the baby up for adoption
and not having the family around.
I shouldn't have even mentioned that.
It's really not your problem.
Oh, I know. It's just...
the baby does have a family around.
Other than Angelo.
My sister.
Her sister.
Right.
Bay.
Yeah.
I just thought maybe
you might wanna meet her
and our family before you
make any final decisions.
But that's it. That's all I had to say.
So...
I'll see you around.
Okay.
(Door closes)
What are you doing?
Checking out the city
college class catalog.
Trying to figure out what to do with myself
now that I'm no longer a hairdresser.
Maybe you should run for office like John.
Don't think diplomacy is my strong suit.
You think his is?
(Light chuckle)
Phlebotomist?
Well, I don't love needles or blood, but...
I can learn. I'm tough.
You are.
I've been doing hair
since I was 19 years old.
I was just a little older than you.
I don't know what's next for me.
I... I really don't.
I do know what it means
not to be able to sign.
You know I do.
I... (Sighs)
I have to figure out a
whole new life for myself.
Everything I thought I had I...
you never know how much
you depend on these things,
huh?
(Quietly) I'm sorry.
I really am.
I know.
Hey. Okay, so,
Natalie and I have called a truce
which means no more retreats.
_
What's wrong?
Noah and I are just friends.
_
No.
Well, I know it must seem like that,
but I really didn't.
_
Emmett, my head is spinning.
I... (Sighs)
I just started this new school.
I'm barely keeping up in classes.
I mean, half the kids here hate me.
I'm... I'm under water.
_
- Well, then help me.
- (Piano music playing)
As my friend.
_
But that's all that I can handle right now.
I'm sorry.
* I knew exactly what this
- * would feel like
- _
* I knew this day was coming
* I knew it right from the start... *
Emmett.
* To hear the same voice
* that said "hello"
* say "good-bye."
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -