My name is Elena Gilbert,
and I'm a vampire.
I'm learning how to survive,
but there are complications.
I know that I'm
sired to you, Damon.
You know what would
make me happy?
That what you actually
felt for me was real.
How together are they?
But there's hope now.
Tell him what the hunter
told you the tattoo leads to.
He said there was a cure.
And we're not
the only ones who want it...
I want to ram it down
Niklaus' throat.
But uncovering it
comes with a price.
What do you know about Silas?
He's the world's
first immortal being,
who just happens to be
imprisoned with the cure.
You said it yourself, right?
Whoever finds the cure first
gets to decide
what to do with it.
So what do you say, partners?
The race for the cure
has begun,
but how far will we
have to go to find it?
I was beginning to worry you
boys wouldn't find the place.
Did you kill all these people?
Killing them is your job.
Unh!
Agh!
Jeremy, voice-over: No way.
I'm not doing it.
What makes you think
you have a choice?
You have to kill vampires to
complete the hunter's mark.
Mark equals cure.
You're in a bar full
of almost vampires,
so get your hunt on.
Screw you. You said I
wouldn't have to kill
any innocent people.
Jeremy, they're not people.
Enough! Have at it,
or else.
I don't take orders
from you, dick.
Hunters can't be compelled.
You're right.
I can't compel you,
but if your conscience
is getting in the way,
then allow me to make
this easy for you
because I can compel them.
I'm gonna give you a
two-minute head start.
Then I'm gonna send every
vampire in here after you.
You kill them, or they
kill your friend... Matt.
Wait a second.
No, no. You turn them,
he kills them.
That was the deal, Klaus.
I'm taking artistic license.
You know he can't take them
all on at the same time.
With you as his
coach, he'll be fine.
It's Matt I'm worried about.
Ehh.
Jeremy, go get
the weapons out of the car.
I'll be right behind you.
Go with him.
If I hear an engine start,
I'll kill Matt myself!
Jeremy: Are you ok?
Yeah. I just
need a second.
We don't have a second.
They can smell your blood.
We need to go.
[Crunch]
Don't hesitate.
You're lucky it was me.
Otherwise, you two
would be dead.
You set us up.
I'm was trying to get
this thing over with.
You're the one that
pissed off Klaus.
Now you have to fight
your way out of it.
Where are the other vampires?
They're newbies. They're still
trying to figure out how to track,
which means you have two
seconds to get ready to fight.
The lake house is this way.
If we can get there, they
won't be able to get inside.
Wait. You want to run?
They're gonna kill Matt.
Fine. Get out of here.
I'll slow them down.
Jeremy, where are you?
Keep going.
We're almost there.
[Snarls]
[Snap]
Are you ok?
Oh, my God.
Get to the house!
Hurry!
Jeremy, what's going on?
They're coming.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
Sun's up.
They're long gone.
What the hell
were you thinking?
All I asked you to do was
to teach him how to fight.
He's not the best
student in the world.
Wait. Now this is
my fault?
Stop talking.
Look. I know
you're angry,
but my way was the
easiest, fastest,
and safest way
to complete his mark
to get you the cure.
I don't care
about the cure, Damon,
not if it means putting the
people that I love in danger.
Hey. There would
have been no danger
if he hadn't gone
all bleeding heart.
He killed someone.
These were innocent people.
But the mark grew, didn't it?
[Sighs]
Ok. Look.
We need a plan.
There's a group of compelled
vampires out there,
and as soon as the sun
goes down,
they're gonna come after Matt,
so we have to find
a away to protect him.
Yes, I know, but there
will be no problem
when big Jer and I here go
on a hunting expedition.
Elena, I know it's tragic,
I get it,
but we also agree
that he had to kill them.
Now we have added incentive,
so you take the least
most valuable player home,
and Jeremy and I
will finish this.
I'm sorry. Are you
saying that I should
leave him here with you?
Trust me.
I will keep him safe, ok?
[Music playing]
Ahem. I know you were, uh,
daggered for a little while,
but, uh, knocking
is still a thing.
So is writing in your
diary apparently.
I'm just checking for doubts.
You can never be too cautious
when it comes to love.
One minute, you're begging me
to compel Elena from your mind,
and the next,
I'm up coffin creek
with a dagger in my back.
Right. Well, you can
read it all you want.
I'm done with her.
Until we find the cure, right?
Hey. I'm talking
to you.
Oh, I know you are.
I'm ignoring you.
Look. We're at a bit
of a disadvantage
in this whole race
for the cure.
Team Klaus has
Jeremy the hunter,
team Shane has
Bonnie the witch.
If you're here to remind me
of our last place status,
I'm very well aware.
Actually I have a plan.
The cure is buried with Silas,
that ancient evil guy my
brother Kol is afraid of.
Shane was so eager
to prove his existence
that he gave away that he has on
of the keys to resurrecting him,
his headstone.
I see. You want to
steal it.
Yes. And then team Shane will
have to join team Rebekah,
and team Klaus will be
left out in the cold
where he belongs.
You know, just because
your eyes are closed
doesn't mean you're meditating.
Come on.
Use your breath.
Use your breath
to calm your nerves.
Great.
So now I can't even
meditate right?
What else can I fail?
Bonnie, you didn't fail.
I did an expression spell
that almost killed April.
Exactly. Almost.
Failing would have been
actually killing her.
You got, like,
a d-minus.
It's not funny.
I have all this power now,
and I'm worried
I won't be able to control it.
Bonnie, look at me.
I'm here with you.
You don't have anything
to worry about.
You are strong,
you are focused.
You are in complete control.
You're here with me.
I'm in complete control.
[Door opens]
Sheriff?
Bonnie, I'm gonna
need you to go.
What the hell are you doing?
We need to ask you
a few questions.
Are you serious? I'm
sure I can answer
without the handcuffs.
Come on. This isn't
even your jurisdiction.
Well, then I guess we better
get you to Mystic Falls asap.
Wait. Why are you
doing this?
That's something you
should ask your dad.
You really think they
went back to the bar?
Where else are they gonna go?
It's all cabins
and vacation homes.
They can't get in anywhere.
All right.
There you go.
Fine. Let's get this
over with.
Listen. Just go
one at a time,
only shoot for the heart,
don't hesitate,
and don't miss.
Save the teaching moment.
Elena's not here.
You don't have to pretend like
you give a damn about me.
I'm trying to keep you
alive, dumbass.
Come on.
[Music playing]
Something's not right.
Ahh.
Looks like we're gonna have
to find some new vampires.
What a waste.
What the hell happened?
I confess.
I did it.
Kol.
Jeremy, good to see you, mate.
Sorry about the mess.
It was a little crowded
when I arrived,
and I prefer more
intimate gatherings.
We 3 need to have
a little chat.
Care for a drink?
He's underage,
and I don't like you,
so let's just cut to it.
My brother bragged
about his plan
to complete
Jeremy's hunter's mark.
It was easy enough
to track this lot down.
They were all hiding
in the shadows.
Now killing
young vampires is easy
or old ones for that matter.
Why? What's it to you
either way?
Because, you fools, in your
zeal to find the cure,
you risk waking someone
very dangerous.
Oh. You must be talking
about Silas.
What do you know of him?
Nothing. Don't want to.
Not our problem.
Isn't it?
A few hundred years back,
I came across a group
that worshiped Silas.
His followers told me
that he would rise again,
and when he did, he would
trigger the end of all time.
You know, being an immortal,
you can see why I'm opposed
to time's ending.
I murdered all of them,
and now here you are
willing to risk raising him
in your search for the cure.
I can't exactly sit back
and let that happen, can I?
We're not gonna back off the
cure because you were told
one too many scary
bedtime stories, you idiot.
Jeremy, we were
mates in Colorado.
You're a smart lad.
Why don't you call off this
imbecilic treasure hunt?
I'm not calling
anything off, mate.
Well, I could kill you,
but then I'd have to deal
with the hunter's curse,
and I... I don't particularly
feel like being haunted
for the next century.
[Snaps fingers]
Better idea.
I'll just rip off your arms.
Jeremy, run!
Well... Headstone's
not here.
Don't ripper out on me.
We'll find it.
Oh, you're all bottled up.
You need a release.
Maybe we can find you
a voodoo doll or something.
Ah. This should
do the trick.
Exactly what you need.
The Professor's stash of herbs.
Not interested.
What happened to you? You were
so much fun in the twenties.
I was a psychotic killer with
no emotions in the 1920s.
You may have been a killer,
but you were far from
emotionless, Stefan.
You had a blast.
I know you remember.
The jazz, the booze, our
little table at Gloria's.
Don't make me
compel it out of you.
All right. Um...
I guess we had
a little bit of fun.
Thank you. So now that
we've established
that fun is, in fact, possible,
maybe you'd like to
start having some.
Don't worry
about the Professor.
He won't be back any time soon.
I made sure of that.
You're accusing me of
orchestrating a mass murder?
Do you know how ridiculous
that sounds.
It's Mystic Falls.
It's actually one of the least
ridiculous things I've heard.
Bonnie: He already
explained this, dad.
Pastor young came to him for help.
He was crazy.
No. Hew was
grief-stricken,
and Shane took advantage of it.
And somehow talked him into
killing a house full of people.
It doesn't make any sense.
I've met people
like this, Bonnie.
They're fast-talking, they're
charismatic, they're manipulators.
They prey
on the weak-minded.
Mmm. And you're worried
that's what he's doing to me.
That's why you brought
him in, isn't it?
No. We brought him in because
April young told us what he did.
Rebekah Mikaelson confirmed it.
He confessed to her.
I'm going in there.
Bonnie, no, you're not.
If he's gonna tell anyone
what he did, it's me.
Unless of course you think
I'm too weak-minded.
Bonnie, now is not the time.
Let her talk.
I think your dad's
confused about the format
of the parent-teacher
conference.
I'm so sorry.
Rebekah told them
you confessed.
I know she's lying.
You know, the truth is,
she's not.
I'm so sorry. Listen.
When I asked you to stay to
Jeremy, I never thought...
what did you expect, Elena?
It's Damon.
I never wanted
anyone to get hurt.
Well, then you shouldn't
have left him in charge.
Look. I'm sorry. I know you
didn't have a choice...
sire bond and all.
Sire bond doesn't
work like that.
All I know, Elena,
is that the old you
would have never left
Jeremy with Damon,
especially after
what happened last night.
[Cell phone rings]
Jeremy?
Jeremy: Elena,
we're in trouble.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down.
Where's Damon?
Listen to me.
Kol attacked us.
I barely got away,
but he's got Damon.
A bit ironic you
coming to me for help.
Weren't your friends just trying
to bury me in a cement tomb?
This is your fault.
You started this when you forced
Jeremy to kill those vampires.
And my little brat of a brother
has gone and made things worse.
Well, he never did like Damon.
I suppose I should do
something, shouldn't I?
Call him off, Klaus.
You are in no position
to make demands, love.
Whilst I'd like to cure you
to make more hybrids,
I do have other reasons
for finding the cure,
not the least of which
is destroying it
so you lot can't
use it against me.
Whatever our differences,
we want the same thing.
Please. Klaus,
I'm begging you.
Little brother.
Just two days home, and I'm
told you've already gone
and made a mess.
Come on, Nik. I was
only having some fun.
Those vampires were
for my hunter.
I'll make some more. There's
no shortage of people.
Where's Damon Salvatore.
I gave him a good
and proper beating
just for old time's sake.
Yes. Well, you've had
your fun.
Now let him go and come home.
Avoid any more trouble, or you'll
find yourself back in a box.
Hey. No need to be
nasty about it.
On the contrary, I find
nastiness to be essential
whenever my siblings
try to sabotage me.
Listen closely, Kol.
Stay away from the Gilbert boy.
Understand?
Fine.
I won't touch him.
You have my word.
Very good, darling.
Now stab yourself
a little bit further.
[Groaning]
If you're gonna kill me,
do it like a man.
I don't want to kill you.
I just wanted to make sure
you could be compelled.
I'm gonna rip out your spleen.
You ought to be thanking me.
You don't really want
the cure found.
You fancy Elena. I mean, even
more now that she's a vampire.
Admit it.
The last vestige
of her humanity
is her annoying
little brother Jeremy,
and deep, deep down, I bet you
want him dead, don't you?
Nope.
You're lying.
I bet you'd love to rip
his head right off...
And I'm gonna give
you your wish.
You're not gonna
remember what I say,
but you're going to
find Jeremy Gilbert,
and when you do,
you're going to kill him.
Jeremy, it's over.
You can put all this away.
Klaus still wants me
to finish the mark.
He's not gonna stop.
Ok. Well, Damon's
gonna be back soon,
and then we can figure
something out.
Seriously?
You still trust Damon?
He saved your life.
He saved the map to the cure.
He couldn't care less about me.
I care about you.
Don't.
Whatever's inside of me
that makes me want to hunt,
right now it's on overdrive.
Jeremy.
I'm sorry.
I know what I have
to do, Elena.
I really want to get
that cure for you,
but...
I just... I don't how
I'm gonna do this.
[Sighs]
So much random crap in here.
Crap, maybe.
Random, no.
Looks like Shane has
a bit of an afterlife fetish.
Hopi prayer feathers, the
han dynasty soul vase,
and that is a polynesian
sacrificial knife.
Brutal way to die, but at
least you appease the gods.
Since when did you become
such an artifact expert?
I enjoy other cultures, Stefan.
I know that might be hard
for you to understand
considering you dated a child
who only thinks about herself.
Still a sensitive
subject, I see.
Do you know why I wouldn't
compel Elena from your memory?
Because you wanted me
to suffer.
I did. It's the only
way you'll learn.
It took me a thousand years
and hundreds of betrayals
to realize
that love, caring ruins you.
Hmm.
That's awfully bleak.
Quite the opposite.
It's liberating actually.
You know why we had so much
fun in the twenties, Stefan?
Because we didn't care.
We just did what felt good...
drinking, feeding, sex.
The sex wasn't good
because we didn't care.
It was good because you're crazy.
Crazy sex is always good.
You were hardly
the model of sanity.
[Music playing]
Stop... Caring.
Good. You found it.
Question is who are you?
What happened?
Are you ok?
Kol happened.
Thank God you both got away.
If Kol had taken Jeremy.
Is here? I just want to
talk to him really fast.
He's at the grill. He
wanted to check on Matt.
Well, I should go
apologize to him.
I was... I was pretty
tough on him today.
Told my dad to
give us a minute.
Camera's off.
You can talk.
Are you sure about that?
Yeah. I don't lie.
I'm not you.
Look. I always gonna tell you the truth.
I just kept putting it off
because I was worried
how you'd react.
Bad. That's how
I react to murder.
I'm not a killer, Bonnie.
Pastor young was depressed...
I've heard this.
Skip to the part
where you convince him
to massacre 11 people.
It wasn't a massacre.
It was a ritual.
It was something
necessary to raise Silas
and get the cure that your
friends so desperately want.
If they knew people
had to die...
it doesn't matter if they die.
Silas will bring them back.
You're crazy.
I'm not crazy.
I'm just passionate.
You're full on crazy.
Do you remember
our first session?
It was about your grams, right?
You thought every time you did
magic you were causing her pain.
Aren't you curious
what's happening to her now?
Wouldn't you like
to see her again?
[Music playing]
Don't you ever take
a night off?
I took two days off
to help you out
at the lake house, remember?
I almost got killed.
Where's Jeremy?
He's in the back I think.
Hmm.
Are you doing ok?
Yeah. All things
considered.
Elena: Damon.
Are you all right?
What's going on?
Damon, what is wrong with you?
It was Kol.
He must have compelled me.
If I find Jeremy...
I might kill him.
Damon: Jeremy...
Get out of here!
Do you hear me?
Don't stop.
Kol compelled me.
There's nothing I can do!
You can't hide in here, Jer.
If I find you, you're dead.
Jeremy, are you
listening to me?
You better run!
I am coming to kill you.
You need to go now!
All you have to do
to make it stop
is tell me who sent you.
You're full of vervain,
so I know you haven't
been compelled.
Or maybe somebody compelled him
before he ingested it.
He was after the headstone.
We need to know who sent him.
Ok. Fine. So we
take him home,
wait till the vervain
is out of his system,
and then compel him and get
whatever information we want.
That's not a bad idea.
[Grunts]
He just bit off his own tongue.
So he does know something.
I guess he was compelled.
Was it my bastard
brother or yours?
Maybe it's option number 3.
There's another team
in the race.
You're saying if I help you
raise Silas you can
bring my grams back?
Don't play on my guilt, Shane.
I'm not playing on anything.
This is the truth.
You told me what happened.
Your reckless use
of magic is the reason...
don't.
Is the reason those spirits
are torturing her on the other side.
Don't.
Hurting her again
and again and again.
I said don't!
Unh!
My hand!
[Whimpers]
You can't stop, can you?
All this power
that you're feeling,
you actually like it,
don't you?
Aah! Aah! Ugh.
Look at yourself, Bonnie.
Bonnie, what are you doing?
Get out.
Get out of here.
Bonnie, stop!
You can't reason with her, mayor.
She's lost control.
Bonnie, baby, baby.
Please.
Do something!
Bonnie...
Bonnie, look at me!
Now take a deep breath.
I'm right here with you.
You are in complete control.
That's it.
Your daughter...
Is a prodigy.
With my guidance...
She'll be one of the most
powerful witches in the world...
But without it...
whew...
she's a time bomb.
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello, Elena.
What did you to Stefan?
Rescued him from his
old, dull life,
but it keeps calling.
Stefan's not in the
mood to talk right now.
Then he can listen.
I know might not care
about me right now, Stefan,
but Kol compelled Damon
to kill Jeremy.
They're somewhere in
the tunnels, and I...
it's one giant maze down here,
and I can't find them, so if
you still care about the cure
or about Jeremy, then
maybe you can come help.
Ok.
[Beep]
That is an interesting
predicament
for both of us.
Damon: Did you miss the part
where I said I'm compelled?
Don't stop!
Seriously?
You're being hunted
by a vampire,
and now you're bleeding?
Aah!
Dumb move, Jer.
You can't fight me
in closed quarters.
It was worth a shot.
Aah!
Ugh.
You're gonna have to shoot
me, Jeremy, in the heart.
I'm not gonna be able
to stop myself.
Jeremy, you are a hunter.
You know what to do.
Do it.
Do it!
Ow.
Ugh.
[Groaning]
He shot me in the head.
Stupid idiot...
Borderline brain-dead moron!
That was dumb, Jeremy.
Eh.
Should have killed me
when you had the chance.
Going somewhere?
I would if I were you.
If Damon kills the hunter,
Nik will not be pleased.
I told Nik I wouldn't
touch the kid.
I didn't.
Oh. Well,
that was clever.
I'm sure he'll really
appreciate it.
You'd really dagger me?
If I do, Damon's compulsion
ends and this is all over.
And then you're no
better than Niklaus.
Daggering siblings when
you disagree with them...
look at what this
family has become.
I mean, Elijah won't
even show his face
he's so disgusted
by our bickering.
This cure has ruined us,
and it hasn't even
been found yet.
Just imagine what would
happen if it is.
This family was ruined long
before we knew about the cure.
Kol!
I won't let you raise Silas.
Enough of this foolishness.
Put it down, Kol.
He was going to kill me.
Well, then, I think
you need a lesson
in how to properly
dagger a sibling.
Burn in hell.
Unh!
Damon, stop!
I know that you don't
want to hurt Jeremy,
so please stop.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
You're strong enough
to resist the compulsion.
I know that you are.
Why, because Stefan did?
Because I love you,
because you love me.
You'd do anything for me,
so please...
Do this for me.
I'm sorry, Elena.
Damon!
Jeremy.
Shoot now.
Hey, brother.
Long time, no see.
[Snap]
You're welcome.
[Groans]
Easy there, buddy.
You lost a lot of blood.
[Groaning]
So you bled me out?
Yeah. I didn't really
have much of a choice.
Kol's compulsion
is still in effect,
so you need to stay locked up.
We don't have
any vervain, so...
This was the only way
I could weaken you.
You sound
real torn up about it.
Shouldn't we be going
after Kol,
make him decompel me.
Yeah, yeah, sure. That
sounds easy enough, Damon.
I'll get right on that.
[Music playing]
[Coughs]
At least let me see Elena.
Come on. You know
you can't do that.
With the sire bond,
all you have to do
is tell her to
let you out of here.
It's too risky.
You're really enjoying
this, aren't you?
It's better for Elena if
you stay in here for now,
at least until we
find the cure,
and then once she's
no longer sired
and you're no longer compelled,
you can both do whatever
the hell you want.
Stefan, wait. Stefan!
[Locks door]
Stef...
Going to see Damon?
I need to talk to him.
Well, you can't. He'll just
ask you to let him out.
I won't let him out.
You won't have a choice.
You're sired.
That all?
Stefan, what are you
doing with Rebekah?
She tried to kill me.
And this will be
the second time that
Damon tried to kill Jeremy.
So I guess nobody's
perfect, right?
Are you trying to punish me?
I don't know how many times
I can apologize.
I never asked you to.
You can do whatever
you want, Elena.
I really don't care.
You're hurt.
You're hurt,
and you're acting out, Stefan.
This isn't you.
Sure it is.
You've just never
seen me like this.
You don't know what I look like
when I'm not in love with you.
I'll let Damon know
you stopped by.
I owe you an apology.
You don't owe me anything.
I'm not happy to be right.
I'm gonna get you some help.
Help? Dad, I'm ok.
Are you kidding me?
I got angry I admit,
but I knew what I was doing.
You lost control,
and Shane said...
didn't we just establish
that we couldn't trust him?
He's trying to get
under your skin.
The only thing that got under
my skin is what I saw,
which is my daughter
using dangerous magic!
And the fact that you
don't think you need help
means you need it even more.
Good evening, Gilbert clan.
What do you want, Klaus?
I've come to fetch my hunter.
Seeing as how my brother's
become a liability,
Jeremy will be safer with me.
I think I'll pass.
I've killed enough
people for you today.
You think you're
safer here? Hmm.
Clearly you don't know Kol.
He'll stop at nothing
to get what he wants,
so strange as it may seem,
I'm your best bet.
Sorry, but I think we'd
rather take our chances.
Fine, but when Kol does come...
and he will come...
be sure to let me know,
preferably before he burns
your nice little home
to the ground.
And as for you, hunter,
there's no shortage
of people to turn
and loved ones to
threaten, so sleep well.
We'll plan on finishing
our work tomorrow.
[Door opens]
Sure. Just barge
right in.
Oh. I thought not
knocking was our thing.
You didn't dagger Kol.
Well, the white oak stake
pointed at my heart
made things a little difficult.
I do believe my brother Kol
has finally lost his mind.
That's all right.
Jeremy's still alive,
and I took care of Damon.
So where'd you put it?
The headstone?
Mm-hmm.
Some place safe.
Wasn't really our deal.
Well, considering that
you've betrayed me twice
and I've betrayed you never,
I think I'm acting brilliantly,
especially since we have no idea
why that guy was looking for it.
Did you work things out
with Elena?
Do you care?
Nope. Just trying to figure
out why you're here.
Do you even have to ask?
No feelings, no attachments.
None...
Whatsoever.
This is never gonna end.
If Kol doesn't kill me first,
then Klaus is just gonna force
me to kill more innocent people.
How many is it
gonna take, 10, 100?
If you kill one
original vampire,
their entire sire line
will die with them.
That's thousands,
maybe tens of thousands
of vampires.
Kol compelled Damon
to kill you.
You're gonna kill Kol instead.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com