A few months ago, I
discovered I had a twin sister.
And then she she asked
me to take her place,
keep the secret, find our real mother
and try to stay alive.
Put yourself in my shoes.
How long could you keep up the lying game?
- I'm not interested.
- Oh, is that right?
You said it was fine, so I slept with him.
It was a mistake, Sutton.
Ted, about the therapy session on Monday,
I'll be there.
I'm so happy for you.
What's going on here?
I was just thanking her
- for tutoring me.
- You know what?
It doesn't matter.
Care to make things interesting?
You want to switch back?
Whoever loses has to stay in the cabin.
That phone I found exonerated him.
I can't beat him. The only
mistake I made was taking
your bastard ass in.
Hey, hey!
There is nothing left for me here anymore.
What about me?
Tough break, but a deal's a deal.
I left some clean towels
for you at the cabin.
I've gotten the feeling that he might
blame me for his arrest.
Hey, baby, I'm home.
Good morning, sunshine.
Uh, what are you doing?
Just watching you sleep.
I missed that.
Well, isn't that romantic?
I've been in prison for a while.
I can't believe I'm actually here with you.
Well...
was it worth the wait?
You tell me.
So, your first day as a free man.
What are your plans?
I was thinking maybe we could take that
honeymoon we've been putting off.
Oh, well, that sounds great, but...
where are we gonna go on such short notice?
As it turns out, I got a
little spot I know about.
- A little bed and breakfast?
- Hmm.
A five-star resort and spa?
Ah, now, it wouldn't be a surprise
if I told you, would it?
Oh, well, come on, just a little hint.
Please tell me.
Let's just say that this weekend
my bride finally gets
everything she deserves.
Finally.
This is Thayer.
You know what to do.
Hey, it's me again.
answer, so I'm trying you here.
I tried your cell and you didn't
that you're okay. I just want to know
I hate the way we left things.
Please call me.
Thayer?
Nope, it's me.
I wanted to see how your
night at the cabin was.
You're checking on me?
Well, of course, you're my sister.
Plus, I know how lonely it can get there.
Yeah, I can't argue with that.
But it's just for a few days, right?
We're switching back
after tennis regionals.
That was the deal.
Anyway, I'm calling
because I wanted to make
sure you're not mad at me
for what I told you
the other day about, you know.
About you sleeping with Ethan?
I told you, it's fine.
Really?
Yes, sleep with whomever you want.
Just promise me you won't do anything
to rock the boat with Ted and Kristin.
If you haven't noticed,
they're getting along better now.
I get it, Emma.
You have my word.
And, in fact, I think
you'll find that I am going
to be a sweeter, nicer
version of myself than you.
Do you have a sec?
You have nothing to
worry about. I have to go.
What's up?
I wanted to talk to you about
what happened last night.
What happened last night?
When I saw Jordan kissing Mads outside?
Oh, right, yeah, that...
that was rough.
I thought things were going so well
between me and Jordan,
and then Mads just totally
goes behind my back...
Okay, look, Laurel.
What you need to remember
is that Jordan Lyle is a worldly,
older,
dangerously sexy guy
who, let's face it,
is way out of your league.
If I remember correctly, uh, the other day,
you said he'd be lucky to have me.
And clearly you blew it,
so I think you should move on.
I mean, go for some lower
hanging fruit like a sophomore.
Or one of those guys in the clubs
in the back of the yearbook.
I... I don't get it.
I know, I know.
Love... it's very confusing.
I'm hungry for breakfast, though.
I'm thinking tofu scramble?
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Hi, Dad.
What are you doing here?
Hi, kiddo.
Your father has some news.
What is it?
Well, remember all that
pro bono work I was doing
at the burn clinic last summer?
Turns out
I was just named
Phoenix Surgical Humanitarian of the Year.
That's awesome.
Is there, like, some kind
of ceremony or something?
Yeah, the banquet's tomorrow.
Originally I was gonna go myself,
but then, since they're giving me
this award, I was kind of hoping...
Well, of course, we'll be there.
There's one more thing.
They usually ask the
recipient's significant other
to say a few words before the presentation.
So I guess the committee
doesn't know about our situation?
Actually, I was going to mention it,
but then I thought things were going
pretty well between us, so...
I know it's a lot to spring on you.
Maybe we can discuss it
during family therapy tomorrow.
Maybe.
Great. I'll see you then.
Bye.
Bye, Dad.
Bye, hon.
Bye.
Well, that was awkward.
We are going, right, Mom?
Of course, of course.
But, I mean, for me to
be giving a speech is...
Mom, please, it would mean so much to him.
And you guys have been doing better.
Well, yes, in the sense
that we can be in the
same room without fighting.
But for me to stand up
in front of an audience
and pretend that we're a happy couple...
No, why don't Laurel and I do it?
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I mean, sure, yeah, we can do it.
Sweetie, it's short notice.
Do you have time to prepare a speech?
For a bunch of nerdy doctors? Yeah.
Plus, I already know what I'm going to say.
Mads, I wasn't expecting you.
Uh, because I'm not here to see you.
Hey, is this about last night?
'Cause until Laurel
had her little meltdown,
you and I were getting
pretty hot and...
I'm not here to discuss that.
Okay, why are you here?
Maddie?
Hi, honey.
Hi.
Oh, I'm so glad to see you.
Me, too.
- You good?
- Yes.
Mr. Rybak,
we didn't get a chance to meet last night.
- I'm Jordan Lyle.
- Jordan.
- Rebecca's stepson.
- Yes, sir.
- You can call me Alec.
- All right.
- I see you two have already met?
- Barely.
We've bumped into each
other a couple times, yeah.
Hmm, well, glad you're acquainted.
Maddie, since I've moved
in here with Rebecca,
I was kind of hoping you might
think about doing the same.
Really?
That's an interesting idea, sir.
We'll see.
It's good to see that everybody's
getting to know each other.
Honey, did you tell them
about our honeymoon plans?
Honeymoon?
Um, yeah...
Sutton?
What are you doing here?
Well, the door was open, so...
So you just walked in?
Well, my godfather
is back and
I was just so excited to see him.
Well, you're kind of
interrupting a family moment.
So let me show you out.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize I was walking
into the Bizarro family reunion back there.
Why are you freaking out?
I'm not freaking out.
You were being careless.
Fine, I screwed up, but I'm
just really excited to tell you
- what happened this morning.
- What?
My dad's getting this award...
- What award?
- I don't know.
I wasn't really listening.
Maybe for giving homeless people
free boob jobs or something?
Anyway,
he asked Kristin to
introduce him at the ceremony.
She said no.
Guess who offered to speak instead.
- Excellent.
- Mm-hmm, and get this:
- we're going to family therapy.
- Mm-hmm.
And don't worry, I already
know what I'm going to say.
Okay, even so, I want
you to run it by me first.
Our plan is moving to the next phase,
and I don't want to
leave anything to chance.
Okay?
Call me later.
Okay.
Look, if you want to take a break, we...
No, let's just keep going.
We have a ton of chemistry to do left.
Okay.
Emma, I just want you to
know that I, I appreciate
you still tutoring me.
'Cause I know you're probably going
through a lot with Thayer leaving.
Ethan, let's not do this.
What?
I'm... I'm just trying to be a friend here.
You're not my friend.
And I may be helping you
study here, but I don't want
to discuss Thayer any
more than I want to talk
about what happened with you and Sutton.
Of course.
She told you that we slept
together after Jordan's party.
It's not my business.
Then, why are you acting like it is?
Because I used to think
you were better than that.
What are they doing here?
Oh, crap.
Alec, I know you wanted to
surprise me, but this place?
What are we, hillbillies?
Hurry, grab everything. They
can't know we were here. All right.
- Is this yours?
- Doesn't matter, just take it.
Damn it.
Hang on, uh, here, give me a towel, quick.
Uh...
Here, take this.
Oh, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Your keys.
Got it. Got it.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm a little rusty.
- Oh.
- Come here.
I had no idea you were so old-fashioned.
Oh, well, there's more
surprises where that came from.
That sounds good.
Look, flat screen.
Are they on their honeymoon?
I guess.
Oh, my God, what if
they start getting naked?
Ted bought this place
when they were still in diapers.
Now you couldn't pay 'em to come up here.
Oh, well, I'm sure
I will come to love it.
After all, you brought me
up here for some reason.
I'm sure I'll figure out what that is.
Why don't I give you
- the grand tour?
- Oh.
She saw us.
- No, she didn't.
- Yes, she did.
She looked right at me.
Oh.
Wait, w... wait, slow down, cowboy.
I'm not done with you in this room.
We have to go.
Let's go. There's a window.
Laurel, come on, I want to apologize
for last night, all right? I...
I don't want it to be weird between us.
Hmm, think it's late for that, don't you?
Well, it doesn't have to be.
When you invited me to
the club the other night,
I didn't know that was a
date. All right, that's my bad.
Look, you're very pretty, all right?
I'm pretty?
Yeah.
Okay, look, Jordan, any misguided feelings
I might have briefly had
for you are definitely over,
so you can save your
patronizing compliments.
That's fair enough.
Anything else?
All right, let me tell you what.
Let's go grab some breakfast,
and you can yell at me all you want.
What do you say?
I say,
have fun kissing your stepsister, creep.
Well, I didn't see that one coming.
Yeah, Alec honeymooning at the cabin.
I kind of figured him for a
Turks and Caicos kind of guy.
You gonna be okay here?
Yeah.
This is the hotel that Sutton stayed
when her car went into the lake.
You want me to come inside with you?
No.
I'm fine. Thanks.
So this means tutoring is out, I guess?
No.
Believe it or not, I don't want
to see you go back to juvie.
So...
just meet me back here later.
We'll finish our session.
Hey.
Emma?
Thanks.
Hi, I need a room, please.
It's you.
I'm sorry?
You owe me money.
I do owe you money
from the last time I was here.
What was the bill again?
You know, this isn't about the bill.
I did you a favor.
When that guy came in asking questions,
you paid me to lie and say
you were in that room alone.
Right.
Alone, well, I...
I was with that woman.
That woman. You mean women.
- What?
- Wow.
You really did take a knock
on the head that night.
Girly, there were two
women with you in that room.
- Two women?
- Yeah, two.
So, where's my 80 bucks?
I got to say, this crappy motel room
isn't exactly the ideal
place for studying Faulkner.
Yeah.
Maybe if we talk louder,
the hookers next door will learn something.
Hey, maybe that's them now.
Sutton, what are you doing here?
What does it look like I'm doing here?
Ethan gave me a little hint
about your cram session.
So I thought I'd hit the books.
Really?
You're here to study?
Well, yeah, thanks to you,
Sutton Mercer has a hefty
GPA to maintain, so...
and studying is all that's
going on here, right?
What do you think?
Anyway, you know,
I figured you'd be pretty
busy working on your speech.
What speech?
Oh, it's nothing.
Just some stupid awards thing for my dad.
Being here brings back
so many memories, which is surprising,
considering I had a head
wound last time I was here.
Yeah, funny you should say that,
because when I was checking in,
the desk clerk said something
kind of weird to me.
Well, he's weird.
What did he say?
He said that when you were here,
Annie wasn't the only person with you.
Someone else was here.
Did he now?
Well, he was so busy
hitting on me that night
that he couldn't have possibly
noticed who I was with.
Who did he think he saw?
He didn't say.
But anyway, you're right.
He...
creeped me out, too.
This is nice.
Cloth napkins,
candlelight.
Le poulet en croûte.
It's from Celine,
your favorite spot.
Well, you really did think of everything.
It's a very special wine.
I've been saving it for
a very special occasion.
I think tonight might just be that night.
Let's celebrate like tonight
is our last night on Earth.
You know, one of the things
we never talked about is what you did
the whole time I was gone.
I mean, that must have been
tough for you, having
your new husband locked up.
It was.
They were the hardest days of my life.
I'll bet.
Did you ever wonder if I was
ever getting out of there?
Now, why would I?
You're an innocent man.
I have faith in the system.
Although there was this one moment.
Oh, it's nothing.
We were both under a lot of stress.
There was this one time that
I went to see you in jail,
and... I...
could have thought that you...
thought that I was somehow...
behind framing you for Derek's murder.
That's crazy talk.
And we both know you were my rock,
you know, through the whole thing.
- Of course.
- Plus, if I thought you were framing me
about anything,
I don't think we'd be sitting here
drinking an $800 bottle of wine.
I'd be outside, burying you in the woods.
Not if I buried you first.
Touché.
Hey, girlie, hold up.
Can I help you?
Actually, I was thinking I could help you.
You know how earlier
you couldn't remember how there were
two ladies with you
that night you were here?
Yes.
My mind was blank, but yes.
So, to jog your memory,
I, uh, put together a couple sketches
of the women you were with.
So what do you think?
I think you're a very
talented artist, Carl.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but wasn't our deal that,
if I won our tennis match,
you stay hidden until after regionals?
Actually, the deal was
that I stay in the cabin,
which is now full of
middle-aged honeymooners.
Here.
What is this?
It's a speech.
I was thinking about Ted's awards banquet,
and I just thought I'd help.
That's really sweet of you, Emma,
but I have it covered. Thank you.
Are you sure?
Because this is huge, Sutton.
I mean, the family is going to be together,
and Ted and Kristin are
in such a precarious place.
I said no.
Sutton?
Laurel, wait!
What's going on?
Look who finally decided
to do her hair today.
What are you doing? What do you want?
Okay, I can't believe I'm
actually about to say this,
but I wanted to thank you
for the advice you gave me about Jordan.
Seriously?
Yeah. I mean, I don't buy
the whole out-of-my-league thing,
but you were right about
him being wrong for me.
Well, you're welcome.
I'll show you to...
Actually, no. Uh, so,
after I told off Jordan,
which was incredibly fun, by the way,
I got to wondering.
What's wrong with us?
Why do the Mercer sisters
keep picking the wrong guys?
Justin, Jordan, Ethan?
Is this you giving me love advice?
I'm just asking.
Why are you wasting your
time tutoring Ethan, the guy
who broke your heart, when
you have someone like Thayer?
Oh, yeah, Thayer.
Of course, he's just so sweet and kind
and loyal as a puppy dog.
You say that like it's a bad thing.
He cares about you.
And for a while there,
I thought you cared about him, too.
Damn it!
Alec? Alec?!
What happened to the power?
Alec? Are you there?
Alec, where are you?
Alec?
Is this a joke?
That was quite a spill you took.
Get away.
You did that on purpose.
- What?
- I know what you're doing.
This whole honeymoon,
the little looks, the cryptic comments.
You're, you're screwing with my head!
I know those lights
didn't go off by themselves.
Yes, they did. That's
exactly what happened, honey.
I went outside to check the breakers,
and the box was locked.
I had to come back in and
get the key. I changed it.
You're lying.
Why don't you just cut this
whole loving husband act
and tell me why you brought me up here?
Do you really think I framed you?
Sweetheart, we've been through this.
If I still thought that, then
where are the divorce papers?
What are we doing up here on our honeymoon?
Why would I move into your house and ask
my daughter to do the exact same thing?
How could I possibly make love to you?
Sweetheart, if I thought you betrayed me
and yet did all those things,
what kind of man would that make me?
Come here.
Why do I get the feeling
you're not just running late?
I'm sorry.
I would have called earlier,
but something really important came up.
Sound like you're on the road.
I'm on a bus... to L.A.
Of course you are.
I care about him, Ethan.
And we both know you're
better off being tutored
by somebody else anyway.
You're right.
Tell Thayer hey.
I'm... really sorry.
So am I.
Thought Sutton was coming
over to help you study.
It's a change of plans.
You pissed her off, didn't you?
Yes, I did. Anything else?
Ethan, the way I see it,
you can either sit here
and feel sorry for yourself,
or you can go find Sutton
and beg for forgiveness.
Because I'm telling you,
her help is the only thing
that is standing between you
and a trip back to juvie right now.
It's a good speech, Dan.
Just a little too late.
Look, nobody wants
these two back together more than I do,
but, I mean, one day,
they're fighting in public,
and the next day we're in counseling trying
to work things out.
Meanwhile, everyone's miserable..
Honey, it's a process.
Your mother and I are both
working very hard to try...
When does it end? I'm sorry, I know
this is going to sound terrible,
but sometimes I look around me and see how
this is affecting everybody,
and I just think maybe the
two of you are better off...
What are you saying, Sutton?
You want Mom and Dad to
get a divorce just because
it's too hard for you to
watch them work things out?
I'm saying that they
need to make a decision
and stick with it.
Do you have any idea how
selfish you sound right now?
Oh, really, Laurel? And what
if Mom actually wants a divorce?
Okay, I think maybe everyone
needs to take a little time-out.
Who asked you?
- Laurel!
- That's okay.
Actually, I think...
I think I understand what Sutton is saying.
And in her own way, she's, she's
just trying to look out for me.
Why do you think that?
Well, Sutton's always been strong-willed,
and while it hasn't made
it easy being her mom,
I've always just admired that strength.
You know, when she was a baby,
the night Sutton came
home to live with us was
the happiest of my life,
but I was terrified.
I mean, the adoption...
it happened so quickly.
I felt so unprepared.
What if I did something wrong?
What if you cried, and
I couldn't comfort you?
I stayed with you in the nursery
all night just holding you.
And you know what?
You didn't cry at all.
You were so calm, just looking around,
taking everything in.
I know this sounds crazy,
but it was almost...
it's almost like you
were being strong for me.
It's great that you
intercepted that drawing of me,
but it is just a reminder that
we are running out of time.
I think it's time we step things up.
Well, what does that mean exactly?
Because we're doing everything that we can.
Well, are we?
I mean, I hate to say it, Sutton,
but it sounds like family
therapy was kind of a bust.
Okay, look, I know it didn't
go as well as I had planned,
but I'm working on this
speech for the banquet,
and trust me...
I am covering everything:
the lies, the infidelity, the fights
between Ted and Kristin.
Well, that's good,
um, but I think we need to take
things a little bit further.
Well, how much further?
I mean, when you take that stage
with Kristin sitting in the front row,
that's when you tell everybody the truth;
that Dr. Ted Mercer is
your biological father.
- You're kidding.
- Not at all.
But are you sure?
I mean, look, I know that that's huge,
But don't you think it's a little much?
Plus, people will know that
you're my mother if I say that.
I know...
And no one will be more shocked than I.
After all, who knew that
you were the daughter
I was forced to give up 17 years ago?
Well, what about Alec?
What's he gonna say when
all of this comes out?
Don't worry about that.
You just work on the speech,
and when the time comes,
I'll take care of Alec Rybak.
What's with the suitcase?
I mean, I know we've been kind
of been avoiding each other,
but you're moving out?
You're right, I have been avoiding you,
but that's not why I'm leaving.
Um...
my dad is staying at Rebecca's now
and wants me to move in with him tomorrow.
Rebecca's... where Jordan lives.
Unfortunately.
You know, if you liked him,
you could have just told me.
Well, the thing is, I don't.
And now I'm just really
sorry that this whole
stupid incident came between us.
Yeah, me, too.
We're friends?
Yeah, friends.
Well, then, as your friend...
and I know you say you're not interested...
but I'm totally over Jordan,
so if you're thinking of
kissing him again, go for it.
Thank you, but there
are a million reasons why
that's never gonna happen,
including the fact that
we are practically related.
And you're sure about that?
Positive.
Hi! Thayer, thank God.
Why didn't you call me back?
Did you get my message about
the desk clerk telling me
that there were two women at the motel?
Okay, slow down.
What? I thought you'd be happy to see me.
You asked me to come here, and here I am.
Yeah, I am, but I asked you to
come with me... two days ago.
I didn't realize there
was an expiration date.
Oh, hey! Who's this?
Uh...
uh...
No one.
Emma...
Emma, could you stop for a second?
That girl you saw is just...
What? Payback? Look, maybe
I should have said yes
and come with you out here.
But you need to get past the stupid idea
that I have feelings for Ethan!
Okay, listen, I really don't
want to talk about this right now, okay?
Right now or ever?
Listen, stop.
Can I at least give you
a ride to the bus station?
Don't bother.
You don't want to keep your blonde waiting.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Big day, huh?
Yeah.
It could end up being a lot
bigger than people realize.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Just nervous for my speech.
Still I'm not quite sure
what I'm going to say.
Yeah, well, before she left, Emma seemed
kind of worried about that, too.
Big surprise.
She always expects the worst of me.
Well, maybe this is your
chance to prove her wrong.
Oh, hey, sweetheart.
Oh, you look beautiful.
Thank you.
You, too.
You feeling nervous about your speech?
Little more than I thought I would.
It's gonna be fine.
Um...
hey, Mom, that story you told yesterday
at therapy about my first night at home?
How come you never told me that before?
Well, honey, I'm... I'm sure I did.
Maybe it's just the
first time you listened.
Oh, my.
Hey there.
Moving in already?
No, not until tomorrow.
- I'm just dropping off a few things.
- Why don't you
drop your bags and hang out for a minute?
No, thank you.
Well, why don't you let me help you?
Unpack later.
What the hell was that?
Stop smiling.
'Cause whatever you think is
about to happen really isn't.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah.
What's really going on here, Mads?
And don't say dropping
the sweaters off and stuff,
'cause you could do that tomorrow.
I promised myself I wouldn't.
Well, then, I guess you lied.
The biggest gift my father
has given me is the example he's set
by donating his time and
talents to others in need.
That's why we're here today,
and it's why I'm proud to call him my dad.
So...
I had written a speech
about my dad...
um, bunch of clichés
about how great of a doctor he is,
how great of a humanitarian,
and don't get me wrong,
that's very true.
But today I want to
talk about another truth.
Something you don't know about Ted Mercer.
And that...
and that...
is...
that his greatest accomplishment
and the smartest thing
he has ever done was to
marry my mom Kristin Mercer.
Because she is the one
who makes this family work.
And together, she and my dad
have built a life that any child would
be so lucky to be a part of.
Even an ungrateful daughter
who hasn't always paid attention
enough to notice.
Honey, that was...
Ladies and gentlemen,
Phoenix Surgical Humanitarian
of the Year, Dr. Ted Mercer.
Hey, Sutton.
Ethan, not right now, please.
W... what? That was great.
No, it wasn't.
You don't understand. It wasn't great.
Are you kidding me? You were real up there.
Okay, so many times you've
talked about how you've changed,
but that was from the heart.
All right, that was the...
that was the Sutton Mercer
from the ranch that night.
Well, wonderful.
I gave a sappy speech about my parents
in front of a bunch of doctors.
What is that going to get me?
This.
Home sweet home.
So quiet.
Jordan.
I think I hear him out by the pool.
All right, well, will you say hi for me?
- I'm gonna go upstairs and take a bath.
- Sure.
Bye, baby.
Alec.
Hey.
How was the, uh, how was the honeymoon?
It was memorable.
Good.
You're doing laps at this hour, huh?
Yeah.
You haven't seen Mads, have you?
She was going to stop by
here and drop some stuff off.
No, I haven't seen her.
She might have been here earlier
while I was gone, though. Don't know.
Good night.
I thought you said you weren't
going to do that anymore.
Well, I thought so, too.
And now we're living under the same roof.
So, things went pretty
bad with Thayer, huh?
Yeah.
Should have known it
wouldn't work out, though,
when he didn't return
any of my phone calls.
Oh, well, when are you coming back?
Soon.
The last bus out last night was canceled,
so I had to sleep here at the
station, and it was just...
Shower's free if you want it.
Who are you talking to?
- Sutton.
- Oh, great.
Hey, I didn't realize you'd
left already, but I just wanted
to say good luck at regionals
and reiterate how completely genius
that speech was last night.
Thank you.
Love you.
Anyways, um,
I guess I will just check
in on you later, okay?
Wait, Mads, no, don't, tell me what...
Sutton, I thought you were on your...
Running late, so do you mind moving?
I can get a yogurt.
Thank you.
Saguaro Bus Lines 237
to Riverside, San Bernardino,
and Phoenix, now boarding.
Thank you.
Let's see...
You missed this.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I checked the bus schedule,
figured I still might be able to catch you.
Listen, Emma, that girl you saw
at my apartment is just a friend.
We surf together, but that's it.
Well, why didn't you just tell me that?
Because I can be hardheaded sometimes.
But I also don't want
to be one of those guys
That lets pride get in the
way of what he really wants.
And what do you really want?
One question:
those messages you left about Sutton
and the second woman at the motel...
did you come here because you want my help
or because you want me?
Both.
Thayer, when you left, I... I...
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
What the hell happened at the banquet?
I don't know, I...
You had a golden
opportunity and you folded.
Are you going soft on me?
No...
Look, I just realized that
my feelings for Kristin
are a little bit more
complicated than I had thought.
And I know she's not my mother, but I...
But maybe you prefer her to be.
No.
I was just up on that stage,
and... and to humiliate her
in front of everybody...
I'm just not as okay with it as you are.
Well, I'm very sorry to
hear that, sweetheart,
because now you've
forced me to do something
I was hoping I could avoid.
What is this?
It's a journal, handwritten
by Kristin Mercer.
Read it and you'll see,
when you were a baby, that
this "wonderful mother" that
you spoke so glowingly about
wanted to give you away.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -