[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.0.2
; 欢迎访问电波字幕组 http://www.dbfansub.com/
Title: DBfansub
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 1280
PlayResY: 720

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00030304,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,5,5,2,0
Style: Image,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,7,0,0,0,0
Style: 工作表,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 背景,Arial,20,&HA0FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 片尾,方正喵呜体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TMP片名,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 电波,张海山锐谐体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.44,工作表,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H666562&\b1}{\fn时尚中黑简体}翻译: 菁菁菁 heya 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.44,0:00:10.57,工作表,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\3c&H666562&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)}{\fn时尚中黑简体}校对: 三好 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.57,0:00:15.69,工作表,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体}后期: 东仔 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.69,0:00:20.69,工作表,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\an8}{\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体\b1}压制: 猴给力 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:20.70,背景,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\c&H96955E&\fscx4200\fscy410\an8\fad(800,800)\pos(642,0)}m 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 4 0 9 0 13 b 4 13 9 13 13 13 b 13 9 13 4 13 0 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.37,0:30:20.11,片尾,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正喵呜体}{\fs70\c&H20F0FF&\b1}电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}官方网站:www.dbfansub.com\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}新浪微博:@电波字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.34,0:02:02.03,TMP片名,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}{\c&H000000&\fn微软雅黑\b1\3c&HAC7400&\fs65}明迪烦事多{\c&HF6DAAD&\3c&H371E00&\fn微软雅黑\b1\fs42}    第一季 第十四集
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.39,0:02:07.02,电波,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(48,713,854,713,0,450)\c&H7BE8DF&}{\fs64\c&H77E8FE&\b1\fn张海山锐谐体}电波诚译
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.53,0:00:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝国大厦在情人节那天竣工的\N{\fs38}The empire state building on Valentine's day,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.89,0:00:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它在一年中最浪漫的一天中\N{\fs38}the most romantic building in the world
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.81,0:00:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荣升为世界上最浪漫的建筑\N{\fs38}on the most romantic day of the year.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.45,0:00:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太多难忘的浪漫史曾在这上演\N{\fs38}So many memorable romances have played out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.35,0:00:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如Deborah Kerr和Cary Grant\N{\fs38}Deborah Kerr and Cary Grant
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.12,0:00:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在电影<金玉盟>中\N{\fs38}in an affair to remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.75,0:00:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说"给我一个吻 就吻在脸上吧 瞧"\N{\fs38}"Give me a smooch, right on the mug", see
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.76,0:00:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对Cary Grant简直了如指掌\N{\fs38}I do a pretty spot-on Cary Grant.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.09,0:00:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 第二最浪漫的喜剧\N{\fs38}And of course, the second-best romantic comedy
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.36,0:00:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是Meg Ryan和Tom Hanks创造的\N{\fs38}that Meg Ryan and Tom Hanks ever made:
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.26,0:00:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,<西雅图夜未眠>了\N{\fs38}Sleepless in Seattle.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.93,0:00:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每隔几周 我就会买张门票\N{\fs38}Every couple weeks, I buy a ticket
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.23,0:00:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去帝国大厦的过道晃悠晃悠\N{\fs38}and hang out in the lobby of the empire state building
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.10,0:00:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看是否能遇见我的真爱\N{\fs38}to see if I will meet my one true love.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.04,0:00:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队长 她又来了\N{\fs38}Captain, she's back.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.28,0:00:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你时不时的来这里\N{\fs38}So you come here regularly
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.49,0:00:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是来监测大厦的设施吗\N{\fs38}to monitor the base of the building.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.46,0:00:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来这是来见某个特殊的人\N{\fs38}I'm here to meet that special someone,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.91,0:00:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我遇到了 我们就会去大厦顶部\N{\fs38}and when I do, we're gonna go to the top,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.17,0:00:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 嘣 放烟花\N{\fs38}and then, boom! Fireworks.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.18,0:00:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么那个特殊的人是谁\N{\fs38}And who is that person?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.47,0:00:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没遇到他\N{\fs38}I haven't met him yet,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.72,0:00:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我一遇到他我就会告诉你\N{\fs38}but I can tell when I find him,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.05,0:00:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会共度余生\N{\fs38}we're going to spend eternity together.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.17,0:00:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能描述下他的样子吗\N{\fs38}Could you describe him?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.39,0:00:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 他30多的样子\N{\fs38}All right, well, he's in his mid-30s.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.18,0:00:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高高的 健康的小麦色 热情但带有神秘感\N{\fs38}He is tall, dark, intense, mysterious...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.85,0:00:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你所说的\N{\fs38}You understand why what you're telling us
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.40,0:01:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会引起我们极大的重视 对吧\N{\fs38}would cause us serious concern.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.15,0:01:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道 但我情不自禁\N{\fs38}Yeah. I can't help it,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.52,0:01:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂得 即便处在危机重重中\N{\fs38}you know, even though it's dangerous,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.19,0:01:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我是个真正的信仰者\N{\fs38}because I am a true believer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.74,0:01:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要国土安全局的Miller\N{\fs38}Hey, we're gonna need Miller from homeland security.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.58,0:01:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国土安全局\N{\fs38}Homeland security?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.99,0:01:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错的电视剧啊\N{\fs38}That's a cool show.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.24,0:01:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你的包里放着护照\N{\fs38}Why do you have a bag with a passport
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.86,0:01:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和3个手机\N{\fs38}and three cell phones?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.08,0:01:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 这个是用来上网的\N{\fs38}Okay, well, this is for the Internet,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.12,0:01:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是用来发短信的\N{\fs38}this is for texting,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.83,0:01:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个翻盖手机是因为我不知道\N{\fs38}and this flip phone is because I do not know
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.50,0:01:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何转交我旧的交易合同才带的\N{\fs38}how to transfer my old contacts.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.84,0:01:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经花了好多时间\N{\fs38}You know, we've been spending so much time
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.49,0:01:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来谈论我的事\N{\fs38}talking about me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.83,0:01:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都还没问你任何问题呢\N{\fs38}that I haven't asked you anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.13,0:01:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你对什么感兴趣  - 保护这栋大楼\N{\fs38}- What are you into?  - Protecting this building.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.71,0:01:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我喜欢 过时的如此完美\N{\fs38}Ooh, I love that. It's so old-fashioned.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.25,0:01:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有完美的络腮胡\N{\fs38}You have great facial hair.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.89,0:01:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就喜欢有络腮胡的男人\N{\fs38}I love a guy with a beard.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.05,0:01:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能摸摸吗\N{\fs38}Can I touch it?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.19,0:01:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把手放在桌上\N{\fs38}Hands on the table, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.69,0:01:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 如果你喜欢我这很正常\N{\fs38}Hey, it's cool if you're into me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.27,0:01:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯文加内特就曾经带我去P.F.Chang喝咖啡\N{\fs38}Kevin Garnett once bought me a coke at a P.F. Chang's.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.27,0:01:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}{\an8}凯文加内特:著名NBA球星 P.F.Chang:美式连锁中餐厅
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.39,0:01:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真不矜持啊\N{\fs38}You're not helping yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.78,0:01:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是说我没看到你戴婚戒\N{\fs38}I'm just saying I don't see a wedding ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.56,0:01:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问这里是不是有位"联合保卫解决条例夫人"\N{\fs38}Is there a Mrs. Confederated security solutions?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.98,0:01:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 大神啊\N{\fs38}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.35,0:01:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本可以回答"是的"\N{\fs38}You could've just said yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.42,0:02:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lahiri医生 Castellano医生\N{\fs38}Dr. Lahiri, there's something wrong
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.72,0:02:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出了点问题\N{\fs38}with Dr. Castellano.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.14,0:02:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他有可能挂了  - 什么\N{\fs38}- He might be dead.  - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.73,0:02:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 都有味道了  - 好吧 \N{\fs38}- There's definitely a smell.  - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.43,0:02:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 哦 老天爷\N{\fs38}Danny... oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.25,0:02:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣母玛利亚 搞毛线啊\N{\fs38}Holy crap! What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.15,0:02:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fs38}Yep?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.35,0:02:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 快起来 你在搞笑吧\N{\fs38}Danny, get up. Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.70,0:02:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好啦 我起来了  - 把裤子穿上\N{\fs38}- Okay, I'm up.   - Put some pants on.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.84,0:02:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都可以看到你小弟弟的轮廓了\N{\fs38}I can see the outline of your penis.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.37,0:02:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道独眼美女抛弃了你\N{\fs38}I know that eye patch dumped you,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.54,0:02:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你不能整夜在办公室喝的烂醉如泥啊\N{\fs38}but you can't just spend the night in your office, drunk,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.43,0:02:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你的小钢琴弹唱怪叔叔Bruce Springsteen的歌\N{\fs38}playing weird Bruce Springsteen songs on your tiny piano.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.55,0:02:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样了\N{\fs38}Stop that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.80,0:02:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 哦 天 我站的太快了\N{\fs38}What's... oh, God. I stood up too quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.72,0:02:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟透了 你到底是怎么了\N{\fs38}This is awful. What's the matter with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.72,0:02:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的声音太大了\N{\fs38}Your voice is too loud.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.84,0:02:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我怎么了 而是你怎么了\N{\fs38}This isn't me. It's you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.94,0:02:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 这可不是我\N{\fs38}Okay, that is not me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.19,0:02:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我躺在地上的时候 可是萌的死人\N{\fs38}When I lay on the floor, it's adorable,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.31,0:02:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,且让人心生犹怜\N{\fs38}and it is tragic.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.44,0:02:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你躺在地上的时候\N{\fs38}When you lay on the floor,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.64,0:02:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来就像只翻过来的瓢虫\N{\fs38}you look like an upside-down ladybug.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.51,0:02:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪 敢情今天我是唯一一个\N{\fs38}My God, am I the only person not crawling about
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.36,0:02:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没在地上爬的人啊\N{\fs38}on the floor today?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.52,0:02:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们 我把Mike和Ike掉地上了\N{\fs38}You guys, I dropped a Mike and Ike on the floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.35,0:02:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你们帮我找找\N{\fs38}I need all eyes on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.79,0:02:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 你是个成年人了 快起来\N{\fs38}Danny, you're a grown-up. Get up.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.35,0:03:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说对了\N{\fs38}You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.40,0:03:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会好好收拾自己的\N{\fs38}I'm gonna get myself together.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.49,0:03:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会努力的\N{\fs38}I'm gonna pull it together.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.82,0:03:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会碰到另一个姑娘 然后一切就会好起来了\N{\fs38}I'm gonna meet another girl. It's gonna be good.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.13,0:03:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现每次我伤心的时候\N{\fs38}I have found that when I am heartbroken,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.53,0:03:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全身心投入工作是最给力的治愈方法\N{\fs38}it is actually best to throw myself into work.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.46,0:03:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是为什么 作为对你的支持\N{\fs38}Which is why, on Thursday, I am going to do you
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.41,0:03:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在周二整个晚上 我会把\N{\fs38}the favor of giving you all of my patients
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.05,0:03:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所有的病人都交给你\N{\fs38}for the whole night.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.17,0:03:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mindy 没问题\N{\fs38}Mindy, it's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.30,0:03:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会在周二晚上照顾你的病人\N{\fs38}I'll look after your patients on Thursday.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.37,0:03:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受你的情人节\N{\fs38}You enjoy your Valentine's day.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.59,0:03:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦 周二是情人节  - 是的 不错吧\N{\fs38}- Oh, is Thursday Valentine's day?  - Yes. Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.06,0:03:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我都不记得了 好吧\N{\fs38}I-I hadn't remembered. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.17,0:03:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 你怎么愿意 所有的病人 \N{\fs38}Wait, how come you, of all people,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.38,0:03:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你就没有情人节计划吗\N{\fs38}don't have plans on Valentine's day?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.66,0:03:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为一个避免\N{\fs38}Well, as a man who's looking to avoid
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.31,0:03:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与人建立承诺关系的人\N{\fs38}a committed relationship,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.60,0:03:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情人节就成了我的雷区\N{\fs38}Valentine's day can be something of a minefield.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.35,0:03:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"哦 12朵玫瑰啊 你肯定真的很喜欢我"\N{\fs38}"Oh, a dozen roses. You must really like me."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.48,0:03:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嘿 你想要一块去吃点点心吗"\N{\fs38}"Hey, do you want to share a dessert?"
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.19,0:03:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"哦 这就意味着你肯定\N{\fs38}"Oh, that means you must want
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.00,0:03:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想见见我住在明尼阿波利斯的父母了"\N{\fs38}to meet my parents, who live in Minneapolis."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.32,0:03:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直是一个感情丰富的波斯尼亚\N{\fs38}It's an emotional Bosnia.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.94,0:03:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 想想看我会出去吗 谢了  - 好吧 谢了\N{\fs38}- Think I'll sit it out, thanks.  - Well, great.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.49,0:03:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会和Jamie一起度过情人节\N{\fs38}Then I can have Valentine's day with Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.69,0:03:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是"Lucy和Jamie"那一对里的Jamie吗\N{\fs38}As in Jamie and Lucy?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.75,0:03:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可真是一对丽人啊\N{\fs38}Now, there's a great couple.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.78,0:03:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是 不是"Lucy和Jamie"那一对里的Jamie\N{\fs38}Nope, not as in Jamie and Lucy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.40,0:03:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是"Mindy和Jamie"那一对里的Jamie\N{\fs38}As in Jamie and Mindy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.73,0:03:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你就不担心他们之间若有若无的\N{\fs38}But aren't you worried about the incredible chemistry
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.50,0:03:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让人难以置信的化学反应吗\N{\fs38}they seem to have?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.57,0:03:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们才没什么良好的化学反应\N{\fs38}They don't have good chemistry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.82,0:03:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和Jamie才有良好的化学反应\N{\fs38}I have good chemistry with Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.12,0:03:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真孤单啊\N{\fs38}I'm really lonely.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.71,0:03:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去现代艺术学博物馆真是个好主意 Mindy\N{\fs38}Moma was such a fun idea, Mindy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.96,0:03:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我爱现代艺术博物馆  - 嗯\N{\fs38}- I love modern art museums.  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.80,0:04:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得它们给我的威胁比较少\N{\fs38}I feel like they're less intimidating
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.18,0:04:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我认为我也可以投身于艺术\N{\fs38}'cause I think I could do the art.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.13,0:04:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 你知道么 你的标签出来了\N{\fs38}Oh, you know what? Your sticker is coming off.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.63,0:04:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 别管它了\N{\fs38}Oh, actually, leave it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.77,0:04:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让大家知道\N{\fs38}I like people to know that I had
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.89,0:04:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比他们多了一个被文化陶冶的一天\N{\fs38}a more cultural day than they did.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.19,0:04:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 就像文艺版的"我投票了"\N{\fs38}Oh, it's like the artsy version of "I voted."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.86,0:04:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是的  我还把两年前的\N{\fs38}Oh, yes, I have a ski lift ticket
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.92,0:04:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滑雪门票放在我的大衣里\N{\fs38}on my parka from two years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.39,0:04:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你以教拉丁语为生的时候\N{\fs38}When you teach Latin for a living,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.56,0:04:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它有时可以让你看起来像个运动员\N{\fs38}it helps to look like a huge jock sometimes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.93,0:04:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 伙计们\N{\fs38}Hey, you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.98,0:04:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我迟到了\N{\fs38}Sorry I'm late.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.98,0:04:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 没关系\N{\fs38}No, not at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.20,0:04:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被告的律师团体\N{\fs38}It turns out the defendant's gang
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.95,0:04:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 有我家庭住址 去我家闹了一把  - 什么\N{\fs38}- had a copy of my home address, became a thing.  - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.82,0:04:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 什么  - 哦 天啊 \N{\fs38}- What? - Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.94,0:04:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们总威胁我 但从未成功\N{\fs38}They always threaten me. Nothing ever pans out.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.77,0:04:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你能相信这姑娘都经历了些什么  - 不能\N{\fs38}- Can you believe what this girl deals with?  - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.04,0:04:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天 她都盯着那些凶手 \N{\fs38}Every day, she looks murderers in the eye and puts them
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.04,0:04:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后送他们去监狱度过下半生\N{\fs38}in prison for the rest of their lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.54,0:04:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哇  - 很重要的\N{\fs38}- Wow. - So important.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.91,0:04:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到压力重重的情况\N{\fs38}I mean, speaking of stressful situations,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.91,0:04:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚我接生了一个宝宝\N{\fs38}I delivered a baby last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.08,0:04:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他并不想出来\N{\fs38}He did not want to be born.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.28,0:04:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他简直恨我入骨\N{\fs38}He was really mad at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.55,0:04:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴他没有我的家庭住址\N{\fs38}I'm glad he didn't have my home address.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.05,0:04:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真搞笑\N{\fs38}That's really funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.39,0:04:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 说真的 \N{\fs38}Hey, seriously, though, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.79,0:04:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你担心你的安危 如果你任何时间想待在我家\N{\fs38}if you ever fear for your safety, you still have a key.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.51,0:04:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂得 你可以随时找我拿钥匙\N{\fs38}If you ever want to stay at my place,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.96,0:04:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你可以的 对吧\N{\fs38}you know you can, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.06,0:04:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我宁愿接下锡那罗亚的企业\N{\fs38}Well, I would rather take on the Sinaloa cartel
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.13,0:04:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不愿意去这个人家里和水压器奋战\N{\fs38}than deal with the water pressure in this guy's shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.18,0:04:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有那么糟吧\N{\fs38}It's not that bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.90,0:04:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那么糟吧\N{\fs38}It's not that bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.10,0:04:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个大好人啊\N{\fs38}You're so great.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.47,0:04:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该找个男朋友\N{\fs38}You should have a boyfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.30,0:04:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真想找个酷酷的男人 除了那些我遇到的\N{\fs38}I would love to meet a cool guy, except all the guys I meet
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.19,0:05:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,19岁的犯人和80岁的法官大人\N{\fs38}are either 19-year-old murderers or 80-year-old judges.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.19,0:05:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗 我想我可以帮你介绍介绍\N{\fs38}You know what, I think I'm gonna find you someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.78,0:05:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不不 我真不想她去试试  - 好啊 不错 \N{\fs38}- No, I really wouldn't try.  - Yeah, great.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.20,0:05:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这姑娘是我一生中遇到的最挑剔的约会对象了\N{\fs38}This girl is the pickiest dater I have ever met in my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.86,0:05:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 实际上我是个优秀的媒人\N{\fs38}No, no, I'm actually a very good matchmaker.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.58,0:05:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧 祝你好运\N{\fs38}Well, I wish you luck,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.03,0:05:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没人可以配上这个姑娘\N{\fs38}but no one's ever good enough for this girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.25,0:05:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我根本没有尝试\N{\fs38}So I wouldn't even try.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.32,0:05:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mindy在博物馆的时候\N{\fs38}So Mindy at the museum...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.42,0:05:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 Danny\N{\fs38}Ah, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.18,0:05:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撕掉你的遗书吧 我有个好消息\N{\fs38}Tear up that suicide note. I have great news.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.13,0:05:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 但这不是遗书\N{\fs38}Okay, that wasn't a suicide note.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.96,0:05:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在写针对擅闯马路的罚单的抗议书\N{\fs38}I was contesting a jaywalking ticket.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.63,0:05:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我真是抱歉\N{\fs38}Oh. I am sorry about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.93,0:05:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 我准备给你安排一次约会\N{\fs38}Danny, I am going to set you up on a date.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.55,0:05:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早你还说我应该积投身于工作当中\N{\fs38}This morning you said I should throw myself back into work.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.89,0:05:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 呃 6小时以前 好吧\N{\fs38}That was, like, six hours ago, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.14,0:05:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于某些虫子来说这已经是一辈子了\N{\fs38}That's an entire lifetime for some bugs.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.34,0:05:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会喜欢这个女孩的\N{\fs38}You're gonna love this girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.47,0:05:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她美丽 聪明\N{\fs38}She is pretty. She is smart.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.39,0:05:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 她还有款小型摩托车  - 啊\N{\fs38}- She owns a motor scooter.  - Ah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.48,0:05:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是Lucy  - 是"Lucy和Jamie"那一对里Lucy吗\N{\fs38}- It's Lucy.  - Lucy of Jamie and Lucy?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.98,0:05:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他们分手了吗  - 我在和"Mindy和Jamie"\N{\fs38}- They broke up?  - I am dating Jamie
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.62,0:05:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对中的Jamie约会\N{\fs38}of Jamie and Mindy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.78,0:05:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们亲过嘴了 Danny\N{\fs38}We kissed mouths, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.82,0:05:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我不知道\N{\fs38}Okay, I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.85,0:05:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是...不确定自己是否准备好了\N{\fs38}I just... I don't know if I'm ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.15,0:05:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还可以顺便帮我个忙\N{\fs38}Well, you would also be doing me a huge favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.04,0:05:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你和Lucy在一起了\N{\fs38}If you spend time with Lucy,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.62,0:05:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jamie就不会花大把时间和她在一起了\N{\fs38}then Jamie won't spend as much time with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.29,0:05:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 这是件大事\N{\fs38}Also, this is a big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.46,0:05:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在给你安排约会\N{\fs38}I am setting you up with someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.54,0:05:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可从没给我安排过约会\N{\fs38}You never set me up with anybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.81,0:05:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是 我可是帮你和Reynaldo拉了红线\N{\fs38}That's not true. I hooked you up with Reynaldo.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.26,0:05:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你的狐朋狗友  - 是啊\N{\fs38}- Your garbage man?  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.15,0:06:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他确实帅的冒烟 但是他有点自负\N{\fs38}He was smokin' hot, but he was a little pretentious.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.12,0:06:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有点读心人的感觉 如果我可以这么说的话\N{\fs38}A little bit too well read, if I may say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.44,0:06:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 就当帮帮我吧\N{\fs38}Danny, please do this for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.45,0:06:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我能考虑考虑吗  - Danny\N{\fs38}- Can I think about it?  - Danny!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.57,0:06:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太自私了\N{\fs38}You are so selfish!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.71,0:06:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不管你是不是灰心丧气\N{\fs38}I don't care if you're depressed!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.94,0:06:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 就帮我这一回吧   - 好了 住手\N{\fs38}- Just help me out for once!  - Okay, stop...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.96,0:06:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好了   - 除非你帮我这一回\N{\fs38}- All right.  - I am gonna die alone
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.08,0:06:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不然我会孤独到死的  - 别再打我了\N{\fs38}- unless you do this for me.  - Stop hitting me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.46,0:06:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去和她约会 行了吧\N{\fs38}I'll go on one date with her, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.83,0:06:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你说真的  - 就一次\N{\fs38}- Are you serious?  - One.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.13,0:06:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 上帝 Danny 谢谢你 太感谢你了\N{\fs38}Oh, my God, Danny, thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.62,0:06:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好了  - 如果有人对你很刻薄\N{\fs38}- Okay.  - When everyone's mean about you,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.95,0:06:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总会处于维护你的前线\N{\fs38}I defend you most of the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.47,0:06:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 抱够了抱够了 谢啦\N{\fs38}Okay, I'm good on the hug, though.Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.80,0:06:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为表示我对你此次善行的衷心感谢\N{\fs38}To show my gratitude for this kindness,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.59,0:06:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,<家庭主妇真人秀> 你可以选一个你想看的城市的哦\N{\fs38}we can choose any city of real housewives to watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.96,0:06:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈阿密\N{\fs38}Miami.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.01,0:06:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题\N{\fs38}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.60,0:06:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Deborah 你喜欢在太平间工作吗\N{\fs38}Deborah, do you like working in the morgue?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.34,0:06:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我不会听到病人的抱怨\N{\fs38}Well, I don't get a lot of patient complaints.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.83,0:06:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在太平间工作真是有意思啊\N{\fs38}It's funny that you work in the morgue
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.60,0:06:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我的名字叫Morg-an\N{\fs38}because my name is Morg-an.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.34,0:06:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请等等 等等 等等\N{\fs38}Please wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.31,0:06:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\N{\fs38}Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.34,0:06:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 抱歉\N{\fs38}Nothing. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.34,0:06:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额 Reed医生\N{\fs38}Uh, Dr. Reed.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.23,0:06:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到我调戏那个妹子了吗\N{\fs38}Did you see me hit on that girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.73,0:06:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不幸的是 我看到了\N{\fs38}Unfortunately, I did, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.86,0:06:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相中她很久了\N{\fs38}I've had my eye on her for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.85,0:06:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备带她去打网球\N{\fs38}I'm gonna take her to the batting cages,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.98,0:07:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你明白我的意思的话\N{\fs38}if you know what I mean.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.29,0:07:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 让我听听看会不会起作用\N{\fs38}Well, let me know how that doesn't work out.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.82,0:07:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 这是我的计划 \N{\fs38}Okay, here's my plan. I am going
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.07,0:07:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备把这个贴在女厕所\N{\fs38}to put these in the ladies' room
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.96,0:07:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的每个隔间里\N{\fs38}in all the stalls.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.54,0:07:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- "我和出去走"  - 不不 倒着读 \N{\fs38}- "Me with out go"...  - No, no, read it up...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.41,0:07:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 "愿意和我约会吗'\N{\fs38}Oh. "Will you go out with me?"
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.69,0:07:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后她就会像这样 "什么\N{\fs38}And then she'll be like, "What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.63,0:07:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题"\N{\fs38}Yes."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.88,0:07:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 万一有人在她之前上了厕所怎么办\N{\fs38}Morgan, what if somebody uses the bathroom before her?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.09,0:07:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 真不是个好主意\N{\fs38}Yep, not a good idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.25,0:07:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,B计划好了\N{\fs38}Plan "B."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.72,0:07:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚在她车里给她惊喜\N{\fs38}Surprise her in her car tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.42,0:07:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 那可是重罪啊  - 在情人节就不是咯\N{\fs38}- That's a felony.  - Not on Valentine's day.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.14,0:07:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和节日无关\N{\fs38}Doesn't matter what the holiday is.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.98,0:07:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查查这个国家的法律吧吧\N{\fs38}Check the laws in this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.76,0:07:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不大确定\N{\fs38}I'm not even sure about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.09,0:07:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 等等\N{\fs38}Morgan, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.40,0:07:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 也许我可以帮你  - 真的\N{\fs38}- Maybe I could help you. - Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.88,0:07:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天啊 那肯定会一招搞定\N{\fs38}Oh, God, that would be so good.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.92,0:07:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了 来了\N{\fs38}Coming, I'm coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.41,0:07:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好啊  - 好啊\N{\fs38}- Hey.  - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.44,0:07:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你来这么早\N{\fs38}Why are you so early?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.99,0:07:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 提前了10分钟吗  - 是啊\N{\fs38}- Ten minutes?  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.58,0:07:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你早到了10分钟 Danny\N{\fs38}You're ten minutes early, Danny,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.74,0:07:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这比迟到2小时更糟\N{\fs38}which is worse than two hours late.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.40,0:07:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"最后十分钟"总是那种\N{\fs38}Those last ten minutes,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.56,0:07:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我从"哇"转换到"糟糕"的时间\N{\fs38}that's when I go from "Whoa" To "Damn."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.28,0:07:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fs38}Wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.50,0:07:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要先到你家来\N{\fs38}Why did I have to come here first, anyways?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.90,0:07:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要和我的朋友约会\N{\fs38}Well, you are going on a date with my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.42,0:07:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嗯嗯  - 我想确保你看起来\N{\fs38}- Mm-hmm.  - And I wanted to make sure
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.92,0:07:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会像怪蜀黍\N{\fs38}that you didn't look weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.59,0:07:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 呃 长了胡子或者其他的东西\N{\fs38}You had, like, a mustache or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.93,0:07:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会一天就长出胡子\N{\fs38}How would I grow a mustache since this morning?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.43,0:08:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道的 我又不是意大利人\N{\fs38}I don't know. I'm not Italian.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.75,0:08:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了 当我在打扮自己的时候\N{\fs38}Also, it's good when I'm getting pretty
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.96,0:08:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个男人在一旁等着会很有感觉 然后他就可以说\N{\fs38}for there to be a guy here, so he can be like,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.13,0:08:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"快点 要迟到了"之类的话 怎么了\N{\fs38}"Hurry up! We're gonna be late!" What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.47,0:08:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你盯着我干什么\N{\fs38}Why are you looking at me?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.52,0:08:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定你要穿成这样\N{\fs38}Are you sure you want to wear that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.14,0:08:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显它穿在我身上就表示我想这么穿\N{\fs38}It being on me implies that I want to wear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.64,0:08:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我挺喜欢的\N{\fs38}Okay. I like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.06,0:08:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇\N{\fs38}Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.31,0:08:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整间屋子作为衣柜吗\N{\fs38}A whole room that's a closet?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.76,0:08:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以把这里改成小型健身房\N{\fs38}You could make this into a little gym,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.03,0:08:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放个拳击用的练习袋在这儿\N{\fs38}hang a heavy bag there.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.27,0:08:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 Danny 这就是我要的\N{\fs38}Yeah, Danny, that's what I want.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.90,0:08:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与我所有的衣服相比\N{\fs38}I want a bag full of sand to punch
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.10,0:08:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要个大大的供我击打的沙袋\N{\fs38}instead of all my clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.61,0:08:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 这件怎么样 你喜欢吗\N{\fs38}Okay, what about this one? You like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.28,0:08:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我猜猜 你想让我穿上黑色小礼裙\N{\fs38}Let me guess: You want me to wear a little black dress,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.46,0:08:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聚拢内衣 高跟鞋\N{\fs38}push-up bra, high heels.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.30,0:08:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无聊 性感的毫无特色的女孩\N{\fs38}Boring, sexy, anonymous girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.17,0:08:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性感不是无聊\N{\fs38}Sexy's not boring.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.33,0:08:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有吃的没 冷的切片面包\N{\fs38}You got any food? Cold cuts?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.75,0:08:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 但是我想还有几块大选夜剩下的披萨\N{\fs38}No, but I think I have some pizza from election night.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.17,0:08:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这次的约会会很有意思\N{\fs38}I think this date's gonna be fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.81,0:08:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们试试 你看起来很美\N{\fs38}Let's take a shot. You look nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.43,0:08:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谢谢  - 敬...\N{\fs38}- Thanks.  - To...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.89,0:08:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 真爱  - 和新的人滚床单\N{\fs38}- True love.  - Sex with new people.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.23,0:08:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny\N{\fs38}Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.51,0:08:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 伙计们\N{\fs38}Hey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.85,0:08:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你们好啊  - 你们好啊\N{\fs38}- Hi. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.98,0:08:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lucy 还记得Danny吗 Danny 这是Lucy\N{\fs38}Lucy, you remember Danny. Danny, Lucy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.32,0:08:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好 很高兴见到你 - 很高兴见到你\N{\fs38}- Hi, nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.00,0:09:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你真美  - 哦 上帝\N{\fs38}- Beautiful.  - Oh, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.87,0:09:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fs38}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.34,0:09:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里挂了一条大王马哈鱼\N{\fs38}That's a king salmon over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.88,0:09:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢\N{\fs38}So?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.93,0:09:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jillian曾经研究过那种鱼的迁徙\N{\fs38}Jillian studied the migration of that fish.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.51,0:09:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不  - 是的 那种鱼从盐水湖里\N{\fs38}- No.  - Yeah. That fish goes from salt water...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.93,0:09:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不 别说了  - 迁徙到淡水湖里\N{\fs38}- No. Stop it.  - To fresh water.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.18,0:09:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是种神奇的鱼\N{\fs38}It's an amazing fish.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.77,0:09:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他们这样做是为了去死  - 没人在意\N{\fs38}They do it to mate.  - Nobody cares.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.80,0:09:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 为了去死  - Danny 没人在意的\N{\fs38}- To mate.  - Danny,nobody cares.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.85,0:09:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈喽 哈喽 伙计们\N{\fs38}Hey.Hey, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.89,0:09:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吧\N{\fs38}Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.92,0:09:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好\N{\fs38}Really good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.14,0:09:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你介意和我换下座位吗\N{\fs38}Would you mind switching seats with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.47,0:09:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那条鱼是我的眼中钉\N{\fs38}Because that fish is in my eye line,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.44,0:09:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它会让我\N{\fs38}just putting me in a...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.03,0:09:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻的心情极度恶劣\N{\fs38}A bad place emotionally right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.90,0:09:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那条鱼\N{\fs38}The fish?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.06,0:09:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 那条 是的  - 是吗\N{\fs38}- That one, yeah.  - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.90,0:09:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好的 没问题 那是你的眼中钉  - 你介意吗\N{\fs38}- Yeah, sure. It's your eye line.  - Do you mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.37,0:09:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 好极了 谢谢了\N{\fs38}Okay, great. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.74,0:09:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想看到我不喜欢的东西\N{\fs38}Wouldn't want to look at something I didn't like.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.94,0:09:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 谢啦 现在好多了\N{\fs38}Oh, yeah, thank you. That's much better.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.91,0:09:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fs38}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.54,0:09:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我能问问你 你和这条鱼\N{\fs38}So can I ask what exactly your problem is
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.58,0:09:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之间有什么纠纷啊\N{\fs38}with sea life?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.88,0:09:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 只是 我的前女友是海洋学家\N{\fs38}Oh, it's just, my ex was an oceanographer.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.45,0:09:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很愚蠢\N{\fs38}It's stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.55,0:09:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 这真是很愚蠢\N{\fs38}Yeah, it is stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.55,0:09:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 看看这里的面包选择\N{\fs38}Hey, look at this bread selection.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.88,0:09:47.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有白皮面包 还有棕色面包\N{\fs38}There's white bread. There's the brown bread.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.92,0:09:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我一直不看那个钩子\N{\fs38}Just if I keep myself from seeing triggers,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.39,0:09:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 你懂得\N{\fs38}then, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.76,0:09:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不会想着她\N{\fs38}I don't fixate on her...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.76,0:09:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎\N{\fs38}Ow!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.93,0:09:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才有人踢了我一下吗\N{\fs38}Did somebody just kick me?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.43,0:09:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你还好吧  - 哎\N{\fs38}- You okay?  - Ow!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.56,0:09:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是怪\N{\fs38}Yeah, that is so weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.68,0:09:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们应该转移到另一张桌子上去\N{\fs38}I think that maybe we should move tables,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.40,0:10:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我们可以试试不再讨论前任们的事了\N{\fs38}or we could try not talking about exes
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.52,0:10:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 然后看看还会不会被踢  - 你知道吗 \N{\fs38}- and see if the kicking stops.  - You know what, though?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.64,0:10:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现最艰难的分手\N{\fs38}I have found that the hardest breakups
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.90,0:10:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和那位你和他在一起的时候\N{\fs38}are the ones where you might have
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.27,0:10:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此了解最透彻的人\N{\fs38}underestimated the person while you were with them,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.11,0:10:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道是不是\N{\fs38}I don't know if...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.31,0:10:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 这正是我现在正在经历的\N{\fs38}Yes. That's exactly what I'm going through.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.11,0:10:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 真的吗  - 是的\N{\fs38}- Really?  - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.15,0:10:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像 像你身处..\N{\fs38}It... it's like you're...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.31,0:10:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 很奇怪\N{\fs38}I know, it's so weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.58,0:10:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是我和Jillian现在\N{\fs38}That's exactly what is going on
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.98,0:10:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 正在经历的 - 不是吧\N{\fs38}- with me and Jillian.  - No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.58,0:10:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实只是我 真的 我只是\N{\fs38}Well, it was me, really. I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.12,0:10:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我\N{\fs38}Tell me about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.29,0:10:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 呃 Jamie  - 嗯\N{\fs38}- Uh, Jamie?  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.66,0:10:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想打扰这一切\N{\fs38}I don't want to jinx this,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.79,0:10:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是想媒人Mindy\N{\fs38}but I think match-dot-Mindy
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.38,0:10:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许已经成功将这两人配对了\N{\fs38}might have another success story.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.59,0:10:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗 你也许能收获一段友谊\N{\fs38}You know, you can have a friendship, maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.80,0:10:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fs38}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.71,0:10:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以Morgan \N{\fs38}So, Morgan, 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.28,0:10:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想带这个姑娘去打网球\N{\fs38}you want to take this girl to the batting cages.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.20,0:10:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还不知道这到底是什么\N{\fs38}I'm still not sure what those are.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.43,0:10:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3交叉推进原则 Morgan\N{\fs38}Three-pronged attack, Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.94,0:10:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一条 若有若无的靠近\N{\fs38}Number one, casual approach.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.64,0:10:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我 看着我 看着我\N{\fs38}Watch me, watch me, watch me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.89,0:10:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备干什么 我准备干什么\N{\fs38}What am I doing? What am I doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.27,0:10:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我准备干什么  - 我不知道你准备干什么\N{\fs38}- What am I doing?  - I don't know what you're gonna...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.31,0:10:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在\N{\fs38}Now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.64,0:10:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好了 你看起来像Joe Biden\N{\fs38}Wow, okay, you look like Joe Biden.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.64,0:10:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs38}美国现任副总统
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.06,0:10:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷死了\N{\fs38}That is awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.28,0:10:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二步 可以开始一些轻微的肢体接触了\N{\fs38}Number two, initiate some light physical contact.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.65,0:10:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -哦 红的\N{\fs38}- Okay. - Oh, red.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.68,0:10:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-颜色不错  -哦 是啊\N{\fs38}-Nice color. -Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.95,0:10:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情人节嘛 还能遮住血迹\N{\fs38}It's Valentine's day, and it hides the blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.49,0:10:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太恶心了  \N{\fs38}That's disgusting. 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.18,0:10:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第三步  送她点小礼物\N{\fs38}Number three. Offer her something small.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.74,0:10:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,类似于象征什么的  建立一种债务关系\N{\fs38}A token of sorts. It establishes a debt.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.86,0:11:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自动贩卖机那儿给你拿的免费可乐\N{\fs38}Got a free cola from the vending machine.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.29,0:11:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我盯着它看了一早上了\N{\fs38}Oh, I've actually been staring at that thing all morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.41,0:11:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 我欠你个人情 医生\N{\fs38}Thanks, doc. I owe you one.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.75,0:11:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 这 就是人之常情嘛\N{\fs38}Oh! It's a... part of the routine.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.75,0:11:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是这样  -很好\N{\fs38}- There it is. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.92,0:11:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 这就是债务关系 - 我懂了\N{\fs38}- It's the debt. - I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.00,0:11:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你随便给她个身边就有的东西\N{\fs38}You just give her whatever you have on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.70,0:11:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 何乐而不为呢  - 没错\N{\fs38}- Why not?  - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.01,0:11:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我只要这样 \N{\fs38}So I'll be like, 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.91,0:11:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嘿 这是送给你的"\N{\fs38}"Hey, this is for you."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.81,0:11:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体去哪儿了\N{\fs38}Where's the body?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.98,0:11:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚在厕所找到了脑袋\N{\fs38}I just found the head in the toilet.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.38,0:11:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\fs38}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.81,0:11:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你体会到心碎之前你永远\N{\fs38}You never know a love song
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.72,0:11:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不会懂那些情歌的 对吧\N{\fs38}until you have a broken heart, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.98,0:11:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fs38}Mm, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.24,0:11:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你最终会意识到所有那些\N{\fs38}And finally you realize that all of these songs
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.05,0:11:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你曾经以为听起来很幸福的歌\N{\fs38}that you thought were so happy-sounding
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.41,0:11:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实都很悲伤\N{\fs38}are actually so sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.77,0:11:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如那首<You can call me Al>\N{\fs38}Like you can call me Al. Mm.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.28,0:11:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我的妻子和家在哪里*\N{\fs38}"Where is my wife and family?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.44,0:11:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*如果我在这里死去会如何*\N{\fs38}What if I die here?"
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.78,0:11:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*谁将成为我人生的榜样*\N{\fs38}Who'll be my role model now that my... once my...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.58,0:11:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*而我的人生榜样已离开我*\N{\fs38}Role model's gone?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.12,0:11:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得再去把那张专辑下下来 嗯\N{\fs38}Man, I gotta download that album again. Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.50,0:11:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太经典了\N{\fs38}It's a great one.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.53,0:11:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他们俩很喜欢对方啊\N{\fs38}I think they really like each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.07,0:11:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只不过都喜欢Paul Simon\N{\fs38}Well, they like Paul Simon.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.07,0:11:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}{\an8}Paul Simon:美国著名摇滚歌手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.37,0:11:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球人谁不喜欢Paul Simon\N{\fs38}So does everyone else on the planet.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.57,0:11:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 他们聊得都忘记我们在这里了\N{\fs38}No, it's like we're not even here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.02,0:11:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你们俩\N{\fs38}Hey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.17,0:11:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 这还有人呢\N{\fs38}Hey, there's four of us here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.43,0:11:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不如\N{\fs38}So let's try to... Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.54,0:11:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 抱歉  - 没事的\N{\fs38}- Sorry. - Oh, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.30,0:11:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny刚刚帮我出主意\N{\fs38}Danny was just helping me
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.51,0:11:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该把第一个纹身纹在哪儿呢\N{\fs38}figure out where I should get my first tattoo.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.52,0:11:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦\N{\fs38}Uh-oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.63,0:12:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是讨厌纹身吗\N{\fs38}Um, you hate tattoos.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.89,0:12:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不这样想\N{\fs38}I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.07,0:12:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我也要弄一个纹身\N{\fs38}I think I'm gonna get a tattoo as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.99,0:12:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在颈部后面纹个小蝴蝶\N{\fs38}A little butterfly on the nape of my neck,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.66,0:12:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样显示我是个无拘无束的人\N{\fs38}and it would signify that I'm a free spirit...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.26,0:12:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想纹个什么纹身\N{\fs38}What tattoo are you gonna get?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.53,0:12:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我还是保持神秘吧\N{\fs38}Well, I think I should keep it a secret,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.68,0:12:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我想纹身的地方\N{\fs38}because where I want to get it,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.76,0:12:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有特定的人才能看到\N{\fs38}only certain people would see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.18,0:12:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 Luce\N{\fs38}I-I don't know, Luce.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.60,0:12:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我担心纹身是不是有点目光短浅呢\N{\fs38}I worry that a tattoo is a little short-sighted.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.84,0:12:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你懂的吧  -我能吃点这个吗\N{\fs38}-You know? -Mmm. Can I try that?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.56,0:12:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后你的孙子真的能理解\N{\fs38}Is your grandson really gonna understand
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.94,0:12:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你的肚脐眼下方\N{\fs38}why you have a radiohead lyric
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.61,0:12:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有电台司令的歌词吗\N{\fs38}under your belly button?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.61,0:12:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}{\an8}电台司令:一支来自英国牛津的乐队
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.06,0:12:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就已经不能理解电台司令了\N{\fs38}I can't understand radiohead now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.18,0:12:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯\N{\fs38}Mmm!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.45,0:12:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想尝一点我的鳕鱼吗\N{\fs38}Do you wanna have some of my COD?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.61,0:12:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 我刚吃过了\N{\fs38}I'm fine. I just had some.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.40,0:12:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 这羊肉太 嗯 鲜嫩多汁了\N{\fs38}Wow, that lamb is so, mmm, succulent.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.24,0:12:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实鲜嫩多汁\N{\fs38}It is succulent.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.69,0:12:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你太会点餐了  - 多谢夸奖\N{\fs38}- You are such a good orderer.  - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.36,0:12:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家都说 选对了餐厅 你知道的\N{\fs38}Pick a good restaurant, and they say, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.02,0:12:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点餐什么的自然就\N{\fs38}the food orders itself, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.19,0:12:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 试试这个  - 好的\N{\fs38}- Mmm, try this.  - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.58,0:12:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 哦 哦 哦 Lucy\N{\fs38}Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh! Lucy!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.05,0:12:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的感冒 -嗯\N{\fs38}- Your cold. - Hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.53,0:12:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她上周得了重感冒\N{\fs38}She had this horrible cold last week.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.72,0:12:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事 我能接受的\N{\fs38}I'm good with it. I'll take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.75,0:12:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能会被传染\N{\fs38}You might get some sick.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.00,0:12:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有生病 你想尝点我的鳕鱼吗\N{\fs38}I'm not sick. Do you want some of my COD?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.47,0:12:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一般不会生病的 我没得过感冒\N{\fs38}I don't get sick that often. I don't have a cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.80,0:12:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你没感冒过  - 没有\N{\fs38}- You don't? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.80,0:12:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃掉这些 很浪漫的\N{\fs38}Eat off my fork. It's romantic.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.04,0:12:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 我不饿\N{\fs38}I don't need it. I'm not hungry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.64,0:12:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃掉 拜托了\N{\fs38}Eat off my fork, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.48,0:12:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃不是吗\N{\fs38}Isn't that good?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.05,0:13:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧 老兄\N{\fs38}You all right, buddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.10,0:13:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一小块鳕鱼\N{\fs38}It was just a little piece of COD.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.77,0:13:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太对不起了  -里面有鱼刺 肯定是这样\N{\fs38}-I'm so sorry. It's got bones in it. That's why.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.07,0:13:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 Jamie 你还好吗\N{\fs38}Hey, Jamie? Are you good?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.18,0:13:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你窒息了 兄弟\N{\fs38}You choking, buddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.27,0:13:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是医生 你应该\N{\fs38}They're doctors. You should just...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.49,0:13:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吗\N{\fs38}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.65,0:13:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定\N{\fs38}You sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.36,0:13:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去   \N{\fs38}I'm gonna...  
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.90,0:13:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 里面肯定有鱼刺  - 我会海姆立克法 我知道  \N{\fs38}- It has bones in it. - I can Heimlich.I know. 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.08,0:13:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我用海姆立克法帮你吧\N{\fs38}Please let me Heimlich you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.66,0:13:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}{\an8}海姆立克急救法:一种最普遍应用于气管异物的抢救 利用冲击腹部使阻塞物吐出
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.91,0:13:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fs38}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.41,0:13:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让你死在这个诡异的餐厅的 Jamie\N{\fs38}I'm not gonna let you die in this weird restaurant, Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.61,0:13:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该点甜点了吧\N{\fs38}Should we get dessert?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.23,0:13:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他窒息了\N{\fs38}I think he's choking.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.03,0:13:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 他很好\N{\fs38}No, he's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.75,0:13:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jamie 停下来\N{\fs38}Jamie, stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.04,0:13:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jamie\N{\fs38}Jamie!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.17,0:13:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦  - 哦 天呐\N{\fs38}- Oh. - Oh, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.29,0:13:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jamie 快停下来\N{\fs38}Jamie, please stop doing that!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.79,0:13:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 大伙们 别担心了\N{\fs38}Hey, guys, don't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.38,0:13:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个医生 她在处理呢\N{\fs38}She's a doctor. She's got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.02,0:13:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不明白了 都2013年了\N{\fs38}I just don't understand why, in 2013,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.51,0:13:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么还有餐厅还会有带鱼刺的鱼\N{\fs38}restaurants have any bones in their fish.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.06,0:13:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且当我感谢赠送的优惠券作为一种礼貌时\N{\fs38}And while I appreciate the gift certificate as a gesture,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.69,0:13:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总觉得经理有点消极攻击\N{\fs38}I did think the manager was passive-aggressive,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.86,0:13:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是他给优惠券的样子\N{\fs38}the way that he gave it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.70,0:13:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得吧\N{\fs38}You remember that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.36,0:13:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你知道吗\N{\fs38}Hey, you know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.73,0:13:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们今天就到此为止吧 Jamie\N{\fs38}I think I'm gonna call it a night, Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.40,0:13:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你差点命都丢了\N{\fs38}You almost died.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.52,0:13:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的鞋子又挤脚\N{\fs38}My shoes are pinching me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.40,0:13:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 所以  - 不 不 不\N{\fs38}- So... - No. No. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.19,0:13:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还得继续约会\N{\fs38}We're gonna continue this date.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.49,0:14:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带你去一个全纽约城\N{\fs38}I am gonna take you to the most romantic place
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.13,0:14:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最浪漫的地方\N{\fs38}in all of New York City.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.54,0:14:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至可能是全世界最浪漫的\N{\fs38}And possibly the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.83,0:14:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请继续往前走\N{\fs38}Keep moving, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.00,0:14:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请保持队伍的畅行\N{\fs38}Please, keep the line moving.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.05,0:14:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jamie 我不敢相信你居然在\N{\fs38}Jamie, I cannot believe you took me
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.92,0:14:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情人节的时候带我来帝国大厦\N{\fs38}to the empire state building for Valentine's day.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.87,0:14:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年 我约会的人\N{\fs38}Last year, the guy I was with,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.37,0:14:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他带我去了一家印度赌场\N{\fs38}he took me to an Indian casino,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.68,0:14:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害我输了2000美元\N{\fs38}and I lost $2,000.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.14,0:14:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实这是我\N{\fs38}Well, this is actually
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.54,0:14:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来想做的事\N{\fs38}something I've always wanted to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.76,0:14:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我觉得我应该在最完美的夜晚跟\N{\fs38}And I figured I'd come with the perfect person
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.40,0:14:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟最完美的人一起来\N{\fs38}on the perfect night.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.48,0:14:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请下一个\N{\fs38}Next, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.49,0:14:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 Jamie\N{\fs38}Wait, wait. Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.05,0:14:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们走进全世界最浪漫的\N{\fs38}Um, before we go into the most romantic building
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.61,0:14:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 建筑之前  - 嗯\N{\fs38}- on the entire planet... -Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.16,0:14:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 请你告诉我一件事  - 好\N{\fs38}- Can you just tell me one thing? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.39,0:14:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是...你没有爱上Lucy 对吧\N{\fs38}Just... you're not in love with Lucy, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.36,0:14:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请下一位\N{\fs38}Next, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.45,0:14:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你一直说这件事呢\N{\fs38}Why do you keep saying things like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.87,0:14:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚餐的时候你看起来真的很嫉妒\N{\fs38}It just seems like you were really jealous
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.67,0:14:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和Danny一起\N{\fs38}of her and Danny at dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.73,0:14:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会嫉妒一个\N{\fs38}Okay, I'm not jealous of a guy
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.34,0:14:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿喇叭牛仔裤的家伙 好吗\N{\fs38}who wears boot cut jeans, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.60,0:14:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 这听起来就很嫉妒\N{\fs38}See? That sounds jealous.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.72,0:14:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lucy 是我最好的朋友\N{\fs38}Lucy is my best friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.11,0:14:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 下一位 - 要是一定爱的话\N{\fs38}- Next. - And if I love her,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.34,0:14:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是像妹妹一样的爱她\N{\fs38}it's the way I would love a sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.73,0:14:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个弟弟 要是Rishi用你那种眼神看我的话\N{\fs38}I have a brother, and if Rishi looked at me that way,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.23,0:14:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就得跟爸爸谈谈了\N{\fs38}I would have to talk to our dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.45,0:14:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一位 下一位\N{\fs38}Next, next!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.15,0:14:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 女士 快点\N{\fs38}Let's go, lady. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.52,0:14:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正在处理一些事情 \N{\fs38}Okay, we're trying to sort something out right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.85,0:14:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗 你们能不能先给我点空间\N{\fs38}All right? Can you just give me a break here?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.90,0:15:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着你爱人的眼睛就行了 \N{\fs38}Just look into your lover's eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.35,0:15:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 今天是情人节 老天 - 快来吧\N{\fs38}- It's Valentine's day, for God's sake. - Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.96,0:15:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快速场景问答 好吗\N{\fs38}Quick scenario, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.21,0:15:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你因为谋杀了一个警察 现在呆在死囚牢房\N{\fs38}You are on death row because you murdered a cop.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.74,0:15:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 什么 - 这只是个假设\N{\fs38}- What? - This is hypothetical.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.46,0:15:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你被执行电刑处死前还能见一个人\N{\fs38}You can only see one more person before they electrocute you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.00,0:15:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会见谁\N{\fs38}Who would it be?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.00,0:15:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的律师\N{\fs38}My lawyer
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.13,0:15:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我不会做那种事\N{\fs38}because I wouldn't do something like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.37,0:15:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 你的律师把案子搞砸了\N{\fs38}Okay, your lawyer bungled the case,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.55,0:15:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你死前只能见一个人\N{\fs38}and you have one person to see before you die.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.97,0:15:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是我就直接说是我\N{\fs38}You can say me if it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.26,0:15:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Lucy\N{\fs38}It's Lucy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.48,0:15:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道\N{\fs38}I knew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.68,0:15:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很擅长做这个\N{\fs38}You're good at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.93,0:15:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Lucy\N{\fs38}It's Lucy!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.32,0:15:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱上了Lucy\N{\fs38}I'm in love with Lucy!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.05,0:15:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不 不 没事 别\N{\fs38}No, no, no, it's okay. Don't...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.32,0:15:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是Lucy\N{\fs38}I'm not Lucy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.83,0:15:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我是说 这不是\N{\fs38}No, I mean, it's not...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.86,0:15:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这没有很伤心啦 \N{\fs38}It's not, like, traumatizing.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.86,0:15:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 这没有\N{\fs38}It's okay. It's not...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.16,0:15:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以接受的\N{\fs38}It's just... I'm okay with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.95,0:15:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大伙们 下一位\N{\fs38}Okay, folks. Next.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.33,0:15:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 走吧\N{\fs38}Come on, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.67,0:15:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恋爱了\N{\fs38}I'm a man in love!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.70,0:15:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\fs38}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.74,0:15:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jamie\N{\fs38}Jamie!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.87,0:15:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天真不顺啊\N{\fs38}This has not been a good day for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.34,0:15:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了\N{\fs38}Okay, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.51,0:15:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 Morgan\N{\fs38}That's it, Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.01,0:16:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假装平常的搭讪\N{\fs38}Casual approach.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.60,0:16:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不错\N{\fs38}Okay, good.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.71,0:16:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在来点轻微的接触\N{\fs38}Now some light contact.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.13,0:16:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻微\N{\fs38}Light.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.35,0:16:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛\N{\fs38}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.55,0:16:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 人类的接触 不是摸狗狗\N{\fs38}Morgan, human touching, not dog touching.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.35,0:16:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊\N{\fs38}Agh.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.22,0:16:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 很好 不错的恢复 我猜\N{\fs38}Good... good... Good recovery, I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.19,0:16:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在给离别礼物 离别礼物\N{\fs38}Now parting gift, parting gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.64,0:16:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 Morgan 加油\N{\fs38}Come on, Morgan. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.48,0:16:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 他找到身体了\N{\fs38}Oh, he found the body.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.95,0:16:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她进入佳境了 谁知道呢 很好\N{\fs38}She's into it. Who knew? Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.23,0:16:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起作用了\N{\fs38}I... it worked!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.77,0:16:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好 Morgan 干得好\N{\fs38}Bravo, Morgan! Bravo.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.60,0:16:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嘿 我在这儿工作呢  - 对不起\N{\fs38}- Hey, man, I'm working here.  - Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.29,0:16:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱神 你终于眷顾我了\N{\fs38}You finally came for me, love!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.04,0:16:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好了 嘘  - 你终于点到我的名了\N{\fs38}- Okay, shh. - You finally called my name!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.94,0:16:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘 过来 过来\N{\fs38}Shh. Come on, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.16,0:16:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要吵醒我的邻居了\N{\fs38}You're gonna wake up my neighbors.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.66,0:16:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不敢相信这都是你的功劳\N{\fs38}I can't believe this is all because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.67,0:16:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把爱情\N{\fs38}You showed me that love
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.88,0:16:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展现在了\N{\fs38}was right in front
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.42,0:16:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我眼前\N{\fs38}of my face.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.50,0:16:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 这很好\N{\fs38}All right, that's so great.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.75,0:16:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没想过感觉会如此之好 Mindy\N{\fs38}I never thought I would feel this way, Mindy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.39,0:16:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好好走路吧  - 感觉真好\N{\fs38}- We can just walk.  - It is great.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.67,0:16:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别边走边跳舞了\N{\fs38}And not dance and stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.84,0:16:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前从来没边走边跳过\N{\fs38}I've never done anything like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.39,0:16:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fs38}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.48,0:16:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 自始至终  - 真恶心 水都溅到...\N{\fs38}- The whole time.  - Disgusting, water on my...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.63,0:16:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都归功于你\N{\fs38}It's all because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.81,0:16:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在Lucy和我的故事之间真是\N{\fs38}You are such an important character
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.52,0:16:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扮演了一个重要的角色\N{\fs38}in the story of Lucy and me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.80,0:16:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你没意识到吗\N{\fs38}Don't you realize that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.44,0:16:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嗯  - 你就是命运拯救者\N{\fs38}- Yeah.  - You're fate's helper.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.77,0:16:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我扮演了你浪漫喜剧生活中的\N{\fs38}I'm like the Joan Cusack character
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.27,0:17:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Joan Cusack式的角色 \N{\fs38}in the romantic comedy of your life, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.27,0:17:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}{\an8}Joan Cusack：美国女演员 曾经获得最佳女配角奖提名
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.61,0:17:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我不敢相信\N{\fs38}Yes! I can't believe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.24,0:17:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信这就是我吗\N{\fs38}Can you believe this is me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.48,0:17:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别人会以为你磕了药呢\N{\fs38}People are gonna think you're on drugs.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.74,0:17:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我恋爱了 - 停下来 Jamie\N{\fs38}- 'm in love!  - Stop it, Jamie.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.95,0:17:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要飞起来了\N{\fs38}I'm flying.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.33,0:17:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天呐\N{\fs38}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.11,0:17:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你们在搞什么\N{\fs38}Hey! What the hell, you guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.97,0:17:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 怎么回事 小鸳鸯\N{\fs38}Hey, what's going on, love birds?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.67,0:17:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实呢 我们算是分手了\N{\fs38}Actually, we kind of broke up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.01,0:17:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 说明一下 不准在我家门口接吻\N{\fs38}And, for the record, there is no kissing on my stoop.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.21,0:17:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是直接引用我房屋管理员的话\N{\fs38}That is a direct quote from my super.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.04,0:17:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我把手套落在你家了\N{\fs38}Okay, well, I left my gloves at your place.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.68,0:17:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是过来取而已\N{\fs38}So I just came here to pick them up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.98,0:17:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是觉得你能在她嘴里找到吗\N{\fs38}Did you think you would find them inside of her mouth?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.98,0:17:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然和这个男人亲热\N{\fs38}You're making out with this guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.18,0:17:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个别人问他要不要鸡尾酒\N{\fs38}This guy, they ask if he wanted a cocktail,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.15,0:17:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果他点了个虾的人吗\N{\fs38}and he ordered shrimp?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.27,0:17:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你吼什么吼  - 因为我爱你\N{\fs38}- Why are you yelling?  - Because I love you!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.44,0:17:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fs38}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.00,0:17:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 等一下\N{\fs38}Okay, wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.07,0:17:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也爱你\N{\fs38}I love you too!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.40,0:17:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 哇 哇  一秒钟前我们还在接吻呢\N{\fs38}Whoa, whoa, guys, we were just kissing a second ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.34,0:17:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 今晚就这样吧 我进去了\N{\fs38}All right, I'm gonna call it a night and head in.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.62,0:17:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 请让一下  - 老天 15年了 我做梦\N{\fs38}- Pardon me.  - God, I've been dreaming about this
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.96,0:17:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都想着这一天\N{\fs38}for 15 years!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.42,0:18:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我能不能  - 你为什么改变主意了\N{\fs38}- Okay, can I...  - What made you change your mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.08,0:18:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我能不能过去一下  - 我被鱼刺卡住的时候\N{\fs38}- Can I squeeze by here? - My life flashed before my eyes
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.24,0:18:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生闪过我的眼前\N{\fs38}when I was choking.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.54,0:18:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 就这样 我茅塞顿开了  - 抱歉\N{\fs38}- Just... it suddenly dawned on me.  - Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.10,0:18:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是要缠着你\N{\fs38}Not to be a stickler,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.60,0:18:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我才是那个\N{\fs38}but I-I was the person
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.80,0:18:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮你茅塞顿开的人\N{\fs38}who helped make it dawn on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.27,0:18:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mindy帮了我 她就像个默默支持的配角一样\N{\fs38}Mindy helped. She was like a supporting character.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.52,0:18:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你\N{\fs38}Oh, thank you!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.72,0:18:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去散个步吧  赶紧离开这里\N{\fs38}Let's take a walk. Let's just get outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.14,0:18:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我见过的最奇葩的事了\N{\fs38}That's the weirdest thing I've ever seen.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.92,0:18:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得要是我穿了第一条裙子\N{\fs38}You know, I feel like if I had just worn the first dress,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.77,0:18:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能就不是现在这种场景了\N{\fs38}that this wouldn't have been the situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.19,0:18:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得那不是问题所在\N{\fs38}I don't think that's the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.43,0:18:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嘿 Reed医生.  - Morgan\N{\fs38}- Hey, Dr. Reed.  - Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.36,0:18:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得去买三四个披萨\N{\fs38}I'm gonna go pick up three or four calzones
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.70,0:18:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后爬上床了\N{\fs38}and crawl into bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.37,0:18:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我骗谁呢 肯定要四个\N{\fs38}Who am I kidding? It's gonna be four.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.94,0:18:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 你三振出局了\N{\fs38}What happened? Did you strike out?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.29,0:18:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 我第一次做体育分析呢\N{\fs38}Ha. My first sports analogy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.21,0:18:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我眼看着就要把她泡到手了\N{\fs38}I had her right where I wanted her.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.37,0:18:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 啪\N{\fs38}And then, bam!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.63,0:18:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我们滚完床单\N{\fs38}She dumps me literally the second
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.83,0:18:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她立马就把我给甩了\N{\fs38}we're finished having sex.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.96,0:18:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 哇 等一下\N{\fs38}Whoa, whoa, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.45,0:18:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 滚床单\N{\fs38}What... sex?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.71,0:18:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全都是按照你说的做的\N{\fs38}I did everything you told me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.92,0:18:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的都很酷\N{\fs38}I was playing it cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.95,0:18:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她把我拉进一个储物柜\N{\fs38}She pulls me into a supply closet.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.55,0:18:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们开始在一大堆拖把前滚\N{\fs38}We start having sex in front of a bunch of mops.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.09,0:18:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经得到你想要的了\N{\fs38}You got exactly what you wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.59,0:18:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想带她去网球练习场\N{\fs38}I wanted to take her to the batting cages.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.76,0:18:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是 这件事你都已经"去粗取精"了\N{\fs38}I mean, you got the good stuff without the boring stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.23,0:18:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全垒打呢\N{\fs38}Home run.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.46,0:18:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又分析了一次\N{\fs38}Did it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.56,0:18:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,网球练习场才是事情的精华好吗\N{\fs38}The batting cages is the good stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.48,0:18:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想跟我在乎的人\N{\fs38}I don't want to have sex 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.48,0:18:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一个拖把储存间\N{\fs38}with someone I care about
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.20,0:18:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻云覆雨啊\N{\fs38}in a mop closet.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.80,0:19:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想把这件事做得更好\N{\fs38}I want to do it the right way.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.30,0:19:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶奶睡着之后\N{\fs38}On the couch, in the living room,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.65,0:19:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在客厅里的沙发上\N{\fs38}after grandmother's asleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.74,0:19:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 我很抱歉\N{\fs38}Morgan, I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.74,0:19:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要补偿你\N{\fs38}I need to make this up to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.91,0:19:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我把你领入歧途了\N{\fs38}I feel like I've led you astray.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.31,0:19:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个流浪者\N{\fs38}A stray?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.48,0:19:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在哪儿\N{\fs38}Where is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.11,0:19:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要找到他\N{\fs38}We're gonna find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.31,0:19:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么进这栋楼的\N{\fs38}How'd he get in the building?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.15,0:19:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一个 再来一个\N{\fs38}Another one, another one.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.29,0:19:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得握球棒的中段 别太疲劳了\N{\fs38}You gotta choke up. Don't get tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.67,0:19:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能放弃 在美国人们从不放弃\N{\fs38}You can't quit. We don't quit in America.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.01,0:19:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇\N{\fs38}Whoa.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.26,0:19:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看那个 Morgan\N{\fs38}Check on that, Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.38,0:19:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我看看你是怎么怪异的一挥\N{\fs38}Show me how you did that weird swing.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.79,0:19:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想试试了 很犀利嘛\N{\fs38}I want to try that. That's pretty bad-ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.93,0:19:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有点像 Michael Caine, Gary Sheffield\N{\fs38}You got, like, a Michael Caine, Gary Sheffield...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.93,0:19:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}{\an8}前者为英国演员 后者为美国棒球运动员
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.78,0:19:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 哦 天呐\N{\fs38}Oh! Oh, God!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.00,0:19:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好打到车钥匙\N{\fs38}Right in the car keys.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.18,0:19:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 哦  不\N{\fs38}Oh! Oh, ho, ho!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.59,0:19:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦\N{\fs38}Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.84,0:19:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 我只差这么一点\N{\fs38}Danny, I was this close
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.17,0:19:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能在帝国大厦过情人节了\N{\fs38}to spending Valentine's day at the empire state building.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.28,0:19:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这个套进你那句话就是\N{\fs38}To put that in you terms,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.81,0:19:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像在扬基体育馆失掉你的处男之身\N{\fs38}that's like losing your virginity at Yankee stadium.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.11,0:19:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到没 这就是你的问题所在\N{\fs38}See, that's your problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.51,0:19:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我正在总结呢 Danny\N{\fs38}Yeah, no, that's what I'm doing, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.95,0:19:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在描述我的问题\N{\fs38}I'm describing my problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.45,0:19:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁跟你说帝国大厦就浪漫了\N{\fs38}Who told you the empire state building was romantic?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.54,0:19:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机场礼品店的明信片吗\N{\fs38}A postcard at the airport gift shop?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.46,0:19:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Tom Hanks演的什么傻电影吗\N{\fs38}Some dumb movie with Tom Hanks
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.19,0:19:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在雨中拥抱还不打伞\N{\fs38}where he's hugging in the rain and there's no umbrellas?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.19,0:19:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs38}{\an8}<西雅图不眠夜>中的经典桥段
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.24,0:19:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗 过来\N{\fs38}You know what? Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.33,0:20:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想给你看个东西\N{\fs38}I want to show you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.80,0:20:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这里了\N{\fs38}This is it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.88,0:20:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错\N{\fs38}Oh, cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.13,0:20:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最喜欢的披萨店\N{\fs38}Your favorite pizza place.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.64,0:20:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 Danny 这确实让我开心不少\N{\fs38}Yeah, Danny, this does cheer me up.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.56,0:20:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好了 我走了 - 别 别 别\N{\fs38}- Okay, I'm ready to go.  - No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.09,0:20:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要给你看个东西 坐下\N{\fs38}I want to show you something. Sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.93,0:20:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- Sal 能给我们来两片披萨嘛  - 好嘞\N{\fs38}- Sal, can we get two slices?  - You got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.89,0:20:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是 <好家伙> 中的场景吗\N{\fs38}This, like, a setting from goodfellas or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.93,0:20:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 这是我遇见我妻子的地方\N{\fs38}No, this is where I met my wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.22,0:20:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 什么  - 没错\N{\fs38}- What? - Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.35,0:20:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 这里吗  - 是啊 看这里\N{\fs38}- Here?  - Yeah. Check this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.10,0:20:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想给你看这个\N{\fs38}I wanna show you this.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.44,0:20:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 你个小坏蛋\N{\fs38}Danny, you little felon.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.79,0:20:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太奇妙了 她叫Christina吗\N{\fs38}That's awesome. Her name was Christina?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.31,0:20:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fs38}Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.31,0:20:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会不会说\N{\fs38}Were you ever like...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.51,0:20:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"呃 Christina\N{\fs38}"Eh, Christina,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.56,0:20:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶好耐你啊"\N{\fs38}I love you so much-a."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.56,0:20:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fs38}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.90,0:20:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦\N{\fs38}Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.52,0:20:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我还是很想她\N{\fs38}I think I still really miss her.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.07,0:20:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你可以\N{\fs38}Well, now you can...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.42,0:20:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fs38}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.61,0:20:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么什么东西都要照下来\N{\fs38}Why do you need to take a picture of everything?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.69,0:20:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你就能永远记住不忘记了啊\N{\fs38}So that you always remember it and you never forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.91,0:20:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 别照了 - 我想给Morgan看\N{\fs38}- Stop it. - I want to show Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.65,0:20:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 别照了\N{\fs38}No, don't...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.70,0:20:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们告诉他就行了 好吗\N{\fs38}We can tell him about it, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.91,0:20:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着 世界上最浪漫的地方\N{\fs38}Look, look, the most romantic place in the world,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.82,0:20:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是永远无法提前知道的\N{\fs38}you don't know it's gonna be romantic ahead of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.00,0:20:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如 对于你 可能是任何地方\N{\fs38}Like, for you, it could be anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.70,0:21:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是个理发店\N{\fs38}Like a barbershop
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.79,0:21:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者自动取款处\N{\fs38}or an ATM shelter
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.16,0:21:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者在h&r block\N{\fs38}or h&r block.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.38,0:21:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 我很确定是在\N{\fs38}Danny, I'm pretty sure it's gonna be
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.60,0:21:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝国大厦\N{\fs38}the empire state building,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.85,0:21:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那些建议倒是挺可爱的\N{\fs38}but those are very cute suggestions.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.26,0:21:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 独眼美女对你的评价并不公正\N{\fs38}By the way, eye patch was wrong about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.13,0:21:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一点都不自私\N{\fs38}You're not mean.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.85,0:21:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只是不够了解你\N{\fs38}She just didn't know you well enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.47,0:21:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,披萨来了 Danny\N{\fs38}There you go, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.72,0:21:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谢谢你  - 谢谢\N{\fs38}- Thank you.  - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.39,0:21:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你\N{\fs38}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.47,0:21:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 这里的披萨怎么样\N{\fs38}Hey, how the... how is the pizza here?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.81,0:21:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城里最差的一家\N{\fs38}Worst pizza in the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.98,0:21:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦\N{\fs38}Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.60,0:21:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 情人节快乐  - 情人节快乐\N{\fs38}- Happy Valentine's day.  - Happy Valentine's day.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.03,0:21:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想吃掉脆皮\N{\fs38}Just want to take only the crust.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.70,0:21:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脆皮是我的最爱\N{\fs38}The crust is my favorite part.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.62,0:21:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真古怪\N{\fs38}You're so weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.41,0:21:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该睡咯\N{\fs38}Go to bed.
