[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.0.2
; 欢迎访问电波字幕组 http://www.dbfansub.com/
Title: DBfansub
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 1280
PlayResY: 720

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,54,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00030304,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,5,5,2,0
Style: Image,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,7,0,0,0,0
Style: 工作表,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 背景,Arial,20,&HA0FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 片尾,方正喵呜体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TMP片名,微软雅黑,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 电波,张海山锐谐体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H666562&\b1}{\fn時尚中黑簡體}翻譯: Heya Keita  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.44,0:00:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\3c&H666562&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)}{\fn時尚中黑簡體}校對: 三好 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.57,0:00:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn時尚中黑簡體}后期: 阿呆 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.69,0:00:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\an8}{\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn時尚中黑簡體\b1}壓制: 猴給力 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\c&H96955E&\fscx4200\fscy410\an8\fad(800,800)\pos(642,0)}m 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 4 0 9 0 13 b 4 13 9 13 13 13 b 13 9 13 4 13 0 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.60,0:21:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正喵嗚體}{\fs70\c&H20F0FF&\b1}電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}官方網站:www.dbfansub.com\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}新浪微博:@電波字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.52,0:01:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}{\c&HF6DAAD&\3c&H371E00&\fn微軟雅黑\b1\3c&HAC7400&\fs65}明迪煩事多{\c&HF6DAAD&\3c&H371E00&\fn微軟雅黑\b1\fs42}    第一季 第十二集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.87,0:01:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(48,713,854,713,0,450)\c&H7BE8DF&}{\fs64\c&H77E8FE&\b1\fn張海山銳諧體}電波誠譯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.58,0:00:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mindy 昨晚我有個前所未有的艷遇\N{\fs36}Mindy, I had the most amazing encounter last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.21,0:00:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看<獅子王>表演的時候\N{\fs36}I met a woman at the merch table
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.11,0:00:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在前排碰到個美女\N{\fs36}of a performance of The Lion King.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.64,0:00:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚她肯定感到自己被深深"愛"了\N{\fs36}Let's just say she felt the love last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.70,0:00:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mindy 是不是...\N{\fs36}Mindy, did a--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.29,0:00:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦 上帝啊  - 哦 上帝 Jeremy 真抱歉\N{\fs36}- Oh, my God!  - Oh, God, Jeremy, I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.32,0:00:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 Jeremy 我很抱歉 抱歉\N{\fs36}Wow. Jeremy, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.45,0:00:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忘了我還戴著這個\N{\fs36}I forgot I was wearing this.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.36,0:00:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近我總是在這里過夜\N{\fs36}I spend so many nights here now,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.78,0:00:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我又害怕有人來殺我\N{\fs36}and I'm scared of getting murdered.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.29,0:00:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想 如果我戴著這家伙\N{\fs36}So I figure, if I'm wearing this,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.63,0:00:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺人狂沒準認為我也是殺人狂\N{\fs36}murderers will think I'm a murderer
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.94,0:00:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就會一邊走開一邊說 "啊\N{\fs36}and they'll just go, "Eh,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.19,0:00:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廚房有好多餅干"\N{\fs36}too many cooks in the kitchen."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.42,0:00:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂的 你一直在這里蹲著\N{\fs36}You know, you're here constantly.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.84,0:00:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我的終極目標是嫁給有錢人\N{\fs36}Well, my plan was to marry rich
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.71,0:00:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后洗洗不干了 或者嫁給有錢的老頭\N{\fs36}and then stop working, or to marry old,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.64,0:00:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等老頭死了 錢就歸我了\N{\fs36}and then when the guy died, inherit all his money.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.50,0:00:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是老頭們覺得我說話太刻薄了\N{\fs36}But old guys think I have sass mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.30,0:00:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 Mindy 你完全想錯了\N{\fs36}No, you're going about it all wrong, Mindy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.24,0:00:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是說 把工作和愛情結合起來確實很難\N{\fs36}I mean, yeah, it's hard to mix work and love.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.32,0:00:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是工作和做愛結合卻不那么難\N{\fs36}But it's not hard to mix work and sex.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.39,0:00:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡做愛 再說具體點\N{\fs36}I like sex. Tell me more.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.60,0:00:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 有一次接生的間隙\N{\fs36}Well, I had an hour between deliveries,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.91,0:00:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在網吧碰到了一個\N{\fs36}and I met this very nubile Russian ballerina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.69,0:00:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常性感的俄羅斯芭蕾舞女\N{\fs36}at an Internet cafe.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.98,0:00:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 伙計 我不要聽你的性愛故事\N{\fs36}Hey, man, don't tell me sex stories.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.98,0:00:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦  - 告訴我更多的... \N{\fs36}- Oh.  - I mean, tell me more about--yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.70,0:00:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 快點  - 我的中心意思就是\N{\fs36}- Come on.  - All I'm saying is,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.90,0:00:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許你應該更多地考慮\N{\fs36}maybe you should consider a more,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.37,0:00:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不確定 那種隨性之約、艷遇之類的\N{\fs36}I don't know, casual arrangement.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.96,0:00:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 記得嗎 我們曾經試過\N{\fs36}I don't know. Remember, we tried that,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.40,0:01:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 但是糟透了  - 那對你來說可不是隨性\N{\fs36}- and it kinda sucked.  - That wasn't casual for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.46,0:01:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你喜歡我  - 拉倒吧 我怎么不知道我深愛著你啊\N{\fs36}- You loved me.  - Okay. I don't know that I loved you--
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.66,0:01:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你確實全心全意地深愛著我\N{\fs36}You were deeply and fully in love with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.92,0:01:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我 再說一次 我覺得  - 好了 我不介意的\N{\fs36}- I again--I think that--  - No, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.74,0:01:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有我想說的就是 如果你想\N{\fs36}All I'm saying is, if you want
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.36,0:01:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始享受生活 跳過約會這段吧\N{\fs36}to start enjoying life, skip the date,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.82,0:01:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接進入最美妙的部分\N{\fs36}move on to the good part.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.62,0:01:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀\N{\fs36}Ow!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.43,0:01:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在搞毛線啊 你戴這個干什么\N{\fs36}Are you kidding me? Why are you wearing that?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.83,0:01:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我不想被殘忍地殺害 Danny\N{\fs36}'Cause I don't want to get murdered, Danny!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.35,0:01:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可解釋不了你為什么戴著這玩意兒\N{\fs36}That doesn't clarify anything!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.04,0:01:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 你能賣給我個鼠標嗎\N{\fs36}Hey, Danny. Can you trade mouses with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.09,0:01:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的油油的\N{\fs36}Mine's all oily.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.98,0:01:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 為什么接生婆們在這里\N{\fs36}Wait, why are the midwives here?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.41,0:01:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為今早我來上班的時候\N{\fs36}Because this morning when I came to work
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.40,0:01:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被天花板上的水擊中了\N{\fs36}I was greeted by water coming from my ceiling,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.86,0:01:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他們二逼的水中分娩浴缸周末的時候爛掉了\N{\fs36}because their stupid water birth tub exploded over the weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.53,0:01:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道最搞的是什么嗎\N{\fs36}You know what this joker does?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.06,0:01:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他還給了我一本新生代怪咖寫的"如何息怒"的爛書\N{\fs36}He gives me this Healing Anger book by some new-age weirdo.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.00,0:01:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想有些人會叫Dalai Lama為新生代怪咖\N{\fs36}I suppose some would call the Dalai Lama a new age weirdo.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.24,0:01:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許是中國的共產主義者\N{\fs36}Chinese communists, maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.06,0:02:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好啊 Mindy  - 別和我打招呼 Deslaurier\N{\fs36}- Hi, Mindy.  - Don't "Hi" Me, Deslaurier.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.10,0:02:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別和她打招呼\N{\fs36}Yeah, don't "Hi" her.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.33,0:02:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許你能用詭計\N{\fs36}You might trick some of our patients
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.75,0:02:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我們這里的病人騙到你們\N{\fs36}to defect to your sham midwife operation
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.81,0:02:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些冒牌貨那里接生 但你別想用詭計\N{\fs36}that you have going on, but you can't trick us
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.55,0:02:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 騙我們和你們打招呼  - 你好\N{\fs36}- into saying hi to you.  - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.53,0:02:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你也好 我擦 - 你怎么說 Duncan \N{\fs36}- Hi. Damn it.  - What do you say, Duncan?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.81,0:02:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是不是來點兒烏龍茶然后就此長談一下\N{\fs36}Shall we take our oolong and say so long?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.17,0:02:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 這話真傻  - 拿到你的.. \N{\fs36}- That's lame.  - Got your--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.57,0:02:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 嘿 怎么沒人通知我這里有場精彩絕倫的會話啊\N{\fs36}Oh, hey, no one told me about the cool convention.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.83,0:02:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好啊 Duncan  - 好啊 Morgan\N{\fs36}- Hi, Duncan.   - Hey, Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.14,0:02:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別和他們說話 他們可不是我們的朋友 Morgan\N{\fs36}Don't talk to him. They're not our friends, Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.45,0:02:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得檢查檢查我的文件夾\N{\fs36}I gotta check something in my file.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.34,0:02:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 Duncan \N{\fs36}Hi, Duncan.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.87,0:02:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 Shauna\N{\fs36}Psst. Shauna.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.55,0:02:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嗯?  - 我知道你現在和Stassen警官在約會\N{\fs36}- Hmm?  - I know that you're with officer Stassen right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.68,0:02:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在此之前 你有沒有\N{\fs36}but before that, did you ever engage
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.64,0:02:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,參加過 像 隨性約會之類的\N{\fs36}in anything kind of, like, casual?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.87,0:02:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家看起來都有著幸福的性生活\N{\fs36}People seem to be having these awesome sex lives,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.19,0:02:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想試試 找個能共享\N{\fs36}and I'm just trying to, like, find a life partner
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.86,0:02:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,云雨的炮友 我是不是有點兒不對勁\N{\fs36}to go apple-picking with. What's wrong with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.63,0:02:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,L醫生 你是不是想玩一夜情\N{\fs36}Dr. L, are you thinking about having a one-night stand?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.66,0:02:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為 我敢擔保 玩一夜情的都是滿臉麻子哦\N{\fs36}'Cause, take it from me, they are the pits.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.41,0:02:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 Morgan\N{\fs36}That's okay, Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.52,0:02:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還沒有隨便到那種程度\N{\fs36}I wasn't really opening it up to the floor,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.25,0:02:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 所以你可以...  - 不不 我只是闡述下\N{\fs36}- so you can just--  - No, no, I'm invested now.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.91,0:02:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 聽我說\N{\fs36}Okay. Listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.03,0:02:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太純潔了\N{\fs36}You are too pure to be having
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.58,0:03:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不適合和那些隨便的人濫交\N{\fs36}a bunch of gross sex with randos.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.21,0:03:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可從來沒有..\N{\fs36}I was never--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.03,0:03:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就像只小小的鹿寶寶 知道嗎\N{\fs36}You are like a little baby deer, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.04,0:03:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身上長著小斑點\N{\fs36}You got little white spots on you,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.48,0:03:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴里還叼著奶瓶\N{\fs36}and you're eating a bottle of milk,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.49,0:03:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須要等到你的雄鹿\N{\fs36}and you got to wait for your ten-point buck.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.73,0:03:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你們倆在一個\N{\fs36}And then the two of you get married
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.65,0:03:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綠蔭如蓋的森林里幸福地結婚\N{\fs36}under, like, a canopy in the forest,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.48,0:03:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可愛的兔子們在場\N{\fs36}and the rabbits are there,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.96,0:03:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有 一只貓頭鷹牧師\N{\fs36}and there's, like, a owl who's the priest.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.26,0:03:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很想那樣\N{\fs36}And I really want that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.59,0:03:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是慢慢的就失去了耐心\N{\fs36}Just getting kind of impatient, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.27,0:03:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想活的有滋有味點兒\N{\fs36}I want to have fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.18,0:03:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別覺得生活很糟 L醫生\N{\fs36}Don't feel bad, Dr. L.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.40,0:03:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都是"拒絕一夜情俱樂部"的成員\N{\fs36}We're in the no one-night stand club together.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.54,0:03:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許周六的時候我們可以\N{\fs36}Maybe Saturday night you and I could meet up
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.27,0:03:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起出去逛逛然后一起制作工作午餐\N{\fs36}and make our lunches for the week.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.44,0:03:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 神啊\N{\fs36}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.64,0:03:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好啊  - 好 \N{\fs36}- Hey.  - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.30,0:03:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能向你討些建議嗎\N{\fs36}Can I ask you some advice?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.35,0:03:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關于今早我們談過的那件事\N{\fs36}About that thing that we were talking about earlier.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.05,0:03:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 激光脫毛術\N{\fs36}Yes. Laser hair removal
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.62,0:03:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很貴 但是你就再也不用擔心\N{\fs36}can be expensive, but then you won't have
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.79,0:03:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼻子下面了 很給力的\N{\fs36}the shadow at least, which will help.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.76,0:03:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 我不是說這個\N{\fs36}No, I'm not talking about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.20,0:03:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 抱歉\N{\fs36}Oh, sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.95,0:03:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想問怎么樣才能找一個好炮友\N{\fs36}I'm talking about how to help pick a guy for stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.62,0:03:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好的 Mindy 關鍵是\N{\fs36}Oh. Well, the key, Mindy, is to find a man
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.49,0:03:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 找一個你喜歡的  - 好的\N{\fs36}- who you're attracted to...  - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.23,0:03:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你并不尊重 也不和他談天長地久的人\N{\fs36}But you don't respect and you can't see a future with.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.85,0:03:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Draco Malfoy(德拉科 馬爾福)\N{\fs36}Draco Malfoy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.68,0:03:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個不是虛構的人\N{\fs36}Someone not fictitious.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.22,0:04:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醫生\N{\fs36}Doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.41,0:04:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暈\N{\fs36}Ugh.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.73,0:04:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我們探討下"暈"的真正含義\N{\fs36}Let's examine that "Ugh" for a moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.44,0:04:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它其實是一種非常有趣的情感\N{\fs36}It's actually a very fascinating emotion.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.84,0:04:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它起源于一種在進化過程中對\N{\fs36}It finds its roots in an evolutionary fear
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.04,0:04:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,污染的恐懼\N{\fs36}of contamination.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.99,0:04:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它其實和討厭沒什么關系\N{\fs36}It has very little to do with disgust.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.45,0:04:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我知道了 Brendan\N{\fs36}Okay, I get it, Brendan.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.30,0:04:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道很多科學事實\N{\fs36}You know a lot about science facts.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.46,0:04:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以忽視這些的\N{\fs36}Choose to ignore if you like.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.66,0:04:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么\N{\fs36}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.16,0:04:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Brendan 呃\N{\fs36}Brendan, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.03,0:04:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 呃\N{\fs36}Would you be interested
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.68,0:04:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天晚上\N{\fs36}in, um, me coming over...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.04,0:04:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你家\N{\fs36}To your house...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.30,0:04:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么樣\N{\fs36}Tomorrow night...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.35,0:04:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去做愛\N{\fs36}To hang out?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.36,0:04:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\N{\fs36}I am so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.38,0:04:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我收回  - 好的 沒問題\N{\fs36}- I take it back.  - Yeah, okay. 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.75,0:04:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 等等 什么  -  聽起來有點意思 \N{\fs36}- Wait, what?  - That sounds fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.19,0:04:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 來吧  - 讓我說清楚點 \N{\fs36}- Let's do it.  - Just to be 100% clear,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.73,0:04:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說的是"做愛"\N{\fs36}when I say "Hang out,"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.54,0:04:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是 你知道我在說什么吧\N{\fs36}I mean, like--do you know what I'm talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.12,0:05:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是的 我懂  - 哇\N{\fs36}- Yeah, I get it.  - Whoa.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.81,0:05:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要做愛了嘛\N{\fs36}We're gonna hang out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.47,0:05:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙計們 今晚去Brendan那兒\N{\fs36}Guys, I am so nervous
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.40,0:05:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我有點緊張\N{\fs36}about seeing Brendan tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.64,0:05:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好極了 我愛死了你要開始隨性愛愛了\N{\fs36}Okay, I love you having random hook-ups.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.83,0:05:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不確定  她最近一次嘗試\N{\fs36}I don't know. The last time
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.86,0:05:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨性愛愛也是在大學的時候了\N{\fs36}she tried this was in college,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.16,0:05:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那一次她抓狂了\N{\fs36}and she got so freaked out
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.32,0:05:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還拉下了Hillel家的的火警警報\N{\fs36}that she pulled the fire alarm at the Hillel House.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.21,0:05:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Gwen 首先 Avi在我們還坐著\N{\fs36}Gwen, first of all, Avi and I were sitting,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.76,0:05:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看CD的時候\N{\fs36}looking at CDs in his CD binder.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.98,0:05:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然開始摸我的胳膊\N{\fs36}All of a sudden, he starts massaging my shoulders.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.09,0:05:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我當然抓狂了  - 我能給你點\N{\fs36}- I freaked out.  - If I can give you
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.49,0:05:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 建議嗎  - 當然可以\N{\fs36}- one piece of advice?  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.43,0:05:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別穿內褲\N{\fs36}Don't wear underwear.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.03,0:05:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉倒吧 我才不會不穿內褲呢\N{\fs36}Okay, I have never not worn underwear.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.34,0:05:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我泳衣下面還要穿內褲呢\N{\fs36}I wear underwear under my bathing suits.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.78,0:05:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 這會讓他抓狂的\N{\fs36}Oh, and this will drive him crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.08,0:05:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給他寬衣\N{\fs36}Undress him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.26,0:05:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我是他老媽一樣嗎\N{\fs36}Like I'm his mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.64,0:05:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就不能自己脫衣服嗎\N{\fs36}Can't he undress himself?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.08,0:05:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 把他當做你等不及\N{\fs36}No, like he's a Christmas present
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.27,0:05:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要拆開的圣誕禮物\N{\fs36}that you just can't wait to unwrap.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.36,0:05:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 真不敢相信我竟然會同意這點\N{\fs36}Okay, I can't believe I'm agreeing with this,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.96,0:05:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是真的 因為每一次\N{\fs36}but it is so true, because every time
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.22,0:05:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開始解開Carl衣服的紐扣的時候\N{\fs36}I start to unbutton Carl's shirt,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.58,0:05:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都會蠢蠢欲動\N{\fs36}that civil war book gets closed.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.29,0:05:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了 同意給這家伙寬衣了\N{\fs36}All right, I can undress this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.09,0:05:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哇哇 為什么你們不做仰臥起坐了\N{\fs36}Whoa, whoa, whoa, why have we stopped doing crunches,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.24,0:05:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你們生蟲了嗎  - 為毛你的小護士可以跑進跑出的\N{\fs36}- you maggots?  - Hey, why is your nurse running our boot camp?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.66,0:05:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他相當廉價\N{\fs36}'Cause he's dirt cheap.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.62,0:05:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 別說話了 多做點仰臥起坐拯救你們的肥臀吧\N{\fs36}Hey, less questions, more crunches with your fat asses.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.85,0:05:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什么\N{\fs36}What'd you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.89,0:06:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我找下Danny\N{\fs36}Hi, I'm looking for Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.91,0:06:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他在這里嗎  - 哦 天啊\N{\fs36}- Is he around?  - Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.44,0:06:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是那個獨眼美女\N{\fs36}Are you eye patch?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.25,0:06:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是Jillian 但是 是啊 我戴了眼罩\N{\fs36}I'm Jillian, but, yeah, I'm wearing an eye patch.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.85,0:06:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 很高興見到你  - 你好 我也很高興見到你\N{\fs36}- It's nice to meet you.  - Hi, nice to meet you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.43,0:06:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫Mindy\N{\fs36}I'm Mindy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.18,0:06:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能說一句嗎 即使你只有一只眼睛\N{\fs36}Can I just say, even though you only have one eye,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.00,0:06:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你還是很漂亮\N{\fs36}you are so pretty.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.49,0:06:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上我有兩只眼睛\N{\fs36}I actually have two eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.87,0:06:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這只只是受了點傷 它會好起來的\N{\fs36}This one's just injured temporarily, but it'll be back.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.85,0:06:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能告訴我Danny的家什么樣子嗎\N{\fs36}Hey, can you please tell me what Danny's apartment is like?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.02,0:06:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直覺得 他家肯定就像一間冒煙的地下酒吧\N{\fs36}In my mind, it's like a smoky speakeasy
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.10,0:06:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面聚了一群抱怨技術難題的老男人\N{\fs36}where old men go to complain about technology.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.81,0:06:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還覺得它是...\N{\fs36}But I could also see it being--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.37,0:06:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告訴你直接去我的辦公室\N{\fs36}Hey, I told you to go right into my office
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.61,0:06:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣你就不用站在這里了\N{\fs36}so you didn't have to stop in this outer area.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.03,0:06:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不用了 拜托\N{\fs36}Oh, no, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.87,0:06:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 這樣我們就不能和她聊天了\N{\fs36}Yeah, but then we wouldn't be able to interact with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.75,0:06:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是Morgan Tookers\N{\fs36}Hi, I'm Morgan Tookers.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.92,0:06:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能給你照張相嗎\N{\fs36}Can I get a quick photo with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.46,0:06:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 我不想再說第二遍了 好嗎\N{\fs36}Morgan, I don't want to have this talk again, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.93,0:06:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny 你女朋友真漂亮\N{\fs36}Danny, your girlfriend is so pretty.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.60,0:06:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且她比你年輕好多\N{\fs36}And she's much younger than you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.46,0:06:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她也不是那么年輕\N{\fs36}She's not that much younger.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.83,0:06:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她看起來可以當我的女兒\N{\fs36}She looks like she could be my daughter,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.61,0:06:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我則看起來像你的女兒\N{\fs36}and I look like I could be your daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.91,0:06:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們今晚的計劃是什么\N{\fs36}What are your plans tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.06,0:06:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們從這里出去\N{\fs36}We're heading out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.36,0:06:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后計劃看場戲劇\N{\fs36}We're gonna go see a play.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.84,0:06:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上是我朋友的短劇表演\N{\fs36}Well, it's my friend's cabaret show.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.51,0:07:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們就是截取<金發姑娘>的經典片段\N{\fs36}What they do is they take these classic episodes
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.89,0:07:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后全部用男演員再演繹一遍\N{\fs36}of Golden Girls, and they recast all of the roles with guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.48,0:07:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 什么 - 非常性感哦\N{\fs36}- What?  - It's very sexual.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.68,0:07:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且有很大的幾率全裸出場\N{\fs36}There's a high, high chance of nudity.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.63,0:07:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道我們不是去看正常的戲劇嗎\N{\fs36}I mean, aren't we gonna see a normal play,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.19,0:07:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如<我們的城鎮>或<推銷員之死>之類的\N{\fs36}like Our Town or Death of a Salesman?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.00,0:07:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在奧迪斯維爾 我曾扮演了\N{\fs36}Back in Otisville, I was in a production
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.60,0:07:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,<推銷員之死>里面的一角\N{\fs36}of Death of a Salesman.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.65,0:07:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我扮演媽媽的角色\N{\fs36}I played mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.46,0:07:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,諷刺的是 這家伙就只\N{\fs36}Ironically, the guy who played happy
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.54,0:07:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他的小房子里自娛自樂\N{\fs36}hung himself in his cell.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.84,0:07:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用"諷刺的是"一詞用對了嗎\N{\fs36}Did I use ironically correctly?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.13,0:07:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我們該去吃晚飯了\N{\fs36}Okay, we're gonna head out to dinner,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.85,0:07:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 謝謝你們了  - 晚飯\N{\fs36}- so thanks, guys.  - Dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.99,0:07:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在才7點 我們晚點再吃\N{\fs36}It's like 7:00. We're gonna eat after.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.75,0:07:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在壽司餐廳訂了晚上11點的座位\N{\fs36}I made a reservation for sushi at 11:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.72,0:07:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上11點 哇 好吧\N{\fs36}11:00 at night? Wow, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.91,0:07:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們什么時候睡覺\N{\fs36}When are we gonna go to bed?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.11,0:07:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,獨眼美女 這些計劃\N{\fs36}Eye patch, these plans
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.93,0:07:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽起來就是Danny超愛的那種\N{\fs36}sound just like the kind of in-your-face,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.88,0:07:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,膽大妄為的深夜狂歡啊\N{\fs36}campy, late-night cultural event that Danny loves.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.71,0:07:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩的開心啊 你們兩個\N{\fs36}Have a great time, you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.22,0:07:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好的  - 謝啦\N{\fs36}- Okay.  - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.13,0:07:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高興見到你們\N{\fs36}It's really nice meeting you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.38,0:07:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜 回見 注意安全\N{\fs36}Bye. See you. Take care.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.25,0:07:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你看到這個了\N{\fs36}If you are watching this,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.28,0:07:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就表明我已經死了\N{\fs36}I am already dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.92,0:07:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被人謀殺了\N{\fs36}I was murdered. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.94,0:07:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個無辜的妹子在\N{\fs36}Just a innocent girl on her way
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.23,0:07:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她自認為純潔有愛的一夜情之路上遭到殺害\N{\fs36}to what she believed would be a harmless one-night stand.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.06,0:07:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你是人生管理處\N{\fs36}If you are a Lifetime executive,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.08,0:08:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會謙虛的我獻上\N{\fs36}I would like to humbly offer up
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.05,0:08:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來的來生選擇建議\N{\fs36}the following casting suggestions.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.39,0:08:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我來說 Freida Pinto\N{\fs36}For the part of me, Freida Pinto
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.39,0:08:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs36}Freida Pinto  <貧民窟的百萬富翁>的女主
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.01,0:08:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者年輕的Halle Berry就可以了\N{\fs36}or a young Halle Berry.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.01,0:08:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs36}Halle Berry 美國影星 曾出演過<X戰警>
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.10,0:08:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于愛情 我希望是一個\N{\fs36}For the part of the cop
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.55,0:08:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在拼湊我的人生故事時深深愛上我的警察\N{\fs36}who falls in love with me as he pieces together
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.86,0:08:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mark Ruffalo(美著名演員)就可以了\N{\fs36}my life story, Mark Ruffalo.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.93,0:08:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于我的閨蜜\N{\fs36}For my best friend...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.38,0:08:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不錯 對吧  - 我 哦 不\N{\fs36}- Not bad, huh?  - I--oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.72,0:08:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進來吧\N{\fs36}Come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.12,0:08:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我們就直接..\N{\fs36}Okay, so we're just--
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.66,0:08:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們直接進入主題吧\N{\fs36}we're just gonna dive right in then.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.16,0:08:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fs36}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.25,0:08:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎到我家\N{\fs36}So welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.31,0:08:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把毛衣穿上了 好 好極了\N{\fs36}You have a sweater on. Okay. Cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.12,0:08:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上去很漂亮\N{\fs36}You look very nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.17,0:08:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝\N{\fs36}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.97,0:08:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有個壞消息\N{\fs36}I've got some bad news.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.84,0:09:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劇院還沒熱鬧起來\N{\fs36}The theater doesn't have any heat right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.08,0:09:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面可是30度啊\N{\fs36}It's 30 degrees out.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.46,0:09:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這場戲有多長時間\N{\fs36}How long is the show?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.99,0:09:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它雖然不大嚴謹\N{\fs36}It's like a really loose structure,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.58,0:09:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是好多好多觀眾\N{\fs36}and there's a lot of audience participation.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.15,0:09:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 演員們\N{\fs36}And, at any second,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.56,0:09:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會隨時隨地把你\N{\fs36}one of the actors could just, like, pluck you out
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.13,0:09:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從觀眾席叫到舞臺上\N{\fs36}from the audience and onto the stage
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.60,0:09:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 參與其中  - 他們叫你上臺\N{\fs36}- and in the scene.  - They just pluck you, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.51,0:09:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 然后你也樂在其中\N{\fs36}Yeah, yeah, and you just go with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.29,0:09:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該會很有趣啊 \N{\fs36}It would be fun... Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.74,0:09:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 如果我去了那\N{\fs36}Yeah. If I was up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.73,0:09:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 上帝 醫院里有點事叫我回去\N{\fs36}Oh, man, they need me at the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.09,0:09:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不是吧 一切還好吧\N{\fs36}Oh, no. Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.50,0:09:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還行 我應該..抱歉了\N{\fs36}Okay, I should probably-- I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.64,0:09:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要走了\N{\fs36}I should get outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.64,0:09:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好的  - 你一個人可以嗎\N{\fs36}- Okay.  - You're cool?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.61,0:09:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好的 沒問題  - 那好 行 \N{\fs36}- Yeah. Yeah, yeah,   - yeah. Yeah. Okay.\N 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.99,0:09:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\N{\fs36}I'm so bummed!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.49,0:09:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要喝點什么嗎\N{\fs36}Can I get you a drink?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.10,0:09:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 伏特加  - 伏特加加點什么嗎\N{\fs36}- Vodka.  - Vodka and what?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.06,0:09:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 就 來一杯純的吧 用紙杯就好\N{\fs36}Nothing. Just, like, in a Dixie cup.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.44,0:09:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fs36}That's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.17,0:09:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有薯條嗎\N{\fs36}If you do have some corn chips,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.11,0:09:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我發現薯條和伏特加配起來很好吃\N{\fs36}I find that those go very well with the vodka.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.19,0:09:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不吃零食\N{\fs36}I don't believe in snacking.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.63,0:09:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天過的怎么樣\N{\fs36}Anyhow, how was your day?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.28,0:09:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始變好了\N{\fs36}It's getting better now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.98,0:09:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嗯  - 你過的怎么樣\N{\fs36}- Mm.  - How was your day?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.77,0:09:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上處理點文件\N{\fs36}Paperwork in the morning,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.24,0:09:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中午的樣子就開會\N{\fs36}had some new consultations midday.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.72,0:10:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我寫了篇犀利的<抗腦膜硬化>論文\N{\fs36}Then I wrote a scathing anti-epidural op-ed
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.31,0:10:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寄給了底特律出版社\N{\fs36}for the Detroit Free Press.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.98,0:10:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fs36}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.85,0:10:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這真是我聽過這二的事了\N{\fs36}That's the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.29,0:10:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在開玩笑嗎\N{\fs36}Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.10,0:10:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬腦膜抵御了如此多沒意義的傷害\N{\fs36}Epidurals prevent so much senseless suffering.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.08,0:10:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎\N{\fs36}You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.57,0:10:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了\N{\fs36}Doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.77,0:10:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不是來討論醫學的\N{\fs36}We're not here to talk about medicine.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.26,0:10:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是來討論化學\N{\fs36}We're here to talk chemistry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.12,0:10:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和生物\N{\fs36}And biology.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.95,0:10:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 還有泌尿學\N{\fs36}And urology.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.26,0:10:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fs36}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.67,0:10:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么地方可以讓我補下妝嗎\N{\fs36}Do you have a place that I could just freshen up?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.24,0:10:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 讓我看看你藥箱里有些什么\N{\fs36}All right, what's in your medicine cabinet,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.65,0:10:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這吸毒的嬉皮士小怪咖\N{\fs36}you little weirdo reefer hippie?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.91,0:10:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 上帝啊\N{\fs36}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.34,0:10:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 天吶\N{\fs36}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.65,0:10:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Brendan的客人 你好\N{\fs36}Hello, guest of Brendan.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.59,0:10:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*拿去我的愛 然后我將此記下*\N{\fs36}Took my love and I took it down
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.51,0:10:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請選擇你所喜歡的淋浴類型\N{\fs36}Please select the kind of shower you would like.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.01,0:10:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想淋浴\N{\fs36}I don't want to take a shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.45,0:10:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,節奏式 先生\N{\fs36}Pulsating. Sir--
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.82,0:10:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴風雨式 我不想淋浴啊\N{\fs36}Thunderstorm. I don't want to shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.16,0:10:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-深入式 -你別再說了喂\N{\fs36}Deep tissue. -Please stop speaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.65,0:10:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞典式 匈牙利式 不 不 不 不 \N{\fs36}Swedish. Hungarian. No, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.54,0:11:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我爬上高山 然后在山尖旋轉*\N{\fs36}I climbed a mountain and I turned around 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.79,0:11:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我在白雪覆蓋的山坡上看到我的倒影*\N{\fs36}and I saw my reflection In a snow-covered hill
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.81,0:11:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 天吶\N{\fs36}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.91,0:11:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*直到纜車把我送到山下*\N{\fs36}Till the landslide brought me down
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.27,0:11:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我如此害怕改變*\N{\fs36}I've been afraid of changing
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.68,0:11:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命 救命 救命啊\N{\fs36}Help! Help! Please help!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.52,0:11:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*在你身邊*\N{\fs36}Around you
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.52,0:11:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*但是時光令你愈發醒目*\N{\fs36}But time makes you bolder
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.55,0:11:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Brendan\N-Brendan!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.50,0:11:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*纜車會把一切送下*\N{\fs36}The landslide will bring it down
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.99,0:11:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 -嘿\N{\fs36}Hey, you. Hey, there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.89,0:11:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要動\N{\fs36}Don't move.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.47,0:12:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨\N{\fs36}Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.30,0:12:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\fs36}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.56,0:12:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用拘束\N{\fs36}Make yourself comfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.42,0:12:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fs36}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.38,0:12:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在準備跟你上床的時候我的確有點瘋瘋的\N{\fs36}I'm really psyched to start hooking up with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.80,0:12:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 噢 你\N{\fs36}Yeah. Oh, you know...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.17,0:12:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還記得<欲望與智慧>嗎?\N{\fs36}Remember kama sutra?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.17,0:12:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs36}欲望與智慧 是印度一部古老的關于愛的圣經
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.27,0:12:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯哼\N{\fs36}Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.46,0:12:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 噢 放輕松\N{\fs36}Oh, oh, take it easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.44,0:12:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢來 好嗎\N{\fs36}Slow to go fast, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.92,0:12:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我幫你把衣服脫掉怎么樣\N{\fs36}Cool. Why don't I undress you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.31,0:12:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 來\N{\fs36}Cool. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.52,0:12:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會喜歡這樣的 好吧\N{\fs36}You're gonna like it. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.80,0:12:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fs36}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.77,0:12:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 這比我想象中要難\N{\fs36}Okay. This is harder than I thought.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.43,0:12:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要幫助嗎  -不\N{\fs36}Do you need help? -No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.35,0:12:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你確認 -嗯\N{\fs36}You sure? Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.32,0:12:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 呃\N{\fs36}Okay. Um...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.92,0:12:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧 我自己來 -你讓我 對了\N{\fs36}Yeah, I'll come-- Just let me. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.90,0:12:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝了 好了 那兒\N{\fs36}Thank you. Okay, there.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.36,0:12:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻煩你能彎著手嗎\N{\fs36}Can you bend your arm, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.51,0:12:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心接縫的地方 你就慢慢來嘛\N{\fs36}Just be careful with the seam. Just go slack.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.36,0:12:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經在放滿了 你的頭可真大\N{\fs36}I'm slack. Your head is crazy big.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.09,0:12:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 噢 搞定了\N{\fs36}Ow! Ow! Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.23,0:12:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 我的眼\N{\fs36}Wow, my eye.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.62,0:12:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 天吶 你還好嗎\N{\fs36}Oh, my God. Are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.68,0:12:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把我的隱形眼鏡弄掉了\N{\fs36}You knocked out my contact.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.83,0:12:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它長什么樣子的\N{\fs36}What does it look like?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.85,0:12:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的隱形眼鏡嗎 是一個透明的 圓形的小盤\N{\fs36}My contact? It's a clear, round disc.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.22,0:12:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒必要用這種語調對我說話吧\N{\fs36}Okay. You don't have to take that kind of tone.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.35,0:12:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想幫上忙而已\N{\fs36}I'm just trying to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.44,0:12:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 來 讓開點兒\N{\fs36}Okay. Here. Just scoot over.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.20,0:12:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\N{\fs36}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.96,0:12:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為我來幫你脫衣服會更性感\N{\fs36}I thought it would be sexy to undress you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.70,0:13:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎 隱形眼鏡是可拋棄的\N{\fs36}You know what, contacts are disposable.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.57,0:13:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚可不\N{\fs36}This night is not.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.11,0:13:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 天吶 你是認真的嗎\N{\fs36}Oh, God. Are you serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.68,0:13:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你剛才真的這么說了嗎\N{\fs36}Did you just really say that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.73,0:13:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fs36}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.66,0:13:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來這么做\N{\fs36}Let me do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.65,0:13:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 Brendan\N{\fs36}Hey, Brendan.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.06,0:13:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 嘿 Duncan 我們有個客人呢\N{\fs36}Oh, hey, Duncan. We have a guest.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.90,0:13:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們一塊住 沒事\N{\fs36}We share this space. It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.75,0:13:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fs36}Okay--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.90,0:13:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也帶了個朋友來坐呢\N{\fs36}I brought a friend to hang out with too.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.58,0:13:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 不錯的地方嘛\N{\fs36}Whoa, nice place.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.26,0:13:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 天吶\N{\fs36}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.34,0:13:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,L醫生\N{\fs36}Dr. L?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.59,0:13:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 你在這干嘛\N{\fs36}Morgan, what are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.42,0:13:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是個有趣的故事\N{\fs36}Funny story.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.96,0:13:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情并不是看上去那樣\N{\fs36}This is not what it looks like.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.81,0:13:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們只是在一塊閑逛\N{\fs36}We are just hanging out.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.43,0:13:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦看上去確實是這樣\N{\fs36}That's exactly what it looks like.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.97,0:13:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可不能告訴 Castellano醫生\N{\fs36}You cannot tell Dr. Castellano.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.25,0:13:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不能承受發生那樣的事 -沒問題\N{\fs36}It was not supposed to happen. -No problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.40,0:13:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的 -嘿 哥們 你好啊\N{\fs36}-That's fine. -Hey, what's up, man?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.11,0:13:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好嗎 -嘿 見到你真高興\N{\fs36}-How are you? -Hey, good to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.51,0:13:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別 我們只是偶然認識的朋友而已\N{\fs36}Don't-- We were accidental friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.37,0:13:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能讓開嗎\N{\fs36}Can you get off--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.81,0:13:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這事兒就擱這兒了現在 而且我得讓你\N{\fs36}It's out there now, and I need you
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.68,0:13:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受事實\N{\fs36}to accept that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.75,0:13:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我你知道了\N{\fs36}Tell me you get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.64,0:13:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了\N{\fs36}I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.54,0:13:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼\N{\fs36}Whew.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.58,0:13:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們這 兄弟之情 發生了多久了啊\N{\fs36}How long's this little bromance been going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.35,0:13:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不是哥們 Morgan\N{\fs36}We're not bros, Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.71,0:13:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實我們準備開始 更進一步的交流的了\N{\fs36}We were actually about to become intimate.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.96,0:14:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 Lahiri醫生\N{\fs36}Ooh, Dr. Lahiri!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.45,0:14:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你這小傻瓜 -停下來\N{\fs36}-You little knucklehead. -Stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.88,0:14:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別搔我\N{\fs36}Stop tickling me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.70,0:14:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你準備什么時候告訴我你交了男朋友了啊\N{\fs36}When were you gonna tell me you had a boyfriend?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.50,0:14:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我才沒男朋友呢 -我能在婚禮上當伴郎嗎\N{\fs36}-I don't have a boyfriend. -Can I be the best man at the wedding?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.37,0:14:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不 Morgan 我們不是... -不需要那么急回答嘛 \N{\fs36}-No, Morgan, we're not-- Don't answer now,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.82,0:14:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過你得清楚我真的很想當\N{\fs36}but know that it's something I really want.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.50,0:14:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這幾乎都不能算是一次約會\N{\fs36}This isn't even a date.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.36,0:14:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我在說什么嗎\N{\fs36}Do you understand what I'm saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.71,0:14:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道這就是你說的 隨性愛愛嗎\N{\fs36}Is this a casual sexual encounter?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.43,0:14:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗯 -不行\N{\fs36}-Yes. -Nope!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.33,0:14:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 但絕對不行\N{\fs36}Excuse me. Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.33,0:14:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么啊\N{\fs36}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.73,0:14:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得跟我的朋友私下談談\N{\fs36}I'm talking to my friend in private.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.45,0:14:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么你不和Duncan去拱廊呢\N{\fs36}Why don't you and Duncan go to the arcade
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.25,0:14:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-或者其他地方啊 -門廊已經因為鼠災關閉了\N{\fs36}-or something? The arcade is closed for rats.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.03,0:14:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Morgan -這是不對的\N{\fs36}-Morgan! -It's not right.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.46,0:14:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好吧 這可能是個壞主意\N{\fs36}Yes, okay, it might be a bad idea,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.85,0:14:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過有些時候你得經歷一下\N{\fs36}but sometimes you need to experience
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.47,0:14:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壞主意萌生的感覺啊\N{\fs36}the outcome of a bad idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.93,0:14:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你跟那些鐵軌一樣\N{\fs36}Like you and train tracks.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.62,0:14:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道是不對的 不過我得拿下那些個發霉的便士啊\N{\fs36}I know it's wrong, but I gotta have those smushed pennies.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.11,0:14:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 而現在 我也需要一些發霉便士了\N{\fs36}Yes, and now I need some smushed pennies.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.83,0:14:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 我不會告訴任何人關于你和Deslaurier的事\N{\fs36}Look, I won't tell anyone about your Deslaurier
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.32,0:14:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你不跟任何人說我和Deslaurier的事\N{\fs36}if you don't tell anyone about my Deslaurier.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.47,0:14:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好 好 好 你的秘密我絕對保守\N{\fs36}Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Your secret is safe with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.99,0:14:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很大程度上是因為我根本不在乎\N{\fs36}Largely because I don't care,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.54,0:14:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我很可能一下子就忘了\N{\fs36}and I'll probably forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.59,0:14:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常謝謝你 好了\N{\fs36}Thank you so much. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.50,0:14:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大伙兒 我現在可真害怕啊\N{\fs36}You guys, I am so scared right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.21,0:14:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小女孩 不要打開那封電郵 噢 天吶\N{\fs36}Little girl, do not open that email--oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.01,0:15:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 好啊 棒棒糖 謝了醫生\N{\fs36}Oh, nice, candy straws. Thanks, doc.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.34,0:15:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 Duncan 你確定你想吃那玩意嗎 伙計\N{\fs36}Hey, Duncan, you sure you want to eat that, buddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.30,0:15:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么他不能吃這些酸味棒啊\N{\fs36}Why can't he eat the sour straws?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.84,0:15:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們可好吃著呢 它們是什么 是毒藥嗎\N{\fs36}They're delicious. What are they, poison?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.51,0:15:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們是由谷物糖漿做的\N{\fs36}It's made of corn syrup,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.58,0:15:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我會說 沒錯 這些是政府允許通行的毒藥\N{\fs36}so I'd say, yes, that's government-subsidized poison.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.12,0:15:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可好吃啊\N{\fs36}It's really good.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.15,0:15:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 如果你開了那電郵 你會死啊\N{\fs36}Okay, if you open the email, you die.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.91,0:15:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谷物糖漿陪伴著我長大\N{\fs36}I was raised eating corn syrup,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.53,0:15:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我認為自己發育得還可以咯\N{\fs36}and I think I turned out okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.46,0:15:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你的孩子們將會為此付出代價\N{\fs36}But your children will pay for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.17,0:15:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用勞煩你為我還沒出生的孩子多慮哦 怪人\N{\fs36}You don't need to worry about my unborn children, weirdo.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.47,0:15:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎 我這就走 好了吧\N{\fs36}You know what, I'm gonna go, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.49,0:15:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又有一個奇怪的 遜斃的浴室\N{\fs36}You have a weird, lame shower,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.25,0:15:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這電影又差透了 而且我們這段對話\N{\fs36}this movie sucks, and this conversation--
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.84,0:15:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫無意義\N{\fs36}I've gained nothing from it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.93,0:15:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fs36}Mm.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.65,0:15:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 等等 等等\N{\fs36}Hey. Wait. Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.04,0:15:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fs36}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.48,0:15:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻煩你把這些玩意兒從我家帶走\N{\fs36}Please take these out of my house.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.07,0:15:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Aoki Aoki 別打開它啊\N{\fs36}Aoki, Aoki, don't open it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.99,0:15:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別打開那電郵 別打開那電郵\N{\fs36}Don't open the email. Don't open the email.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.64,0:15:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 天吶\N{\fs36}Oh, God!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.64,0:15:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哮喘發作了\N{\fs36}Asthma attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.14,0:15:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙計們 噢 天吶\N{\fs36}Guys. Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.42,0:15:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 Morgan Morgan 你的呼吸器呢\N{\fs36}Okay, Morgan, Morgan, where's your inhaler?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.89,0:15:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的呼吸器呢 -在我袋子那\N{\fs36}-Where's your inhaler? -It's in my duffel.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.53,0:15:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天吶 Morgan 你帶著一人體模型的腦袋干嘛\N{\fs36}God, Morgan, why do you have a mannequin head
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.84,0:15:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一本<Bossypants>?\N{\fs36}and Bossypants in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.84,0:15:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs36}<Bossypants> Tina Fey著作
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.23,0:15:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看看Tina Fey是怎么在多種人物中游刃有余的\N{\fs36}I wanted to see how Tina Fey can juggle it all.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.49,0:15:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 好了 這 這 拿著\N{\fs36}Okay, okay, here, here. Take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.48,0:16:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拿著 拿著 拿著 -噢 天吶 把它給我\N{\fs36}-Take it, take it, take it. -Oh, God, give it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.00,0:16:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空的 它是空的\N{\fs36}It's empty. It's empty.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.15,0:16:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 天吶\N{\fs36}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.47,0:16:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他得冷靜下來\N{\fs36}He needs to calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.93,0:16:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哮喘和恐懼之間有一種強烈的\N{\fs36}There is a strong link between panic
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.95,0:16:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聯系 好嗎\N{\fs36}and asthma, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.10,0:16:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能在一個做夢者犯呼吸道毛病\N{\fs36}You can't just wave a dream catcher
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.73,0:16:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的時候只是簡單地搖醒他 Brendan\N{\fs36}at a respiratory condition, Brendan.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.08,0:16:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我處理 好嗎\N{\fs36}Let me handle this. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.45,0:16:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 聽我說\N{\fs36}Morgan, listen to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.61,0:16:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你的腦子里想著這世界上\N{\fs36}I need you to envision the most relaxing place
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.60,0:16:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最放松的地方\N{\fs36}in the whole world.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.56,0:16:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\fs36}What is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.89,0:16:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-采石場 -啊\N{\fs36}-The quarry. -What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.18,0:16:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,采石場 好嘞 采石場 采石場  \N{\fs36}The quarry. Good, the quarry. The quarry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.73,0:16:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,描述一下這采石場 \N{\fs36}Describe the quarry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.75,0:16:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它很漂亮 有一大堆石頭\N{\fs36}It's nice. It's got a lot of rocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.69,0:16:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很多下層人 -才不是下層人 他們是朋友\N{\fs36}-A lot of lowlifes. -Not lowlifes. They're friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.83,0:16:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧 他們才不應該是朋友 Morgan -別評論\N{\fs36}-Well, they shouldn't be, Morgan. -No judging.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.61,0:16:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我只是 我比你更了解他好嗎\N{\fs36}Okay, I just--I know him better than you, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.32,0:16:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 想象你這是在一個漂亮的海洋里\N{\fs36}Morgan, picture that you're in a beautiful ocean
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.88,0:16:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你準備來個美美的 安靜的游泳\N{\fs36}and you're going for a nice, calming swim.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.66,0:16:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 看那 那是Denise Richards\N{\fs36}Oh, look, it's-- Denise Richards
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.66,0:16:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs36}Denise Richards 演員 曾任邦女郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.35,0:16:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向你走來 而且她穿著一件特省布的比基尼\N{\fs36}comes up to you, and she's wearing a skimpy bikini.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.21,0:16:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她不喜歡我的身材呢\N{\fs36}What if she doesn't like my body?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.65,0:16:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果這是一個偷拍電視秀呢\N{\fs36}What if it's a hidden camera show?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.28,0:16:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別人就會有我的把柄了\N{\fs36}I have handles.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.48,0:16:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-影響我的愛情的把柄 -忘掉那沙灘\N{\fs36}-I have love handles. -Forget the beach.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.30,0:16:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到采石場里去\N{\fs36}Back to the quarry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.39,0:16:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被一些從時間開始之端就存在的\N{\fs36}You're surrounded by rock formations
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.27,0:16:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巖石結構包圍著\N{\fs36}that have existed since the dawn of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.47,0:16:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在時間開始之前\N{\fs36}Pre-dawn of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.58,0:17:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 時間開始之前 這玩意的\N{\fs36}There's no such thing as pre-dawn of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.28,0:17:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間開始之端的前夜\N{\fs36}The night before the dawn of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.37,0:17:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始就是開始 沒開始之前的\N{\fs36}The beginning is the beginning. There's no before.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.90,0:17:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在這兒打住好嗎\N{\fs36}Just please stop it, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.66,0:17:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在這些石頭準備開始依偎著你了\N{\fs36}Now these rocks are gonna start to snuggle you,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.25,0:17:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你會開始感到安全\N{\fs36}and you're starting to feel safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.49,0:17:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被石頭擁抱著\N{\fs36}Hugged by rocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.68,0:17:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得很安全\N{\fs36}I feel safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.68,0:17:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 現在把你的手給我\N{\fs36}Okay, now give me your hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.68,0:17:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們這就來拿著一塊漂亮的 光滑的 冰涼的石頭\N{\fs36}We're gonna take a nice, smooth, cool stone.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.11,0:17:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不知道哪兒 -盆栽那兒啊 \N{\fs36}-I don't know-- -the bonsai tree right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.83,0:17:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-給塊石頭我 -我該怎么清潔它啊\N{\fs36}-Give me a stone. -How was I supposed to clean that?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.35,0:17:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們這就把石頭放在你手上\N{\fs36}We're gonna place the stone in your hand
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.78,0:17:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后說 采石場與我常在\N{\fs36}and say, "I'll always have the quarry with me."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.57,0:17:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,采石場與我常在\N{\fs36}I'll always have the quarry with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.06,0:17:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以我可以呼吸 -呼吸 \N{\fs36}-So I can breathe. -Breathe...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.51,0:17:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-吸入 -吸入\N{\fs36}-Respira... -Respira...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.28,0:17:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇\N{\fs36}Whoa.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.96,0:17:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在和我開玩笑嗎\N{\fs36}Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.10,0:17:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是在他的 我是說 我懂了\N{\fs36}He had it in his-- I mean, I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.24,0:17:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Duncan 我沒事了 哥們\N{\fs36}Duncan, I'm okay, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.71,0:17:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 我得送你去醫院\N{\fs36}Morgan, I'm gonna take you to the hospital...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.68,0:17:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 然后你能被照顧\N{\fs36}Yeah. So you can get looked at.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.17,0:17:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以去醫院啊 這完全沒必要而已\N{\fs36}You can go to the hospital. It's completely unnecessary.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.95,0:17:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好著呢 噢\N{\fs36}He's fine. Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.78,0:17:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好著呢 醫生 真快呢\N{\fs36}He's fine. Doc, real quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.89,0:17:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 這家伙剛剛救了我的命\N{\fs36}Yeah. This man just saved my life
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.67,0:17:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且變了一個我看過的最好的魔術\N{\fs36}and did the best magic I've ever seen.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.69,0:17:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 如果你想讓我在你跟他辦事時做點別的話\N{\fs36}So, if you want me to look the other way while you do him,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.35,0:17:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以等\N{\fs36}I can wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.68,0:18:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有這個需要嗎\N{\fs36}You want to do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.41,0:18:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fs36}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.03,0:18:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7 調轉\N{\fs36}Seven, reverse,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.53,0:18:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過 過\N{\fs36}skip, skip,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.04,0:18:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藍色 萬能牌 紅色 哦 看啊 \N{\fs36}blue, wild card, red, uno, what?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.65,0:18:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坑爹呢吧\N{\fs36}Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.97,0:18:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至都還來不及打呢\N{\fs36}I didn't even get to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.15,0:18:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,L醫生 這兩個帥小伙\N{\fs36}Dr. L, these two cool guys
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.44,0:18:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一起打發了漫漫長夜 就像我們一樣\N{\fs36}spent the night together, just like we did.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.88,0:18:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mindy 你在跟Morgan幽會嗎\N{\fs36}Mindy, was your tryst with Morgan?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.41,0:18:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥 不\N{\fs36}What? No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.42,0:18:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙計們 我今晚試著來一發邂逅\N{\fs36}Guys, I tried to have a hook-up tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.91,0:18:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果糟透了\N{\fs36}and it went horribly.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.87,0:18:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次或許會好點\N{\fs36}Maybe it'll be better next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.66,0:18:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不這么認為 我試著跟一個我不尊重\N{\fs36}I don't think so. I tried for a guy
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.74,0:18:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的男人來一發 猜猜看 伙計們\N{\fs36}that I don't respect. Guess what, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.87,0:18:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有做愛 可是現在我尊重他了\N{\fs36}No sex, and now I respect him.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.36,0:18:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到沒 我早告訴你你必須先有愛才有性\N{\fs36}See, I told you you got attached.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.27,0:18:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯Danny 你是對的\N{\fs36}Yes, Danny, you were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.20,0:18:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我唯一的安慰是你在這兒\N{\fs36}My only consolation is that you are here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.07,0:18:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就是說你今晚過得跟我一樣糟糕\N{\fs36}So it means that your evening went as badly as mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.61,0:18:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\fs36}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.15,0:18:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 哎呀\N{\fs36}Hey. Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.81,0:18:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼罩女 你看起來比之前又漂亮了點兒\N{\fs36}Eye patch, you look prettier now than you did before.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.82,0:18:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝\N{\fs36}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.55,0:18:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出于好奇 你們四個知道\N{\fs36}Out of curiosity, do the four of you know
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.16,0:18:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醫生休息室這有多難聞嗎\N{\fs36}how terrible it smells in this doctors' lounge,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.76,0:18:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是你們已經習慣了\N{\fs36}or are you used to it?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.08,0:18:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們習慣了 習慣了\N{\fs36}We're used to it. Used to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.03,0:18:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不覺得這兒難聞\N{\fs36}I don't think it smells bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.70,0:18:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jeremy Reed醫生\N{\fs36}Dr. Jeremy Reed.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.39,0:18:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高興認識你 眼罩小姐\N{\fs36}Pleasure to meet you, miss patch.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.91,0:18:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的 你的眼罩吸引了全部人的注意力\N{\fs36}You know, your eye patch gets all the attention,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.60,0:18:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我認為你的鼻子更加引人注意\N{\fs36}but I think your nose is rather noteworthy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.09,0:18:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟Danny該找一下你的與眾不同\N{\fs36}Should you and Danny find your differences--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.89,0:18:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伙計 謝了\N{\fs36}Okay, buddy, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.19,0:19:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是時候走了 好了\N{\fs36}Time to go. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.51,0:19:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿 -嘿\N{\fs36}-Hey. -Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.97,0:19:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 我不知道 我只是覺得\N{\fs36}So, I don't know, I just have this feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.48,0:19:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天離開然后返回醫院是不是\N{\fs36}like maybe you left and came here
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.81,0:19:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你不是很喜歡我們今晚的計劃\N{\fs36}because you didn't really like our plans tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.92,0:19:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 我只是覺得\N{\fs36}I'm sorry. I just think
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.90,0:19:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們喜歡的都是不同的東西 而且\N{\fs36}we're into different things, and...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.90,0:19:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對于你來說 太老了嗎\N{\fs36}Am I too old for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.65,0:19:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不這么認為啊 我喜歡你已經32歲了\N{\fs36}I don't think so. I like that you're 32.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.14,0:19:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-38 -你說真的嗎 伙計\N{\fs36}-38. -Are you serious, dude?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.85,0:19:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fs36}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.90,0:19:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊\N{\fs36}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.51,0:19:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是試著搞清楚\N{\fs36}I'm just trying to figure out
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.03,0:19:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你經歷過幾次奧運會\N{\fs36}how many Olympics you've been around for.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.57,0:19:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柏林那會兒你在世嗎\N{\fs36}Were you alive for Berlin?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.26,0:19:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1936那次\N{\fs36}In 1936?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.45,0:19:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan 對不住\N{\fs36}Morgan! I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.66,0:19:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是表示他喜歡你\N{\fs36}That just means he likes you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.90,0:19:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻煩你能幫我擋一下門嗎 \N{\fs36}Can you hold the door, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.22,0:20:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 這真是極端尷尬\N{\fs36}Okay, this is massively awkward,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.53,0:20:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我只是試著開始說些話\N{\fs36}so I am just going to start saying things.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.37,0:20:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Brendan 我是沒能夠\N{\fs36}Brendan, I was not able to have
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.82,0:20:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你來一發隨心的邂逅 這不打緊\N{\fs36}a casual hook-up with you. That's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.17,0:20:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在其他國家 這不是讓人尷尬的事情\N{\fs36}In other countries, that is not embarrassing.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.82,0:20:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上這還是美德呢\N{\fs36}It is actually a virtue.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.96,0:20:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能對你來說不是\N{\fs36}Maybe not for you
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.02,0:20:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是無論你是在哪一種奇怪的社會中長大的\N{\fs36}and whatever weird commune that you were raised in,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.63,0:20:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我還是能依據國際慣例很確定的說\N{\fs36}but I'm pretty sure that internationally
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.70,0:20:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還是相對靠譜的那一個\N{\fs36}I have the upper hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.89,0:20:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里有客人來時\N{\fs36}It is rude to not have snacks
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.63,0:20:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連點心都不準備是很粗魯的\N{\fs36}at your house when someone's coming over.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.46,0:20:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嗎 椒鹽卷餅啊 薯片啊 一些汽水啊\N{\fs36}All right? Pretzels, chips, some soda--
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.60,0:20:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這有多難啊\N{\fs36}how hard is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.48,0:20:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有你的吉他彈得 技術上來說 還是有點造詣的\N{\fs36}And your guitar playing, while technically proficient,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.05,0:20:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但缺乏深度\N{\fs36}lacks depth.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.97,0:20:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你的家里有把小刀\N{\fs36}There is a small knife at your house.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.38,0:20:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帶去的\N{\fs36}I brought it with me
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.28,0:20:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萬一你準備襲擊我的話可以拿來自衛\N{\fs36}to stab you with it in case you tried to attack me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.65,0:20:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它被偷偷地收在了我的女士手套里\N{\fs36}It is hidden discreetly in a woman's glove.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.86,0:20:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果Duncan試圖傷害他自己的話我會恨自己的\N{\fs36}I would hate for Duncan to hurt himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.06,0:20:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我沒有 但還是謝謝你\N{\fs36}I did not however thank you
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.12,0:20:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救了我的朋友 所以 謝謝你\N{\fs36}for helping my friend. So thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.79,0:20:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客氣了\N{\fs36}You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.96,0:20:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么祝你今天過得愉快\N{\fs36}So good day to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.03,0:20:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們準備做愛吧\N{\fs36}We are going to have sex.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.80,0:21:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是為了讓你知道\N{\fs36}Just so you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.07,0:21:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是現在 在一電梯里\N{\fs36}Not now... in an elevator.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.62,0:21:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 當然啦\N{\fs36}Yeah, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.47,0:21:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的樓層 -嗯 是的 \N{\fs36}Your floor. Yeah, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.55,0:21:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝了\N{\fs36}Thank you.
