1
00:00:00,757 --> 00:00:02,575
我叫Elena Gilbert  
My name is Elena Gilbert. 

2
00:00:02,576 --> 00:00:03,217
我是只吸血鬼
I'm a vampire.

3
00:00:03,750 --> 00:00:05,417
你对我认宗了
You're sired to me,

4
00:00:05,418 --> 00:00:06,819
Elena   你感受到的每一件事
Elena. Everything you think you fell,

5
00:00:08,721 --> 00:00:09,971
都可能不是出自你真心
might not even be real.

6
00:00:09,972 --> 00:00:11,589
但是现在有救了
But there's hope now.

7
00:00:11,590 --> 00:00:12,873
告诉他们猎人说这个纹身指向何处
Tell them what the hunter told you the tattoo leads to.

8
00:00:12,874 --> 00:00:14,475
他说有解药
He said there was a cure.

9
00:00:14,476 --> 00:00:16,678
每个人出自不同的理由都想要得到它
Everyone wants it for a different reason.

10
00:00:16,679 --> 00:00:17,896
为了复仇...
For revenge...

11
00:00:19,649 --> 00:00:22,183
为了成为一个能坠入爱河的人类
To be human and in love...

12
00:00:22,184 --> 00:00:23,284
亦或是为了追寻真相
For the truth...

13
00:00:23,285 --> 00:00:24,775
我放你自由 Elena 
I'm setting you free, Elena.

14
00:00:25,322 --> 00:00:27,156
有人会不顾一切地得到它
And some will stop at nothing to get it.

15
00:00:27,157 --> 00:00:28,740
捅啊
Do it!

16
00:00:34,730 --> 00:00:39,167
Carol Lockwood说过在悲剧发生的时候
Carol Lockwood always said that togetherness,

17
00:00:39,168 --> 00:00:40,952
团结一致总是能治愈受伤的心灵
in times of tragedy,leads to healing.

18
00:00:43,739 --> 00:00:48,024
一个团结的集体强于一千各自为政的人
That one community is stronger than a thousand of its members.

19
00:00:49,077 --> 00:00:51,679
但怎样使一个团体 在失去领袖之后
But how does a community stay strong

20
00:00:51,680 --> 00:00:53,914
保持强大呢
after losing its leader?

21
00:00:53,915 --> 00:00:57,518
Carol不仅仅是一位好镇长
And Carol was so much more than just a mayor.

22
00:00:57,519 --> 00:01:00,471
她还是...
She was...

23
00:01:00,472 --> 00:01:03,324
一位胸怀宽阔的朋友
An open-minded friend...

24
00:01:04,643 --> 00:01:07,278
一位无微不至的母亲
And a concerned mother,

25
00:01:07,279 --> 00:01:09,647
但却早早地因为一场可怕的事故
taken from us too soon

26
00:01:09,648 --> 00:01:12,951
离开了我们
by a terrible accident.

27
00:01:14,486 --> 00:01:16,537
去他的
Screw this.

28
00:01:16,538 --> 00:01:18,286
Tyler
Tyler.

29
00:01:18,287 --> 00:01:20,291
Tyler
Tyler.

30
00:01:23,829 --> 00:01:26,113
请和我一起
Please join me in observing

31
00:01:26,114 --> 00:01:28,213
为她默哀
a minute of silence in her memory.

32
00:01:45,985 --> 00:01:48,186
你还好吗
You ok?

33
00:01:48,187 --> 00:01:50,805
我一会回来
I'll be right back.

34
00:01:50,806 --> 00:01:54,125
非常感谢各位
Thank you very much.

35
00:01:54,126 --> 00:01:55,568
紧接着 这场悲剧之后
In the wake of this tragedy,

36
00:01:55,569 --> 00:01:57,578
我们选出了一位临时镇长
the town has selected an interim mayor.

37
00:01:57,579 --> 00:02:00,031
许多人已经认得他了
Many of you already know him.

38
00:02:00,032 --> 00:02:02,039
请欢迎Rudy Hopkins先生
Please welcome Mr. Rudy Hopkins.

39
00:02:07,790 --> 00:02:10,714
谢谢 警长
Thank you, sheriff.

40
00:02:10,715 --> 00:02:14,312
Carol Lockwood总是以小镇为重
Carol Lockwood put this town first,

41
00:02:14,313 --> 00:02:16,848
所以现在我要对大家说
and that's why I'm here to talk to you guys.

42
00:02:16,849 --> 00:02:19,389
大家...
You folks...

43
00:02:35,367 --> 00:02:37,324
April
April?

44
00:02:38,871 --> 00:02:40,538
你怎么了
What's wrong?

45
00:02:40,539 --> 00:02:43,374
没什么 我很好
Nothing. I'm fine.

46
00:02:43,375 --> 00:02:45,248
但是你在哭啊
But you're crying.

47
00:02:46,462 --> 00:02:48,046
只是镇长的事情
It's just the whole mayor thing.

48
00:02:48,047 --> 00:02:50,128
你知道的 让我想起了我爸爸的那些事
You know, it's bringing up stuff with my dad.

49
00:02:51,917 --> 00:02:53,799
而且我知道你是个吸血鬼
And I know you're a vampire.

50
00:02:55,504 --> 00:02:57,719
等一下  什么
Wait. What?

51
00:03:03,312 --> 00:03:04,979
有必要这样吗
Oh, was that necessary?

52
00:03:04,980 --> 00:03:07,565
没有必要 只是这样有趣多了
No, but it was fun.

53
00:03:07,980 --> 00:03:010,565
===BTM字幕组出品===
仅供交流 请勿商用

53
00:03:010,980 --> 00:03:013,565
翻译：小蚊子 蝴蝶  严冬
校译：shmily  圈圈  大牌  袖子
后期：芷  心我

53
00:03:14,440 --> 00:03:16,056
嘿 你刚错过了
Hey, you just missed

54
00:03:16,057 --> 00:03:17,658
必须要到的全校集会
the mandatory all-school assembly.

55
00:03:17,659 --> 00:03:18,893
好吧 那是因为我
Well, that's because I'm

56
00:03:18,894 --> 00:03:21,299
身在强制性的独身酒会里
at a mandatory all-alone drinking party.

57
00:03:21,300 --> 00:03:22,933
真的吗  你决定去参加
Seriously? You decided to go

58
00:03:22,934 --> 00:03:24,918
开膛者的狂欢吗
on a ripper bender now?

59
00:03:24,919 --> 00:03:26,720
我哥哥和Elena睡了
My brother slept with Elena.

60
00:03:26,721 --> 00:03:28,755
这让事情有些扫兴了
Kind of puts a little bit of a damper on things.

61
00:03:28,756 --> 00:03:31,024
首先 你不该知道这件事的
First of all, you are not supposed to know that.

62
00:03:31,025 --> 00:03:34,928
其次 Tyler正伺机等候而且抢占先机了
Second of all, Tyler is already spiraling, and he gets priority.

63
00:03:34,929 --> 00:03:37,397
他的妈妈刚过世  你还在期盼什么?
His mother just died. What do you expect?

64
00:03:37,398 --> 00:03:39,733
我是他女朋友 我当然希望他能跟我说说
I'm his girlfriend. I expect him to talk to me.

65
00:03:39,734 --> 00:03:41,902
但是他却极度愤怒  别人都说他母亲的死只是一场意外
But instead he's all angry, and it doesn't help that

66
00:03:41,936 --> 00:03:43,937
这一点让他更生气
everyone keeps referring to his mother's death as an accident,

67
00:03:43,938 --> 00:03:47,574
这只是变相的说她当时醉酒罢了
which is really just a polite way of saying that she was drunk.

68
00:03:47,575 --> 00:03:49,209
你觉得是Klaus杀了她吗
You think Klaus killed her?

69
00:03:49,210 --> 00:03:52,245
至少 我觉得她不是因为喝多马提尼酒死的
Well, I don't think she drowned in a Martini glass.

70
00:03:52,246 --> 00:03:56,449
我们聚起来吧  我一个人做不来
Just get it together. I can't do it alone.

71
00:04:10,181 --> 00:04:11,515
集会结束了
The assembly's over.

72
00:04:11,516 --> 00:04:13,350
这里到底发生了什么
What the hell's going on?

73
00:04:13,351 --> 00:04:14,796
学校里马上就要空了
The school will be empty soon.

74
00:04:15,937 --> 00:04:18,688
你到底控制了我多少次
How many times did you compel me?

75
00:04:18,689 --> 00:04:21,274
别...  别对我撒谎
Don't... Just don't lie.

76
00:04:21,275 --> 00:04:23,160
Rebekah说你撒谎了
Rebekah says you lie.

77
00:04:23,161 --> 00:04:24,828
Rebekah不是你想的那种人 April
Rebekah's not who you think she is, April.

78
00:04:25,389 --> 00:04:27,767
怎么 她不是一只千年的吸血鬼始祖吗?
What, she's not a thousand-year-old original vampire?

79
00:04:27,768 --> 00:04:30,951
听着 我们可以一起找出这个答案 好吗 
Listen, we can figure this out, ok,

80
00:04:30,952 --> 00:04:32,669
但是我们首先要离开这
but we have to get out of here.

81
00:04:34,154 --> 00:04:37,027
抱歉  不允许了
Sorry. Not allowed.

82
00:04:39,510 --> 00:04:40,994
为什么你不坐下来呢?
Why don't you take a seat?

83
00:04:40,995 --> 00:04:42,879
班里其他的人马上就要到这里来了
The rest of the class will be here shortly.

84
00:04:47,351 --> 00:04:48,835
收到一条语音留言
First saved message.

85
00:04:48,836 --> 00:04:50,854
嘿 是我
Hey, it's me.

86
00:04:50,855 --> 00:04:53,857
听着 我知道你为什么让我走
Look, I know why you sent me away.

87
00:04:53,858 --> 00:04:54,882
你觉得我对你的感觉
You think that what I'm

88
00:04:54,883 --> 00:04:56,843
都只是因为认祖归宗
feeling for you is because of the sire bond,

89
00:04:56,844 --> 00:05:00,280
但是我讨厌不能和你在一起
but I hate not being near you.

90
00:05:07,572 --> 00:05:10,123
来吧 出招吧
Go ahead. Make a move.

91
00:05:10,124 --> 00:05:13,146
我是当陪练的 不是扁你的
I drove up here to be your wingman, not kick your ass.

92
00:05:19,417 --> 00:05:20,487
啊 好的
Aah! Ok.

93
00:05:21,053 --> 00:05:22,869
好了 我明白了
I get it. I get it.

94
00:05:22,870 --> 00:05:25,204
你够厉害啊
You're a badass.

95
00:05:29,477 --> 00:05:30,760
看到没
You see that?

96
00:05:30,761 --> 00:05:33,597
不能错过 是慢动作
Couldn't miss it. It was in slow motion.

97
00:05:33,598 --> 00:05:35,398
教我点有用的
Then teach me something useful.

98
00:05:35,399 --> 00:05:37,050
我们来了好几天了 目前为止
We've been here for days, and so far

99
00:05:37,051 --> 00:05:38,755
你所做的只是发号施令
all you've done is bark orders.

100
00:05:42,823 --> 00:05:44,511
好的
Ok.

101
00:05:45,928 --> 00:05:47,727
退后坐椅子上去 四分卫
Take a seat at the bench, quarterback.

102
00:05:47,728 --> 00:05:49,562
空手道小子 咱两对一局吧
Karate kid wants a a shot at the title.

103
00:05:49,563 --> 00:05:52,102
Jeremy 你还没准备好
Jeremy, you're not ready for this.

104
00:05:54,568 --> 00:05:55,814
怎样?
Well?

105
00:05:57,672 --> 00:05:59,420
现在 我所需要做的
Now, all I have to do 

106
00:05:59,421 --> 00:06:01,945
只是在你下巴上施加一点压力
is apply a little pressure under your jaw.

107
00:06:05,763 --> 00:06:07,931
真的吗 又来 
Really? Again?

108
00:06:10,584 --> 00:06:11,830
好的
Ok.

109
00:06:13,387 --> 00:06:15,388
连续第三天双份意大利辣香肠披萨 
Double pepperoni 3 days in a row.

110
00:06:15,389 --> 00:06:17,307
你们要不要吃点别的
You guys eat anything else?

111
00:06:17,308 --> 00:06:19,129
为什么 你请客 
Why? Are you offering?

112
00:06:20,394 --> 00:06:21,978
这是小费 
A little something extra, cut off

113
00:06:21,979 --> 00:06:23,697
接下来几天不要来送披萨了
the pizza pipeline for a couple days.

114
00:06:23,698 --> 00:06:25,802
不论他们怎么求你 不要回来
No matter how much they beg, don't come back.

115
00:06:27,652 --> 00:06:29,152
抱歉 伙计们
Sorry, guys.

116
00:06:29,153 --> 00:06:30,453
你这是要饿死我们吗?
You're gonna starve us now?

117
00:06:30,454 --> 00:06:31,705
这样你才能成为
If that's what it takes

118
00:06:31,706 --> 00:06:32,939
吸血鬼猎人
to make you a hunter.

119
00:06:32,940 --> 00:06:35,992
接下来 围着湖跑两圈
Now run around the lake, twice.

120
00:06:38,796 --> 00:06:40,580
陪着他 
Keep him company.

121
00:06:40,581 --> 00:06:42,465
我不用听你的
I don't have to listen to you.

122
00:06:42,466 --> 00:06:44,070
你想吃东西 就必须听我的
You do if you want to eat.

123
00:06:52,426 --> 00:06:55,128
在你身边 我想你 Damon
Being near you, and I miss you, Damon.

124
00:06:55,129 --> 00:06:57,167
我希望你让我去你身边
I wish you would just let me come to you.

125
00:07:01,969 --> 00:07:03,403
什么 
What?

126
00:07:03,404 --> 00:07:04,854
猜猜我是谁?
Guess who.

127
00:07:04,855 --> 00:07:06,639
我回来了 完好无恙
I'm back, dagger-free,

128
00:07:06,640 --> 00:07:07,974
我正在学校 把Elena抓来当人质
and I'm holding Elena hostage at the High School.

129
00:07:07,975 --> 00:07:09,359
觉得该通知你一声
Just thought you should know.

130
00:07:09,360 --> 00:07:10,610
谁这么蠢 
Who the hell was dumb enough

131
00:07:10,611 --> 00:07:11,811
把你的匕首拔掉了
to pull that dagger out of you?

132
00:07:11,812 --> 00:07:13,830
我也想知道呢
I'll be asking the questions today.

133
00:07:13,831 --> 00:07:15,332
回见
See ya soon.

134
00:07:26,043 --> 00:07:28,044
除非你回归文明  
I'm only ready to talk to you

135
00:07:28,045 --> 00:07:30,575
我才会跟你讲话
if you're ready to rejoin civilization.

136
00:07:30,576 --> 00:07:32,074
你觉得把古橡树枝
How would you like to drive

137
00:07:32,075 --> 00:07:34,517
插进Rebbeca心脏里如何?
the white oak stake through Rebekah's heart?

138
00:07:34,518 --> 00:07:36,094
如果你没在神秘烧烤餐馆喝多了的话
If it means you're not

139
00:07:36,095 --> 00:07:39,606
没问题 
drinking your way through the mystic grill, sure.

140
00:07:39,607 --> 00:07:41,358
那么
So...

141
00:07:41,359 --> 00:07:43,393
第一次跟你本人谈话
First speech under your belt.

142
00:07:43,394 --> 00:07:45,895
现在开始有趣的部分
Now for the fun part.

143
00:07:45,896 --> 00:07:48,531
欢迎来到小心掩饰的世界
Welcome to the world of careful cover-ups.

144
00:07:48,532 --> 00:07:51,350
我们已经排除了Carol因坠落头部受伤致死的可能性
We've ruled Carol's death as head trauma from a fall.

145
00:07:51,351 --> 00:07:53,236
官方尸检的结果
That's the official autopsy.

146
00:07:53,237 --> 00:07:55,688
她去的不平静 是吗?
She did not go gently, did she?

147
00:07:55,689 --> 00:07:57,240
有线索没有
Any leads?

148
00:07:57,241 --> 00:07:58,908
我们有些想法
We have ideas.

149
00:07:58,909 --> 00:08:00,076
让我猜猜
Let me guess.

150
00:08:00,077 --> 00:08:01,878
锋利的牙齿 不良的餐桌礼仪?
Sharp teeth and bad table manners?

151
00:08:01,879 --> 00:08:03,997
你确定你想要这工作?
You sure you want this?

152
00:08:03,998 --> 00:08:06,666
我是说 在你之前我请了六个人做这工作
I mean, 6 people were offered this job before you.

153
00:08:06,667 --> 00:08:08,385
他们都因种种理由拒绝了
They all said no for a reason.

154
00:08:08,386 --> 00:08:10,236
我接受 也有理由
I'm saying yes for a reason,

155
00:08:10,237 --> 00:08:12,889
我的理由刚进来了
and my reason just walked in.

156
00:08:14,341 --> 00:08:16,760
我会通知你进展的  谢谢你 警官
I'll let you know what we find. Thank you, sheriff.

157
00:08:16,761 --> 00:08:19,345
嘿 警官  嘿 爸爸
Hey, sheriff. Hey, dad.

158
00:08:19,346 --> 00:08:21,898
- 嘿   - 那么
- Hey. - So...

159
00:08:21,899 --> 00:08:24,717
跟旅行医药代表有天壤之别啊
Far cry from being a traveling pharmaceutical rep.

160
00:08:24,718 --> 00:08:27,737
我注意到你一些朋友从聚会上消失了
I noticed a few of your friends missing from the assembly.

161
00:08:27,738 --> 00:08:29,939
我还以为那是强制性的呢 是吧?
So much for mandatory I guess, huh?

162
00:08:29,940 --> 00:08:31,908
爸爸 别说了 
Dad, stop it.

163
00:08:31,909 --> 00:08:34,861
你不能一回来就这么指手画脚的
You can't come in here and start making rules.

164
00:08:34,862 --> 00:08:37,363
我觉得这个镇子需人多管管
I think this town could use a few more rules.

165
00:08:37,364 --> 00:08:39,949
你忘了 我可以帮忙保护这个镇
You're forgetting I can help protect the town.

166
00:08:39,950 --> 00:08:43,787
我很了解你的天赋 Bonnie
I am well aware of your gifts, Bonnie...

167
00:08:43,788 --> 00:08:45,939
但是别忘了我是你爸爸
But don't forget I'm your father.

168
00:08:45,940 --> 00:08:48,758
那意味着我要保护你
That means that I get to protect you.

169
00:09:36,507 --> 00:09:37,952
你好 Stefan
Hello, Stefan.

170
00:09:39,426 --> 00:09:42,095
我来了 你想要什么?
I'm here. What do you want?

171
00:09:42,096 --> 00:09:45,181
跟你帮Klaus刺我的时候要的一样
The same thing I wanted when you helped make Klaus stab me.

172
00:09:45,182 --> 00:09:46,850
解药
The cure.

173
00:09:49,904 --> 00:09:52,634
我希望你不是在等Caroline来刺杀我
I hope you're not waiting for Caroline to show up and stake me...

174
00:09:54,658 --> 00:09:56,971
因为我已经找到她了
Because I already found her.

175
00:10:07,568 --> 00:10:08,818
Stefan
Stefan.

176
00:10:08,819 --> 00:10:10,443
谁允许你随便乱动的
Did I say you could move?

177
00:10:12,739 --> 00:10:14,707
现在是审判时间
Class is in session.

178
00:10:14,708 --> 00:10:17,076
你们都已经被我控制了  现在按我的规矩来
You've all been compelled. You know the rules.

179
00:10:17,077 --> 00:10:19,745
老实回答我的问题
Answer my questions honestly,

180
00:10:19,746 --> 00:10:21,581
不要反抗
no disobedience,

181
00:10:21,582 --> 00:10:22,865
别妄想逃跑
no one leaves.

182
00:10:22,866 --> 00:10:24,867
我亲爱的April 好好记着
April, my sweet, take notes.

183
00:10:24,868 --> 00:10:26,793
在这个镇上 想得到答案只有这个办法
This is how you get answers in this town.

184
00:10:26,794 --> 00:10:29,138
先来做个小测试吧
Let's start with a little quiz.

185
00:10:29,139 --> 00:10:30,070
1114年 
In the year 1114, 

186
00:10:30,071 --> 00:10:32,708
我哥哥得知 这还得归功于你们兄弟俩
my brother learned... thanks to yours truly...

187
00:10:32,709 --> 00:10:35,377
得知吸血鬼猎人之间有兄弟联系
About a brotherhood of vampire hunters with tattoos

188
00:10:35,378 --> 00:10:37,346
他们的纹身会随着猎杀的增多而延伸
that grew with each kill.

189
00:10:37,347 --> 00:10:40,733
Elena 这些纹身是什么
And these tattoos reveal what? Elena?

190
00:10:40,734 --> 00:10:42,234
一幅地图
A map.

191
00:10:42,235 --> 00:10:45,154
Caroline 地图指向什么
Which led to, Caroline?

192
00:10:45,155 --> 00:10:46,689
治愈吸血鬼的解药
A cure for vampirism.

193
00:10:46,690 --> 00:10:48,724
很好  我们都理清了
Perfect. We're all caught up.

194
00:10:48,725 --> 00:10:50,687
Stefan Salvatore 
Stefan Salvatore, 

195
00:10:50,688 --> 00:10:51,727
上次我们见面的时候
the last time we saw each other,

196
00:10:51,728 --> 00:10:53,365
你抓到了一个吸血鬼猎人 
you had a vampire hunter, 

197
00:10:53,366 --> 00:10:54,730
只不过要是想破译地图
but in order to decode the map,

198
00:10:54,731 --> 00:10:57,066
你还需要知道猎人之剑在哪里
you needed the location of the hunter's sword,

199
00:10:57,067 --> 00:11:01,454
所以你就用了些下三滥的手段从我身上套出来了
which you got out of me using some very dirty tricks.

200
00:11:01,455 --> 00:11:02,715
如果你找到猎人之剑了 
Assuming you found the sword, 

201
00:11:02,716 --> 00:11:04,090
那你肯定也已经拿到解药了
you must have found the cure,

202
00:11:04,091 --> 00:11:06,542
不过既然你们都还是吸血鬼
and yet you're all still vampires,

203
00:11:06,543 --> 00:11:08,260
那中间肯定有什么地方出了岔子
which means something went wrong.

204
00:11:08,261 --> 00:11:09,545
你在干什么
What are you doing?

205
00:11:09,546 --> 00:11:12,598
你不是叫我做记录的吗
You asked me to take notes.

206
00:11:12,599 --> 00:11:14,266
亲爱的 听别人说话能不能别只听字面意思
I wasn't being literal, darling.

207
00:11:14,267 --> 00:11:16,302
不过既然你想做 那干脆做个流程表吧
But now that you mention it, a flow chart would be nice,

208
00:11:16,303 --> 00:11:19,053
还差索引卡和图钉  去拿吧
which means index cards and push pins. Go fetch.

209
00:11:20,807 --> 00:11:22,475
你这样纯属浪费时间
You're wasting your time.

210
00:11:22,476 --> 00:11:24,426
我们什么都不知道
We don't know anything.

211
00:11:24,427 --> 00:11:26,445
那你就这样放弃了啊
So you just gave up?

212
00:11:26,446 --> 00:11:29,148
我还以为 为了Elena 你赴汤蹈火在所不惜呢
I thought you'd do anything to save Elena,

213
00:11:29,149 --> 00:11:31,784
甚至都甘愿自己使用解药
even if it meant taking the cure yourself

214
00:11:31,785 --> 00:11:33,693
陪着她生老病死
so you could grow old and die with her.

215
00:11:37,290 --> 00:11:39,616
你们干嘛这么惊讶
Why do you look so surprised?

216
00:11:44,998 --> 00:11:46,706
我是不是错过什么了
I'm missing something. What is it?

217
00:11:48,835 --> 00:11:50,752
好吧 他们分手了
They broke up, ok?

218
00:11:52,556 --> 00:11:53,889
放我们走吧
Now let us go.

219
00:11:53,890 --> 00:11:55,465
分手
Broke up?

220
00:11:57,010 --> 00:11:58,811
等会儿  我有点混乱
Wait. I'm confused.

221
00:11:58,812 --> 00:12:02,430
Stefan 我还以为Elena是你此生挚爱呢
I thought Elena was your epic love, Stefan.

222
00:12:04,685 --> 00:12:06,736
到底发生了什么
I asked you what happened,

223
00:12:06,737 --> 00:12:08,738
老实回答我
and you have to tell me.

224
00:12:08,739 --> 00:12:10,980
她跟Damon睡了
She slept with Damon.

225
00:12:28,341 --> 00:12:29,666
很好
Good.

226
00:12:30,994 --> 00:12:32,661
现在
Now...

227
00:12:34,131 --> 00:12:35,806
重做 就跟你必须得做一样 
Now do it like your life 

228
00:12:35,807 --> 00:12:36,966
事实上也确实是这样
depends on it 'cause it does.

229
00:12:36,967 --> 00:12:38,500
别一副你在乎我生死的样子
Don't act like you care about my life.

230
00:12:38,501 --> 00:12:40,335
你只关心猎人的标记和治愈Elena
You care about the hunter's mark and curing Elena

231
00:12:40,336 --> 00:12:42,304
那样她就不会对你认宗了
so she's not sired to your ass.

232
00:12:42,305 --> 00:12:44,673
要想要达成这两个目标 都需要你还活着
Both require you to be alive,

233
00:12:44,674 --> 00:12:46,318
所以我才把我们的关系提升到
which is why I've updated

234
00:12:46,319 --> 00:12:49,344
复杂的层面
our relationship status to "It's complicated."

235
00:12:51,648 --> 00:12:53,532
你跟她谈过吗
You talked to her at all?

236
00:12:53,533 --> 00:12:55,184
Elena
Elena?

237
00:12:55,185 --> 00:12:56,902
嗯
Maybe.

238
00:12:56,903 --> 00:12:59,872
干嘛  听她把我的语音信箱打爆吗
Why? Run out of voicemails to listen to?

239
00:12:59,873 --> 00:13:02,992
不好意思啊  我是不是破坏了气氛
I'm sorry. Did I interrupt play time?

240
00:13:02,993 --> 00:13:04,160
你来这儿搞什么鬼
What the hell are you doing here?

241
00:13:04,161 --> 00:13:05,327
我只是过来享受
I'm simply appreciating

242
00:13:05,328 --> 00:13:07,329
大自然的气息
the sights and smells of nature,

243
00:13:07,330 --> 00:13:10,549
远离腐烂的吸血鬼
neither of which presently include rotting vampire flesh,

244
00:13:10,550 --> 00:13:12,918
所以我想知道
so I'm a bit concerned.

245
00:13:12,919 --> 00:13:14,970
他杀了多少吸血鬼了
How many vampires has he killed?

246
00:13:14,971 --> 00:13:17,113
如果我们现在把Jeremy带出去 
If we throw Jeremy out into the world right now, 

247
00:13:17,114 --> 00:13:18,374
他一定能钓不少吸血鬼
he's chum.

248
00:13:18,375 --> 00:13:20,760
少来了 你还没说多少个
Now, see, that's not a number.

249
00:13:20,761 --> 00:13:22,762
12个 这是个数字
12... that's a number.

250
00:13:22,763 --> 00:13:26,015
这是我用剑杀掉的混血儿数目
That's how many of my hybrids I slaughtered with my sword.

251
00:13:26,016 --> 00:13:28,184
3 这是我用来压制住要杀掉你弟弟的怒火
3... that's how many days it took

252
00:13:28,185 --> 00:13:29,885
所花费的天数
to quell the urge to kill your brother, after

253
00:13:29,886 --> 00:13:32,905
要知道 他故意看着我杀了那么多混血儿
he knowingly watched as I walked into a death trap.

254
00:13:32,906 --> 00:13:34,240
1
One...

255
00:13:34,241 --> 00:13:37,243
这是你的目标的个数
That's the number of purposes you serve.

256
00:13:37,244 --> 00:13:41,113
既然你到这儿来是为了延伸Jeremy的标记
You are here to grow Jeremy's mark,

257
00:13:41,114 --> 00:13:44,083
那我再问一遍
so I ask again...

258
00:13:44,084 --> 00:13:47,586
他来这儿之后杀了多少吸血鬼了
How many vampires has he killed since he's been here?

259
00:13:47,587 --> 00:13:49,738
一个也没有
Zero.

260
00:13:49,739 --> 00:13:52,081
真是可惜
Hmm. That's a pity.

261
00:13:53,460 --> 00:13:57,746
我可是急需解药啊
I'm going to need that cure sooner rather than later,

262
00:13:57,747 --> 00:14:00,766
我的混血儿数量不多了
hybrid shortage and all.

263
00:14:00,767 --> 00:14:02,935
有什么需要我帮忙的吗
How can I help?

264
00:14:02,936 --> 00:14:05,137
既然
You know...

265
00:14:05,138 --> 00:14:08,107
既然你都提出来了
Now that you mention it,

266
00:14:08,108 --> 00:14:10,309
Jeremy 好好学着
Jeremy... Watch and learn.

267
00:14:15,482 --> 00:14:17,774
这是替Carol Lockwood报的仇
That's for Carol Lockwood.

268
00:14:22,622 --> 00:14:26,325
也就是说 吸血鬼Elena是一个喜欢坏家伙的花心女
So, vampire Elena is a trollop who likes bad boys,

269
00:14:26,326 --> 00:14:28,443
这也就是为什么Stefan浑身散发着酒气的原因
which explains why Stefan reeks of alcohol.

270
00:14:28,817 --> 00:14:33,494
不过我就不明白了 这么甜美单纯的Elena
But what it doesn't explain is why sweet, loving,

271
00:14:34,614 --> 00:14:38,641
怎么会对Stefan这么残忍呢
innocent Elena could be so heartless towards Stefan.

272
00:14:42,676 --> 00:14:45,635
她怎么对你这么残忍啊  回答我
How could she hurt you like that? Answer, please.

273
00:14:46,930 --> 00:14:48,364
她当时是不自知的
She didn't know it at the time,

274
00:14:48,365 --> 00:14:49,972
她对Damon认宗了
but she was sired to Damon.

275
00:14:52,903 --> 00:14:55,971
认祖归宗  真是有趣
A sire bond. Fascinating.

276
00:14:56,436 --> 00:14:58,140
Elena 你怎么想
And what do you think about that, Elena?

277
00:14:58,141 --> 00:15:01,493
我觉得你既可悲又无聊
I think you're sad and bored

278
00:15:01,494 --> 00:15:04,146
极度渴望有个乐子
and in desperate need of a hobby.

279
00:15:04,147 --> 00:15:07,482
你在掩饰什么  快说
You're hiding something. 'Fess up.

280
00:15:07,483 --> 00:15:10,870
我不是因为什么认祖归宗才和Damon睡的
I didn't sleep with Damon because of his sire bond.

281
00:15:10,871 --> 00:15:13,204
我和Damon睡是因为我爱上了他
I slept with Damon because I'm in love with him.

282
00:15:25,719 --> 00:15:28,553
这些跟那该死的解药有什么关系
What does any of this have to do with the stupid cure?

283
00:15:30,223 --> 00:15:32,725
你说的对  我们跑题了
You're right. We got off the point.

284
00:15:32,726 --> 00:15:35,694
Stefan 我怎么能找到解药呢
Stefan, how do I find the cure?

285
00:15:35,695 --> 00:15:36,228
除非你想
Unless you'd rather

286
00:15:36,229 --> 00:15:39,031
一整天这样讨论Damon和Elena的事儿
 talk about Damon and Elena all day.

287
00:15:39,032 --> 00:15:41,317
有个教授  他知道解药在哪
There's a Professor. He knows where the cure is.

288
00:15:41,318 --> 00:15:45,287
谢谢  那么 我要到哪找到这个教授呢
Thank you. And, uh, where do I find this Professor?

289
00:15:45,288 --> 00:15:47,581
哦 现在我又变成天赐宝贝了  
Oh, and so now I'm "Gifted"? 

290
00:15:47,582 --> 00:15:48,958
他痛恨我继承了巫术
He hates my witch heritage.

291
00:15:48,959 --> 00:15:50,859
这也是他为什么一直出门在外  他承受不了
That's why he travels all the time. He can't handle it.

292
00:15:50,860 --> 00:15:53,579
突然间他想变成个保护我的父亲了
And suddenly he wants to be a protective father?

293
00:15:53,580 --> 00:15:55,547
不  不应该是这样的
No. Not like this.

294
00:15:55,548 --> 00:15:57,700
喂  分散一下我的注意力嘛
Come on. Distract me.

295
00:15:57,701 --> 00:15:59,668
难道没有什么
Isn't there some...

296
00:15:59,669 --> 00:16:03,172
还没展示给我的魔力治疗法吗
Magic therapy thing you haven't shown me yet?

297
00:16:03,173 --> 00:16:04,924
听着 Bonnie 我讨厌告诉你这事
Listen, Bonnie, I hate to tell you this...

298
00:16:04,925 --> 00:16:06,508
实际上 你知道吗  我收回刚才那句话
Actually, you know what? I take that back.

299
00:16:06,509 --> 00:16:08,877
我很自豪地告诉你
I'm proud to tell you this.

300
00:16:08,878 --> 00:16:10,312
你已经不需要我的帮助了
You don't need my help anymore.

301
00:16:10,313 --> 00:16:12,263
实际上
In fact...

302
00:16:17,237 --> 00:16:20,062
我本来想配个小蛋糕什么的拿出来给你看的
I was hoping to present this with a cupcake or something.

303
00:16:23,660 --> 00:16:25,067
毕业快乐
Happy graduation.

304
00:16:30,250 --> 00:16:31,417
真漂亮
It's beautiful.

305
00:16:31,418 --> 00:16:33,669
- 是块人骨   - 哦
- It's human bone. - Oh.

306
00:16:33,670 --> 00:16:35,921
传说这是
Legend says it was worn

307
00:16:35,922 --> 00:16:38,257
2000岁的女巫Qetsiyah打磨的
by the 2,000-year-old witch Qetsiyah,

308
00:16:38,258 --> 00:16:40,125
她在上面刻画
who drew on it...

309
00:16:40,126 --> 00:16:41,743
来寻求力量
For strength.

310
00:16:41,744 --> 00:16:45,747
Bonnie 你很快的就学会了这么多
Bonnie, you have come so far so fast.

311
00:16:45,748 --> 00:16:47,749
你要相信我的想法
If you trust my opinion,

312
00:16:47,750 --> 00:16:49,717
你的魔力现在刚好够用了
your magic is exactly where it needs to be.

313
00:16:50,971 --> 00:16:52,938
是说我得回家了的意思吗
Does this mean I have to go home?

314
00:16:52,939 --> 00:16:55,806
我是说我被工作缠身 我明天才能批卷子
It means I got a stack of papers I got to grade by tomorrow.

315
00:16:55,807 --> 00:16:57,016
我能听懂你的暗示
I can take a hint.

316
00:16:59,929 --> 00:17:01,646
谢谢你Shane
Thanks, Shane.

317
00:17:16,713 --> 00:17:18,630
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.

318
00:17:18,631 --> 00:17:20,115
是Kol
Kol.

319
00:17:21,835 --> 00:17:23,584
Shane?
Shane?

320
00:17:46,825 --> 00:17:48,525
我说了我不想聊天
I told you I don't want to talk.

321
00:17:48,526 --> 00:17:50,844
我听出来了  你在把所有的愤怒
I heard. You're keeping all that rage

322
00:17:50,845 --> 00:17:52,830
都憋在心里
bottled up inside.

323
00:17:52,831 --> 00:17:54,615
Caroline非常担心你
Caroline's worried sick about you.

324
00:17:54,616 --> 00:17:55,833
Rebekah?
Rebekah?

325
00:17:55,834 --> 00:17:57,418
你好啊Tyler
Hello, Tyler.

326
00:17:57,419 --> 00:18:00,421
我听说我哥哥把你生活搅的一团糟
I heard my brother made a real mess of your life.

327
00:18:00,422 --> 00:18:04,174
相信我 我能明白  我对你表示慰问
Believe me, I can relate. You have my condolences.

328
00:18:04,175 --> 00:18:05,585
其实 你可以来学校里
In fact, why don't you come down

329
00:18:05,586 --> 00:18:07,878
你可以当面接受我的慰问
to the high school so you can accept them in person?

330
00:18:07,879 --> 00:18:09,079
我为什么要那么做
And why would I do that?

331
00:18:09,080 --> 00:18:11,131
因为你女朋友在我手上
Because I have your girlfriend.

332
00:18:11,132 --> 00:18:12,263
也许比起你妈妈
Maybe you have a better

333
00:18:12,264 --> 00:18:14,427
你这回有更好的机会救你女朋友  拜拜啦
shot at saving her than you did your mother. Bye now.

334
00:18:21,860 --> 00:18:24,528
姐
Sister...

335
00:18:24,529 --> 00:18:25,879
看看这场面
Look at this.

336
00:18:25,880 --> 00:18:27,881
你比Klaus还坏
You're even worse than Klaus.

337
00:18:27,882 --> 00:18:29,683
Kol  你终于回来了
Kol. Finally.

338
00:18:29,684 --> 00:18:31,485
你带来我要的了吗
Did you bring me what I asked for?

339
00:18:37,659 --> 00:18:39,243
你一定是Shane了
You must be Shane.

340
00:18:49,036 --> 00:18:51,388
你要是来这报仇的 尽管来吧
If you're here for payback, go for it.

341
00:18:51,389 --> 00:18:54,558
那你就要被困在这照顾小猎人了
But you'll be stuck baby-sitting the little hunter that could.

342
00:18:54,559 --> 00:18:56,877
你知道吗
You know...

343
00:18:56,878 --> 00:18:59,150
你要是再调整一点角度
If you adjust your angle a little bit,

344
00:18:59,151 --> 00:19:00,765
你就能削出更锋利的边缘了
you'll find a sharper edge.

345
00:19:02,434 --> 00:19:05,602
我知道怎么削木棍  谢谢
I know how to whittle. Thanks.

346
00:19:05,603 --> 00:19:07,571
现在我知道为什么那些混血而讨厌你了
Now I know why those hybrids hated you.

347
00:19:07,572 --> 00:19:08,906
你太烦人
You are annoying.

348
00:19:08,907 --> 00:19:11,075
其实 我现在只是困惑
Actually, I'm just perplexed

349
00:19:11,076 --> 00:19:13,201
想问问你为什么Jeremy到现在还没有
as to why Jeremy hasn't 

350
00:19:13,202 --> 00:19:13,761
猎杀吸血鬼
killed any vampires.

351
00:19:13,762 --> 00:19:15,312
达尔文进化论 知道吗Klaus
Darwinism, Klaus.

352
00:19:15,313 --> 00:19:16,914
在我们给他抓好一窝吸血鬼之前
He needs to be able to protect himself

353
00:19:16,915 --> 00:19:19,566
他需要先有能力保护自己
before we hunt down his first vampire nest.

354
00:19:19,567 --> 00:19:21,752
我坐在这里 想起了你真是个有趣的哥哥
And here was I, thinking you were the fun brother.

355
00:19:21,753 --> 00:19:23,737
那么 我们来玩个小游戏 怎么样
Well, let's play a little game, shall we?

356
00:19:23,738 --> 00:19:24,918
Jeremy需要更多的牺牲品 
Jeremy needs more victims, 

357
00:19:24,919 --> 00:19:25,706
这里有一整个小镇的人
and there's a whole town of people

358
00:19:25,707 --> 00:19:27,221
就在路旁等着我们
down the road just waiting

359
00:19:27,222 --> 00:19:29,843
把他们变成吸血鬼
to be turned into vampires for the slaughter.

360
00:19:29,844 --> 00:19:31,879
你以为我没想到过吗 Klaus
You don't think that occurred to me, Klaus?

361
00:19:31,880 --> 00:19:33,914
Damon 悲剧的是
The tragedy is, Damon,

362
00:19:33,915 --> 00:19:36,767
你想到过 但是你选择无视它
it did occur to you, yet you chose to ignore it.

363
00:19:36,768 --> 00:19:39,770
我猜你那么做是为了打动Elena
And my guess is you did it to impress Elena.

364
00:19:39,771 --> 00:19:43,807
为了尊重她 你不愿再滥杀无辜
Somehow, to honor her, you'll find a way to spare innocent lives

365
00:19:43,808 --> 00:19:46,268
并带领Jeremy走上道德之路
and walk Jeremy down the moral high road.

366
00:19:48,363 --> 00:19:51,482
这也是为什么我已经做了些必要的修正
That's why I've already made the necessary corrections.

367
00:19:53,635 --> 00:19:55,528
你做了什么
What did you do?

368
00:20:01,826 --> 00:20:03,744
别告诉我他又订了个披萨
Don't tell me he ordered another pizza.

369
00:20:03,745 --> 00:20:05,329
不 是我太不注意了
No, I'm just an idiot.

370
00:20:05,330 --> 00:20:07,714
我的汽车没油了 手机也没电了
I ran out of gas and my phone's dead.

371
00:20:07,715 --> 00:20:08,938
我在想我可不可以借用你的手机  
Think I could use yours? 

372
00:20:08,939 --> 00:20:09,550
可以 进来吧
Yeah, come on in.

373
00:20:09,551 --> 00:20:11,502
那我上楼去拿手机
I'll run upstairs and grab my cell.

374
00:20:15,557 --> 00:20:17,925
怎么回事儿
What the hell?

375
00:20:17,926 --> 00:20:19,810
你怎么在这儿
What are you doing here?

376
00:20:19,811 --> 00:20:21,395
车出了点问题
Car drama.

377
00:20:21,396 --> 00:20:23,296
你朋友去拿他手机了
Your friend just went to go get his phone.

378
00:20:23,297 --> 00:20:24,681
我要去冲个澡
Well, I'm about to go take a shower,

379
00:20:24,682 --> 00:20:26,892
不如你进来等着吧
but you're more than welcome to wait inside.

380
00:20:34,025 --> 00:20:35,909
谢了
Thanks.

381
00:20:41,749 --> 00:20:43,149
Kol...
Kol...

382
00:20:43,150 --> 00:20:45,485
还有Rebakah Mikaelson 吸血鬼始祖的
And Rebekah Mikaelson, two members of

383
00:20:45,486 --> 00:20:48,122
两个成员都来了 真不枉此行
the original vampire family. This is such a trip.

384
00:20:49,440 --> 00:20:51,291
解药在哪
Where's the cure?

385
00:20:51,292 --> 00:20:54,044
控制对我不起作用
Compulsion won't work.

386
00:20:54,045 --> 00:20:56,630
这是我在西藏学到的小伎俩
It's a little trick I picked up in Tibet.

387
00:20:56,631 --> 00:21:01,001
是吗 那我们就用老办法来
Right. Well, we'll just have to do this the old-fashioned way.

388
00:21:01,002 --> 00:21:04,021
打他 打到他告诉你怎么找到解药为止
Beat him until he tells you where to find it.

389
00:21:08,443 --> 00:21:11,061
都乖乖坐着没动啊
Still glued to your seats?

390
00:21:11,062 --> 00:21:13,189
这气氛有点紧张啊
Ooh, it's thick with tension in here.

391
00:21:14,449 --> 00:21:16,483
不如我们来活跃一下气氛
Let's spice things up a bit.

392
00:21:16,484 --> 00:21:18,869
Elena 真心话还是大冒险
Elena, truth or dare?

393
00:21:18,870 --> 00:21:21,021
Rebakah 我们对你幼稚的游戏没兴趣
We're done playing your stupid games, Rebekah.

394
00:21:21,022 --> 00:21:23,123
真心话还是大冒险 Elena
Truth or dare, Elena?

395
00:21:23,124 --> 00:21:25,142
你现在是身不由己  回答我
You're compelled. Answer.

396
00:21:25,143 --> 00:21:26,452
大冒险
Dare.

397
00:21:27,745 --> 00:21:29,580
我要你告诉Stefan
I dare you to tell Stefan

398
00:21:29,581 --> 00:21:31,048
你对Damon的真感情
the truth about Damon.

399
00:21:31,049 --> 00:21:32,458
开玩笑吧
Seriously?

400
00:21:38,056 --> 00:21:40,308
跟Damon在一起让我很开心
Being with Damon makes me happy.

401
00:21:40,309 --> 00:21:43,560
让你开心吗  小丑才能让人开心 Elena
Make you happy? Clowns make you happy, Elena.

402
00:21:43,561 --> 00:21:45,178
说点更实际的
Dig a little deeper.

403
00:21:45,179 --> 00:21:47,981
当我跟他在一起时...
When I'm with him...

404
00:21:49,400 --> 00:21:53,437
感觉难以预测 就像...
It feels unpredictable, like...

405
00:21:53,438 --> 00:21:55,397
我感觉很自在
Like I'm free.

406
00:21:57,659 --> 00:22:00,027
那你跟Stefan在一起是什么感觉
And how do you feel when you're with Stefan?

407
00:22:00,028 --> 00:22:01,795
别说了 
Stop.

408
00:22:01,796 --> 00:22:03,780
她做不到  她被我控制了
She can't. She's compelled.

409
00:22:03,781 --> 00:22:07,618
这段时间 我感觉自己就像个烂摊子一样
Lately, I feel like I'm a project,

410
00:22:07,619 --> 00:22:11,705
好像我是个需要被修理的问题一样
like I'm a problem that needs to be fixed.

411
00:22:13,041 --> 00:22:15,442
我觉得我让他很难过
I think I make him sad,

412
00:22:15,443 --> 00:22:17,544
我不能跟那样的人在一起
and I can't be with someone like that

413
00:22:17,545 --> 00:22:20,097
因为...
because...

414
00:22:20,098 --> 00:22:24,093
当他看着我时 他看到的只是一个破碎的玩具
When he looks at me, all he sees is a broken toy.

415
00:22:31,025 --> 00:22:32,977
你还爱Stefan吗
Do you still love Stefan?

416
00:22:34,729 --> 00:22:36,146
爱
Yes.

417
00:22:38,116 --> 00:22:40,008
你还想和他在一起吗
Are you still in love with Stefan?

418
00:22:42,370 --> 00:22:43,529
不想
No.

419
00:22:49,794 --> 00:22:52,129
刚刚那样是不是很心痛
Did that hurt,

420
00:22:52,130 --> 00:22:54,581
你所爱的人刺痛了你的心
having someone you love drive a dagger through your heart?

421
00:22:54,582 --> 00:22:55,882
去死吧你
Go to hell.

422
00:22:55,883 --> 00:22:59,253
你痛苦吗
Did... that... hurt?

423
00:23:04,142 --> 00:23:05,467
痛苦
Yes.

424
00:23:08,896 --> 00:23:12,808
那么 你终于可以理解这900多年来我的痛苦了
Welcome to the last 900 years of my life.

425
00:23:17,989 --> 00:23:21,491
很好 你来了啊  刚才这里可压抑了
Ah, good, you're here. It was just getting depressing.

426
00:23:21,492 --> 00:23:22,993
这里到底发生了什么
What the hell is going on?

427
00:23:22,994 --> 00:23:25,362
你们听好规则
Listen to the rules carefully.

428
00:23:25,363 --> 00:23:26,676
全部待在楼里  
Stay in the building. 

429
00:23:26,676 --> 00:23:28,481
在走廊里不准用吸血鬼的速度逃跑
No vamp-running in the hallways.

430
00:23:28,482 --> 00:23:30,200
为什么要用吸血鬼的速度逃跑
Vamp-running from what?

431
00:23:34,372 --> 00:23:36,173
- 变身吧   - 你说什么
- Turn. - What?

432
00:23:36,174 --> 00:23:38,091
不能那样  他会失控的
You can't. He'll lose control.

433
00:23:38,092 --> 00:23:39,509
就是要让他失控
That's the whole point.

434
00:23:39,510 --> 00:23:41,128
我对你们的小伎俩已经厌倦了
I've exhausted all your knowledge.

435
00:23:41,129 --> 00:23:43,380
而现在我又抓到教授来帮我找解药
Now I have the Professor to help me find the cure,

436
00:23:43,381 --> 00:23:44,998
来竞争吧
you're just competition.

437
00:23:44,999 --> 00:23:47,884
第一个找到解药的人可以决定如何使用它
Whoever finds it first gets to decide what to do with it:

438
00:23:47,885 --> 00:23:51,722
不管是使用 分享 破坏 还是保留它
Use it, share it, destroy it, save it...

439
00:23:51,723 --> 00:23:53,357
那个人必须是我
I want that to be me.

440
00:23:53,358 --> 00:23:55,142
可是我要是变身 我会杀了他们的
But if I turn, I'll kill them.

441
00:23:56,694 --> 00:23:58,312
没错 你会的
Yes, you will.

442
00:24:00,148 --> 00:24:01,899
变身吧
Turn.

443
00:24:21,883 --> 00:24:24,084
你找到你的手机了吗
Did you find your phone?

444
00:24:28,343 --> 00:24:29,673
给我下来
Get off!

445
00:24:29,674 --> 00:24:30,719
下来
Get off!

446
00:24:52,780 --> 00:24:56,000
Bonnie? 你怎么知道大家都在这儿
Bonnie? How did you know everone is here?

447
00:24:56,125 --> 00:24:57,735
你说大家是指谁  我是来找Shane的
What's everone? I came to find Shane.

448
00:24:57,735 --> 00:25:01,105
你是做了什么GPS定位的咒语还是什么吗
Did you do a GPS magic located spell or something?

449
00:25:01,390 --> 00:25:03,390
Rebekah告诉我 你是个女巫
Rebekah told me that you're a witch.

450
00:25:03,391 --> 00:25:05,587
Rebekah  这究竟是怎么回事啊
Rebekah? What the hell is going on?

451
00:25:05,588 --> 00:25:08,211
Rebekah控制了Stefan Elena和Caroline
Rebekah has Stefan, Elena, and Caroline compelled.

452
00:25:08,212 --> 00:25:10,592
她让他们全部都实话实说
She's getting them to actually tell the truth for a change.

453
00:25:11,066 --> 00:25:13,066
怎么了
What?

454
00:25:13,067 --> 00:25:14,651
Shane是不能被控制的
Shane can't be compelled.

455
00:25:14,652 --> 00:25:17,771
她为了开他的口一定会折磨他的
She'll have him torture him to find out what he knows.

456
00:25:17,772 --> 00:25:20,207
- 你在找什么   - 我需要盐
- What are you looking for? - I need salt.

457
00:25:20,208 --> 00:25:22,576
我刚才看到了一些
I think I just saw some.

458
00:25:29,000 --> 00:25:30,784
你在做什么
What are you doing?

459
00:25:30,785 --> 00:25:32,402
如果这个链子能把我和Shane联系起来
If this pendant will connect me to Shane,

460
00:25:32,403 --> 00:25:34,158
那我就能施一个保护咒
then I can do a protection spell.

461
00:25:53,524 --> 00:25:55,692
解药在哪
Where is the cure?!

462
00:26:00,031 --> 00:26:01,727
解药在哪
Where is the cure?

463
00:26:14,489 --> 00:26:16,880
你只是个人类  你到底为什么想要它
You're human. Why do you want it anyway?

464
00:26:16,881 --> 00:26:18,114
这就是它的美妙之处
That's the beauty of this.

465
00:26:18,115 --> 00:26:19,549
你可以拿去  我只要Silas
You can have it. I just want Silas.

466
00:26:19,550 --> 00:26:22,135
不
No.

467
00:26:23,638 --> 00:26:25,788
关于Silas你知道多少
What do you know about Silas?

468
00:26:25,789 --> 00:26:27,757
他是这个世界上第一个不死之身
He's the world's first immortal being,

469
00:26:27,758 --> 00:26:30,393
又刚好被这解药所封印
who just happens to be imprisoned with the cure.

470
00:26:30,394 --> 00:26:32,466
我想放他自由
And I want to free him.

471
00:26:32,467 --> 00:26:33,800
不
No!

472
00:26:39,103 --> 00:26:40,603
April?
April?

473
00:26:42,773 --> 00:26:44,240
怎么了这是
What's happening?

474
00:26:52,616 --> 00:26:54,417
住手
Stop!

475
00:27:02,626 --> 00:27:03,877
他要是死了就帮不上忙了
He's of no use dead.

476
00:27:03,878 --> 00:27:05,161
你没听到他怎么说的吗
Did you not hear what he said?

477
00:27:05,162 --> 00:27:06,625
Silas会杀了我们所有人 姐姐
Silas will kill us all, sister.

478
00:27:07,049 --> 00:27:10,300
Silas是不存在的  他只是为了
Silas does not exist. He is a fairy tale

479
00:27:10,301 --> 00:27:12,852
骗小孩吃下蔬菜编出来的童话而已
made up to scare children into eating their vegetables.

480
00:27:12,853 --> 00:27:14,883
Silas真的存在
Silas is very real.

481
00:27:16,857 --> 00:27:18,841
我知道他被埋在哪
I know where he's buried,

482
00:27:18,842 --> 00:27:21,061
而且不久我就能得到唤醒他的咒语
and soon I'll have the spell that wakes him.

483
00:27:21,062 --> 00:27:22,896
等会儿  你在撒谎
Wait a second. You're lying.

484
00:27:22,897 --> 00:27:24,731
你不可能唤醒他 除非你有他的
You can't get to him without his...

485
00:27:24,732 --> 00:27:25,852
墓碑吗
Tombstone?

486
00:27:26,284 --> 00:27:28,818
无数的流血牺牲吗
Dozens to die in a blood sacrifice?

487
00:27:28,819 --> 00:27:30,537
相信我 我知道
Believe me, I know.

488
00:27:30,538 --> 00:27:32,288
我干过
I've done it.

489
00:27:32,289 --> 00:27:35,525
那些大屠杀对制造者来说是痛苦的回忆
Those massacres are a pain to engineer.

490
00:27:35,526 --> 00:27:38,962
委员会的爆炸事件是你造成的
You're the one who got the council blown up.

491
00:27:38,963 --> 00:27:41,748
那是崇高的牺牲
It was a noble sacrifice...

492
00:27:41,749 --> 00:27:44,584
而且只是暂时的
And temporary

493
00:27:44,585 --> 00:27:47,053
因为一旦我唤醒Silas
because once I raise Silas...

494
00:27:47,054 --> 00:27:49,472
Silas就能让他们起死回生
Silas will raise the dead.

495
00:27:49,473 --> 00:27:53,176
他能唤回每一条逝去的灵魂
He will bring back every last soul...

496
00:27:53,177 --> 00:27:55,895
为他而逝去的灵魂
Who died on his behalf.

497
00:27:55,896 --> 00:27:57,313
不
No!

498
00:28:03,104 --> 00:28:05,100
April 哦 天呐
April, oh, my God!

499
00:28:22,506 --> 00:28:24,624
等会儿  我能控制住
Wait. I can fight it.

500
00:28:42,693 --> 00:28:45,228
快离开这儿
Get out of here!

501
00:28:45,229 --> 00:28:47,225
走
Go.

502
00:28:49,483 --> 00:28:52,702
那扇门是拦不住他的
That door's not gonna hold him.

503
00:29:50,329 --> 00:29:51,987
你应该感谢我
You should be thanking me.

504
00:29:51,988 --> 00:29:53,873
你杀了我找到解药唯一的希望
You killed my only chance at finding the cure.

505
00:29:53,874 --> 00:29:56,408
把Silas放出来的话 一切就完了
Silas on the loose would be hell on earth.

506
00:29:56,409 --> 00:29:59,194
坦白地说 姐姐
And frankly, sister...

507
00:29:59,195 --> 00:30:01,747
我不认为你能处理好
I don't think you could handle it.

508
00:30:01,748 --> 00:30:03,049
你怎么拿到它的
How did you get that?

509
00:30:03,050 --> 00:30:04,967
不费吹灰之力
Way too easily.

510
00:30:41,505 --> 00:30:43,455
是Bonnie
Bonnie.

511
00:30:43,456 --> 00:30:46,091
救命啊 快来人啊
Help! Someone help!

512
00:30:47,878 --> 00:30:49,011
Bonnie 发生什么事了
Bonnie, what's going on?

513
00:30:49,012 --> 00:30:50,012
快来救救她
She needs help.

514
00:30:50,013 --> 00:30:51,514
到底怎么回事
What happened?

515
00:30:51,515 --> 00:30:53,215
我施了一个保护咒 但是却意外地把Shane
I did a protection spell, but it accidentally linked

516
00:30:53,216 --> 00:30:54,517
和April相通了
Shane to April.

517
00:30:54,518 --> 00:30:55,935
你不能控制你的法力吗
And you couldn't control it?

518
00:30:55,936 --> 00:30:57,469
我根本就不知道我施成了咒语
I didn't even know I was doing it.

519
00:30:57,470 --> 00:30:59,104
往常我都是感觉到疼痛 或者会流鼻血 但这一次
Usually I feel pain or I bleed, but this time I just

520
00:30:59,105 --> 00:31:01,359
我只是感觉更有能量了
felt more power.

521
00:31:04,027 --> 00:31:05,427
没事了  没事了
It's ok. It's ok.

522
00:31:05,905 --> 00:31:09,097
你没事了 你没事了 你会好的 好了
You're ok. You're ok. You're ok. Ok.

523
00:31:09,659 --> 00:31:11,266
Bonnie 赶快带她离开学校
Bonnie, get her out of the school.

524
00:31:11,267 --> 00:31:14,486
千万要小心  Tyler在附近 而且他变身了
Just be careful. Tyler is out there, and he turned.

525
00:31:14,487 --> 00:31:15,988
那你们呢
What about you?

526
00:31:15,989 --> 00:31:17,918
我们走不了了 Rebekah控制了我们
No, we can't leave. Rebekah's compelled us.

527
00:31:17,919 --> 00:31:21,243
赶紧走吧  我们一会儿还要对付她  走吧
Just go. We'll deal with her later.  Come on

528
00:31:28,635 --> 00:31:29,668
Stefan
Stefan...

529
00:31:29,669 --> 00:31:30,722
什么都别说
No.

530
00:31:31,138 --> 00:31:33,308
Stefan 我们必须谈谈  求你了
Stefan, we have to talk about this. Please.

531
00:31:33,309 --> 00:31:35,257
谈什么
Talk about what, huh?

532
00:31:35,258 --> 00:31:38,344
你到底还要用多少种方法来伤透我的心啊
How many more ways are there for you to rip my heart out?

533
00:31:38,345 --> 00:31:39,397
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.

534
00:31:39,847 --> 00:31:41,630
你是为你的所作所为抱歉 还是为你的东窗事发抱歉呢
Sorry that it happened, or sorry that I found out?

535
00:31:41,631 --> 00:31:44,033
我是为所有的事向你道歉
I'm sorry about all of it.

536
00:31:44,034 --> 00:31:45,634
我真的很对不起你 Stefan
I'm really sorry, Stefan.

537
00:31:45,635 --> 00:31:50,072
我并不想伤害你的  这不是我想要的结果
I didn't mean to hurt you. I didn't want that.

538
00:31:52,826 --> 00:31:56,623
为什么我最讨厌的家伙总能坚持得最久呢
Why are my least favorite people always the most durable?

539
00:32:03,286 --> 00:32:05,754
Tyler
Tyler...

540
00:32:26,364 --> 00:32:29,449
真的很对不起
I'm so sorry.

541
00:32:29,450 --> 00:32:32,035
这不是你的错
It wasn't your fault.

542
00:32:34,038 --> 00:32:37,240
这就是我的错
Yes, it was.

543
00:32:37,241 --> 00:32:39,793
从头到尾
This whole thing.

544
00:32:39,794 --> 00:32:42,128
全都是我的错
It's all my fault.

545
00:32:43,581 --> 00:32:46,449
不是的 Tyler
No, Tyler.

546
00:32:46,450 --> 00:32:48,885
我本应该可以救她的
I should have saved her.

547
00:32:58,979 --> 00:33:00,180
别把Elena扯进来
Leave her out of this.

548
00:33:00,181 --> 00:33:01,815
这是咱们俩之间的事儿
This is between me and you.

549
00:33:01,816 --> 00:33:04,768
你还继续护着她
You're still protecting her?

550
00:33:04,769 --> 00:33:07,984
你非要我把你鲜血淋漓的玻璃心从你的胸腔里取出来
Must I rip your bleeding heart from your chest

551
00:33:07,985 --> 00:33:11,324
让你看清所有的伤痕都是Elena Gilbert造成的吗
and show you the scar tissue that is Elena Gilbert?

552
00:33:14,301 --> 00:33:15,467
我这儿有个方案
There's a solution

553
00:33:15,468 --> 00:33:17,269
能解决你所有的问题
to all your problems, you know.

554
00:33:17,270 --> 00:33:18,872
我可以控制他
I could compel him...

555
00:33:19,357 --> 00:33:24,002
抹去他记忆里每一个有关于你的片段
Erase every memory he has of you.

556
00:33:24,003 --> 00:33:25,754
每个心心相印的时刻 每个深情款款的亲吻
Every day you've spent together,

557
00:33:25,755 --> 00:33:31,051
每个欲盖弥彰的谎言 每个痛彻心扉的伤口
every kiss, every lie, every ounce of pain.

558
00:33:31,052 --> 00:33:36,038
我可以让他彻底抛开他对你一点一滴的绵绵爱意
I can take away every bit of love he has for you,

559
00:33:36,039 --> 00:33:37,990
我能让你们相忘于江湖
give you both a clean slate.

560
00:33:37,991 --> 00:33:40,442
就等你一句话 我就能让你
Just say the word, and I'll make you

561
00:33:40,443 --> 00:33:44,046
和所有你给他造成的悲情记忆随风而逝
and all that misery you've caused him disappear.

562
00:33:44,047 --> 00:33:45,046
那就来吧
Do it.

563
00:33:47,751 --> 00:33:50,219
你说什么
Excuse me?

564
00:33:50,220 --> 00:33:52,405
抹去一切吧  一切的回忆
Erase it all. Every memory.

565
00:33:52,406 --> 00:33:53,806
Stefan 别
Stefan, no.

566
00:33:53,807 --> 00:33:56,091
来吧
I said do it.

567
00:34:04,235 --> 00:34:08,971
我才不要  那太便宜你了
No. That would be far too easy.

568
00:34:08,972 --> 00:34:11,807
我才不要让你像被Klaus强迫忘记我一样
I refuse to make you forget her

569
00:34:11,808 --> 00:34:14,693
轻而易举地忘了她
the way Klaus made you forget me.

570
00:34:17,247 --> 00:34:19,949
但是至少你也明白他的真实想法了
But at least you know how he really feels.

571
00:34:24,371 --> 00:34:29,592
考虑到我的报复会给你带来的永恒的痛苦 Stefan
Consider your eternity of pain my revenge, Stefan.

572
00:34:29,593 --> 00:34:31,010
对我来说留你已经没意义了
I've used you for all you're worth.

573
00:34:31,011 --> 00:34:34,129
现在你可以走了
So now you're free to go.

574
00:34:50,397 --> 00:34:52,731
Stefan 等等
Stefan, wait.

575
00:35:20,686 --> 00:35:21,801
百密一疏啊
Turns out I miscalculated.

576
00:35:21,802 --> 00:35:24,002
怎么就忘了Kol会是个大麻烦
Kol's gonna be a problem.

577
00:35:24,973 --> 00:35:27,891
我差点儿失手杀了人
I almost killed someone,

578
00:35:27,892 --> 00:35:29,859
你就轻描淡写地说这是你的百密一疏
and that's what you miscalculated?

579
00:35:29,859 --> 00:35:31,127
April今天差点儿就死了
April could've died today.

580
00:35:31,128 --> 00:35:33,662
那只是因为你不知道自己的能力到什么程度
That's only because you didn't know the extent of your abilities.

581
00:35:33,663 --> 00:35:35,131
我父亲刚刚上任镇长一职
My father just became mayor.

582
00:35:35,132 --> 00:35:37,788
我不能在外面游荡使什么黑魔法
I can't be out doing black magic.

583
00:35:37,789 --> 00:35:40,070
亡灵魔法可不是黑魔法
That's not what expression is.

584
00:35:42,740 --> 00:35:44,174
那它是什么
Then what is it?

585
00:35:44,175 --> 00:35:45,475
它是一种摆脱了
It's a way of doing magic

586
00:35:45,476 --> 00:35:46,910
自然和灵魂控制的魔法
that isn't monitored by nature or the spirits.

587
00:35:46,911 --> 00:35:48,480
它不好但也不坏
It isn't good nor bad.

588
00:35:49,080 --> 00:35:52,248
而且它没有什么限制
But it also has no limits,

589
00:35:52,249 --> 00:35:54,317
怎么来用取决于你
so how you use it is up to you.

590
00:35:54,318 --> 00:35:57,704
这才是我来这儿的目的
That's what I'm here for...

591
00:35:57,705 --> 00:36:00,540
我是为了帮你
To help you.

592
00:36:00,541 --> 00:36:04,662
Bonnie 你听我说  你是所有事情的关键点
Bonnie, listen to me. You are the key to everything.

593
00:36:06,881 --> 00:36:10,100
我是不会让任何不好的事情发生在你身上的
I'm not going to let anything bad happen to you.

594
00:36:27,568 --> 00:36:29,686
希望你今天过的比我好啊
Hope your day is going better than mine.

595
00:36:29,687 --> 00:36:32,372
不过老实说 如果真的比我好 我会开心的
Got to say, I'm liking the odds.

596
00:36:32,373 --> 00:36:34,692
Stefan知道咱俩的事儿了
Stefan knows about us.

597
00:36:38,462 --> 00:36:39,906
那他什么反应
How'd he take it?

598
00:36:40,415 --> 00:36:42,158
你觉得他什么反应
How do you think?

599
00:36:43,701 --> 00:36:45,635
我认为 这将会是我这周以来第一次
I'm thinking, for the first time all week,

600
00:36:45,636 --> 00:36:49,723
心甘情愿地被踢出家门
I'm happy to be at camp nowhere.

601
00:36:49,724 --> 00:36:50,834
Jeremy怎么样了
How's Jeremy?

602
00:36:50,835 --> 00:36:54,177
那取决于你对我有多信任啦
That depends on how much you trust me.

603
00:36:54,178 --> 00:36:56,879
你知道我完全信任你的
You know that I trust you.

604
00:36:56,880 --> 00:37:01,251
那我就告诉你 他一定会顺利渡过这一关的
Then I think he's gonna get through this thing just fine.

605
00:37:01,252 --> 00:37:03,603
谢谢你照看他
Thanks for looking out for him.

606
00:37:03,604 --> 00:37:05,388
我答应他们 要是表现良好
Yeah, well, I told them if they were good,

607
00:37:05,389 --> 00:37:10,160
可是有冰激凌奖励的嘛 所以我该走了
I'd buy them both ice cream, so I got to go.

608
00:37:10,161 --> 00:37:11,855
等等
Not yet.

609
00:37:13,347 --> 00:37:16,282
今天出了点事
Something happened today.

610
00:37:16,283 --> 00:37:21,371
我弄清了对你 对我们之间的感觉 
I realized something about you, about us.

611
00:37:21,372 --> 00:37:23,790
你当然可以说这是由于认祖归宗
And you can say that it's the sire bond,

612
00:37:23,791 --> 00:37:26,376
当然  也许真的是这样
and you know what? Maybe... maybe it is,

613
00:37:26,377 --> 00:37:30,580
但是 我要告诉你 
but I'm telling you it's the most real thing 

614
00:37:30,981 --> 00:37:33,141
这是我此生最真实的感受
that I ever felt in my entire life

615
00:37:36,470 --> 00:37:39,215
我爱你 Damon
I love you, Damon.

616
00:37:45,896 --> 00:37:49,365
我爱你
I love you.

617
00:37:49,366 --> 00:37:52,452
听着
Look.

618
00:37:52,453 --> 00:37:54,856
我将会为你找到解药
I'm going to get this cure for you.

619
00:37:58,108 --> 00:38:01,494
我也将不得不做些你不喜欢的事
And I'm gonna have to do things you don't like.

620
00:38:01,495 --> 00:38:02,662
Damon
Damon...

621
00:38:02,663 --> 00:38:04,824
但你现在听着
But listen carefully.

622
00:38:06,167 --> 00:38:11,387
我要你立刻去开车
Get in your car right now.

623
00:38:11,388 --> 00:38:13,124
到我身边来
Come to me.

624
00:38:15,142 --> 00:38:17,060
我马上就来
I'll be there soon.

625
00:38:32,409 --> 00:38:33,770
欢迎 虽然你没敲门
You let yourself in.

626
00:38:33,771 --> 00:38:35,328
是你打电话找我
You called me.

627
00:38:35,329 --> 00:38:38,648
我是不是该检查你有没有窝藏刀具呢
Should I be checking for hidden daggers?

628
00:38:38,649 --> 00:38:40,010
你还想找解药吗
Do you still want to find the cure?

629
00:38:40,401 --> 00:38:42,035
日思夜想
More than anything.

630
00:38:42,036 --> 00:38:43,803
我想把解药灌进Niklaus的喉咙
I want to ram it down Niklaus' throat

631
00:38:43,804 --> 00:38:47,590
看着他的双眼 直到他变回人类
and look into his eyes as he realizes he's mortal again.

632
00:38:47,991 --> 00:38:50,260
但Shane死了 而你对我没用了
But Shane's dead and you are useless,

633
00:38:50,261 --> 00:38:52,962
所以我又回到了起点
so I'm right back where I started.

634
00:38:52,963 --> 00:38:55,500
Shane没死
Shane's not dead.

635
00:38:55,501 --> 00:38:58,184
但我看到Kol刺穿了他
But I watched Kol impale him.

636
00:38:58,185 --> 00:39:00,687
你不该单独留下他
Well, you probably shouldn't have left him alone.

637
00:39:00,688 --> 00:39:02,522
Bonnie施了一点小法术
Bonnie did a little spell.

638
00:39:02,523 --> 00:39:04,357
所以他毫发无伤
He's perfectly fine.

639
00:39:07,511 --> 00:39:09,612
你没必要告诉我这个
You didn't have to tell me that.

640
00:39:09,613 --> 00:39:12,315
到底为什么要叫我来
Why am I really here?

641
00:39:12,316 --> 00:39:14,167
你是对的
You were right.

642
00:39:14,168 --> 00:39:15,785
我会永远活着
I'm gonna be here for an eternity,

643
00:39:15,786 --> 00:39:18,037
如果我不知道Elena对Damon的真意
and I will go insane if I don't know

644
00:39:18,038 --> 00:39:20,733
那我会疯掉
how Elena truly feels about my brother.

645
00:39:23,794 --> 00:39:26,212
如果你真想要解药
If you really want the cure,

646
00:39:26,213 --> 00:39:27,630
你得知道Shane有所计划
you should know that Shane has an agenda,

647
00:39:27,631 --> 00:39:29,699
黑暗的计划
and it's a dark one.

648
00:39:29,700 --> 00:39:32,585
他说他会组织一群人 让他们死掉 完成牺牲
He said he organized dozens of people to die in sacrifice.

649
00:39:32,586 --> 00:39:34,889
他承认那次炸死了十二个委员会成员
He admitted to the council explosion 

650
00:39:34,889 --> 00:39:36,059
的爆炸是他干的
where 12 people died,

651
00:39:36,059 --> 00:39:37,206
这也就不难说明
and I'm guessing it's not a coincidence

652
00:39:37,207 --> 00:39:40,844
为什么十二个混血死在我哥手里
that 12 hybrids died at the hand of my brother.

653
00:39:40,845 --> 00:39:43,897
十二
12...

654
00:39:43,898 --> 00:39:45,815
和通过大量死亡使用黑暗能量
Channeling the energy from a mass death is used

655
00:39:45,816 --> 00:39:48,985
的魔法操作相吻合
in witchcraft to perform dark spells.

656
00:39:48,986 --> 00:39:51,487
这种魔法叫做亡灵魔法
It's called expression.

657
00:39:51,488 --> 00:39:54,100
Shane向你供认不讳?
Shane admitted all this to you?

658
00:39:54,101 --> 00:39:55,859
还自鸣得意呢
Proudly.

659
00:39:55,860 --> 00:39:57,460
那也许咱们该想想看 怎么搞定他
Well, then I guess we'll have to figure out how to manage him

660
00:39:57,461 --> 00:39:59,605
同时自己去找解药
while we find the cure for ourselves.

661
00:40:01,455 --> 00:40:03,355
咱们
"We"?

662
00:40:03,356 --> 00:40:05,194
我才不和你一起 Stefan
There's no "We," Stefan.

663
00:40:05,195 --> 00:40:08,911
听着 我恨我哥 你也一样
Listen, I hate my brother, and you hate yours.

664
00:40:08,912 --> 00:40:11,497
但Damon手里有Jeremy Klaus有剑
But Damon's got Jeremy, and Klaus has the sword,

665
00:40:11,498 --> 00:40:12,915
Shane有Bonnie帮忙
and Shane has Bonnie.

666
00:40:12,916 --> 00:40:14,954
你和我才叫孤立无援
You and I are the only ones left with nothing.

667
00:40:14,955 --> 00:40:16,873
你自己也说过 不是吗
You said it yourself, right?

668
00:40:16,874 --> 00:40:18,387
谁最先找到解药
Whoever finds the cure first

669
00:40:18,388 --> 00:40:20,923
谁就决定怎么使用
gets to decide what to do with it.

670
00:40:20,924 --> 00:40:25,394
你认为呢  想和我合作吗
What do you say? You want to be partners?

671
00:40:27,047 --> 00:40:30,216
我爸爸没有杀掉十一个人的动机
My father had no reason to kill 11 people.

672
00:40:30,217 --> 00:40:32,768
也没有自杀的动机
He had no reason to kill himself.

673
00:40:32,769 --> 00:40:34,820
他爱我
He loved me.

674
00:40:34,821 --> 00:40:38,908
也爱神秘瀑布镇
He loved Mystic Falls.

675
00:40:38,909 --> 00:40:41,827
他被洗脑了 所以才会去放火
He was brainwashed into sparking that fire.

676
00:40:41,828 --> 00:40:44,163
Shane教授设计了他
Professor Shane organized his death

677
00:40:44,164 --> 00:40:46,069
和其他十一个人的死亡
and the 11 others who died with him.

678
00:40:49,655 --> 00:40:53,456
是时候向整个小镇揭露真相了
It's time this entire town started telling the truth.

679
00:41:13,199 --> 00:41:14,332
我刚开始担心
I was beginning to worry

680
00:41:14,333 --> 00:41:16,140
你们该不会找不到这里了
you boys wouldn't find the place.

681
00:41:16,141 --> 00:41:18,753
见鬼
What the hell...?

682
00:41:18,754 --> 00:41:20,789
这些人都是你杀的吗
Did you kill all these people?

683
00:41:20,790 --> 00:41:23,041
不完全是
Not exactly.

684
00:41:23,042 --> 00:41:26,234
他们正在转化中
They're in transition.

685
00:41:26,235 --> 00:41:28,778
而杀掉他们是你的任务
Killing them is your job.

686
00:41:32,435 --> 00:41:33,718
你说过你会让Klaus
You said you were going to convince Klaus

687
00:41:33,719 --> 00:41:35,326
改用其它方式的
to do this another way.

688
00:41:39,108 --> 00:41:40,608
我考虑过
I thought about it.

689
00:41:40,609 --> 00:41:45,169
但我还是觉得他的主意更好
And then I realized his idea was better.

