Grace!
Homework?
Nope.
Campaign?
- I already did my homework, Mom.
- I know.
How's Dad doing?
He's good.
I don't see much of him, though.
It's mostly...
What?
- Nothing.
GRACE: Morning, Mom.
- I have to call Eli.
- Hi.
I don't need breakfast.
Too bad. You're getting it.
Sit down.
What's he doing?
I don't know.
I've given up on parenting.
- How'd you sleep?
- Well.
You look good.
- I look...?
- Yeah.
Your hair--
it's-it's cool.
ZACH:
Uh, Eli Gold, please.
No, no, tell him
it's important.
For those of you
who don't know Jordan,
he was chief of staff
to Barbara Boxer
and has worked
on three California
senatorial campaigns.
JORDAN: Hello,
print journalists.
How does it feel
to perpetuate a dying medium?
WOMAN: Does this mean the candidate
has lost faith in you, Eli?
No. It means we're expanding.
JORDAN:
Let me, uh, backstop that.
There's been absolutely
no loss of confidence in Eli.
MAN: But Maddie Hayward
is gaining on you in the polls.
That's just a temporary
novelty bounce.
Yeah, Zach, is
this important?
I think so. I was checking out
the Maddie Hayward Web site,
and they accidentally left a link open
to internal political documents.
Okay...
It's an easy thing to do,
but I got
a screen grab before they closed it.
(Beeping)
Hold on.
That's our call waiting.
Oh, sure. Take your time.
That's why I'm here.
Hello? No.
Okay, hold on.
Uh, Mom, do you know an Elsbeth?
Tascioni? Is that
her on the phone?
Yeah, she wants to talk to you,
but I have Eli
- on the other line.
- Zach, give me the phone.
Sorry, Eli. I have to call you
back on my cell phone.
Elsbeth, hi.
Are you all right?
Uh, yes.
I just need your help on a case.
Okay. What's the case?
It's a contract
enforcement arbitration
for my client, Anna.
It should only take a few hours.
We've got it covered, Zach.
Don't worry.
No, Maddie Hayward is going
after race-- racial bias.
There is no racial bias.
Don't worry.
It says right here that they
have two ASAs
working under Dad
who will say that he's biased
against them
because they're black.
It's a bluff.
They want us to chase our tails.
I don't think so, Eli.
When did you start talking
to me like I was a peer?
Sorry, Mr. Gold.
Okay, send me your screen grab,
and I'll look into it.
Okay, I'm
sending it now.
Yeah. Okay.
No, I'm going to come right in.
I'll see you there.
Nice having breakfast
with you, too.
(Laughing)
That joke was written
for me by my staff,
so they appreciate your laughter.
(Laughter)
But, uh, this
is no joke.
I love business.
I am not the type of feminist
that hates to make a dollar.
I am a feminist
that wants you to make money.
With women.
(Laughter)
And with
African-Americans.
And Latinos and
all minorities.
I think racial bias
is an impediment to business.
(Quietly): Where the
hell did that come from?
(Applause)
We need to talk about debates.
Okay. We're talking.
- Four debates?
- Better talk to Eli.
Eli says one.
Well, Eli speaks for me.
Nice to see you.
Yes. Say hello to Alicia.
I will.
ELI:
What'd she say?
(Sighs)
The debates.
She wants four.
(Groans)
She may be coming
after you about race.
Preferential hiring
and promotion
in the State's
Attorney's Office?
Uh, let it go.
Race is a scab--
you don't pick at it.
We think she has a couple
of ASAs who are...
- gonna go public.
- Public about what?
- And who's "we"?
- Zach.
He found an open link
on Maddie's Web site
- to some confidential memos.
- Who's Zach?
- Your son.
- Yeah.
So talk to the ASAs.
- See if anyone's disgruntled.
- Just let it go.
Let me think
about it.
Hi. Elsbeth Tascioni.
Elsbeth?
Alicia! In here. Hi!
(Quietly):
Oh, boy.
ELSBETH:
I was trying to question
Simon Fassel,
the defendant
in this arbitration.
He was giving a Q and A
after a speech,
and he had me arrested.
I've never been
arrested in my life.
And then I turned around.
This is nice.
What is this?
Tahari, I think.
So you want me to cover
for a case for you.
- Is that it?
- Yes, yes.
This defendant, Fassel,
is the CEO of Erobos,
the running shoe company.
Do you know it?
Well, they reneged on
an endorsement contract
for $5 million
with my client,
and the contract enforcement
arbitration is in two hours,
and I won't be out in time.
And what time
is your bond hearing today?
Not until 2:00, so if you
could just cover for me,
that would be great.
Hi, Judy.
Meet Alicia.
Hi.
WILL:
This is in Skokie?
ALICIA:
Yes, on a Friday.
They don't do bond hearings
on the weekend.
Get her a transport to downtown
in the next 20 minutes
or she won't get a hearing
until Monday.
So, I have to ask a favor, Will.
Can you handle
a contract arbitration
in an hour?
No, I've got a deposition.
Can someone else there
handle it?
It's Elsbeth Tascioni.
It's Elsbeth?
That's the lawyer you're with?
Yes.
Miss Buday?
Hello.
I know you were expecting your
lawyer, Elsbeth Tascioni.
I'm her friend,
Will Gardner.
She asked me to take
the arbitration today.
What happened?
She was arrested
for harassing Simon
Fassel, the CEO.
Oh, my gosh.
So she's not coming?
Just for today.
I'll ask for a continuance,
but don't worry.
Your endorsement
contract is ironclad.
This is just a formality.
Now, you won two silver medals.
They can't argue
nonperformance.
If I can't get
the continuance,
I'll handle today's evidence
and Elsbeth will take over
on Monday, okay?
You got her arrested?
Don't answer that, Simon.
I'll meet you inside.
Is this your new lawyer?
Temporarily.
I'm Will Gardner.
Morgan Croft.
Sorry to lose Elsbeth
as an opponent.
She was very entertaining.
Can you beat them?
Yes.
The Erobos team shot that
commercial last December.
- Is that correct, Anna?
- Yes.
- Were you ever paid for it?
- No.
It was also never shown.
Payment was not dependent
- on distribution, was it, Anna?
- No.
Sir, very simply,
Erobos owes my client
$5 million,
and we understand
they've overextended themselves
with endorsement contracts,
but there's no reason
my client...
Actually, sir, the company
has always reserved the right
to void
- any endorsement contract.
- Yes, with cause.
- Erobos has shown no such cause.
- That's true, sir.
We haven't-- until now.
The contract
may be voided
if the athlete is banned
from a race due to doping.
- What? - Ann Buday has been banned
from Monday's world team trials.
- I have not.
- I have here an AADL release
of their findings last night.
Anna has been accused
of using dexitetrasolone
and has been banned
from Monday's...
I have never doped.
My parents would kill me
before they'd let me dope.
The AADL disagrees,
and if Anna misses
her race on Monday
due to this ban,
her contract is voided.
You need to get me Elsbeth.
This was all a setup.
- No.
- Yes.
I can't get a bond hearing
until Monday,
and Anna has to appeal
the AADL decision
this weekend in order
to run on Monday.
They knew this was gonna happen.
Well, Will is gonna take
- the appeal...
- I like Will.
I-I do, too.
How is he?
Good. He's good.
I was sad when he was suspended.
I was, too.
He's gonna take the appeal
to the, um...
CAS--
Court of Arbitration for Sports.
Tell Will that the CAS
doesn't run
like an American court, okay?
It has a whole set of rules
based on Swiss law.
Okay, and I'm gonna work on
getting you transported downtown
for a weekend
bond hearing.
Good, and I'll do what?
You're gonna sit tight.
We're on it.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
You know what
the lesson is here?
Don't get arrested
in the suburbs.
Not on a Thursday night.
Unfortunately, we need
a little relief now, Your Honor.
I can't help you on the arrest.
Oh, no, it's not that.
We just need to get
my client transferred
so we can get a bail hearing
here on the weekend.
Otherwise she's stuck
in the suburbs till Monday.
Skokie won't transfer her?
She missed the last transport.
Please, Your Honor?
How's Peter doing?
Good. Well.
I bet you that bitch
is nipping at his heels, huh?
Yes.
Hey, John.
It's Tommy, upriver.
How you doing?
Listen, you've got an arrestee
there by the name of...
Elsbeth Tascioni.
...Elsbeth Tascioni?
Yeah, listen, uh,
get another transport
to drag her ass up here, okay?
Yeah, it's nothing big.
(Chuckles)
What?
No, no, no, no, okay.
You do what you got to do.
All right.
Thank you. Bye.
Is your client erratic?
My... Why?
He says this Elsbeth has, uh,
been demonstrating
some erratic behavior,
and they have to do
a psych evaluation
before they can
transport her.
Liability.
Well, I can trump
a lot of things,
but I can't trump
insurance issues,
so you tell your client
to pass her psych eval
and I'll get her up here.
We think we can get
Elsbeth out in a few hours,
but I'll have to
take this for now.
They're going to do
the hearing here?
It's the only place
the arbitrators could find
on such short notice.
It's a three-judge panel
like any other appeals hearing.
We'll be fine.
Le Tribunal Aribtral du Sport
est en session.
Je m'appelle
Antoine Villapique.
Je serai le président
du comité.
Il y aura trois membres
du comité,
à moins qu'il n'y
a pas d'objection.
Monsieur Plunkett?
Je n'ai aucune
objection.
Et bienvenue à nouveau
aux Etats-Unis,
monsieur le président.
VILLAPIQUE:
Merci.
Ca me fait plaisir
de te revoir.
What the hell? It's in French?
I don't know.
This is my first.
A ma droite,
Alberto Ciccone d'Italie.
Et à ma gauche,
Karl Heinrich
de l'Allemagne...
- Excuse me, Your Honor.
- Yes?
I apologize for interrupting.
I don't speak French.
You... don't?
No, I'm sorry. This is...
all new to me.
Je n'ai aucun problème conduite
de ces procédures en anglais.
- Monsieur Plunkett?
- Bien sûr.
Une autre victime de notre
système éducatif américain.
(Laughter)
VILLAPIQUE: Mr. Plunkett from
the American Anti-Doping League
has agreed to let us conduct
this panel entirely in English
for your benefit, Mr....
Gardner, Will Gardner,
from good old U.S. of A.
Good to know.
(Speaks French)
Good, so we're set to begin.
Please proceed, Mr. Gardner.
- Excuse me?
- Please proceed.
With?
Your defense.
What is the charge?
There is no charge.
Miss Anna Buday has been banned
from Monday's race
due to her use of boosters,
dexitetrasolone.
If you have no defense,
there is no reason
for a hearing.
Yes, but Anna has passed
every drug test,
including the one last week
for Monday's race, Your Honor.
Technically, she did
pass her drug test,
monsieur le président,
but afterward,
the tester found ghosting.
Her B-sample had the
same marker ratios
as the Notorious Six.
Notorious six?
Six runners banned from Monday's
race for using boosters,
designer drugs.
In fact, the tester found
a surge of ICSH,
interstitial cell stimulator,
the fingerprint
for booster use.
(Panel conversing in French)
Uh, I-I need...
I'm sorry. Excuse me, all right?
Objection.
There's no objection here,
Mr. Gardner.
This is not Law & Order.
(Laughter)
Yeah. Thank you.
How do I express my displeasure
with something
that has transpired,
- monsieur le...
- You may speak it to me.
Well, given
that we've established
I flunked out of French, uh,
it seems unfair to conduct
in a colloquy in a language
unknown to the defendant.
- Appellant.
- Merci, monsieur.
VILLAPIQUE: Your point is
well-taken, Mr. Gardner.
And Mr. Plunkett
referred to a witness
who saw a courier carry drugs
to Anna Buday at the Olympics.
Here is the affidavit.
Well, then we call
this witness to the stand--
- Chenise Jayes.
- There is no stand, Mr. Gardner.
Well, to the chair
in the middle of the room.
(Panel conversing in French)
Excuse me, Your Honors...
Uh, I mean, uh, uh,
messieurs, uh, le présidents...
We are debating whether
to grant you your request
- to question your witness.
- Grant my request?
No.
Oui.
By a two to one margin,
we grant your request.
We shall suspend this panel
until we contact the witness.
(Gavel bangs)
I'm gonna need
to get some help here.
I'll be right back.
(Sighing)
(Cell phone ringing)
Will, how'd the deposition go?
What?
Yes, how's your French?
"Elle était fort déshabillée
"Et de grands arbres indiscrets
"Aux vitres jetaient leur
"feuillée
Malinement, tout près,
tout près."
Good.
I need you at a sports hearing.
Oh, ha, ha, ha.
Thank you. I have
a massage in two hours.
Diane, I need your help.
This CAS panel-- that's the
Court of Arbitration for Sport--
they're talking in French.
- What is this again?
- It's something for a friend.
I need your help, Diane.
Will, it's the weekend.
Another time.
It's Elsbeth Tascioni.
Where?
You are one of
the most brilliant
lawyers I have ever met.
Aw. Really?
But that's not
going to help you.
You need to pass
your psych eval.
Okay. How?
They're gonna ask
you 120 questions,
and they are going to
pause for a long time
between each question to
encourage you to talk.
And I'm not
supposed to talk?
No, you are, but
just not as much
as you normally would.
- Do I talk too much?
- No. I just think
it's best to be... circumspect.
Okay.
So they'll ask you
questions like,
"Do you resent
being given advice?"
Oh, well, what advice?
Just... any advice.
Okay. But...
Of course not.
I like getting advice.
Is that bad? Does that
make me seem noncommittal?
No. That's fine.
Just don't worry
about it afterward.
- Like I just did?
- Right.
Okay. Give me another one.
Um... um...
do you like
to stay active,
and are you bored
really easily?
No.
I mean...
I like to stay active,
but I don't really get bored.
That's a tough one, because
it's a compound question.
But I guess that's the point.
Huh. (Clicks tongue)
They want my mind to chase
down the two tracks.
Yes, that's why
they ask them that way.
So, it is best just to...
let the silence rest.
Okay?
Oh. (Laughs)
Good. Exactly.
Good. Very good.
Thanks for doing this, Geneva.
For doing what?
Talking with me,
helping me.
Can I get you anything?
Water? Soda?
No. Thanks.
(Clears his throat)
So, how am I doing?
How are you doing?
Yeah, you know,
promotions, reductions,
fostering limited funds,
managing the office.
That kind of thing.
Fine.
Uh-huh. Good.
And do you find any, uh,
bias in how I'm
handling things?
Well, I know. I know.
You're in my office,
and I'm asking you whether
I'm doing a good job.
It puts you in a very
uncomfortable position, I know.
But let me just say this.
I need to self-evaluate.
There will be
no repercussions
one way or another--
none-- so...
how am I doing
on racial bias?
You're asking about racial bias
in the office?
Yes.
And you want me
to speak honestly?
- Yes, and with no repercussions.
- You're racially biased.
I am?
Well, what do you mean by that?
You have fired
five African-Americans
and promoted two Caucasians.
That's racially biased.
Well, that's strictly
coincidence.
You're right.
- Thank you.
- Oh, wait.
Wait. Geneva,
I'm sorry.
Let's start over.
Tell me.
(Laughs)
Cary Agos was not ready
to be promoted to deputy.
Matan Brody was.
I was.
Together, we had two decades
more experience,
but you promoted Cary
because you liked him.
You fired Wendy Scott-Carr.
- You demoted Dana Lodge.
- Wait a minute.
There might have
been reasons.
There are always reasons.
But you didn't listen
to their reasons for staying.
It's about
who you listen to.
That's the key.
Well, let's say
that you're right.
What should I do?
Rethink.
Review all promotions.
Return hiring
to a pure meritocracy.
And you rejected the request
to speak at the Minority Rights
Coalition last week?
It was considered
a slap in the face.
So the Minority Rights
Coalition is offended?
Yes.
Your opponent is going.
I would talk to them.
You're a good talker.
Talk to them.
WOMAN:
Chenise Jayes.
I'm an anchor on the 400-meter
U.S. relay team,
and Anna's roommate.
VILLAPIQUE: This isn't
necessary, Mr. Gardner.
We know who she is.
Of course.
Thank you, Your...
Uh, monsieur...
le président.
So, you claimed
you saw a man giving my client,
Anna Buday, drugs.
Could you describe
what you saw?
Yeah. It was the night
before we left for London,
and this Asian guy
in a Cubs cap shows up
around 2:00 in the morning.
And he was talking
all hush-hush,
and handed her
a bottle of pills,
and then Anna went
into the bathroom.
Did you see the pills?
Uh-uh, I was over on the couch.
Oh, couldn't they have been
vitamins or aspirin?
We had all that stuff
in our room.
So you didn't know this guy?
You'd never seen him before?
I didn't know him at the time,
but now I do.
- You do?
- Yeah.
It was Nelson Kimora,
one of the
Notorious Six.
(Panel conversing in French)
Excuse me.
- Yes. - We are not stumbling
our way through anything.
And we ask that you show
our defense its due respect.
My apologies, madam.
We have come here
not to be prejudged,
and we ask nothing
other than you listen
to us with an open mind.
Uh, what is the quote?
"Ceux qui sont libérés
de préjugés ordinaires
peuvent acquérir
les autres."
Prejudices have no place here.
Yes, you are right.
My personal apology.
- Ask for something.
- Like what?
I don't know.
Something.
Uh, and, uh, we ask the panel
for a brief recess
until tomorrow.
We are looking
at an arrière-pensée
- for this persecution.
PLUNKETT: I believe
the defendant has already been
allowed an extended break.
- Appellant.
VILLAPIQUE: I believe this panel
can allow the appellants time
to prepare
for their... attaque au fer.
Merci, monsieur.
WILL:
Okay, all those years
I disparaged French
as a pointless class--
I take them back.
Nice job.
Anna, who is this guy
who visited you-- Nelson Kimora?
Someone on the
team, a sprinter.
- Did he bring you these drugs?
- No.
Did he bring you anything?
But he meant something to you.
I mean, who is he?
My boyfriend...
before the Olympics.
We're not
together now.
So he was your boyfriend,
but he didn't bring you drugs?
That's correct.
Anna, if you don't
tell us the truth,
- we can't help you.
- I am telling the truth.
There were no drugs.
Nothing happened.
ALICIA:
And you don't believe her?
DIANE:
She's, uh, hiding something.
We don't know what.
Maybe just her boyfriend's
drug use.
Or maybe she's hiding
the drugs for him.
Well, I don't know,
but we can't defend her
unless she tells us.
Could you check with Elsbeth?
She knows Anna more
than we do.
I already did, but she's in
a psych evaluation right now.
Well, when she's done,
would you ask her again?
We need some help
with Anna here.
We only have one more day left.
Okay.
I will, and, Diane,
thanks for doing this.
Hey, it's just the weekend.
MAN: Do you feel
guilty about drinking
or using chemicals?
I don't feel guilty
about drinking,
which I do do...
Do do?
But I don't
use chemicals,
which, I imagine you
mean chemical stimulants,
so it would be impossible
to feel guilty about that.
(Laughing)
Why did you laugh,
Ms. Tascioni?
No reason.
Just... your pause
seemed funny.
Why?
- No reason.
- Well, there must be some reason.
No. Just the oddity
of human behavior.
What do you mean,
the oddity?
What do I mean?
The...
Yes, Ms. Tascioni?
She was pregnant.
Excuse me?
(Gasps)
ICSH is the male equivalent
of LH.
Luteinizing hormone,
a pregnancy-related hormone.
- Ms. Tascioni... - That's why the
unexplained hormonal surge.
It wasn't drug use.
She was pregnant.
- Do you mind? - But that was ten
months ago-- the Olympics.
- She doesn't have...
- I know. I know. Wait.
The pills
her boyfriend brought her.
What if it wasn't boosters?
What if it was
mifepristone?
And that's why
she doesn't want to tell us.
You have to go talk to her, tell
her she has to tell the truth.
Okay.
(Sighs)
What was the question again?
You have to tell them.
That I had an abortion?
No.
No, I can't.
Anna, you didn't dope.
You terminated
a pregnancy.
You need to tell them.
I can't.
DIANE:
Your family?
My parents, my-my sister.
WILL:
They'll understand.
It's worse
that you were doping.
No.
It's not worse.
Not to my family, not to me.
I wanted to medal.
I was pregnant,
and I wanted to medal.
Here's the problem, Anna.
We can defend you
with the truth.
If you tell the truth,
you will get
your $5 million contract,
and you will run on Monday.
If you don't,
you will lose both.
Then I'll lose both.
I can't break their hearts
in this, Will.
So what do we do?
You need to help me win this.
With a lie?
If that's what it takes.
Hi. Um, how's it going?
No, no, no, no, no, no, I...
I was just checking in.
Oh, thanks.
So, what are you doing?
Trying to get a lawyer out
of lockup. What about you?
I'm, uh, watching
Eli and Jordan
argue over whether
I should go
to the Minority Rights
Coalition today.
What did you say
you were doing?
A lawyer friend of mine
got arrested in Skokie,
and she missed the transport
to her bail hearing.
That's not good.
Why don't you have
the presiding judge
transport her downtown?
I tried that.
The lawyer failed
her psych eval.
Mmm. Liability.
You want me to make a call?
Could you?
Yeah. What's the lawyer's name?
You know her. Elsbeth Tascioni.
Ah.
What?
She was the lawyer
on my retrial.
It's gonna look
- like a political favor.
- Not a personal one.
Right. Um...
look, let me think about it.
No, no.
Peter, that is not why I called.
Why did you call?
Uh... I was just checking in.
Oh. Then why don't you...
come visit me
at the campaign bus?
We're at Morgan Park, and then
maybe we'll get a bite to eat.
If I get a break, I will.
Good. And one thing you might
try with Elsbeth--
question the arrest itself.
Make it a constitutional issue,
and that way,
the presiding judge
will have to transport her.
Good. Thanks.
All right. See you.
DIANE:
Thank you for answering
our questions, Mr. Chesterfield.
- Dr. Chesterfield.
- Ah.
C'est ma faute.
I'm sorry. I don't speak French.
Ah.
My mistake.
So, you are the chemist
who tested Anna
Buday's B-sample?
I'm lead analyst at Edgar Labs.
We test and interpret samples
for all U.S. athletes.
So that's a yes?
- Yes.
- And you are familiar with
the booster scandal, docteur?
Yes, I'm the one
who discovered it.
- And the new compound, dexitetrasolone.
- Uh-huh.
And after you discovered it,
did you test this... substance?
No.
We're still waiting on
subpoenas of private labs
- in China who manufacture it.
DIANE: I see, so...
you have never seen
this mysterious substance.
You have never held it,
never tested it.
- So how can you be positive
it even exists?  - I don't need
the actual drug to know
that it's real, ma'am.
Think of contrails
from an airplane--
they don't just appear;
Something had
to make them.
So how do you prove definitely
that Anna used
this compound
when she denies it?
Does she have contrails?
PLUNKETT:
If we are to argue
in metaphors, gentlemen,
then contrails are enough.
They were enough
with Lance Armstrong.
I'm sorry.
Is it your turn to argue?
This isn't
about arguments.
These Chicago lawyers
continue to think
that this is
an adversarial proceeding.
Oh, our mistake. I guess
we should all just agree
- Anna is guilty.
VILLAPIQUE:
- This is not an American court, Mr. Gardner.
There's no need to be
at each other's throat.
Uh, this is not Rambo.
Les règles d'LAAD
n'exigent pas
la preuve définitif.
The rules don't
require actual proof
to keep her from
running on Monday.
We have to find
another way.
Hi.
- Hi.
- What do you need?
Will and Diane are running
into a dead end at the CAS
and have asked me
to review your trial notes.
These.
- Diane? Diane's on it, too?
- Yeah.
She's so elegant.
Yeah. Um...
what does that say?
That's background
on Dr. Chesterfield.
- What happened with him?
- Contrails.
(Sighs)
Yeah.
He loves his contrails.
The problem with doping charges
is the burden of proof
is reversed-- you have
to prove you're innocent.
- What?
- Where's Alicia?
She's trying to get you
a trial downtown,
but what is it
you were about to say?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Oh, yes.
Tell Will and Diane
they have to attack
the three pillars.
- The three...
- Pillars.
It's the way
they substantiate
doping charges--
Pillar one: Analysis.
I guess we lost on that one.
- What are the other two?
- Uh, I-I don't know.
- No, I'm asking myself.
- Oh.
Co... confidentiality.
And, uh...
chain of custody.
- Chain of custody?
- Yes. Like a three-legged stool,
you knock that out,
the CAS falls over.
(Chuckles)
Okay. Thanks.
- You know what?
- What?
I hate depending
on other people.
(Chuckles)
Me, too.
Look, I'll be back.
(Door opens)
Oh, looks like your transport
downtown has arrived.
(Gasps)
Yay!
PETER:
Now, we all know
that I have made mistakes,
but I want to learn.
That's why I'm here
speaking to you,
- the Minority Rights Coalition.
MADDIE: Three debates?
You do the voters a disservice
if you give them anything less.
Oh, yes, that's what
this is all about,
doing the voters a service.
- We'll consider three.
- We will not. Two.
You give us
two town halls,
- we will consider three.
- This is not an official negotiation.
Why not, Eli?
- What's wrong with three?
- Maddie,
send your representatives
over to me...
I do things myself.
Write my own speeches,
spend my own money.
Why don't we just shake
right now on three?
No. Not right now.
(Audience clamoring)
My office...
prosecutes more
African-Americans
than any other group,
and I want to know why.
(Audience jeering)
President Obama...
promised a discussion
on race in this country.
We've never had it.
I'm not the type that likes
to point fingers, Eli, but...
you should listen
to me more.
I know what I'm doing.
ALICIA: No, court's
at 9:00 tomorrow.
I should have her out by noon.
Okay, got to go.
- Did... you have a break?
- Yeah.
- You all right?
- Yeah. It was a...
just a bad speech.
You have time for a bite?
Sure.
♪ Non, rien de rien ♪
♪ Non, je ne regrette rien... ♪
(Knocking)
ELI (Outside):
Come on, Peter.
It's not as bad as you think.
ELI:
Come on! Peter, let's talk!
I need a minute!
Just a minute?
(Whispers):
A campaign minute.
♪ Ca commence avec toi. ♪
(Grunting, clattering)
(Sighs)
Okay.
I've got to get going.
- What?
- Nothing.
So, uh...
do I have to ask
how we're doing?
No.
Okay.
So we're just...
where we are.
Do you want us
to be somewhere else?
Oh, no, no, just...
just checking.
Okay.
I'll talk to you later.
You want some water?
Sure.
Oh. Don't worry.
Just the wife.
ALICIA: That is not
true, Your Honor.
This is a constitutional matter.
No, it is a stupid matter.
Would one of you take a break
from your scrimmage
and please fill me in?
Ms. Tascioni was arrested
for harassing Mr. Fassel,
CEO of Erobos Sports
and a defendant...
He was speaking
at Braddock University
- and invited questions.
- Yes, which would've
been fine, except she followed
him out to his car.
What is the constitutional
matter here?
ALICIA: The campus
police who arrested
Ms. Tascioni did so
illegally by leaving
- their area of jurisdiction.
- That's why we're here on a Sunday?
As you can see
from this map, Your Honor,
the campus police
arrested Ms. Tascioni
beside Mr. Fassel's car
here in Parking Garage C.
Which is a part
of the university grounds.
No, it is aDJacent
to the university,
but it is owned by the Illinois
Trust & Loan Bank here.
(Whispers):
Fassel's lawyer.
Okay. Your Honor,
if we're sinking to this level
of ludicrousity...
- "Ludicrousity"?
- Braddock University
leases the garage
from Illinois Trust,
and is thus entrusted
to patrol it.
Not the second
and third floor.
How do you know that?
I don't know how I know
half the things I know.
POLITI:
Mrs. Florrick?
Yes, Your Honor.
The university does not lease
the second and
third floors.
It only leases the...
First and the fourth.
...the first
and the fourth floors.
The second and third floors
are for bank customer
parking only.
Ms. Tascioni was arrested on...
The third floor stairwell.
...in the third floor stairwell.
Okay, here's how
we're doing things.
The four of you get all of your
whispering out of the way.
Go and discuss everything
you want to discuss
outside the court.
Come back in here
in 20 minutes
with your best arguments.
And Ms. Pine?
I have to say this.
I'm inclined to
toss this arrest,
'cause I, too,
think it's stupid.
So, Anna Buday gave
a urine sample
on the 20th of July 2012
at 7:00 a.m.?
Yes, that's what
my intake form states.
Good.
And that was the sample
that led you to conclude
that Anna had
a contrail, oui?
Well, that she had
a burst of ICSH.
Similar to the Notorious Six.
Ah. No more metaphors.
Good.
And when did
the technician
give the sample
to your designated
- shipping company?
- I don't know.
Well, hopefully
this will refresh your memory.
It is a receipt
for the shipping of the sample.
Can you see the time
and the date there?
Would you read it?
July 21, 5:18 p.m.
Rule 44G, subpart M of
the AADL code states,
"All samples shall be shipped
"via approved courier
on the same day
that they are
collected."
I am aware of the code.
"Any unexplained
delay in shipping
"will constitute a break
"in the chain
of custody,
and the test must be discarded."
Occasionally, a technician
is unable to mail the sample
on the same day, usually because
the courier is closed.
There's no violation
as long as the sample
remains in our facility.
You're right.
That is why we,
um...
Merci, mademoiselle.
That is why we
checked the log
at your testing
facility.
It was closed.
It could not have remained
in your facility.
It must have remained
with this technician.
PLUNKETT:
Objection.
This is a respect
of form over substance.
I thought there were
no objections.
PLUNKETT: There is
no scientific way
the delay in delivering
the sample
- could create a false positive.
- One moment, please.
(Speaking French)
Judge Villapique says the sample
should still be allowed.
- Why?
- The delay was a technicality.
DIANE:
The Italian judge is for us.
The German is
against us,
but not as strongly.
(Speaking French)
Villapique says this is what
comes from these Rambo tactics.
What is it with
him and Rambo?
Does anybody even
watch Rambo anymore?
(Speaking French)
DIANE: He is suggesting a 30-minute
recess to discuss this further.
We need to flip the German.
Where's Tascioni?
Here we are again.
With your argument
this time, Ms. Pine.
While the State continues
to maintain the campus police's
jurisdiction included
the parking garage-- all levels
of said garage--
their arrest
on the third floor
also qualifies
for the hot pursuit exemption.
Your Honor, please,
if I may borrow
the ASA's word
"ludicrousity..."
POLITI:
You may not.
I'm banning that word.
ALICIA:
Um...
POLITI:
Mrs. Florrick...
The hot pursuit doctrine
applies only
in emergency situations
when the officer
doesn't have time
to alert another jurisdiction.
Neither of these elements
existed here.
GENEVA:
The defendant
threatened a guest lecturer
at the university.
He fled, she followed him,
verbally assaulting the victim
while he was trying to get
to his car.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, everyone.
I think we're gonna
make history here today,
spending more time on less.
And yet, I have come
to my decision.
Afterward, you can all appeal
to the Supreme Court.
He's gonna rule against us.
POLITI:
It was a legal arrest.
The campus police--
loath as I am to give them
any kind of a win--
did step out of their
jurisdiction, but with cause.
And on that note...
Your Honor, we request
that you allow Ms. Tascioni
to be taken to bond court
currently in session
down the hall.
GENEVA:
No, Your Honor.
Respectfully, this court
lacks the authority
to overrule a Skokie
psychologist's determination
on her mental state.
Your Honor, it was in Skokie
that they determined
that my client was too risky
for transport, yet here she is.
If you rule against her,
they will take her
back to Skokie
and then drive her
back here again on Monday.
This is
bureaucratic insanity.
And yet, it's the law.
What is even more insane
is this emergency hearing,
which was just deployed
to get the defendant here
in the first place.
Your Honor, all we are asking
is that you allow my client
- to walk down the hall. - We request
that Ms. Florrick be sanctioned.
Oh, my God.
(Gavel slams)
Stop it. Seriously, stop.
Please, go find some criminals
to prosecute and defend.
Jim, please escort the
defendant down to bond court
so she can post bail.
GENEVA: Your Honor, that is not...
- Come on, Ms. Pine.
When the law is an ass,
someone has to kick it.
(Squeals, laughs)
POLITI: You can do all your crying
and hugging
down the hall.
Get her out of here.
Thank you all
for the fervor and passion
you brought to our proceedings.
It has been quite dramatic.
We have considered
your arguments, pro and con,
and we have decided against
your chain of
custody concern.
You've decided?
It's in your own rule book.
You can't just decide.
Yes, it's in our discretion
to apply the guidelines
as we see fit, depending
on the unique set of facts.
The ruling stands.
So, they're
guidelines now?
(Speaking French)
ELSBET
I'm coming!
Hi!
I'm here!
I'm here.
Hello?
I'm coming.
Sorry.
(Laughs)
I was delayed.
Uh, pardonnez-moi,
messieurs.
Puissionsnous
confèrent un instant?
We are ready, Your Honor.
We have a new lawyer
joining us.
Ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow. Okay.
Sorry.
Je tiens à appeler un
autre témoin, messieurs.
We're conducting this
in English, Elsbeth.
Ah, well, Yes.
Will! Hey.
Oh, thank you.
And Diane.
- ...what an elegant dress.
(Laughs) Thank you.
Uh, I've just been
really moved by
you guys doing this...
Excuse me.
We have a hearing.
Ah, yes.
(Giggles)
Hi. I'm Elsbeth Tascioni,
and I am late
because I was under arrest.
But I have one more witness:
Dedrick Klein.
Mr. Klein, the cyclist?
Why is he here?
To speak regarding
the CAS rule application.
I don't think
we need this witness.
Pourquoi?
Pourquoi ne pouvons-nous
entendre Klein?
(Conversation continues
in French)
Uh, uh, uh, gentlemen?
Gentlemen, please, please.
We ask for a consensus.
Par un vote à main levée.
ELSBETH:
Judge Villapique,
you're outvoted
two to one.
Thanks for coming,
Mr. Klein.
Welcome.
Two years ago, you were accused
of using banned substances
and suspended from cycling.
Did you appeal like Anna?
Yes.
My arbitration
was in Lausanne.
- And can you tell us what happened?
- Yes.
There was no evidence,
but the panel confirmed
my guilt, two to one.
Judge Villapique convinced
the Egyptian judges,
- which is wrong.
- Excuse me.
This is not relevant.
So, Judge Villapique
was on your panel?
KLEIN: Yes.
VILLAPIQUE: I think Mr. Plunkett
makes a very good
observation.
The relevance
has not been established.
Uh, you were the one?
The witness is excused.
You pushed our
cyclist out?
Mr. Klein's arbitration
was confidential.
ELSBETH:
Except if the athlete
chose to waive confidentiality,
which Mr. Klein just did.
She's correct.
ELSBETH: Mr. Klein, who
convinced the Egyptian judge
to vote against you?
Judge Villapique.
And when you were
stripped of your title,
who was the runner-up?
Xavier Lanier.
Xavier Lanier, who is French?
KLEIN: Yes.
- This has nothing to do with it.
I'm appalled by the insinuation.
Antoine, you should
have recused yourself.
He cheated.
He didn't deserve that medal.
(Speaking French)
(Panel arguing in French)
I just realized...
you're Rambo.
PETER:
President Obama
promised a discussion
on race in this country.
Well, now, why would I
want to hear that?
Because it went viral.
Because people
are calling you brave,
standing up
to special interests.
Let's wait till
the polls
come out tomorrow.
Yeah, let's wait.
The polls will prove
what the editorials are saying.
This is your
Sister Souljah moment.
ELI: You spoke truth
to minority interests,
so when those two ASAs
go public,
they'll be seen as sour grapes.
You inoculated yourself.
Yeah, that's some win.
Winning by pissing
off minorities.
Here's a thing that some people
just never learn.
We are not teaching
a fifth-grade ethics class.
We're here to win.
Win pretty, win ugly--
it's still winning.
(Door opens and closes)
Go easier on him, Eli.
Why?
Because we need him.
Do you want to get
into this now?
I want to know why we need him.
Are you being investigated?
Then you know why.
ELSBETH:
To my friends.
Thank you for getting me
out of the suburbs.
WILL:
No need to thank us.
Especially once
you see the bill.
(Diane laughs)
Eli.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Okay.
What are you doing?
You know I'm being
investigated?
Yes.
And you know I'm being
edged out of the campaign?
No, I didn't know that.
And you guys can't represent me
because you're being
investigated.
Yes, I had heard that.
I need a lawyer to represent me.
Ms. Tascioni?
Got a minute?
Sure.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com