♪
CARY: And does this abandoned pool
belong to one of your
foreclosed properties?
MAN: It belongs to one of the properties
where the householder
could not repay his loan.
And therefore, we exercised our prerogative
as the bank holding the lease to foreclose.
And this pool at 233 Graham Court...
WOMAN: Can I interrupt here?
It would save us all a lot
of time to just stipulate
that the five swimming pools are part
of the foreclosure package exercised
by the Atlantic Commerce Bank.
Good. If you stipulate to
that, it will save us time.
I'll be right back.
You okay, Kaley?
Yeah. Thank you, Mr. Gardner.
How's it going?
Pulling teeth.
What's that?
Notice of mediation.
For?
Both of us. Wednesday.
Why?
The bankruptcy.
We have another five weeks.
- I know.
- We need 60 million by February.
And yet, one of our creditors
wants a mediation on our progress.
- Which one?
- I don't know.
Check with Clarke.
If we're being called on
the carpet, he is, too.
Hmm. Wouldn't hurt to
go in with the 15 million
from Atlantic Commerce.
We went down to 13.
It would be nice to keep
that settlement above ten.
I'm doing my best.
Counsel, please tell your client
to stop evading and answer.
WOMAN: Yes, after you rephrase.
Very simply, sir, you
foreclosed on these...
- The homeowners neglected to pay.
- You left these homes
abandoned, you left these pools...
- We did nothing. These pools?
- No, sir.
After you kicked the homeowners out,
you did nothing with the swimming pools.
You let the water stagnate.
- The water was stagnant already.
- And that water
drew mosquitoes. These
mosquitoes, to be exact.
And those mosquitoes carried
West Nile virus to my client,
- Kaley Spence.
- WOMAN: Oh, come on.
Palsgraf v. Long Island Railroad.
There is no way that
Mr. Millam and his bank
could know of this proximate cause.
WILL: Good, then let your
client testify to that.
Because what I have here
is a warning from the CDC
mentioning your pools as the culprit.
- We were not aware of that.
- "We"?
Are we speaking for the whole bank here?
- I was not aware of that.
- Well, were you aware
of this letter of complaint written
by the neighbors, including Mrs. Spence,
about the declining conditions
of the foreclosed homes,
including the pools?
No. I was not aware of it. You can see
- it was not addressed to me.
- Yes.
It was addressed to your bank
president, Wilkes Ingersol.
Luckily, that's who we're deposing next.
♪ I love mountains, I love rolling hills ♪
♪ I love the flowers,
I love the daffodils ♪
♪ I love the fireside
when the lights are low ♪
♪ Boom-dee-a-da, boom-dee-a-da,
boom-dee-a-da, boom... ♪
WILL: It's up to you now, Alicia.
They sent it up the line
to the bank president.
I'm supposed to depose him in ten minutes.
How's Minnesota?
Quiet.
WILL: Ask the president
if he ever saw the letter
from the homeowners.
If he lies, we got them.
They don't know we have the notes
from the bank's quarterly meeting.
Get his backtracking on record, and we win.
Okay. I'll call you back in a few hours.
♪ I love the ocean...
Wow, look who's here.
Everywhere I turn.
Alicia. What a pleasant surprise.
How's bankruptcy going?
That which doesn't kill
us makes us stronger.
Yeah, well, then you're
gonna be pretty strong.
So, where are we?
Uh, the business center.
They got a business center here?
For the record, I want
to restate our agreement.
Mr. Ingersol's a busy man,
and he can only offer you
three hours for your deposition.
After that, he has to
get back to his ranch.
For his vacation?
His working vacation.
Chopping wood? Milking cows?
It's hard work.
So, we're in agreement, Mrs.
Florrick, about three hours?
If it's a true three hours, yes.
And if you're in
agreement to have the judge
on call so that she can immediately
settle any and all objections.
Yes, of course.
Are you getting cell phone coverage here?
If I stand on my bed and
put my arms over my head.
Okay, we're ready.
So, the clock will start as soon
as he walks through that door.
As soon as he sits in that chair.
Oh, let's not quibble.
Good. Then the chair.
MAN: Wilkes Ingersol.
I'm the president of the
Atlantic Commerce Bank,
and a trustee of the Mercantile Exchange.
Well, it's nice to finally
meet you, Mr. Ingersol.
You're a hard man to find.
Really? Well...
that's not what my accountant says.
(laughter)
We've been trying to depose
you for 14 months now.
CANNING: Mrs. Florrick, if you wanted
to read that into the record,
you could have done so
before Mr. Ingersol arrived.
INGERSOL: It's all right,
Louis. My apologies, ma'am.
I don't mean to be flippant.
Thank you for arranging this
deposition near my ranch.
I hope you weren't inconvenienced.
I'm fine.
Now, sir, if we could turn
to these foreclosed homes
and their swimming pools...
- Yes. Um, could I say something first?
- Certainly, sir.
I understand there are a lot of homeowners
who are underwater.
I understand many homebuyers
were enticed into taking on
adjustable mortgages that
eventually bankrupt them.
But what I often think is that banks
are made the bad guys in these equations,
and that is unwarranted.
- Thank you, sir.
- But what I wholly condemn
are any efforts to advance political causes
through legal means.
I mean, for example,
uh, communities using eminent domain
to address bank foreclosures.
Or here, using this painful
circumstance of a young child
with West Nile virus to force us to
change our methods on foreclosures.
I think you've been
misinformed, Mr. Ingersol.
Kaley Spence is suing you for $15 million.
13 million.
She's suing you because she had a
promising career as a ballet dancer,
and now she needs full-time care.
- We don't need the photos.
- I think we do.
INGERSOL: Please leave them.
She's a lovely girl.
I have a 15-year-old daughter myself.
ALICIA: Sir,
did you see this letter,
written by the residents
of the community complaining
about the state of these foreclosed homes?
CANNING: Objection. We have no foundation
- for this letter. ALICIA:
- Mr. Canning, this is
a deposition. There's
no need for foundation.
That's not true, Mrs.
Florrick, and I won't have
Mr. Ingersol sandbagged...
Then let's call the judge.
She made you sit down for this deposition.
She will make you address my question.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Florrick.
We're gonna have to leave it there.
No. Wha... wait a minute.
INGERSOL: I just received an
emergency text I have to address.
Sir, you have barely been
here for three minutes.
I have only asked you one question.
- Two.
- No, one.
The judge was explicit in her ruling.
If we made the effort
to be near your ranch,
you must sit down with us
- for at least three hours.
- And I will.
- But, a in, this is an emergency.
- No, sir!
I'll be back this afternoon at 2:00.
Please be patient.
You will get your time.
I promise you.
Well, that is unfortunate.
FRANK: No, I think you're doing well.
We expected a bump in Maddie's polling.
She's the fresh new thing.
Yes, we expected that, too.
We're still beating her 47 to 42.5.
That's outside the margin of error.
I know. We're not worried.
And yet you're here.
It's a visit.
The Democratic Committee
has a lot invested in your boy Florrick.
We want to make sure he wins.
And you're worried he won't?
I'm worried the sun
won't rise tomorrow, Eli.
It's a visit. That's all.
Thank you.
Come again sometime.
I heard something.
Something that worried me.
I heard your offices were raided.
It's nothing, Frank.
It's not nothing.
No raid is nothing. A raid is something.
- It's not about the candidate.
- I know it's not
about the candidate. It's about you.
(closing door): I'm not
hiding anything from you.
There are forces within
the Justice Department
that do not want Peter
to win the governorship.
Now, they don't have the
facts to come after him,
so they're coming after me
as a steppingstone to Peter.
- And they have the facts to come after you?
- N... no.
I'm just saying, they know
that Peter without me would be limping.
So, they want this.
They want you coming to me suggesting...
What are you suggesting?
Not that you resign.
You're not an issue yet.
But you need a strong second
in case you do become an issue.
- I know you don't like it, Eli.
- (laughs quietly)
But you need a second.
♪
So, 2:00 p.m., huh?
Yes. I'm not sure what happened.
The judge won't be happy.
Mr. Ingersol is a very...
If I hear one more time
how busy Mr. Ingersol is,
I will strangle you.
(phone rings)
Hello?
Yeah, yeah. I understand.
No, uh, she's here. I'll tell her.
Okay, thank you. Bye.
Mr. Ingersol would like to apologize...
- Let's get the judge on the line.
- It's an emergency.
He said he just has to
delay until tomorrow morning.
He set aside three hours starting at 10:00.
He won't count today's
ten minutes against it.
He wanted me to apologize
to you personally.
He said he really enjoyed his
time with you this morning.
Let the record reflect that Mr.
Ingersol has refused to attend...
- He didn't refuse to attend.
- ... failed to appear
in a court-mandated deposition,
despite promising to attend
between the hours of
2:00 and 5:00 p.m. today.
Alicia, you might want
to look at this tonight.
The CDC has revised their report.
It seems there's another
possible cause for the outbreak
of West Nile virus besides
just our swimming pools.
WILL: A koi pond?!
ALICIA: Yes, from a house
that wasn't foreclosed.
Damn it.
The CDC report isn't saying
it's definitely from the koi pond
or from the swimming pools.
But the koi pond also had stagnant water.
The bank just got its wiggle room.
- Yup.
- Okay, Alicia,
we'll handle this on our end.
You just get the bank president on record
about the neighbors' letter.
When is he supposed to arrive?
10:00 a.m. tomorrow, but I
think I'm getting the runaround.
Yeah. They'll probably
wait until you're out get
breakfast or something,
then they'll tell the judge
the witness was available,
but they couldn't find you.
Mm. Unfortunately, you'll
have to outwait them.
Stay close to your room so
they can't say you were out.
Oh. Yeah, okay. But I was only
planning to stay for one night.
We'll get clothes and
incidentals out to you.
Mr. Hayden.
Hello. I've been trying
to get to you all day.
Yes. I've been in meetings
Do you have a minute?
No, actually, I don't.
Have you, uh, received
a notice of mediation?
No.
But you...
Mr. Hayden, is... is there
something I should know?
(elevator bell dings)
(door opens, Clarke sighs)
I requested the mediation.
You?
Why?
You need to be removed from your positions.
The firm can't be merged
with you in control.
Mr. Hayden, this is...
we've been nothing but cordial.
This is not about cordial.
I had a firm ready to merge,
to pay off your creditors,
and you sabotaged it.
- It was a bad deal. They wanted to break us up.
- Yes, they did.
That's exactly the point, Ms. Lockhart.
You have creditors, you owe them money.
They are not interested
in your self-fulfillment.
They are interested in their money.
Then let us make them their money.
Well, you'll have a chance
to argue that in mediation.
(elevator bell dings, buzzing)
If we merge the firm,
the creditors will receive
70 cents on the dollar right now.
Or they can trust that you
will bring this firm back.
Either way, I'll see you in mediation.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Oh! Oh!
- No, no, take it.
- No, no.
- I'm fine.
- You. I probably have more in my room.
Are you sure? I can split it with you.
No, that'd be messy.
Thanks. I think the next
store is 50 miles away.
- Are you here for the air show?
- No.
- There's an air show?
- Yeah, I think so.
The hotel clerk kept
talking about it. It was...
Oh. Excuse me. I have to run.
Mr. Canning! Hi. I'm
here. I'm here. What's up?
Oh, yeah, Alicia, I was... I was
just about to leave you a note.
Mr. Ingersol can come
in earlier this morning.
Right now, as a matter of fact.
Uh, we thought we'd missed you.
I'm ready. I will meet
you at the business center.
Right.
(clock ticking)
Must have been delayed.
That seems to happen a lot.
I have a friend who... who's dying.
Wants me to give the
eulogy at... at his funeral.
He just e-mailed me.
He's dying, and he sent you an e-mail?
His wife did.
I hate that people my
age are starting to die.
It's really horrible.
It is.
He was my roommate in college.
Ian Keyes.
Smartest guy I ever met.
Ever give a eulogy?
Yes.
To someone close?
Who?
My father.
I'm sorry.
How old was he when he died?
60.
That's young.
It is.
(clock ticking)
Am I upsetting you?
No. Um, why don't you call Mr. Ingersol,
and see what time he's gonna be here?
I'm not playing you, Alicia. He's coming.
I know.
Yeah. We're here.
No?
Okay, wh... when?
All right, well, just keep me in touch.
2:00 this afternoon.
Let the record reflect that Mr.
Ingersol has refused to appear
at a court-mandated deposition...
again.
DIANE: You sure you want to do this?
What's the downside?
You're a low priority.
Provoking them with a harassment suit
could make you a high priority.
I don't think I have any option.
WENDY: I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm brand-new on this case,
and there was a disagreement
about who should take this meeting.
Ms. Lockhart, Mr. Gold,
good to see you again.
Oh, come on!
This is a conflict of interest.
What's that, Mr. Gold?
You ran against my boss. You lost.
- I beat you.
- Yes, that's true.
Two years ago.
You asked for a proffer
against Mr. Florrick. That
is a conflict of interest.
No, that was my investigator,
Mr. LaGuardia. I have
since rescinded that offer.
Discounts for donations is
a serious business, Mr. Gold.
The DOJ takes it very seriously.
God. No one disappears.
They all come back, like zombies.
Eli. This is a complaint, Ms. Scott-Carr,
against the DOJ and your department.
We are charging you with harassment.
- Please read it.
- I will.
And I'll have my secretary contact you
about a time to interview.
ELI: You want to beat Peter,
do it at the ballot box.
Don't use this petty ploy.
This is not about beating Peter.
So you're angry at me now?
(laughs)
Do I look angry?
My directive here is simple:
clean up political corruption.
That's all.
You underestimate me
if you think I'm working from bias.
I'll be in touch.
And you'll read our complaint?
Oh, yes. I have it right here.
Sorry, I have to get to my next meeting.
ALICIA: Hello?
Oh, hi.
I just saw you had to run off, so, I...
Oh, my gosh.
You didn't have to do that.
I know. It was nothing.
Well, thank you.
Uh... what do I owe you?
- No, no, no, nothing.
- Well, I have to pay you something.
No, you don't. No. Next time. I'm Simone.
Oh, um, Alicia.
- There aren't many people around here.
- Yes, I know.
It's so strange that they
built this big hotel up here.
So, are you here for vacation or something?
- Oh, no. Work. You?
- Uh.
Oh, my husband's here for work.
You are probably the lawyer
that he's here to meet.
Are you Mrs. Canning?
Yes. Are you Mrs. Florrick?
- Yes.
- My husband speaks so highly of you.
- He does?
- Yes.
He does. He thinks you're fantastic.
For a while there, I
thought I should be jealous.
(laughs) I'm joking.
But we should have breakfast sometime.
You know, if we're going
to be here for a while.
Are we going to be here for a while?
I don't know. You tell me.
(laughs) (laughs)
Well, it was really nice to meet you.
So, I'll call you for breakfast?
- Good. Yeah.
- Okay.
Simone?
Yes?
I was so sorry to hear
about your husband's friend.
The one who's dying?
Who's that?
Oh, never mind. It was my mistake.
It was lovely to meet you, Simone.
You, as well, Alicia.
Good job, Kalinda. He's sure?
Yeah. Look, as far as I can tell,
the Aedus... Eedus... ? Aed... ?
Aedes albopictus.
The...
this kind of mosquito breed
doesn't transmit West Nile,
so it couldn't have come from the koi pond.
That virus is transmitted by the ae-aed...
- The other one?
- Aedes aegypti.
Aedes aegypti.
By a different type of mosquito.
Excellent. Very good.
Just get him on the record.
Ah, that'll be fun.
We'll call you back, Kalinda.
What's going on out there?
He's getting Cary in line
to testify against us.
I just want to make sure
we're on the same page.
I think we are. Yeah.
Good. Thank you, Cary.
Cary?
Yes?
What was Clarke discussing with you?
Uh, nothing. He just wanted to know
about the clients who left last week.
And what did you say?
I said nothing.
I just listened. We're just a little
worried he's trying to line
up a case against us, Cary.
And that he might use you.
Do you think that's a possibility?
He didn't say anything about that.
Can we, um, talk to you, Cary,
about possibly testifying for us?
(crows cawing)
2:30. And here we are again.
Why don't you go for a walk?
I'll get you when he comes.
(laughs)
How's your friend who's dying?
Have you heard any more from him?
No. Why?
Maybe you should call him.
Maybe he's dead.
Excuse me?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Am I being insensitive?
How's the eulogy coming? I mean,
maybe you could ask
Simone to help you on that.
You met my wife.
Yes, I did.
She's wonderful.
Yes, she's... my better half.
She's your only half.
Funny, she'd never heard
of Ian Keyes, your roommate.
Yeah, well...
I don't share everything with her.
Your lies, for example.
You don't share your lies?
No.
Those I save for you.
(laughs)
What was even the point
of lying about a dying friend?
I don't know. It was a way of connecting.
Didn't you feel we were connected?
How does a bastard like you end
up with such a wonderful wife?
Women like bastards.
Didn't you notice that?
It's like a challenge.
Beauty and the Beast.
It fits in with all the fairy
tales you grew up consuming.
(laughing): Oh, my God.
(phone ringing) Oh, there's Godot.
Hello.
All right. Really?
Let the record show that
Mr. Ingersol has refused
to attend a court-mandated
deposition for the fourth time.
He was literally
- a minute away when he had another call.
- Oh, really?
Just a minute away? Wow.
He says he can reschedule
for tomorrow at 10:00.
Okay, sure. Um, it'll just...
it'll give you some time to read this.
It's saying that the CDC is
updating their report again.
The mosquito carrying
the West Nile virus could not
have come from the koi pond.
That's the wrong kind of mosquito.
The right kind of mosquito could only
have come from the swimming pools.
So, nice try, Mr. Canning, but you lost.
And every day that this
deposition is delayed,
the judge is getting angrier, so...
(clicks tongue)
might want to rethink your strategy.
(dialing touch tones)
Yeah, it's me.
Yeah, I need you to look into something.
So, Kaley, hi.
Hi.
I just want to ask you a few questions,
and I know they might
seem odd to you, but please
bear with me. Have you
ever heard of Aedes aegypti?
No.
Well, I can understand why.
That's a very long word
for a very small mosquito.
You don't have to patronize
her. She's not eight years old.
Thank you, Mr. Agos.
This is an Aedes aegypti, Kaley.
This is the breed of mosquito
that carries the West Nile virus.
We didn't know that until
your attorneys pointed it out,
so thank you, Mr. Gardner,
Mr. Agos. What do you have?
Now here are diagrams of the
five abandoned swimming pools
that bred the mosquitoes.
WILL: Seems you've
dropped the "supposedly".
Are we in agreement, the
pools bred these mosquitoes?
- Yes, we are.
- Hallelujah.
Now, here are five diagrams of the five
backyards, and do you see here?
Here are the distances between the pools
and the perimeter fences.
30 yards, 40 yards. And so on.
Do you see?
Yes.
The thing about Aedes aegypti:
they are peridomestic mosquitoes.
That means they exhibit short flight ranges
of less than 50 feet.
That means there is no way
they could have flown beyond
their respective yards.
Are you testifying here, Martha?
All preamble.
Here's my question.
Kaley, did you climb the fence
into one of these abandoned yards?
Sorry to ask you again, Kaley,
but you must tell the truth here.
Did you climb the fence into one or more
of the yards of these abandoned houses?
(sniffles)
One.
With my friends.
Then, I'm sorry, but the plaintiff
trespassed onto our property,
and we cannot be held
liable for that trespass.
This suit is over.
My name is Serafina Norvey,
and before we get started,
I'd like to set the ground
rules for this mediation.
Granted, we're in your offices,
and outside those doors,
you may all be bosses, but
in here, I am the empress.
Now, I understand,
as the court-appointed trustee,
you'd like to have
the two principals removed
as managing partners?
CLARKE: Yes.
They blocked a merger of the firm
that I'd arranged with Burl Preston.
That merger would have met
all the financial obligations
- of the bankruptcy.
- Is that true?
A merger was never part of
the original arrangement.
Mr. Hayden overstepped his authority
when he tried to arrange that deal
before the full term of
the five-month deadline.
My job was to satisfy the
terms set down by the court.
Actually, it was against
the terms of the court,
in that it did not honor
the original timeframe.
Also, it worked to undermine our progress.
What progress?
We've managed to raise
a great deal of money
in a short amount of time.
How much?
Excuse me?
How much money?
$20 million.
Which is 40 million
short of what they need.
WILL: And we are very close
to finalizing a $13 million settlement
with Atlantic Commerce Bank.
They are not "very close."
They are in deposition.
Which is how it works, Mr. Hayden.
You negotiate in depositions.
You try to stay out of court.
Ma'am, if we had a trustee
who understood the law...
Excuse me. I know as much as anyone... !
All right, all right.
This is not marriage court.
I'm not here to make you like each other.
But, Ms. Lockhart,
Mr. Gardner, I think you're losing
sight of the big picture here.
This isn't about you.
This is about your creditors.
- Yes, Your Honor.
- "Ma'am."
I'm not a judge.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Our creditors are voting
with their pocketbook
by buying up our debt.
- They are?
- WILL: Yes.
We recently got in touch with our
creditors about this mediation,
and they informed us that they
no longer are our creditors.
A consortium of financiers
called Encinal Equity
has purchased their debt.
And people don't buy bad debt.
Yes, but by that logic,
your creditors are fleeing
your debt by selling it.
People don't sell good debt.
DIANE: Ma'am, all we ask is
for enough time to present our arguments.
This mediation has come
as quite a surprise to us.
How long will you need?
We should be prepared to present
witnesses and evidence by next week.
Tomorrow.
CARY: Let's talk about the
swimming pool at 233 Graham Court.
This one here.
This pool had several
water features, correct?
I'm not sure what you mean.
In addition to having a
deep end and a shallow end,
there was also a diving board,
a waterfall, and a grotto?
Okay.
I agree.
Was the grotto boarded up
after the bank took possession?
No.
Did you receive reports from neighbors
that the waterfall feature was
being used by skateboarders?
Where's this going, gentlemen?
Mr. Millam, would you admit
the pool was an attractive nuisance?
Objection.
That does not apply here.
Kaley climbed a fence to reach the pool.
Which makes it a textbook
case of attractive nuisance.
It's the responsibility of the homeowner...
in this case, Atlantic Commerce Bank...
to secure the swimming pool
and make sure it did not
become a danger to children.
Once again, there was a fence,
and your client is not a child.
WILL: Kaley Spence was
12 years old at the time.
A very young, sheltered 12.
So you were sheltered? Is that it, Kaley?
You want to question
our client, depose her.
Oh, you sure are well-dressed.
Thanks.
And you are in my office.
FRANK: Oh, I see you two have met.
Eli Gold, Jordan Karahalios.
Oh!
The boy wonder.
(chuckles): God, I hate that name.
The ever-quotable Rahm Emanuel.
Never gonna live that down.
We were headed out to see Peter.
I figured you two should meet first.
Because... ?
FRANK: That thing we discussed before,
about how you needed a second.
I like Peter.
He's not one of those processed sales jobs.
He's got grit.
Jordan wants to offer you guys some time.
He's had lots of offers.
Even Maddie Hayward, isn't that right?
Yeah, she's great.
A little green, maybe.
So, you think you two can work together?
I heard you like to work alone, Jordan.
I do.
But I also like to learn from my elders.
I just want to get an idea
how you might handle
certain situations, okay?
Okay.
Would you ever go into a
store and take something
without paying for it?
KALEY: No.
MARTHA: If you got lost in
an airport, what would you do?
Find a policeman and ask him to help.
Were you ever allowed to stay
home alone without a babysitter?
Sometimes.
Well, I used to.
Not now, because of what happened to me.
Thank you, Kaley.
That's all.
Your client is mature enough
to understand right and wrong.
Attractive nuisance does not apply here.
That's not for you to decide.
That's right. It's for a jury.
Which means court.
Which means we're not
negotiating a settlement.
Damn it.
Still in a holding pattern.
He's supposed to be here in an hour,
but I'm not holding my breath.
We really need Ingersol.
The case is going down the drain.
I think it's about this merger
- with Corsica Pacific.
- What do you mean?
Alicia, they're stalling because they
don't want a $13 million settlement
- to mess up this merger.
- Well, we can't wait.
Alicia, is there any way you
can get proof they're stalling?
Bad news, unfortunately.
Really? What a surprise.
Yeah, it'll have to be
pushed till this afternoon.
Something came up at the last minute.
I say, it's pushed till this afternoon.
I thought we would use this
time to depose someone else.
- What, for practice?
- Rita!
What's going on here, Alicia?
Please have a seat, Ms. Neves.
Would you state your name and
your occupation for the record?
Rita Neves.
I am a housekeeper here at the
Janesville Mountain Retreat.
What, are we playing games here?
And this morning, were you near enough
to Mr. Canning to overhear
his telephone conversation?
RITA: Yes. I was in his room cleaning
while he was talking on the phone.
Objection. That's hearsay.
Can you describe what you heard?
He say, "No, don't come now.
I call when Florrick steps out."
Objection.
That had nothing to do
with Wilkes Ingersol.
Is that statement for the record?
This conversation is
totally taken out of context.
It had nothing to do with Wilkes Ingersol.
It was to my... partners in Chicago.
Ed, you can come in now!
What now, Mrs. Florrick?
You got some farmers you want to depose?
Can you state your name and occupation?
Ed Jeffries. I work at the front desk.
And, um, can you tell me
how many calls were made
from Mr. Canning's hotel room?
Objection.
Your objection has been
preserved for the record.
Please tell me how many calls
were placed from Mr. Canning's room?
- Four.
- That is private information.
And were all those calls
placed to the same number?
Three to the Ingersol Ranch,
one to another local number.
So no calls were placed to Mr.
Canning's partners in Chicago?
Well, there were no calls to Chicago.
Thank you, Ed.
Oh.
Don't you want to stay
for my call to the judge?
Or do you want to be held
in contempt in absentia?
(dialing)
JUDGE: Given this evidence, Mr. Canning,
I rule for the plaintiff.
Present the witness or be held in contempt.
When is the earliest he can be deposed?
Tomorrow morning at 10:00.
Your Honor, Mr. Canning has been
saying that for two days now.
Mr. Ingersol is dealing
with an ongoing emergency.
Mr. Canning, have your client there
at 10:00 a.m. or be held in contempt.
Do you understand?
I do.
(line clicks)
I'll see you at 10:00.
I don't need a lawyer.
Yes, but you never know about
the future, Mr. Ellstrom.
Tobin.
I'm not in politics anymore, Ms. Lockhart.
The Department of Justice is making moves
against past and current campaign managers,
so I think that you should
review your past campaigns.
"Making moves"?
On what issue?
Discounts for donations.
Campaign managers offering
discounted legal services
in exchange for campaign contributions.
That's just Chicago politics.
And since you were a
lawyer prior to your work
as Wendy Scott-Carr's campaign strategist,
I thought there might be some issue there.
This is about Wendy Scott-Carr?
No.
It's about all your campaign work.
But Wendy Scott-Carr especially?
Okay.
I'll think about it.
Certainly. Here's my card.
Don't forget.
(cell phone ringtone playing)
Hello, Tobin.
How nice to hear from you.
TOBIN: Do you know a
lawyer named Diane Lockhart?
Yes, I do. Why?
She just approached me
about my past work with you.
She did?
Yeah, she said the Department
of Justice is investigating
discounts for donations, and
that I might be implicated.
(sighs)
She wanted you to call me.
What?
She wanted you to call me
so I would know that if I pursue them
on discounts for donations,
they'll pull you in.
No, she just wanted me to hire her.
No, Tobin, she didn't.
This was a warning shot across my bow.
So what are you gonna do?
We ran a clean campaign, Tobin, didn't we?
Well, yes, but nothing's 100%.
No, we ran a clean campaign.
Just don't talk to her again.
(knocking)
Kalinda.
And clothes.
And incidentals.
Ah.
(sighs): God, it's quiet.
Yeah.
You've had two days of this?
And two nights.
It's not that bad, actually.
(sighs)
Really?
I'd kill someone.
You know what I miss about my old life?
Before the glamour of the law?
What?
The quiet.
At home, in the afternoons,
I would drink every day at 3:00.
A glass of red wine.
Waiting for the kids to come home.
I miss the silence in the house at 3:00.
Just...
nothing going on.
I miss this.
Yeah.
(chuckles softly)
I'm sorry.
I know.
(chuckles softly)
You know, I don't think Ingersol's
gonna show up tomorrow at 10:00.
I know.
Cary thinks that they're trying to avoid
a road bump in their merger.
Do you have that other
number Canning was calling?
There were three to the ranch
and one to a local number.
Yeah.
What's your thinking?
(sighs): I don't know.
Maybe there's a real emergency.
Cary Agos. A fourth-year
associate at Lockhart/Gardner.
DIANE: And were you asked by
Mr. Hayden for your assistance
- over the last three months?
- Yes.
And for how many hours a week
were you asked to help him?
Roughly...
ten hours a week.
And this was done on your time?
CARY: As a fourth-year associate,
very few hours in a day
actually constitute my time.
But you managed?
Yes. Yes, I did manage.
DIANE: And what did Mr. Hayden ask of you?
He asked me to be his tutor.
DIANE: His tutor?
Yes.
He asked me to help him study
for the upcoming bar exam.
DIANE: And what prompted that arrangement?
Mr. Hayden had attended
law school years earlier,
but never attempted to pass the bar.
Now working at Lockhart/Gardner
had reinvigorated him.
DIANE: And did you feel you had any
choice in the matter but to help him?
No.
Thank you, Mr. Agos.
Anything, Mr. Hayden?
Uh, yes.
Uh, you stated that fourth-year associates
rarely have time of their own.
Yes.
But you found the time to help me?
I didn't feel as if I had a choice.
You held sway over the entire firm.
Isn't it true that I offered
to pay you for your assistance?
Yes, you did.
- And did you refuse my offer?
- Yes.
Did I ever state or imply
that you would be afforded
preferential treatment for your help?
- No, you did not.
- Did I ever state or imply
that you would be penalized
if you refused to help me?
No, you did not.
- Your Honor...
- "Ma'am."
Ma'am.
Lockhart/Gardner...
has no shame
in trying to besmirch my name
for their own personal gain.
It goes to their...
illogical passion for winning at all costs.
Once again, I ask that Diane
Lockhart and Will Gardner
be removed from their
managerial positions at the firm.
I'll take your words under
advisement, Mr. Hayden.
Ingersol's not dodging the depositions
because of the merger.
WILL: Why then?
He's been seeking treatment at
an experimental cancer center.
He's... since when?
A few months ago. The number Canning
dialed from here was a center
run by Vivek Assadullah,
a cancer specialist.
Ingersol's battling non-Hodgkin lymphoma.
That's not public knowledge.
No, it's not.
Thanks, Kalinda. Is Alicia there?
Sure. Alicia.
Yeah?
Use it. They don't want it
to come out before the merger.
I know. I'm on it.
(indistinct chattering)
What the hell?
Oh, no. Ms. Scott-Carr,
do you have an appointment?
No. We're here to
confiscate Eli Gold's files.
He operated his crisis management firm
out of these offices,
which makes Lockhart/Gardner
open to investigation as well.
That is bizarrely tenuous.
And yet, supported by the judge.
Thank you...
for the warning shot.
It gave me time to acquire the warrant.
This investigation is so hypocritical.
Okay, the files in here first.
(clock ticking)
Don't worry. He's coming.
He's just... a few minutes late.
(car approaching)
O ye of little faith.
(car doors shut)
ALICIA: Good afternoon, Mr. Ingersol,
- and welcome back.
- Thank you.
How are you feeling today?
Good. Why?
Just a pleasantry.
Well... thank you.
I'm good. (chuckles)
Good. Why don't we pick
up where we left off.
Did you see this letter
that was written by the
residents of the community,
complaining about the state
of the five foreclosed homes
and their swimming pools?
I, uh, did not.
You see it's addressed to you?
I do.
If I read every letter addressed to me,
I wouldn't have time to... shave or sleep.
(chuckling)
So that answers that, Alicia.
Any other questions?
Mr. Ingersol, are you aware
that it is an SEC violation
to withhold an illness
from shareholders?
Objection. Relevance.
Your objection has been noted.
Are you aware that it is an SEC violation?
Yes, but I'm not sure what this
has to do with your lawsuit.
It has to do with your
intent to delay, Mr. Ingersol.
Atlantic Commerce is a
publicly held company.
The shareholders have a
right to know if the leader
is facing a critical illness.
And according to his profile,
Dr. Vivek Assadullah is a specialist
who conducts experimental treatments
- for non-Hodgkin lymphoma.
- CANNING: Objection.
- This is beneath you, Alicia.
- No, unfortunately, it's not.
The emergency you were dealing
with, Mr. Ingersol, was...
uh, Ms. Court Reporter,
do you mind stepping
out for a moment, please?
My name is Mika.
So sorry. Mika. Of course.
(door opens) You were being
treated for non-Hodgkin lymphoma,
and you didn't want this
knowledge made public
before your merger with Corsica Pacific.
This does not have to go
on the record, Mr. Ingersol.
We have been trying for weeks now
to negotiate with Mr. Canning.
And if you approve this
settlement of $15 million,
the questioning can end right here.
(door opens)
DIANE: Uh, one second, Eli.
(quietly): Alicia?
Yes. $12 million.
$3 million to us.
Uh, good.
I'll be right there. Yeah.
As I was saying, Eli, unfortunately,
- this changes everything.
- Wendy's doing this so you can't be my lawyer.
I know. But now that we're part of this...
probe into your practices,
we are precluded from representing you.
We have a list of potential attorneys.
I've called the top three.
- All are ready for your call.
- And so it goes,
the endless cycle of
Chicago investigations.
JORDAN: Hey, guys. Do you know
when the old man is coming back?
Eli. There you are.
Let's talk about debate prep.
- Let's.- Maddie Hayward is
putting all her time into prep.
That's when she really
wants to make her mark.
And I looked at the schedule, and you...
you barely have Peter down.
WILL: We received a settlement
offer today for $12 million.
DIANE: And just today, Encinal Equity
completed their purchase
of Lockhart/Gardner debt.
They are invested in our financial health,
and we intend to honor that commitment.
Mr. Hayden,
I understand your disappointment
in losing a merger opportunity,
but I do believe this
purchase of debt suggests
the financial community
has faith in management.
Therefore, I have determined
Ms. Lockhart and Mr. Gardner not
be removed as managing partners
and that they continue to
work, with your guidance,
toward financial health.
After the deadline,
five weeks from now,
Mr. Hayden, then you might
find a merger partner.
That's my ruling.
(door shuts) Escaped the executioner.
WILL: For now.
We can never meet a five-week deadline.
I know.
We talk to the new creditor.
Get an extension?
(thunder rumbles)
SIMONE: Alicia.
I'm so sorry we didn't
get to have that breakfast.
Oh, me, too.
You heading out?
Yeah, Louis has business, so...
no rest.
Be seeing you soon.
And why's that?
Oh, you didn't hear?
I purchased the Lockhart/Gardner debt.
I'm your new creditor.
You two will be working together?
That's fantastic.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -