??????
Stone & Son Suit Warehouse
recently lost their paper provider.
They're a family-owned business.
Jim and I
used to clean up at those.
We'd go in pretending to be
family-- brothers.
We did it
at a family-owned law firm,
at a family-owned
construction company,
and a family-owned
motorcycle store.
Jim and Dwight Shrupert.
I was the dynamic Likeable winner
that was doted upon by mom.
Whoo!
And Jim was the closeted
foot fetishist pretending to belong.
The client
never knew any of that.
But I knew.
I hope you've been paying
your wig storage bills, Jimbo,
'cause it's time for another episode of
"handsome and stinky,paper brothers for hire."
Sorry, stinky.
Can't do it-- too busy.
Oh, God, this again?
You're stinky.
Okay. There's no possible way
I can get there,
so just ask Phyllis.
She can be your older sister or something.
Phyllis my sister?
More like my dead
great-great-grandmother who died of stupidity.
I have ears, Dwight.
Oh, do you really
have ears, Phyllis?
Like all human beings?
We all have ears.
See what you leave me with
here, Jim?
Hey, I'm in Philadelphia
right now.
How is that my problem?
Get in your car and drive down here.
You can make it in 30 minutes
if you drive 240 miles per hour.
Huh. How long would it take me
if I drove 300 miles an hour?
Mm. That's a good...
question.
300 times
Um... that comes
to 25 minutes.
Yes.
Oh, well, thank you, Jim.
Yes, I am better than you.
Thanks for acknowledging that.
Okay, bye-bye.
Love you.
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync:Î÷ÃÅ@FRS
The Office S09E11
Darryl, looking good!
Heading to Philly.
Interview with Jim's company.
Hey, good luck.
When you get to Philly,
will you tell Jim I miss him?
Why don't you come along
and tell him yourself?
Ha ha.
That'd be great.
Kinda like ditching school,
except instead of getting
suspended, you get...
what do you get?
Oh, my God!
Why didn't I think of this?
Andy's not here.
Oh, hey, Erin,
I'm expecting
a shipment of pens.
- Can you cover that?
- Mm-hmm. Cover that.
What does that mean, exactly?
What are we talking here?
Details.
A delivery guy
will deliver a box of pens,
and you just make sure
everything's in order.
what? Everything?
What-- how do I make sure
it's in order?
haven't been
trained for this.
Okay, see you later.
Hey, guys.
- Clark.
- Hey.
Hey, look who's back.
Dwight Junior.
Hey, so how was it?
I mean...
the sex with Jan.
A gentleman doesn't
discuss such matters.
Especially when the feelings
of a lady are involved.
Women reach their sexual peak
at whatever age Jan was last week.
I mean, it was... like making
love with a wild animal.
But not like a cougar
like you might think.
It was, uh...
like a swarm of bees.
Bees that just find
something wrong with every hotel room.
Nothing wrong
with being a gentleman.
Like my mom used to say,
"talk classy, act nasty."
What's with the wig, Meredith?
What, is it on backwards?
Nope.
You got it. You fixed it.
Uh, I have a gift from Jan.
It's an espresso maker.
We came to be quite fond
of espresso on the Amalfi Coast, so...
bon appetit.
Ooh!
16 types of espresso.
Now, that's Italian.
My friend has one of these.
Fool-proof espresso
every time.
Always with the friends, Oscar.
Can't we just enjoy
the new espresso machine?
Actually,
it's pronounced espresso.
Wait.
That's what you said.
I apologize. I just assumed
you would mispronounce it.
So...
There he is!
Ha ha!
We are all so proud of you
for the small part that you played
in landing the White Pages.
Prouder of me, but...
If you really want
to show appreciation,
Just give me
half the commission.
Gosh, you know,
I wish I could but, uh...
no.
Hey, listen,remember how everyone
used to call you Dwight Junior
and how much you loved that?
Ha ha ha.
I loved it.
How would like to pretend
to be my son in order to land a sale?
If it'll lead to me
being a salesman,
I'll pretend to be your friend.
Then, looks like
we have a deal...
son.
Hi, guys.
Hey, look who it is.
Sorry. Super-busy.
Pens coming in later.
Just grabbing a java
before all hell breaks loose.
- Try this one.
- Thank you.
I don't really have time
to think about Pete right now.
I just have a lot going on with
this whole shipment of pens.
And I have a lot of people
trusting me,
and I would feel super-guilty
if I broke anyone's trust.
About the pens.
You ready for your interview?
I was born ready!
No.
I suck at interviews.
I had Andy's job in the bag
until my interview.
Well, you shouldn't be
nervous about this.
This is a tiny start-up
with a bunch of guys
just as dorky as Jim.
Yeah, I guess.
Really, you can't be scared
of a room full of Jims.
I love the guy, but he's
basically gumby with hair.
It's kind of funny.
Father and son sales team
meeting with a father and son suit store.
You know, you're right!
We hadn't even thought of that,
had we, boy?
No, we sure hadn't, pop.
Oh!
You're a hunter, I see.
Spend your early mornings out in the blinds
like Clarky and me? Huh?
He calls me Clarky
'cause he's my dad.
Guilty.
You don't meet
many hunters these days.
My dad is
the best hunter there is.
I mean, he's like
a serial killer... of animals.
One time he snuck up
behind a sleeping deer
and just sawed its head
right off-- it was sick!
It was his birthday.
Just turned three, so...
You guys, I kinda think
I want to try them all.
Is that crazy?
No. Look,
without a taste test,
how are we supposed to know
which flavors we like to reorder?
Taste test?
I'm in.
Yolo
It's a thing.
It means you only live once.
Yeah, we're aware
of what it means, Oscar.
You just do not look cool
saying it.
- Well--
- All right, everybody.
- Who's in?
- Yep.
Angela.
Don't make us come over there.
No, I don't-- no.
All right, let's go.
Can't I just agree
without putting my hand in?
- Absolutely not.
- No way.
Oh, fine.
Okay, guys.
We all drink them all.
- Yes.
Hey, Where's my ring?
I'm sure it'll turn up.
Yes, ma'am, you wanna go
east on Franklin,
take that all the way
to Commonwealth.
You'll see us on the right side.
You can't miss us.
- Whoa.
- Yes.
And I want to reach
every demographic possible.
No, I hear what you're saying,
and we will.
The thing is, we gotta lock down
this key demographic first.
The rest will come.
I promise.
Just give me a couple weeks,
all right?
We're talking weeks here,
not months, right?
Weeks.
Always weeks.
Man, the last time
I talked months was, like...
- a million weeks ago.
- All right. Good.
Thanks, Dennis, appreciate it.
Hey!
- How are you?
- Good.
- What are you doing here?
- I just wanted to see you.
- That's so great!
- Damn.
Jim, you got a real Facebook
energy going on here, man.
You Zuckerberged
this place out.
It's pretty great, right?
I mean, we're coming along--
hey, Wade, we gotta just push up
Dennis's timeline.
- Okay.
- Actually, you know what?
Give me one second, okay?
Make yourselves at home.
But I think that all of
your concerns will be answered
when you see the brochure that
Clark's getting out of my car.
He's a good boy.
Does whatever I say.
I can't relate to that.
My son hates my guts.
Oh?
Really?
Bring him into the business,
and he resents me.
How do you like that?
Well, things
between me and Clark are good,not great.
In fact, I will say
that they're not even good.
Really, they're bad.
Like you and your son.
Here you go, pop.
I know it was just
a couple minutes, but...
- God, I missed you.
- What took you so long?
Were you loitering out there
like a Hooligan,Smoking a doobie?
I sure was.
Just like he taught me.
- Looking cool.
- You're being disrespectful!
And I love you...
for saying that.
We don't get along.
Ha ha!
I just burned him.
Because the truth is...
our relationship is...
- Ter-- terrible.
- Terrible.
Yes.
Genius.
Stupid, stupid genius!
Wow! This place is...
so great.
I had no idea-- on the phone,
you made it sound kind of dinky.
Well, I mean, I don't even
have the paycheck yet.
It is a start-up, so...
These things go down
all the time.
If this company's going down,
I wanna go down on it.
With it.
I wanna go down with it.
Are you cool to just hang out?
- Sure, no problem.
- Yeah?
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Let's do it.
The pen delivery went amazing,
and now I've got all these pens
just waiting to be unpacked.
But Pam did not tell me
to unpack the pens,
and I'm not one of those people
who's just like, "uh, sure,
I'll accept the pens
when they come in,"
and then as soon
as your back's turned,
I unpack the pens and get all this
credit and some great pen unpacker.
On the other hand...
they are just sitting here.
Pam didn't tell me
not to unpack them.
Don't wanna be a busybody, but I
don't wanna be a lazybones.
Busybody, lazybones.
Aah! My brain is ping-ponging
around in my head right now.
It's insane.
I'm sorry.
What was your question again?
Oh, yeah.
No. I've never had
an espresso before.
They're good, though.
A-bam!
My favorite
is Viennese Amaretto.
And the worst flavor
I've tried so far is Alpine Select!
Yes!
- Ah!
- One!
- Kevin! Kevin! Kevin!
- Two!
- Stop it!
- Three!
- That's enough, Kevin.
- Stop it, Kevin! That's enough.
- Four
So for your menswear catalogue,
I think we can offer you some very competitive pricing.
- I heard that before.
- Well, I understand, but--
- I bet you have.
He knows nothing About
what people have heard before, my son.
Here we go again, another
lecture from the old man.
Listen to him.
He created you.
Maybe if you listened
a little bit, you'd improve.
No wonder women despise you.
Women don't despise me.
His last girlfriend
was a transvestite.
I knew it right away.
Adam's apple
like the prow of a ship.
Thumbs like a lowland gorilla.
Ha. But this one couldn't see it
or didn't wanna see it.
All right, that's enough,
'cause I can say some things about him too.
- Yeah, like what?
- Like the time that you got drunk and-- and then...
killed those kids
on their way to prom.
That never happened.
He's always been a liar.
Ever since he was a little kid
and he got caught "saving treats"
from the kitty litter box.
Really shameful.
So we can offer you matte
or glossy printing--
Glistening brown morsels tumbling from every pouch
in his trousers.
There's obviously
a volume discount if you--
Following the cat around
on his knees
with his hands cupped
beneath its tail,
going, "Please, kitty,
may I have some more?"
You can't make this stuff up!
No, I think someone
could make it up.
Someone with very few friends.
Hey, fellas,
sorry to keep you waiting.
There he is.
My son.
Got cat turd
collector written all over him.
Did you say cat turd collector?
So definitely looking
to expand our market,
but for now we're just concentrating on athletes
that are popular here in the Northeast.
Of course,
that's not a mandate.
"Mandate"-- always think
of two men on a date.
I have gay friends.
I have one gay friend.Oscar.
Mm-hmm.
All right,so what makes you think
you'd be a good fit here?
Okay.
Um...
all right.
Obviously,
y'all look really busy,
and I don't want to waste
your time anymore.
Sorry, I just, uh...
obviously, I'm not qualified
to be here, man, I'm...
I'm a warehouse manager,
you know...
Darryl,I was a newspaper editor.
Science teacher.
Volleyball coach.
I work
at a home shopping network.
I'm a lawyer.
I'm the only one here
who can honestly help.
And as you know,
I was a paper salesman.
Hey, I find it helps if you just
picture everybody naked.
Cool.
Hey, thanks.
So how about we start over, hmm?
Darryl, do you have
any thoughts on the company?
Yes, as a matter of fact,
I, uh...
- I wrote some down.
- Oh.
There you go.
Wow, this guy came prepared.
It impresses me!
Ah. So this is what 2:00 PM
looks like around here.
I usually take a siesta
about now.
Stocking pens, huh?
You're like
the new office administrator.
No. I just took over
the pen shipment because Pam had to leave.
When I say it out loud,
I know that sounds insane,
- but it's the truth, I swear.
- Pam!
Pam, look out!
- Erin's gunning for your job!
- No, I'm not.
It's not like that at all.
- Forget it. I'm so sorry.
- Pam, look out!
Pens, you did not
buy into this.
I am sorry.
What a day you've had.
By the way, Jim talks
about you all the time.
That's sweet
that he talks about me.
It's too bad he still has
to work part-time in Scranton though.
Well, that's funny,
'cause I think of him as working part-time in Philadelphia.
We can't wait
until you move here.
I'm sorry-- you guys are here
to sell us paper?
Do you mind?
The men are talking.
Sons used to idolize
their fathers.
Us old-timers
need to stick together.
And how better
than by signing a contract?
I'd love to.
Sam Junior here,
he runs the business now.
Kinda pushed me out,
truth be told.
I'm just here
for human contact.
Okay, pop.
Wait.
So you're the boss?
That's right.
- Hi. I'm Clark.
- Hey.
- Let's talk.
- Okay.
So if you look
at our catalog here...
- Well,thanks for coming down, Darryl.
- It was nice meeting you,
Darryl.
I think you'd fit in great here.
Yeah.
Yeah, me too.
I think it'd be like...
you know what?
I think it'd be like
a Kevin Durant jump shot--
perfecto!
Oh, my God.
They are the ones put a fish tank
next to a basketball hoop.
It's like if I put
a glass of milk
on the edge of the table
and Cece knocks it over,
I don't blame Cece.
So I'm like a three-year-old
girl in this scenario.
Say they don't hire you.
It's not like
you're out on the street.
You have a great job
with people who love you.
And I'd only get to see Jada
on the weekends.
You know, I'm... I'm not so sure
I'd like living in Philadelphia.
Right? Thank you!
It's just Philly.
Everyone's acting like it's
New York or Paris or London.
- Who needs it?
- Not us.
Okay.
So the consensus was that that was unique.
They're gonna make you pay
for the fish,
and...they wanted to know
when you can start.
What?
How 'bout yesterday?
- Congratulations.
- Oh, thank you.
I guess you gotta move
to Philly after all.
Yes, I love Philly!
Two-one-five or die!
No, I'm not upset.
I'm really excited for Darryl.
Maybe I'm a little disappointed
that we'll be losing him.
It feels really hot in here.
Is it hot in here?
It feels really,
really hot in here.
It's insane! They need
to have the AC on year-round!
January too!
I don't get the point
of this stupid window!
I mean, look,
you and I both know that in paper or fashion,
styles change.
Check out my dad's suit.
You are looking
at pure acrylic.
That's why his face
always breaks out.
Does that suit
come with a fire extinguisher?
Ha ha ha.
You know what, dad?
Maybe you should buy me a suit.
I mean,I'm gonna need one, right,
if I'm ever gonna get a "real" job
and move "my lazy ass"
out of your "GD house."
He's got ya there.
That's Italian silk.
Very comfortable.Very tasteful...
although expensive.
Yeah, you don't want Italian.
You'll look like a mafia don.
Next thing you know, you'll be
doing life in Rikers Island.
Well, that's better than
looking like the undertaker from boring island.
That place doesn't exist.
It's not a documented island.
Cartograph much?
How do I look?
Actually...
you look great.
They steered you right.
I guess it does make sense
buying from a father-son team.
You know what?
I'll take one too.
Everyone, now that we have
all this energy,
why don't we move the copier
into the annex like we've always wanted to?
- Whoo!
- Frickin' A!
So long, noise!
One, two, three!
Oh!
And we have torn up the carpet.
- Oh, we're gonna be in so much trouble!
- Wait!
It's beautiful.
Hardwood.
I always knew it was down here.
I just never dreamed
that I would actually see it.
Tear up the carpet!
Kill their fish,
and they still hire me.
That's how you do that, baby.
It's all good.
I'm ready.
Y'all ready for this?
* Every body dance now *
Kevin, move.
I can't pull up the rug
If you're standing on it
with your rhinoceros feet.
WEll, I can't stand here
if you pull the carpet out from under me.
Oh, my head is killing me.
Does anyone have
a baby Aspirin?
Oh,
enough with the whining already.
Why don't you just have
some more coffee?
It's all gone.
I didn't get a chance
to try them all
because creed poured
my Bogota Sunrise in the plant.
I saw the leaves twitch.
- Shut up.
- You shut up!
Everybody shut up and work.
- We don't work for you.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
It's 5:00.
- Kevin, can--
- What is going on?
Yes!
We did it!
You opened the door.
And you closed it.
The boys are back in town.
High fives!
Ha ha!
Hey, so all that really
specific cat turd business--
that was about you, right?
You got me!
- I used to collect 'em.
- Why?
Each one is very different,
like a snowflake.
Hey.What happened here?
You left me in charge
of the pens, Pam.
That's what happened.
The pens happened.
Are the pens here?
Join our FRS and have fun!
QQ Group No. 77207643
frzhaopin2@gmail.com
welcome to www.1000fr.net