Previously on
The Mob Doctor
As long as you're in Chicago,
I own you. That's the deal.
What are you doing here?
Did you kill my dad?
I swear to you
I did not kill your father.
Who the hell is this guy?
It's me, dad.
What do you need?
The money I borrowed
belongs to the Nogales Cartel.
You're in a lot of trouble.
I floated the message
to the cartel
that you're willing to pay off
Luke's debt.
There's something you're not
telling me, Al.
They've already taken
punitive measures.
They've ordered a hit on Luke.
Trapani lied about the cartel.
There is no truce.
Trapani never even passed on
your offer to pay Luke's debt.
If they find out
you killed their man
without trying to negotiate,
this is going to get ugly fast.
Where's Constantine?
Help!
Somebody, help!
Help!!
- Watch your back.
- Get out of the way.
58-year-old male,
multiple gunshot wounds
and unresponsive.
All right, this is where
we take over, folks.
We'll take it from here.
He's hypotensive
to 87 systolic.
Expanding hematoma.
Must have nicked the carotid.
Pressure's down to 55.
We need to tie off his artery
right now.
Move him. 3, 2, 1.
Hang two bags... O-neg.
Suction.
54-year-old female with gunshot
wounds to the thigh and shoulder.
Heart rate's 130.
GCS is 6.
Be right back.
Take over.
- Grace.
- It's my mom.
She's lost at least
2 liters of blood... B-positive.
Recurrent loss
of consciousness.
All right, stop.
First, we got to move her,
get her hooked up.
On my count.
3, 2, 1.
I got your page.
Dr. Robinson,
Mrs. Devlin is your patient.
She got bullet wounds to her chest and thigh.
What do you want to order?
Chest, hip, and femur films.
Type and cross for four
and prep an O.R.
- Come on, mom.
- You need to get cleaned up.
- No, I'm not gonna leave her.
- You need to go.
I'm sure the police
want to talk to you.
Right now,
this is how you help your mom.
We need to get him to the I.R.,
stent his carotid.
Gonna be a long night.
Excuse me, doctor. I need
you to sign the run sheet.
Clear here.
Pack the gauze.
Scalpel.
Nate, it's me.
Grace.
Somebody shot up the bakery.
What? It was like a
fricking massacre.
Gus, Gio, Stavos...
They're all dead.
Why are you
answering Constantine's phone?
He's here at the hospital.
So is mom.
Mom?
There was a drive-by
at the house.
They were both hit.
Mom is going into surgery.
You need to get here.
I'm on my way.
Dr. Devlin?
Agent York.
I'm sorry to
hear about your mother.
I spoke to the paramedics.
He said you were there when she
was shot. Did you see anything?
No, I-I was inside.
I heard gunshots,
and then I-I raced outside.
Did you see or hear
a car speeding away,
anything that could
help the investigation?
No, I'm sorry.
I need to go.
Dr. Devlin, we believe that
Constantine Alexander
was the target.
An hour before he was shot,
at least four of his men
were killed at his workplace.
It seems the shooter
was looking for him,
and one of his own men
pointed him to your house.
I-I really...
I understand you manage
Mr. Alexander's diabetes.
Yeah, that's right.
Had he mentioned if
anyone had threatened him,
either personally
or professionally?
No.
I need your cooperation here.
Wh-when we're together,
we talk about
his blood sugar levels
and his diet.
That's it.
What about your brother Nate?
What about him?
We both know Constantine
took Nate under his wing.
My mother is being
prepped for surgery right now.
Will you excuse me?
Suction.
Bone fractured distal
to the greater trochanter.
Side biter.
Grace.
Your brother's here.
How's your mom?
Well, they transfused
four units,
but, uh,
pressure's still borderline.
What does that mean?
The doctors
are repairing the damage,
but the bleeding
is still a problem.
Is she gonna be okay?
I don't know.
The Mob Doctor 01x13
Life And Death
Original Air Date  January 7. 2013
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com
Hey.
That took longer than
it should have. What happened?
I mean,
if you hadn't been there,
she probably wouldn't
have made it this far.
You really
slowed the blood loss.
She's in critical condition.
Her femoral artery
was punctured.
We stabilized the fractures
and repaired the artery.
Well, that all sounds good.
Yeah, it's just,
with this kind of injury,
the 24 hours after surgery
are pretty critical.
I'm not leaving the hospital
until she's stable.
If you need anything, I'm here.
Thank you.
It's ironic, isn't it?
What is?
The two of us
doing all this work
to save the life of
a known killer.
Don't hold back, doctor.
This man spent years in prison,
cost taxpayers hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
Now that he's out,
who knows what he's up to?
My guess...
he's not selling bibles.
Constantine Alexander
is our patient,
and he's in critical condition.
Our job is to
get him out of it alive.
Of course.
I wasn't suggesting otherwise.
I was merely
pondering the reality...
Watch your catheter.
You don't want to
break through the wall.
It's in position.
Deploying the stent.
All right.
Stent's in good position.
Bleeding is stopped.
Of course,
I can't help but wonder
how his shooting
reflects on our hospital.
Excuse me?
Our patient was found
shot on the doorstep
of Dr. Devlin's home.
I don't have to
spell it out for you.
No, you don't.
But perhaps
you should find a hospital
where the doctors
are more to your liking.
I'm just saying
what everyone else is thinking.
And I think you've done
enough pondering for the day.
The Nogales Cartel...
that's who shot mom?
I think so.
Constantine killed their guy
after he came after Luke.
- Luke?
- Constantine's son.
Right.
So going after Constantine
was payback?
Looks like it.
Constantine stopped by
our house. Do you know why?
All right, you got to
stay away from him.
An FBI agent was just here
asking me questions about him,
and then he asked me about you.
Me?
Yeah, they're keep tabs
on his organization,
including me and you.
Grace.
How's she doing?
The same.
Constantine
made it through I.R.
He's being prepped
for the O.R. now.
Thanks.
You text me
if anything changes...
If she wakes up, anything?
Is your mom okay?
I'd like to scrub in
on Mr. Alexander.
Dr. White,
I can't just do nothing.
I understand.
But not today, Grace.
This man
was shot on your doorstep.
You two know each other.
I'm his doctor.
His doctor?
I treat his diabetes.
It only makes sense that
I'm involved in
his treatment here.
Only if I were to okay it,
which I'm not gonna do.
You think I don't notice
all your
mysterious disappearances
and your unusual patients?
I turn a blind eye
because I care about you
and it was easier
not to ask questions.
Now that your life
has so publicly
found its way
into my hospital, my O.R.,
I can't allow it.
Not anymore.
Constantine Alexander
is my patient.
You'll stay away from him.
I heard
your mother's in recovery.
That's great news.
Thanks?
Nate, you and I
want the same thing...
To catch whoever
shot your mom.
It's probably the same
person or persons
who shot up
Constantine Alexander's place.
Do you have any leads?
The bullets we recovered
from both crime scenes
are Aguila 9mm
from Centurion Arms.
You know who uses those?
No idea.
The Nogales Cartel.
I never heard of them.
Nate, I know
you work for Constantine.
The blackmail, insurance scams,
the extortion of
the bars on Pilsen Street.
Yeah, I heard
you were keeping tabs on me.
You heard that?
From who?
It doesn't matter.
You can't prove anything.
Actually, I can.
And it all adds up...
20 years behind bars.
If you help me
with this investigation,
it all goes away.
Think about it.
Grace, I came soon as I heard.
How's your mom?
Uh, she's in recovery.
And Constantine?
Surgery.
Don't you worry.
He's gonna pull through.
He's a real tough guy.
The toughest guy I know.
But you know that
better than anyone, huh?
What do you mean?
It's okay, Grace.
I know what he did for you.
Sorry? What...
What he did for me?
To protect you and your mom
when you were a kid.
I was there when Constantine
took care of business...
Quick, decisive.
Your deadbeat dad
never saw it coming.
If you ask me,
after what he did to you guys,
I think he got off lucky.
You just keep the faith, Grace.
Constantine will be fine.
I'll call you later, huh?
I just work here. How would
I know anything about the shooting?
You're friends
with Dr. Devlin.
I have a lot of friends.
Actually, I don't,
but that doesn't
really matter here.
Look...
I know Grace is a good person
and she's only involved with
the outfit on the periphery.
But right now,
she's not thinking clearly.
As a friend,
tell her to talk to me.
Why would I do that?
Because I can protect her
or I can prosecute her.
Ms. Quintero,
help me help your friend.
I got to get back to work.
Just one more question...
What can you tell me about
Grace and Franco Leoni?
There's nothing to tell.
They broke up years ago.
So they used to date.
The bureau appreciates
your cooperation.
Grace, I think I screwed up.
That FBI guy cornered me
and asked me a bunch
of questions about you.
What did you say?
I kind of mentioned
you and Franco used to date.
He caught me off guard.
I'm so sorry.
Look, um...
Whatever happens to me,
just know that I love you
and I-I never meant to
take your friendship
for granted.
Please, please,
don't talk like that.
Is Constantine
out of surgery yet?
Yeah, about an hour ago.
Why?
I-I just need to
talk to him.
Is that the smartest thing
for you right now?
Probably not.
The men who did this to me,
the ones that murdered
my friends in cold blood...
They're gonna pay for this.
This all happened
because of me.
I'm so sorry.
Don't blame yourself.
You're my son,
and I would do it again.
Come here.
I want to tell you something.
Grace.
Hi.
You're Grace Devlin.
I'm Luke.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, may I
talk to Constantine alone?
So, is your mother all right?
She's in critical condition.
Don't worry...
she's gonna pull through this.
She's a strong woman.
Trust me.
Why, 'cause you've always
been so trustworthy?
What does that mean?
You know, my father was
an abusive drunk.
He destroyed my family.
And you have managed to hurt me
more than he ever did.
You can't mean that, Grace.
Al Trapani just came by.
He thought I knew.
He told me he was there
when you did it.
When I did what?
When you killed my father.
And you believe him?
Just for once
be the man you pretend to be.
Spit it out.
I mean, you got something
to say, just get it out.
I was 6 years old
when I saw your car pull away,
and I convinced myself
that it wasn't you.
You got it all wrong, Grace.
Oh, my God. Stop it.
Just stop.
I didn't kill your father.
I couldn't have.
And why is that?
Deep down, you know why.
Your mother,
she never wanted you to know,
maybe with good reason.
But love me or hate me,
I'm your father.
That's the reason why
I was
at your house last night...
To finally tell you.
Mr. Alexander...
how are you feeling?
Better, doc.
Dr. Devlin,
why are you here?
His phone, um,
dropped in the E.R.
I was just returning it.
And saying goodbye.
Ah.
Ma.
Hi.
Hey.
Hey, Grace.
Hmm.
How you feeling?
I've been better, but...
I'm a survivor...
You know that.
- Ma.
- Huh?
Constantine
just told me something...
About you and him...
and me.
Oh?
He told me that...
He told me that he's my father.
Yeah, right. I mean, he probably
hit his head when he got shot.
Come on.
That's not true.
I was married to Alan
for two years.
He was very cruel,
and I was so lonely.
But...
When I found out
I was pregnant with you...
You lied to dad?
I had to, Nate.
He would have killed us.
You know that.
He died years ago, mom.
Why didn't you tell us after?
H-how do you t-tell somebody
something like that?
I didn't
want to hurt you, Grace.
You know,
when I found him dead,
I, uh...
I thought
something was wrong with me.
I mean,
what 6-year-old girl is glad
when their father is murdered?
What?
And now I find out
he's not even my dad.
Oh, Grace.
I'm sorry.
I'm just gonna get some air.
I'm so...
Grace, I'm so sorry.
Did a great job, doc.
You saved my life.
So, how's it look?
The carotid stent
is functional.
You should be out of here
in a couple weeks.
I wanted to talk to you
about Dr. Devlin.
Sure. Go ahead.
You're gonna
ruin her career... or worse.
I know who you are,
I-I know what you do,
and I-I know about your...
arrangement.
So you know who I am,
and yet
you talk to me like this?
You care about Grace,
don't you?
Well, don't worry
about her, doc.
I'm not gonna
let anything happen to her.
The only way that works
is if you leave her
the hell alone.
I'll be back
to check on you later.
Hello?
Grace?
Oh, thank God.
Franco, I thought you said
it wasn't safe
for us to contact each other.
Uh, it's a disposable phone.
I heard about the drive-by.
It's all over the news.
Yeah, my mom and Constantine
were hit, but they're alive.
Are you okay?
I'm not hurt.
That's not what I'm asking.
Are you okay?
Not really.
Look, there's
something you need to know.
Agent York was here,
and he's been
questioning everybody.
And Ro let it slip
that we used to date.
That's not good.
How long before he figures out
you've been covering for me?
All right, listen to me,
all right?
Now, if he comes to you,
you can't let him
catch you in a lie.
You got to remember
the three most powerful words...
"I don't know."
Say it.
I don't know.
Good.
I can't handle this.
Yes, you can.
Yes, you can, you just got to
focus on getting through today,
all right?
Okay.
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
I should know these things.
I don't want any of this
to change
the way you feel about me...
about Grace.
Alan was my dad, though, right?
Of course he was.
Oh.
I forgive you.
And Grace will, too,
when she's done freaking out.
All right, I'm gonna go
find Grace and calm her down.
Mom? Mom! Mom, are you okay?
Get a doctor!
Help! Help!
Someone, I need help!
My mom needs help!
Grace, where have you been?!
They paged a code blue
on your mom.
They're working on her now.
Mom!
Give me the paddles.
Grace, stop.
I need two amps of bicarb.
Give me the paddles!
Hey, she went
from v-fib to asystole
and never had a rhythm
after that.
Did you try vasopressin?
She threw a lipid embolism.
There was nothing we could do.
I'm really sorry.
She's gone.
Hey.
I've been looking for you.
We were just... talking.
And then...
Out of nowhere...
Sometimes,
when a long bone shatters,
it, uh...
It showers pieces of the marrow
throughout the body.
And one of those pieces
got lodged in her lung.
So her doctors screwed up.
No. It's just not
that easy to predict, you know?
That's why the 24 hours
after surgery are so critical.
God, Grace.
Shut up.
Mom's dead.
Nate...
The things I said to her
were really ugly.
And she died
thinking that I hated her.
Grace...
mom knew you loved her.
That's... that's what
we were talking about,
right before...
She knew.
I promise you... she knew.
I just went after her.
You know,
I didn't think about it.
I just was so mad.
You had a right to be angry.
I'm not angry at ma, though.
There's something
I have to do, okay?
Grace...
I'm so sorry
to hear about your mother.
The last thing
I would have ever wanted
was for Daniella to get hurt.
Well, she was.
And all of it,
the blood and the...
the bodies,
it all goes back to you.
Don't do this.
Please, just listen.
I let myself believe
there was something good in you,
and I was wrong.
I'm gonna tell the FBI
everything I know.
I just don't care.
It's over.
Fine.
I won't stop you
if that's what you want to do.
But just know Stavos
left me this message yesterday.
I didn't get it
until you gave me my phone.
Listen.
We have a problem.
Trapani lied about the cartel.
There is no truce.
Trapani never even passed on
your offer to pay Luke's debt.
If they find out
you killed their man
without trying to negotiate,
this is going to get ugly fast.
An hour after
he sent me this message,
he and half my crew
were gunned down... executed.
It was Trapani who set me up.
He didn't
negotiate with the cartel.
He sent the cartel.
Why would he do that?
Why do you think?
He saw an opportunity
to seize power, and he took it.
Why do you think
he told you about me?
Trying to
drive a wedge between us.
Grace, the cartel
may have pulled the trigger,
but Al Trapani
is the one who's responsible
for your mother's murder.
And if you want the bloodshed
to end and you want justice,
then you and me
are gonna have to take him down.
What would I have to do?
No way.
That's insane.
You're the only one who can
contact the Nogales cartel
without involving Al Trapani.
Yeah, of course
they'd like to hear from me,
so they can
find me and kill me.
All I'm asking you to do
is use your Miami contacts
to set up a meeting
between me and Tiago Enriquez.
He's cartel's
lieutenant here in Chicago.
This is crazy. Why do you think
this guy will even meet you?
Because I'm authorized to
speak for Constantine.
'Cause I'm his daughter.
So you know.
Will you make the call?
Grace, I'm just a real-estate
guy who screwed up.
-I shouldn't even be here.
-And I'm a surgeon.
We're both out of our element.
I am asking you to help.
How can I say no to my sister?
What's that?
Grace Devlin's phone records.
So?
Looks like you two are
a lot closer than I thought.
Until you left town
a month ago,
you spoke several times a day.
The calls are highlighted.
She's Constantine's doctor.
I was gaining her trust.
She has his ear.
Cut the crap, Franco.
You used to date.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, a long time ago.
You just failed to mention it?
It wasn't relevant.
It ended
the day I was recruited.
You told her she was
being investigated, didn't you?
You lied to me, Franco.
She's not just
Constantine's doctor.
She's under his thumb,
and she aided and abetted
outfit activity.
I don't know.
Okay.
Well, then,
let me tell you what I know.
I know you still
got the hots for Dr. Devlin
and I know you two
started up again recently.
She helped me with
my investigation. That's it.
Then how do you explain
CSU finding her fingerprints
all over your safe house...
You know, the motel room
the bureau set you up in
before you took off?
I'm reporting you to
the Attorney General's office.
They're gonna press charges.
I need your gun and your badge.
If you're going after Grace,
you're wasting your time.
Well, that's not
your call to make.
I checked the back parking lot.
There's no sign of him.
He's late.
We're not in a rush.
When I told him we wanted to
meet at the police station,
he didn't seem too happy.
Yeah, well, we need to be safe.
You're sure he listened
to Stavos' message?
Yeah, it's the whole reason
he agreed to meet.
Here we go.
Mr. Enriquez,
I'm Grace Devlin.
Constantine Alexander's
daughter?
That's right.
And this piece of crap
is Constantine's son?
Yeah.
Al Trapani...
Seems he played me
against Constantine.
Is your father
as pissed off as I am?
Yeah, that's why we're here.
What do you propose
we do about it?
Constantine is willing to
forgo retaliation
and give you free access to
the West Side
Eisenhower Expressway.
It's worth millions.
It's not his to offer.
Al Trapani
controls the expressway.
In exchange,
you'll agree to a truce
and you'll forgive Luke's debt.
You'll take the hit off of Luke,
and you'll put it on Trapani.
And you're telling me
Constantine's got enough juice
to take over the West Side
from his hospital bed?
Well, he owns enough aldermen
to shift city council votes.
He's got enough
soldiers on the street
to crush anyone
who won't play ball.
And the CPD
will turn a blind eye,
thanks to every cop
he's got in his pocket.
If I agree to this
and Constantine
doesn't keep up his end,
we'll come after
the both of you.
You understand?
You have my father's word
and mine.
It's done.
Not yet.
Which one of you
shot my mother?
Now we're done.
Does the patient need Insulin?
No, his sugar levels are fine.
I just gave him a sedative.
Can we have a moment, please?
Of course, doctor.
So, what happened?
It's done.
Enriquez will take care
of Trapani
in exchange for the Expressway,
and Luke will get a free pass.
Okay.
That'll give us
the breathing room we need
until we're
ready to make our move.
What do you mean,
"ready to make our move"?
What do you think?
Why don't you tell me?
After the ambush, the cartel...
they could have
taken everything away from us.
We had to trick them into
a sense of security.
All war is deception, Grace.
And a war with the cartel
is one we can't lose.
But we're not losing
'cause we're not fighting.
That's the deal we made.
There is no deal.
There never was a deal.
It's all a tactic, an illusion.
You used me?
Well, if you knew the plan,
you wouldn't have done it.
And there is nobody
that could have
pulled this off like you,
Grace... nobody.
I don't want any part of this.
You don't have a choice.
Don't you see?
You're my blood, my family.
What is in me is in you.
I'm tired now.
I need to rest.
I'm gonna need all my strength
for the fight ahead.
Nate.
Grace.
How's Constantine?
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's...
He's doing good.
Can I see him?
Oh, he's...
He needs his rest right now.
I'm done.
Yeah?
Constantine,
the organization...
I don't want
anything to do with it anymore.
What about you?
I made my decision
a long time ago.
I love you.
I love you, too.
♪ Finger on the trigger, baby
♪ come on, take me down
♪ I drug your name
across my wrist ♪
♪ just to hear the sound
♪ want to feel the metal,
hot, smoking on my lips ♪
♪ take me low and take me high
♪ I just need a hit
♪ let's melt into the shadows
until there's nothing left ♪
♪ my blood spreads like a fire
♪ with your breath
across my neck ♪
♪ I'm not looking for a lover
to be gentle through the night ♪
♪ won't you be my killer?
♪ Keep me in your sight
♪ bang, bang, bang
are you sure
you're ready for this?
It's you and me now.
Mexico, here we come.
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com