The empire state
building on Valentine's day,
the most romantic building
in the world
on the most romantic day
of the year.
So many memorable romances
have played out here.
Deborah Kerr
and Cary Grant
in an affair to remember.
"Give me
a smooch, right on the mug, see?"
I do a pretty spot-on
Cary Grant.
And of course,
the second-best romantic comedy
that Meg Ryan
and tom Hanks ever made:
Sleepless in Seattle.
Every couple weeks,
I buy a ticket
and hang out in the lobby
of the empire state building
to see if I will meet
my one true love.
Captain, she's back.
So you come here regularly
to monitor the base
of the building.
I'm here to meet
that special someone,
and when I do,
we're gonna go to the top,
and then, boom!
Fireworks.
And who is that person?
I haven't met him yet,
but I can tell
when I find him,
we're going to spend
eternity together.
Could you describe him?
All right, well,
he's in his mid-30s.
He is tall, dark,
intense, mysterious...
You understand why
what you're telling us
would cause us
serious concern.
Yeah. I can't help it,
you know,
even though it's dangerous,
because I am
a true believer.
Hey, we're gonna need Miller
from homeland security.
Homeland security?
That's a cool show.
Why do you have a bag
with a passport
and three cell phones?
Okay, well,
this is for the Internet,
this is for texting,
and this flip phone
is because I do not know
how to transfer
my old contacts.
You know, we've been
spending so much time
talking about me
that I haven't
asked you anything.
- What are you into?
- Protecting this building.
Ooh, I love that.
It's so old-fashioned.
You have great facial hair.
I love a guy
with a beard.
Can I touch it?
Hands on the table, please.
Hey, it's cool
if you're into me.
Kevin Garnett once bought me
a coke at a P.F. Chang's.
You're not helping yourself.
I'm just saying
I don't see a wedding ring.
Is there a Mrs. confederated
security solutions?
Oh, my God.
You could've just said yes!
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.Addic7ed.Com/
Dr. Lahiri,
there's something wrong
with Dr. Castellano.
He might be dead.
What?
There's definitely a smell.
Okay.
Danny... oh, my God.
Holy crap!
What the hell?
Yep?
Danny, get up.
Are you kidding me?
Okay, I'm up.
Put some pants on.
I can see the outline
of your penis.
I know that eye patch
dumped you,
but you can't just spend the night
in your office, drunk,
playing weird Bruce Springsteen
songs on your tiny piano.
Stop that.
What's... oh, God.
I stood up too quick.
This is awful. What's
the matter with you?
Your voice
is too loud.
This isn't me.
It's you.
Okay, that is not me.
When I lay on the floor,
it's adorable,
and it is tragic.
When you lay on the floor,
you look like
an upside-down ladybug.
My God, am I the only person
not crawling about
on the floor today?
You guys, I dropped
a Mike and Ike on the floor.
I need all eyes on this.
Danny, you're a grown-up.
Get up.
You're right.
I'm gonna get
myself together.
I'm gonna pull it together.
I'm gonna meet another girl.
It's gonna be good.
I have found that
when I am heartbroken,
it is actually best
to throw myself into work.
Which is why, on Thursday,
I am going to do you
the favor of giving you
all of my patients
for the whole night.
Mindy, it's fine.
I'll look after your patients
on Thursday.
You enjoy
your Valentine's day.
Oh, is Thursday Valentine's day?
Yes. Nice.
I-I hadn't remembered.
Okay.
Wait, how come you,
of all people,
don't have plans
on Valentine's day?
Well, as a man
who's looking to avoid
a committed relationship,
Valentine's day can be
something of a minefield.
"Oh, a dozen roses.
You must really like me."
"Hey, do you want to share
a dessert?"
"Oh, that means you must want to meet
my parents, who live in Minneapolis."
It's an emotional Bosnia.
Think I'll sit it out, thanks.
Well, great.
Then I can have Valentine's day
with Jamie.
As in Jamie and Lucy?
Now, there's a great couple.
Nope,
not as in Jamie and Lucy.
As in Jamie and Mindy.
But aren't you worried
about the incredible chemistry
they seem to have?
They don't have
good chemistry.
I have good chemistry
with Jamie.
I'm really lonely.
Moma was such
a fun idea, Mindy.
I love modern art museums.
Yeah.
I feel like
they're less intimidating
'cause I think
I could do the art.
Oh, you know what?
Your sticker is coming off.
Oh, actually, leave it.
I like people
to know that I had
a more cultural day
than they did.
Oh, it's like the artsy version
of "I voted."
Oh, yes, I have
a ski lift ticket
on my parka
from two years ago.
When you teach Latin
for a living,
it helps to look like
a huge jock sometimes.
Hey, you guys.
Sorry I'm late.
No, not at all.
It turns out
the defendant's gang
had a copy of my home address,
became a thing. What?
- What?
- Oh, my God.
They always threaten me.
Nothing ever pans out.
Can you believe what
this girl deals with? No.
Every day, she looks murderers
in the eye and puts them
in prison for the rest
of their lives.
- Wow.
- So important.
I mean, speaking
of stressful situations,
I delivered a baby
last night.
He did not want
to be born.
He was really mad
at me.
I'm glad he didn't have
my home address.
That's really funny.
Hey, seriously, though,
you know,
if you ever fear for your
safety, you still have a key.
If you ever want to stay
at my place,
you know you can, right?
Well, I would rather take on
the Sinaloa cartel
than deal with the water
pressure in this guy's shower.
It's not that bad.
You're so great.
You should have
a boyfriend.
I would love to meet a cool guy,
except all the guys I meet
are either 19-year-old murderers
or 80-year-old judges.
You know what, I think
I'm gonna find you someone.
No, I really wouldn't try.
Yeah, great.
This girl is the pickiest dater
I have ever met in my life.
No, no, I'm actually
a very good matchmaker.
Well, I wish you luck,
but no one's ever
good enough for this girl.
So I wouldn't even try.
So Mindy at the museum...
Ah, Danny.
Tear up that suicide note.
I have great news.
Okay, that wasn't
a suicide note.
I was contesting
a jaywalking ticket.
Oh. I am sorry about that.
Danny, I am going
to set you up on a date.
This morning you said I should
throw myself back into work.
That was, like,
six hours ago, okay?
That's an entire lifetime
for some bugs.
You're gonna love
this girl.
She is pretty.
She is smart.
She owns a motor scooter.
Ah.
It's Lucy.
Lucy of Jamie and Lucy?
They broke up?
I am dating Jamie
of Jamie and Mindy.
We kissed mouths, Danny.
Okay, I don't know.
I just... I don't know
if I'm ready.
Well, you would also
be doing me a huge favor.
If you spend time
with Lucy,
then Jamie won't spend
as much time with her.
Also, this is a big deal.
I am setting you up
with someone.
You never set me up
with anybody.
That's not true.
I hooked you up with Reynaldo.
Your garbage man?
Yeah.
He was smokin' hot,
but he was a little pretentious.
A little bit too well read,
if I may say that.
Danny, please do this
for me.
Can I think about it?
Danny!
You are so selfish!
I don't care
if you're depressed!
Just help me out for once!
Okay, stop...
All right.
I am gonna die alone
unless you do this for me.
Stop hitting me.
I'll go on one date
with her, okay?
Are you serious?
One.
Oh, my God, Danny,
thank you. Thank you.
Okay. When everyone's
mean about you,
I defend you
most of the time.
Okay, I'm good
on the hug, though.
Thanks.
To show my gratitude
for this kindness,
we can choose any city
of real housewives to watch.
Miami.
Yes.
Deborah, do you like
working in the morgue?
Well, I don't get a lot
of patient complaints.
It's funny that you work
in the morgue
because my name
is morg-an.
Please wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Nope.
Nothing. Sorry.
Uh, Dr. Reed.
Did you see me
hit on that girl?
Unfortunately,
I did, yes.
I've had my eye on her
for a while.
I'm gonna take her
to the batting cages,
if you know what I mean.
Well, let me know
how that doesn't work out.
Okay, here's my plan.
I am going
to put these
in the ladies' room
in all the stalls.
"Me with out go"...
No, no, read it up...
Oh. "Will you go out
with me?"
And then she'll be
like, "what?
Yes."
Morgan, what if somebody uses
the bathroom before her?
Yep, not a good idea.
Plan "B."
Surprise her
in her car tonight.
That's a felony.
Not on Valentine's day.
Doesn't matter what the holiday is.
Check the laws in this country.
I'm not even sure
about that.
Morgan, wait.
- Maybe I could help you.
- Really?
Oh, God,
that would be so good.
Coming, I'm coming.
- Hey.
Why are you so early?
- Ten minutes?
- Yeah.
You're ten minutes
early, Danny,
which is worse
than two hours late.
Those last ten minutes,
that's when I go from "whoa"
to "damn."
Wait a minute.
Why did I have to come
here first, anyways?
Well, you are going
on a date with my friend.
Mm-hmm.
And I wanted to make sure
that you didn't look weird.
You had, like,
a mustache or something.
How would I grow a mustache
since this morning?
I don't know.
I'm not Italian.
Also, it's good
when I'm getting pretty
for there to be a guy here,
so he can be like,
"hurry up! We're gonna be late!"
What?
Why are you looking at me?
Are you sure
you want to wear that?
It being on me implies
that I want to wear it.
Okay. I like it.
Wow.
A whole room
that's a closet?
You could make this
into a little gym,
hang a heavy bag there.
Yeah, Danny,
that's what I want.
I want a bag
full of sand to punch
instead of all my clothes.
Okay, what about this one?
You like that?
You want me
to wear a little black dress,
push-up bra, high heels.
Boring, sexy, anonymous girl.
Sexy's not boring.
You got any food?
Cold cuts?
No, but I think I have
some pizza from election night.
I think this date's
gonna be fun.
Let's take a shot.
You look nice.
- Thanks.
- To...
True love.
Sex with new people.
Danny.
Hey, guys.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Lucy, you remember Danny.
Danny, Lucy.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Beautiful.
Oh, man.
What?
That's a king salmon
over there.
So?
Jillian studied the migration
of that fish.
No. Yeah.
That fish goes from salt water...
No. Stop it.
To fresh water.
It's an amazing fish.
They do it to mate.
Nobody cares.
To mate.
Danny, nobody cares.
- Hey.
- Hey, guys?
Is everything okay?
Really good.
Would you mind
switching seats with me?
Because that fish
is in my eye line,
just putting me in a...
A bad place emotionally
right now.
The fish?
That one, yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, sure. It's your eye line.
Do you mind?
Okay, great.
Thanks.
Wouldn't want to look
at something
I didn't like.
Oh, yeah, thank you.
That's much better.
Good.
So can I ask what exactly
your problem is
with sea life?
Oh, it's just,
my ex was an oceanographer.
It's stupid.
Yeah, it is stupid.
Hey, look
at this bread selection.
There's white bread.
There's the brown bread.
Just if I keep myself
from seeing triggers,
then, you know,
I don't fixate on her...
Ow!
Did somebody
just kick me?
You okay? Ow!
Yeah, that is so weird.
I think that maybe
we should move tables,
or we could try
not talking about exes
and see if the kicking stops.
You know what, though?
I have found
that the hardest breakups
are the ones
where you might have
underestimated the person
while you were with them,
I don't know if...
Yes. That's exactly
what I'm going through.
- Really?
- Yes.
It... it's like you're...
I know, it's so weird.
That's exactly what
is going on
with me and Jillian.
No way.
Well, it was me, really.
I just...
Tell me about that.
- Uh, Jamie?
- Yeah.
I don't want
to jinx this,
but I think
match-dot-Mindy
might have
another success story.
You know, you can have
a friendship, maybe.
Yeah?
So, Morgan,
you want to take
this girl
to the batting cages.
I'm still not sure
what those are.
Three-pronged attack,
Morgan.
Number one, casual approach.
Watch me, watch me,
watch me.
What am I doing?
I don't know what you're gonna...
Now.
Wow, okay, you look
like Joe Biden.
That is awesome.
Number two, initiate
some light physical contact.
- Okay.
- Oh, red.
Nice color.
Oh, yeah.
It's Valentine's day,
and it hides the blood.
That's disgusting. Number three.
Offer her something small.
A token of sorts.
It establishes a debt.
Got a free cola
from the vending machine.
Oh, I've actually been staring
at that thing all morning.
Thanks, doc.
I owe you one.
Oh! It's a...
Part of the routine.
- There it is.
- Okay.
It's the debt.
I got it.
You just give her
whatever you have on you.
Why not?
All right.
So I'll be like,
"hey, this is for you."
Where's the body?
I just found the head
in the toilet.
Oh, God.
You never know
a love song
until you have
a broken heart, right?
Mm, yes.
And finally you realize
that all of these songs
that you thought
were so happy-sounding
are actually so sad.
Like you can call me Al.
Mm.
"Where is my wife
and family?
What if I die here?"
Who'll be my role model
now that my... once my...
Role model's gone?
Man, I gotta download
that album again. Mm-hmm.
It's a great one.
I think they really like
each other.
Well, they like Paul Simon.
So does everyone else
on the planet.
No, it's like
we're not even here.
Hey, guys.
Hey, there's four
of us here.
So let's try to...
Oh.
Sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
Danny was just
helping me
figure out where I should get
my first tattoo.
Uh-oh.
Um, you hate tattoos.
I don't think so.
I think I'm gonna get
a tattoo as we.
A little butterfly
on the nape of my neck,
and it would signify
that I'm a free spirit...
What tattoo
are you gonna get?
Well, I think I should
keep it a secret,
because where I want
to get it,
only certain people
would see it.
I-I don't know, Luce.
I worry that a tattoo
is a little short-sighted.
You know?
Mmm. Can I try that?
Is your grandson
really gonna understand
why you have
a radiohead lyric
under your belly button?
I can't understand
radiohead now.
Mmm!
Do you wanna have some
of my COD?
I'm fine.
I just had some.
Wow, that lamb
is so, mmm, succulent.
It is succulent.
You are such a good orderer.
Thank you.
Pick a good restaurant,
and they say, you know,
the food
orders itself, so...
Mmm, try this.
Okay.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Lucy!
- Your cold.
- Hmm?
She had this horrible cold
last week.
I'm good with it.
I'll take it.
You might
get something.
I'm not sick.
Do you want some of my COD?
I don't get sick that often.
I don't have a cold.
- You don't?
- No.
Eat off my fork.
It's romantic.
I don't need it.
I'm not hungry.
Eat off my fork, please.
Isn't that good?
You all right, buddy?
It was just
a little piece of COD.
I'm so sorry.
It's got bones in it. That's why.
Hey, Jamie?
Are you good?
You choking, buddy?
They're doctors.
You should just...
Okay?
You sure?
I'm gonna...
It has bones in it.
I can Heimlich. I know.
Please let me Heimlich you.
Okay.
I'm not gonna let you die
in this weird restaurant, Jamie.
Should we get dessert?
I think he's choking.
No, he's okay.
Jamie, stop!
Jamie!
- Oh.
- Oh, boy.
Jamie, please stop
doing that!
Hey, guys,
don't worry about it.
She's a doctor.
She's got it.
I just don't understand
why, in 2013,
restaurants have any bones
in their fish.
And while I appreciate
the gift certificate
as a gesture,
I did think the manager
was passive-aggressive,
the way that he gave it.
You remember that?
Hey, you know what?
I think I'm gonna
call it a night, Jamie.
You almost died.
My shoes are pinching me.
- So...
- No. No. No.
We're gonna continue
this date.
I am gonna take you
to the most romantic place
in all of New York City.
And possibly the world.
Keep moving, guys.
Please,
keep the line moving.
Jamie, I cannot believe
you took me
to the empire state building
for Valentine's day.
Last year,
the guy I was with,
he took me
to an Indian casino,
and I lost $2,000.
Well, this is actually
something I've
always wanted to do.
And I figured I'd come
with the perfect person
on the perfect night.
Next, please.
Wait, wait. Jamie.
Um, before we go
into the most romantic building
on the entire planet...
Yeah.
Can you just tell
me one thing? Yeah.
Just... you're not in love
with Lucy, are you?
Next, please.
Why do you keep saying
things like that?
It just seems like
you were really jealous
of her and Danny
at dinner.
Okay, I'm not jealous
of a guy
who wears boot cut jeans,
all right?
See? That sounds jealous.
Lucy is my best friend.
Next.
And if I love her,
it's the way I would love
a sister.
I have a brother, and if rishi
looked at me that way,
I would have to talk
to our dad.
Next, next!
Let's go, lady.
Come on.
Okay, we're trying to sort
something out right now.
All right? Can you just give me
a break here?
Just look
into your lover's eyes.
It's Valentine's day,
for God's sake. Come on.
Quick scenario, okay?
You are on death row
because you murdered a cop.
What?
This is hypothetical.
You can only see one more person
before they electrocute you.
Who would it be?
My lawyer
because I wouldn't do
something like that.
Okay, your lawyer
bungled the case,
and you have one person
to see before you die.
You can say me
if it's me.
It's Lucy.
I knew it.
You're good at this.
It's Lucy!
I'm in love with Lucy!
No, no, no, it's okay.
Don't...
I'm not Lucy.
No, I mean, it's not...
It's not, like,
traumatizing.
It's okay. It's not...
It's just...
I'm okay with it.
Okay, folks. Next.
Come on, let's go.
I'm a man in love!
Oh, my God!
Jamie!
This has not been
a good day for you.
Okay, all right.
That's it, Morgan.
Casual approach.
Okay, good.
Now some light contact.
Light.
What are you doing?
Morgan, human touching,
not dog touching.
Agh.
Good... good...
Good recovery, I guess.
Now parting gift,
parting gift.
Come on, Morgan.
Come on.
Oh, he found the body.
She's into it.
Who knew? Okay.
I... it worked!
Bravo, Morgan!
Bravo.
Hey, man, I'm working here. Sorry.
You finally came
for me, love!
Okay, shh.
You finally called my name!
Shh. Come on, come on.
You're gonna wake up
my neighbors.
I can't believe this is
all because of you.
You showed me that love
was right in front
of my face.
All right,
that's so great.
I never thought I would feel
this way, Mindy.
We can just walk.
It is great.
And not dance and stuff.
I've never done
anything like this.
Okay.
The whole time.
Disgusting, water on my...
It's all because of you.
You are such
an important character
in the story
of Lucy and me.
Don't you realize that?
Yeah.
You're fate's helper.
I'm like
the Joan Cusack character
in the romantic comedy
of your life, yeah.
Yes!
I can't believe it.
Can you believe
this is me?
People are gonna think
you're on drugs.
I'm in love!
Stop it, Jamie.
I'm flying.
Oh, my God.
Hey! What the hell,
you guys?
Hey, what's going on,
love birds?
Actually,
we kind of broke up.
And, for the record,
there is no kissing on my stoop.
That is a direct quote
from my super.
Okay, well, I left my gloves
at your place.
So I just came here
to pick them up.
Did you think you would find
them inside of her mouth?
You're making out
with this guy?
This guy, they ask
if he wanted a cocktail,
and he ordered shrimp?
Why are you yelling?
Because I love you!
Really?
Okay, wait a minute.
I love you too!
Whoa, whoa, guys, we were
just kissing a second ago.
All right, I'm gonna call it
a night and head in.
Pardon me.
God, I've been dreaming about this
for 15 years!
Okay, can I... what made
you change your mind?
Can I squeeze by here?
My life flashed before my eyes
when I was choking.
Just... it suddenly dawned on me.
Excuse me.
Not to be a stickler,
but I-I was the person
who helped make it
dawn on you.
Mindy helped. She was like
a supporting character.
Oh, thank you!
Let's take a walk.
Let's just get outta here.
That's the weirdest thing
I've ever seen.
You know, I feel like if I had
just worn the first dress,
that this wouldn't
have been the situation.
I don't think
that's the problem.
Hey, Dr. Reed.
Morgan.
I'm gonna go pick up
three or four calzones
and crawl into bed.
Who am I kidding?
It's gonna be four.
What happened?
Did you strike out?
Ha. My first sports analogy.
I had her right
where I wanted her.
And then, bam!
She dumps me
literally the second
we're finished having sex.
Whoa, whoa, wait.
What... sex?
I did everything
you told me.
I was playing it cool.
She pulls me
into a supply closet.
We start having sex
in front of a bunch of mops.
You got exactly
what you wanted.
I wanted to take her
to the batting cages.
I mean, you got the good stuff
without the boring stuff.
Home run.
Did it again.
The batting cages
is the good stuff.
I don't want to have sex
with someone I care about
in a mop closet.
I want to do it
the right way.
On the couch,
in the living room,
after grandmother's asleep.
Morgan, I'm so sorry.
I need to make this
up to you.
I feel like
I've led you astray.
A stray?
Where is he?
We're gonna find him.
How'd he get in the building?
Another one,
another one.
You gotta choke up.
Don't get tired.
You can't quit.
We don't quit in America.
Whoa.
Check on that, Morgan.
Show me how you did
that weird swing.
I want to try that.
That's pretty bad-ass.
You got, like, a Michael Caine,
Gary Sheffield...
Oh! Oh, God!
Right in the car keys.
Oh! Oh, ho, ho!
Oh!
Danny, I was this close
to spending Valentine's day
at the empire state building.
To put that in you terms,
that's like losing
your virginity
at Yankee stadium.
See, that's your problem.
Yeah, no, that's what
I'm doing, Danny.
I'm describing my problem.
Who told you the empire state
building was romantic?
A postcard
at the airport gift shop?
Some dumb movie
with tom Hanks
where he's hugging in the rain
and there's no umbrellas?
You know what?
Come here.
I want to show you something.
This is it.
Oh, cool.
Your favorite pizza place.
Yeah, Danny,
this does cheer me up.
Okay, I'm ready to go.
No, no, no.
I want to show you something.
Sit down.
Sal, can we get two slices?
You got it.
This, like, a setting
from goodfellas or something?
No, this is
where I met my wife.
- What?
- Yep.
Here?
Yeah. Check this out.
I wanna show you this.
Danny, you little felon.
That's awesome.
Her name was Christina?
Yep.
Were you ever like...
"Eh, Christina,
I love you so much-a."
Yeah.
Oh.
I think I still
really miss her.
Well, now you can...
What are you doing?
Why do you need
to take a picture of everything?
So that you always remember it
and you never forget.
Stop it.
I want to show Morgan.
No, don't...
We can tell him
about it, okay?
Look, look, the most romantic
place in the world,
you don't know it's gonna be
romantic ahead of time.
Like, for you,
it could be anywhere.
Like a barbershop
or an ATM shelter
or h&r block.
Danny, I'm pretty sure
it's gonna be
the empire state building,
but those are
very cute suggestions.
By the way, eye patch
was wrong about you.
You're not mean.
She just didn't know you
well enough.
There you go, Danny.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Thanks.
Hey, how the...
How is the pizza here?
Worst pizza
in the city.
Oh.
Happy Valentine's day.
Just want to take
only the crust.
The crust
is my favorite part.
You're so weird.
Go to bed.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.Addic7ed.Com/