Aw, crap.
Morning, sleepyhead.
God, what did I do?
Me.
Several times, actually.
Don't you remember?
I was really drunk.
Ow, I wasn't thinking.
Um, we've both know we've been thinking
about doing that for a while now.
It was only a matter of time.
I never should've come here.
What are you doing? I thought
we'd spend the day together.
I've got school.
Well, you had a good time
last night though, didn't you?
That's not the point, okay?
It was a mistake, Sutton.
Can I have my shirt back?
This is because of Emma, isn't it?
I'm... I'm just really sorry
about the whole thing, okay?
Well, you didn't seem to
be too sorry last night.
I... I know... y... you're right.
You're right and that
just was not fair to you.
I realize that and, um...
I promise it won't happen again.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
You really shouldn't have
left the party so early.
You still had guests to entertain.
Like Laurel Mercer?
Admit it: she's just a way for
you to get closer to her dad.
Maybe, but I'd play along if I were you.
'Cause it be a real shame
if some of your past mistakes
were to come to light.
Wouldn't it?
You know what?
We can talk about this later.
'Cause you're late for school.
I hate it when you get parental on me.
Sutton?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm sorry, but this is an emergency.
I slept with Ethan.
That's not an emergency.
Unless, of course,
you didn't use protection?
No, I did.
He... he freaked out this morning.
And told me that he
wished it didn't happen.
I'm so sorry, Sutton.
Boys can be so cruel.
This is her fault.
If I could just get rid of Emma,
Ethan will forget about her.
She's your sister.
Someday we're going to be a family again.
And you need to get along with her.
He's holding out hope for her.
Just like your father.
Holding out hope for Kristin.
Amazing how you can make
my problems all about you.
The truth is, you could
learn by my example.
Ted and I kind of had a moment last night.
Yay for you.
Yay for you too.
If you follow my lead.
I don't give up so easily,
and neither should you.
All right, thanks for the ride, man.
Where the hell you been all night?
Screwing up like usual.
You know?
I had to hitch a ride.
You're damn right you screwed up.
Your teacher called.
Mr. Beattie?
You plagiarize a paper?
Sounds like you already
know the answer to that.
Yeah, he ran it through some software.
Found out it was bought online.
Dan, I know I shouldn't
have done that, okay?
Save it, Ethan.
I can't let you go back to juvie.
So I got Beattie to
give you a second chance.
You're going to take an
exam on all the coursework.
It's real simple: you pass
the test, you pass the course.
Okay, thanks.
When is the test?
Tomorrow morning.
It's tomorrow morning?
How am I going to pass
a test tomorrow morning?
I don't know, but you better figure it out
because your whole life depends on it.
What happened to your eye?
I'm just making friends.
Everybody in jail loves the D.A.
Let me get this straight.
Dan, our Dan,
came up with this crazy theory
that I'm trying to frame myself?
You know it makes more
sense than your own theory.
After all, it was a man
who called the waitress to set you up.
Rebecca could've done that.
She could've hired someone.
Or... you made the call yourself.
I thought you were trying
to represent me here.
The objective was to get me out of jail.
Whose side are you on?
When you hired me, you told me
that if you could convince
me of your innocence,
you could convince a jury too. Well...
I'm not as convinced as I used to be.
Pull the waitress's phone records.
That'll prove I didn't make the call.
Dan's already on it.
Should have them this afternoon.
You know, Theresa, you really ought
to keep your eye on the ball.
Rebecca's pulling the strings on this one.
Not me.
I heard the strange ringtone
and I found this hidden in the garage.
- A cell phone?
- Yeah.
I thought the police already
searched your whole house.
Well, I know, it's weird
that they didn't find it,
but it's got to be my dad's,
so I have to turn it in.
No, hold on, we need to check
it and see who he called.
I already did.
All incoming calls were blocked.
And if he made any calls
out, he cleared the log.
Can't you hack into it
and see what he deleted?
But that might be considered
tampering with evidence.
Thayer, this is going to be our only way
we're gonna know what he's
been up to all this time.
Please?
Can you just try?
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Aren't they adorable?
I can't believe they finally got together.
She's coming.
Uh, act natural.
Oh, hi.
- Hey, how's everything?
- Hey.
Everything is fine.
Were you spying on me?
Us?
No.
Just came in here to brush my hair.
With my brush?
Okay, we were totally spying.
Oh, my God.
You and Thayer... this is awesome.
Way to hold firm, Laurel.
Mads, you should've come
out and talked to him.
Especially after what happened last night.
Well, his lips seemed pretty busy just now.
So, I figured I'd do it later.
Okay, listen, not to
make this all about me,
but I need to ask you guys a question.
What do you think about
me asking Jordan out?
Okay...
terrible idea.
No...
How well do you know him?
What? You think he's out of my league?
No, of course not.
I just think that...
I think you guys'd be great together.
You should totally go
for it. No reason not to.
This is disgusting!
What is this?
God!
- What's going on?
- Are you okay?
Well, the sink is clogged.
Ew, well, maybe Dad could fix it.
No, I don't want to have
to rely on him right now.
I can take care of this myself.
But I thought therapy went well.
That doesn't mean we are
getting back together.
Have you tried the disposal?
Maybe that'll clear it?
That is a very good idea.
You see, girls?
We can handle this ourselves.
Oh, my God.
Um, I'll call a plumber.
Dude.
You and Sutton Mercer
back together again, huh?
Look, I might've seen her when
I dropped you at the cabin.
I mean, that girl moves fast.
Nothing happened, okay?
No, like literally fast.
Like The Flash.
You know, she was at the party one minute,
then the cabin the next.
She must've taken a shortcut.
So, she races down there
for a secret rendezvous,
and you guys don't even hook up?
Come on, you don't really expect
me to believe that, do you?
Jordan, you need to keep your mouth shut.
All right?
You didn't see anything.
Got it?
Got it.
She wasn't there.
And she's definitely
not down the hall either.
Ladies.
He was totally checking you out.
Ew, he's my stepbrother.
Regardless, you have to tell Laurel
that you hooked up with him.
You heard her this morning.
She was talking about asking him out.
It was a meaningless one-time thing,
and we've agreed never
to speak about it again.
It's like it didn't even happen.
But it did happen.
I'm late for Bio.
Cleaning out?
Dropping out, actually.
Beattie found out I plagiarized
that World Civ paper.
So, now I'm history.
Not that it's any your business.
Well, won't you go back to juvie.
Well, maybe that's where I belong.
No, Ethan, there has to
be something you can do.
Yeah, there's a test I'd have
to pass tomorrow on
all the course material,
but I can't do that
because I'm too far behind,
which is why I cheated in the first place.
Wait.
What?
I'll tutor you.
Why do you even care?
After everything I did.
Aren't you with Thayer now?
Oh, come on. This has
nothing to do with him.
This is about your future.
You can't just give up.
Please, just let me help you.
Whoa, oops.
Excuse me.
Let me help.
Oh, my gosh, I'm such a klutz.
Maybe they should put warning
labels on these things.
You're hilarious.
Um, hey, look,
I know this is really short notice, um,
but DJ Beat Baron is
spinning tonight at Hangar 19.
And I was thinking of going.
Would you want to come?
I didn't even know that
Beat Baron was in town.
His mixes are so sick.
So, you in?
Yeah, for sure.
Um, pick up around 7:00?
It's a date.
I mean, a date in the calendar
sense of the word. Right.
All right, I'll see you then.
Okay.
Woo.
Mads, I thought you said
you wanted to apologize.
I am apologizing.
For last night, but not
for thinking Dad's innocent.
I told you, he said...
I don't care what he said.
He's playing you just
like he plays everyone.
Guys?
Everything okay?
Yeah, fine.
No, it's not fine.
Rebecca, tell him about the fingerprint
they found on the golf bag.
They can prove that Dad's been set up,
just like he's been saying all along.
Well, I didn't want to
get anybody's hopes up,
but things are looking a lot better now.
Well, I wouldn't pop
that champagne just yet.
Excuse me, guys. I have work to do.
Wait. We weren't finished talking.
Thayer, stay.
Why don't we all go to dinner together?
My treat.
Sutton and I are playing tennis tonight.
She has regionals coming up. Sorry.
He just won't listen.
Oh, he'll come around.
Mads, it's you
that I'm actually worried about.
Between all of this,
your dad being in jail,
living at the Mercers while
they're going through divorce.
Well, Ted and Kristin are
actually in therapy now.
So, things seem better.
Really?
Yeah.
That's so good to hear.
Oh, good, you made it.
I didn't think you would get here so...
Wait a second.
I told the girls
specifically not to call you.
Really? 'Cause Laurel made it sound
like you were practically
begging me to come over.
Did they clog the drain too?
Wouldn't put it past them... our girls.
Pretty crafty.
Aww, what is this?
Lamb chops, some kind of fish, chicken.
What are you thinking, piccata?
Parmigiana.
Mmm.
Kill for a home-cooked meal,
not that I'm hinting at anything.
Don't you think it's a
little early for that?
Right.
Speaking of which, I spoke
to Dr. Sandy's office.
She said she has a time
for us Monday at 10:00?
I actually have another
appointment at that time.
And I'm not...
I'm not sure that I
want to cancel it, so...
No pressure, that's fine.
Just let me know.
I have to rent a rooter for this,
- so can you wait till tomorrow?
- Sure.
The call to Jessica Whitman
was made from a burner cell,
so chances are it's been destroyed by now.
In other words, anyone could've
called her, including Alec.
Which is why I called his secretary
to check his schedule that day.
And from that look, I'm
guessing you found something.
He took off early.
Was gone all afternoon. Didn't say where.
Huh, that's interesting.
Yeah, huh.
I'm so sorry. I have to
bail on you for tennis. Something came up.
Well, whatever it is, it should wait
because I found out who my dad
called with that cell phone.
Apparently, he made one
call to a Jessica Whitman.
Number's been disconnected, but
I figured we could work together
and try and find her.
I can't tonight.
But...
but you can do it without me.
I'll call you later, okay?
Wait, they're getting along now?
I thought they hated each other.
That was during the Seven Years' War.
During World War I, France
and England were allies.
Well, how am I supposed
to keep this stuff straight
if even they can't decide who likes who?
This is worse than high school.
Maybe if you just focus
and put the ball down.
I am focused.
I really am.
But I am focusing on how this is going
to be a huge waste of my time.
You're right.
I can't teach you if
you don't want to learn.
So have fun in juvie.
All right, wait, wait.
Hang on a second, okay?
I just feel like I don't deserve this.
What?
Your help.
Okay.
You made a mistake, Ethan.
And now you have a chance to make it right.
Ethan, I believe in you.
Emma, I have to tell you something.
I...
Well, hope I'm not interrupting anything.
Sutton, are you crazy?
Oh, would you relax?
I checked to make sure
Dan was still at work.
I was stopping by to see if Ethan
wanted to join me for dinner,
but, apparently, he has plans.
It's not what you think, all right?
I've... I've got a test tomorrow.
We're... we're studying. She's helping me.
Oh, well, that's really sweet.
I approve.
Seriously?
Yes, seriously, we don't want lover boy
to end up back in juvie now, do we?
Lover boy?
Oh, come on. It's a figure of speech.
We really have a lot
of work to do right now.
Okay, well, then I will leave you these.
Just for a little snack.
For later.
It's from that favorite
barbeque place you like.
Good luck tomorrow.
He doesn't need luck.
He has me.
You should have seen her.
Playing all innocent.
I'm telling you that if
I would have stayed there,
Alec wouldn't be the only
one in jail for murder.
You're going to be a lot happier
after you hear what I have to say.
What could you possibly say
that would make me feel better?
I want you...
to take your life back from Emma.
Since when is switching back
ever been part of the plan?
It's just there's only so much I can do
to keep Ted and Kristin apart.
So, you want me to work from
the inside to split them up?
Well, think about it this way:
Emma will be here in isolation,
while you're out and about,
which means you'll have
Ethan all to yourself.
You know she's not going
to do this willingly
Mmm, you're going to have to
find a way to persuade her.
Don't let me down, pumpkin.
Mads.
Hi.
Am I at the right house?
Yeah, I'm just staying
here for a little bit.
Come on in.
Laurel, uh, should be ready in a minute.
Sorry, I didn't realize you'd be here.
Guess this is kind of awkward.
Why would it be awkward?
Gotcha.
All set. Thanks for entertaining him.
Yeah, not a problem. You two have fun.
Hey, do you want to come?
Uh, I can't.
I don't want to impose.
Are you kidding? We're just hanging out.
Mm-hmm.
But I thought...
No, you should come.
It's not like it's a date or anything.
Jordan, can you give us a sec?
Okay, now you have to come with us.
No, I'm so not in the mood.
You were the one who
told me to ask him out,
and now I'm totally confused.
If you come along, you
can help me figure out
whether or not he's really into me or not.
Please?
Fine.
- For the record...
- She's in. Let's roll.
Not a word.
You left work early the day
that call to Jessica Whitman was made.
The only thing I'm guilty of is
leaving work early to play some golf.
And before you say anything,
you're not allowed to have cell
phones on the golf course, okay?
We should get out next week.
What do you say? You free?
She is. You aren't.
Oh, think again, Danny Boy.
I've got a witness that'll back me up.
You two just gave me a
get-out-of-jail-free card.
Hey, sis.
You were out late.
Oh, you scared the crap out of me, Sutton.
Hey, you know, you should really get
these re-strung every now and then.
What do you think you're doing?
You can't go play tennis.
You're supposed to be staying out of sight.
And you're supposed to be
practicing for regionals,
but that doesn't seem to stop you
from going over to
Ethan's and tutoring him.
I knew you were upset about that.
Oh, I'm not upset.
I'm thrilled that you're helping him.
Mm-hmm.
I just don't want to lose regionals either.
You know, a lot is riding on it:
a chance to play D-1 tennis,
and scholarship.
Since when has any of that mattered to you?
Since I had a lot of time
to think up at that cabin.
And the fact of the matter
is, you and I are both going
to have to go to college someday.
Well, don't worry. I'm
ready for the tournament.
And I'm gonna win the scholarship.
Yeah, but a little bit
of practice wouldn't hurt.
So, I was thinking, I can
just give you some pointers.
We go out tomorrow.
Just for fun.
Someone will see us, Sutton.
Then, we'll do it across town.
No one will recognize us.
What is the big deal?
Why is this so important to you?
Geez, just thought I'd spend
some quality time with my sister,
but if you're not interested.
No.
Actually, I would love to.
You're on, sis.
Thanks for coming down.
Actually, I was already
planning on talking to you.
About what?
Well, you first. You said it was important.
Well, we need you to make a statement.
Some new evidence has come to light.
Someone called a waitress at the club
and paid her to plant the tire iron
in your father's golf bag.
- Wait. Somebody called?
- Yeah.
What was the waitress's name?
Jessica Whitman.
Whoever called her set
your father up, Thayer.
Oh, my God. Dan, he wasn't set up.
He's the one who called.
Hello, T.
- What the hell?
- It's okay, Thayer.
We just need to ask you some questions.
Well, I've got some questions of my own.
Like...
how do you explain this, for example?
Dad?
How can you say you've
never seen that phone before?
- I found it in our house.
- If it was there the whole time,
why didn't the police find it
when the searched the house?
They must have missed it.
Come on. Look, whoever
planted the phone there,
planted it there after the search.
And then they called it
to be sure you'd find it.
Or maybe you just screwed up.
And you didn't hide it as
well as you think you did.
I'm no fool, son.
- But you're a murderer.
- Okay,
that's enough.
This isn't getting us anywhere.
I got the lab results.
Our techs confirmed that...
it is indeed the cell phone used
to call Jessica Whitman.
Ouch.
Case closed.
They also determined
that the call to Jessica...
was made from Flagstaff, Arizona.
Weren't we playing golf the exact time
that phone call was made?
Yeah, it was a Friday, right?
I remember it 'cause you beat me
by one... you birdied 18.
- I know. I remember.
- So how could I be
playing golf with you in Scottsdale,
and also be in Flagstaff,
150 miles away?
I don't know. Maybe you hired someone.
Or maybe there's two of me.
Well, it backfired.
'Cause we got enough to go to the judge
and get the charges against you dropped.
Oh, my God. No, no, no, please, please,
- you can't let him out.
- T, face it...
You were wrong about everything,
and the only mistake I made
was taking your bastard ass in
when nobody else gave a crap about you.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Okay, okay...
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
Damn it. This can't be happening right now.
You dad's getting out
whether you like it or not.
You need to find a way to deal with that.
Now go home and cool off.
Hi, this is Lindsey Ridgeway's office
reminding you of your
appointment for Monday
at 10:00 a.m. Please
call us back to confirm.
You're still going to meet
with your divorce attorney?
I don't know.
Maybe.
It turns out we have a therapy session
the exact same time, so I do
have to cancel one of them.
Do I get a vote on which one?
Oh, I already know your
vote, thank you very much,
and don't think I don't know
what you girls were up to
with the whole plumbing thing. You are not
as clever as you think you are.
The point is, we would do anything
to keep this family intact.
And canceling on the divorce attorney
is hardly going to extremes.
I like this place.
What do you think, Mads?
I think there's too many people
trying too hard to be cool,
but I'm not surprised you like it.
Excuse me?
She's just kidding.
You were just kidding, right?
Yes, and you would know, Laurel,
because you have an amazing sense of humor,
an infectious laugh,
great personality...
- Stop.
- Some might say that she is the total package.
Well, don't sell yourself short.
Ugh. Well, thank you, stepbrother.
I'm gonna go to the bar.
Anyone want a drink?
Sure. You want any help?
No. You stay here with
Laurel. I'll get the drinks.
- Well, at least let me buy.
- I really don't want your money.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Did I do something wrong?
Ha! There she goes again.
Hey, I'll just take a water.
If that's cool.
What're you gonna drink, Mads?
A Cosmo? Sex on the beach?
You know what? I'm gonna go home.
He's all yours. You two enjoy your evening.
Um, I'm really sorry.
I have no idea what just happened.
Forget about it.
It's fine.
Let's dance.
Hey.
- Hi.
- You playing today?
No, I was just warming up.
I'm actually headed across town
to have a match with Sutton.
- Seriously?
- Mm-hmm. It was her idea.
I'm sure she has some
sort of ulterior motive.
You guys are gonna just be alone together?
Yes, we're gonna be alone together.
I can't wait to hear
what she has on her mind.
Hey...
how did your test go?
Uh, 73.
I passed.
- That's awesome.
- Yeah, well, I had a pretty good tutor.
You think you might
want to keep helping me with that stuff?
So I can stay a free man.
Yeah, I can do that. Yeah.
All right. Thanks.
Come here.
I'm so happy for you.
Hey...
what's going on here?
Um, I was just thanking her for helping me.
Uh, she tutored me.
Tutoring you?
Yeah. I thought you knew.
Uh, no, actually.
Wait, hold on. So last night...
that's where you had to go?
The test was today.
Wow.
You know what? It doesn't matter.
Thayer...
Alec is getting out?
The judge is signing off on it now.
It's obvious that he was framed.
Of course. By whom?
Well, the call to the waitress
came from Flagstaff, Arizona.
Does that mean anything to you?
Flagstaff, uh, no.
Not at all.
Anyway, he should be out by this evening.
You two should celebrate.
Yes, I thought this day would never come.
Thank you so much, Theresa.
Hey, Ted, I just got
- the most amazing news.
- Really? What?
Alec's being released.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Wow. That...
I didn't expect that.
Neither was I.
Actually.
Well why are you so upset?
I'm scared, Ted.
It's just whenever I've gone to see
Alec in jail, I've gotten the feeling
that he might blame me for his arrest.
Well, that's ridiculous.
You've been more supportive than anyone.
Yeah, well...
you know how he gets.
His temper.
Well, if you are that afraid,
why don't you leave town?
Go back to L.A.?
You don't really mean that?
I thought that...
You thought wrong.
I see.
Well, I can't...
run away, not again.
I mean, everything I love is here.
My roots are here.
My family is here.
You mean Jordan?
Who else would I mean?
Well, I'm, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have fallen
apart on you like this.
And I thank you for being there for me.
Thayer, hi. It's Emma again.
Are you okay?
Please call me back.
Trouble in paradise?
Are you sure nobody's
gonna recognize us here?
Please, anyone worth knowing
wouldn't be caught dead here.
All right.
You serve.
I'm sure you haven't played in a while.
Always so considerate, Emma.
Well, care to make things interesting?
Well, what did you have in mind?
Well, whoever wins
is obviously the best player,
so she should be the one
that plays at regionals.
So that's what this is about.
You want to switch back.
For a few days. Just for regionals.
Unless, of course,
you're too scared, then...
you don't have to.
Oh, I'm not scared. You should be scared,
'cause I will wipe these courts with you.
Feisty, Emma.
Fine. We have a deal?
No, actually, I have some of my own terms.
Whoever loses...
has to stay in the cabin.
For real this time.
Can't step foot out of it. Understand?
Good luck.
May the best sister win.
Oh, I will.
Oh, hey.
I wanted to apologize
for last night. I, um,
- I guess I kind of screwed things up.
- Oh, no.
Leaving was the best
thing you could've done.
I never should've asked you to come along.
Oh, so things worked
out with you and Jordan?
We danced for a while and
talked for, like, hours
about music and bands and life.
He's so sweet and cute.
I think we're gonna go out again next week.
Awesome. Well, I'm really happy for you.
Me, too.
You're the best.
Hey, Thayer. What's up?
What?
It's the first set. 6-2.
You're on fire.
Well,
we can quit if you want.
No, no. I'm just a little off.
Haven't really been getting
much sleep this week.
That's 'cause you're running around town
when you should be up at
that cabin just relaxing.
Yeah, well, it's kind of hard to relax
when Ethan just drops by
in the middle of the night.
Excuse me.
Oh...
after Jordan's party, he stopped by,
and you said it was
fine, so I slept with him.
You're cool with that, right?
Yeah, whatever. He can...
he can do what he wants.
Good, 'cause I totally thought
you'd be, like, really upset.
I'm not.
Obviously.
My serve.
Hey.
The, um, the cam, um...
Chain tensioner.
Yeah, that's the one.
It's making noise again. Do
you mind taking a look at it?
All right.
Sutton's not here, is she?
Why would she be?
Just asking.
Never seem to know where
she's gonna pop up next.
It didn't sound like
your tensioner, but, um,
we're probably gonna check
your plugs out, all right?
What's the deal with you guys anyways?
Look, it's, uh... it's complicated.
Okay, she used to be one person and...
now she's someone else.
And you don't know which one you like more.
- Something like that, yeah.
- Chicks.
Even when you know they're
completely wrong for you,
you still can't stop thinking about them.
Sounds to me like you're
the one with the problem.
Yeah, tell me about it.
But hey, I did see Sutton at the cabin.
She's into you, man.
Like, hardcore into you.
If I were you,
I wouldn't overthink it.
I wouldn't either.
Emma!
Mads?
Time-out.
Thank God I found you.
- Hey.
What's the matter?
Thayer just called to say good-bye.
He's moving back to L.A.
I guess things got pretty ugly
between him and my dad.
Oh, I knew something was wrong with him.
Uh-oh. Drama.
I really wanted to make peace between them,
but he won't listen to me,
and Emma, I think you might be
the only person who can keep him here.
And you've got to hurry
'cause he's packing right now.
Tick-tock.
Congratulations, Sutton.
You win. I forfeit.
Thayer.
You shouldn't have come, Emma.
I don't understand.
What happened with Alec?
He won, like he always does.
He's getting out of jail,
so I can't stay here anymore.
What, he's getting out?
How?
That phone I found exonerated him.
Can you believe that?
Okay...
well, you don't have to leave.
I mean, you could stay someplace else.
Emma, I don't really live here.
I only came back to help you and Sutton,
but every single time I do, it always leads
back to my father, and I
can't, I can't beat him.
It's killing me.
I'm sorry.
You know what, the truth is,
there is nothing left for me here anymore.
What about me?
I'm... I'm sorry I didn't
tell you about Ethan, but...
It's not about that.
I want you to come with me.
Uh... uh... Thayer, I can't do that.
The Mercers are the only
family I've ever known.
I can't leave them right now.
Well, I can't...
I can't stay either.
So then that's it?
Maybe it's for the best.
No, I... I...
Take care of yourself.
See? Good as new.
Guess I'll just get out of your way.
Ted, about that counseling
session on Monday.
I'll be there.
What about your other appointment?
I canceled it.
That's good to hear,
but I hope you brought
your checkbook, ma'am,
'cause you've rung up
quite a hefty plumbing bill.
Chicken parmigiana?
Leftovers.
Looks like everything is getting
back to normal around here.
Yes, your father fixed the drain.
I wasn't talking about the plumbing.
Do you want me to get Laurel?
You know, honestly, I can't figure you out.
One minute, you're hot; the
next minute, you're cold.
Do you even know what you want?
What about you? You're
practically stalking me.
I am not interested, okay?
Oh, is that right?
Yeah.
Well, I love the smell
of freedom in the evening.
The press is at the other entrance,
just like you requested.
Perfect.
There'll be plenty of time
for grandstanding later.
Do you need a lift home?
No.
I've got a stop to make.
Tell my wife I'm coming for her.
You were in Flagstaff?
You were supposed to make
that call from the golf course
so no one would question it.
No, I don't want you to do anything.
Alec will be here any minute.
I know exactly how to handle him.
Hey, baby, I'm home.
Darling, I've missed you so much.
I'll bet.
God, you scare easily.
Well, what do you expect?
There's a murderer out there.
Hey, so, I'm really sorry
about the Thayer thing.
Tough break, but a deal's a deal.
And if you remember, not one
foot outside of the cabin.
Your terms, I recall.
And what if I refuse?
You wouldn't dare.
Try me.
Shoot. I was afraid this would happen.
See, I'm not going to go either, so...
I think we're gonna just have to
tell the family our big secret,
which is going to be really
tough because Kristin,
I don't really know how
she's going to react.
She's very fragile right now.
You're bluffing.
Try me.
Fine.
I'm leaving,
but Ted and Kristin are
making really good progress,
so just promise me that
you'll keep pushing them
in the right direction.
Yes! Of course! They're my parents.
You think I don't want them together?
All right, I'll see you in a couple days.
I left some clean towels
for you at the cabin.
You may need them.
See,
I can be considerate too, Emma.
Good luck at regionals.
I don't need luck.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -