1
00:00:00,960 --> 00:00:03,120
My name is Elena Gilbert, and I'm a vampire.
我叫Elena Gilbert 我是个吸血鬼

2
00:00:03,120 --> 00:00:06,350
I'm learning how to survive, but there are complications.
我正在学习如何生存 但问题层出不穷

3
00:00:06,350 --> 00:00:07,720
You're sired to me, Elena.
你臣服于我 Elena

4
00:00:07,720 --> 00:00:09,020
Everything that you think you feel
你的所想所感

5
00:00:09,020 --> 00:00:10,250
might not even be real.
也许都不是真实的

6
00:00:10,250 --> 00:00:11,420
But there's hope now.
但新的希望出现了

7
00:00:11,420 --> 00:00:12,680
Tell them what the hunter told you the tattoo leads to.
告诉他们 那猎人说纹身有什么作用

8
00:00:12,680 --> 00:00:14,780
He said there was a cure.
他说有吸血鬼解药

9
00:00:14,780 --> 00:00:16,980
Everyone wants it for a different reason.
每个人都想要它 原因各不相同

10
00:00:16,980 --> 00:00:18,220
For revenge...
有的为了复仇...

11
00:00:18,220 --> 00:00:19,950
Ohh!
噢!

12
00:00:19,950 --> 00:00:22,480
To be human and in love...
有的为了成为人类 坠入爱河

13
00:00:22,480 --> 00:00:23,580
For the truth...
有的为了真相...

14
00:00:23,580 --> 00:00:25,620
I'm setting you free, Elena.
我放你走 Elena

15
00:00:25,620 --> 00:00:27,450
And some will stop at nothing to get it.
有人为了获得解药 将不惜一切 

16
00:00:27,450 --> 00:00:29,050
Do it!
快点啊!

17
00:00:35,020 --> 00:00:39,450
Carol Lockwood always said that togetherness,
Carol Lockwood常说

18
00:00:39,450 --> 00:00:41,250
in times of tragedy,
面对悲剧之时

19
00:00:41,250 --> 00:00:44,050
leads to healing.
团结能带来安慰

20
00:00:44,050 --> 00:00:49,380
That one community is stronger than a thousand of its members.
团队的力量 要大于一千个成员各自分散的力量

21
00:00:49,380 --> 00:00:51,980
But how does a community stay strong
可一旦群体失去了它的领袖

22
00:00:51,980 --> 00:00:54,220
after losing its leader?
又将如何保持强大?

23
00:00:54,220 --> 00:00:57,820
And Carol was so much more than just a mayor.
Carol不仅是一位镇长

24
00:00:57,820 --> 00:01:00,780
She was...
她还是...

25
00:01:00,780 --> 00:01:03,620
An open-minded friend...
一个胸襟开阔的朋友...

26
00:01:04,950 --> 00:01:07,580
And a concerned mother,
一名关心孩子的母亲

27
00:01:07,580 --> 00:01:09,950
taken from us too soon
却被一场可怕的事故

28
00:01:09,950 --> 00:01:13,250
by a terrible accident.
瞬间夺去了生命

29
00:01:14,780 --> 00:01:16,820
Screw this.
去你的吧

30
00:01:16,820 --> 00:01:18,850
Tyler.
Tyler啊

31
00:01:18,850 --> 00:01:20,620
Tyler.
喂 Tyler

32
00:01:24,120 --> 00:01:26,380
Please join me in observing
请与我一起为她

33
00:01:26,380 --> 00:01:28,750
a minute of silence in her memory.
默哀一分钟

34
00:01:46,250 --> 00:01:48,450
You ok?
你还好吧?

35
00:01:48,450 --> 00:01:51,080
I'll be right back.
我马上回来

36
00:01:51,080 --> 00:01:54,420
Thank you very much.
感谢大家

37
00:01:54,420 --> 00:01:57,850
In the wake of this tragedy, the town has selected an interim mayor.
悲剧过后 镇里选举出了一位代理镇长

38
00:01:57,850 --> 00:02:00,320
Many of you already know him.
你们大多数人都认识他

39
00:02:00,320 --> 00:02:02,520
Please welcome Mr. Rudy Hopkins.
欢迎Rudy Hopkins先生

40
00:02:08,050 --> 00:02:10,980
Thank you, Sheriff.
谢谢你 警长

41
00:02:10,980 --> 00:02:14,580
Carol Lockwood put this town first,
Carol Lockwood事事以小镇为先

42
00:02:14,580 --> 00:02:17,120
and that's why I'm here to talk to you guys.
这也正是我站在这儿跟大家讲话的原因

43
00:02:17,120 --> 00:02:19,850
You folks...
你们...

44
00:02:35,650 --> 00:02:37,820
April?
April啊?

45
00:02:39,150 --> 00:02:40,820
What's wrong?
怎么了?

46
00:02:40,820 --> 00:02:43,650
Nothing. I'm fine.
没事 我很好

47
00:02:43,650 --> 00:02:45,750
But you're crying.
可是你在哭啊

48
00:02:46,720 --> 00:02:48,320
It's just the whole mayor thing.
只是因为镇长的追悼会

49
00:02:48,320 --> 00:02:50,650
You know, it's bringing up stuff with my dad.
让我回想起我爸爸的一些事情

50
00:02:52,180 --> 00:02:54,320
And I know you're a vampire.
我还知道你是个吸血鬼

51
00:02:55,750 --> 00:02:58,250
Wait. What?
等等 你说什么?

52
00:02:59,750 --> 00:03:03,250
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==-- 
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途 

53
00:03:03,580 --> 00:03:05,250
Oh, was that necessary?
天哪 有必要那么做吗?

54
00:03:08,580 --> 00:03:14,250
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==-- 
协调：。沫
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：小沫也想变菇暖  Harrypotter  秋  Gabriella  末末很辛未  水果哥 
校对：桃茜茜

55
00:03:05,250 --> 00:03:07,850
No, but it was fun.
没必要 不过这样好玩

56
00:03:14,720 --> 00:03:16,320
Hey, you just missed
嘿 你刚错过了

57
00:03:16,320 --> 00:03:17,920
the mandatory all-school assembly.
全校的强制性集会

58
00:03:17,920 --> 00:03:19,150
Well, that's because I'm
那是因为我正在参加

59
00:03:19,150 --> 00:03:21,580
at a mandatory all-alone drinking party.
强制性的独饮派对

60
00:03:21,580 --> 00:03:23,220
Seriously? You decided to go
不是吧? 你现在是

61
00:03:23,220 --> 00:03:25,180
on a ripper bender now?
打算变成开膛手兼酒鬼吗

62
00:03:25,180 --> 00:03:26,980
My brother slept with Elena.
我哥哥和Elena上床了

63
00:03:26,980 --> 00:03:29,020
Kind of puts a little bit of a damper on things.
这有点扫了我的酒兴

64
00:03:29,020 --> 00:03:31,320
First of all, you are not supposed to know that.
首先 这事本不该让你知道

65
00:03:31,320 --> 00:03:35,220
Second of all, Tyler is already spiraling, and he gets priority.
其次 Tyler现在已经茫然无措 该以他为先

66
00:03:35,220 --> 00:03:37,680
His mother just died. What do you expect?
他妈妈才刚死 你想怎么样?

67
00:03:37,680 --> 00:03:40,020
I'm his girlfriend. I expect him to talk to me.
我是他女朋友 我想让他跟我谈谈

68
00:03:40,020 --> 00:03:42,220
But instead he's all angry, and it doesn't help that
可他现在却气昏了头 大家都说

69
00:03:42,220 --> 00:03:44,220
everyone keeps referring to his mother's death as an accident,
他妈妈的死是意外 这样无济于事

70
00:03:44,220 --> 00:03:47,850
which is really just a polite way of saying that she was drunk.
因为这只是委婉地提到他妈妈是酗酒

71
00:03:47,850 --> 00:03:49,480
You think Klaus killed her?
你认为是Klaus杀了她?

72
00:03:49,480 --> 00:03:52,520
Well, I don't think she drowned in a martini glass.
我认为她并不是因为酒喝多了才淹死

73
00:03:52,520 --> 00:03:56,720
Just get it together. I can't do it alone.
你快振作起来 我一个人没法应付

74
00:04:10,480 --> 00:04:11,820
The assembly's over.
集会已经结束了

75
00:04:11,820 --> 00:04:13,650
What the hell's going on?
到底发生什么了?

76
00:04:13,650 --> 00:04:15,320
The school will be empty soon.
学校很快就会空无一人

77
00:04:16,220 --> 00:04:18,980
How many times did you compel me?
你究竟催眠控制了我多少次?

78
00:04:18,980 --> 00:04:21,550
Don't... just don't lie.
不要... 不要对我撒谎

79
00:04:21,550 --> 00:04:23,450
Rebekah says you lie.
Rebekah说你骗了我

80
00:04:23,450 --> 00:04:25,120
Rebekah's not who you think she is, April.
Rebekah并不是你想的那样 April

81
00:04:25,120 --> 00:04:27,980
What, she's not a thousand-year-old original vampire?
怎么 她不是个上千岁的原始家族吸血鬼?

82
00:04:27,980 --> 00:04:31,220
Listen, we can figure this out, OK,
这事我们以后再说 好吗

83
00:04:31,220 --> 00:04:32,950
But we have to get out of here.
但我们必须离开这里

84
00:04:34,420 --> 00:04:37,480
Sorry. Not allowed.
抱歉 我不允许

85
00:04:39,820 --> 00:04:41,280
Why don't you take a seat?
为什么不坐下来呢?

86
00:04:41,280 --> 00:04:43,180
The rest of the class will be here shortly.
班里的其他人马上就来了

87
00:04:47,650 --> 00:04:49,120
First saved message.
第一条保存的信息

88
00:04:49,120 --> 00:04:51,150
Hey, it's me.
嘿 是我

89
00:04:51,150 --> 00:04:54,150
Look, I know why you sent me away.
听着 我知道你为什么要送我走

90
00:04:54,150 --> 00:04:57,120
You think that what I'm feeling for you is because of the sire bond,
你认为我对你的感觉是出于臣服关系

91
00:04:57,120 --> 00:05:00,550
But I hate not being near you.
可我讨厌不在你身边的感觉

92
00:05:07,850 --> 00:05:10,380
Go ahead. Make a move.
来吧 出击

93
00:05:10,380 --> 00:05:13,650
I drove up here to be your wingman, not kick your ass.
我来这里是为了做你的搭档 而不是把你打趴下

94
00:05:19,720 --> 00:05:21,350
Aah! Ok.
啊! 行了

95
00:05:21,350 --> 00:05:23,150
I get it. I get it.
我明白了 我明白了

96
00:05:23,150 --> 00:05:25,480
You're a badass.
你就是坏蛋

97
00:05:29,750 --> 00:05:31,050
You see that?
你看到了吗?

98
00:05:31,050 --> 00:05:33,880
Couldn't miss it. It was in slow motion.
当然看到了 那可是慢动作

99
00:05:33,880 --> 00:05:35,680
Then teach me something useful.
那么就教我些有用的

100
00:05:35,680 --> 00:05:37,320
We've been here for days, and so far
我们已经在这里待了几天了

101
00:05:37,320 --> 00:05:39,250
all you've done is bark orders.
可你只会在这里瞎发令

102
00:05:43,080 --> 00:05:45,050
Ok.
好吧

103
00:05:46,050 --> 00:05:48,020
Take a seat at the bench, quarterback.
在长凳上坐会儿 四分卫

104
00:05:48,020 --> 00:05:49,850
Karate kid wants a shot at the title.
空手道小子想尝尝冠军的滋味

105
00:05:49,850 --> 00:05:52,620
Jeremy, you're not ready for this.
Jeremy 你还没有准备好

106
00:05:54,850 --> 00:05:56,350
Well?
怎么样?

107
00:05:57,950 --> 00:06:02,450
Now, all I have to do is apply a little pressure under your jaw.
现在 我只需要在你颚上使一点劲就够了

108
00:06:06,050 --> 00:06:08,220
Really? Again?
真的? 要再来一次吗?

109
00:06:10,850 --> 00:06:12,350
Ok.
好吧

110
00:06:13,650 --> 00:06:15,650
Double pepperoni 3 days in a row.
双倍意大利腊肠 三天的分量

111
00:06:15,650 --> 00:06:17,580
You guys eat anything else?
你们都不吃别的东西吗?

112
00:06:17,580 --> 00:06:19,650
Why? Are you offering?
怎么? 你们提供吗?

113
00:06:20,680 --> 00:06:22,280
A little something extra, cut off
再给你些小费

114
00:06:22,280 --> 00:06:23,980
the pizza pipeline for a couple days.
这几天就别送披萨过来了

115
00:06:23,980 --> 00:06:26,320
No matter how much they beg, don't come back.
不管他们怎么恳求 都不要回来

116
00:06:27,950 --> 00:06:29,450
Sorry, guys.
打扰了 各位

117
00:06:29,450 --> 00:06:30,750
You're gonna starve us now?
你现在又要饿死我们吗?

118
00:06:30,750 --> 00:06:31,980
If that's what it takes
如果这样可以让你

119
00:06:31,980 --> 00:06:33,220
to make you a hunter.
成为一个猎人的话

120
00:06:33,220 --> 00:06:36,280
Now run around the lake, twice.
现在绕湖跑步 两圈

121
00:06:39,080 --> 00:06:40,850
Keep him company.
跟他一起

122
00:06:40,850 --> 00:06:42,750
I don't have to listen to you.
我可不用听你的

123
00:06:42,750 --> 00:06:44,580
You do if you want to eat.
想吃东西就得听

124
00:06:52,720 --> 00:06:55,420
Being near you, and I miss you, Damon.
接近你 而且我很想你 Damon

125
00:06:55,420 --> 00:06:57,680
I wish you would just let me come to you.
我希望你可以让我来到你身边

126
00:07:02,250 --> 00:07:03,680
What?
干什么?

127
00:07:03,680 --> 00:07:05,150
Guess who.
猜我是谁

128
00:07:05,150 --> 00:07:06,920
I'm back, dagger-free,
我回来了 身上没有匕首

129
00:07:06,920 --> 00:07:08,250
and I'm holding Elena hostage at the high school.
而且抓了Elena在学校当人质

130
00:07:08,250 --> 00:07:09,650
Just thought you should know.
只是觉得应该通知你

131
00:07:09,650 --> 00:07:10,880
Who the hell was dumb enough
是谁那么笨

132
00:07:10,880 --> 00:07:12,080
to pull that dagger out of you?
把匕首从你身上拔下来的?

133
00:07:12,080 --> 00:07:14,120
I'll be asking the questions today.
今天是我来问问题

134
00:07:14,120 --> 00:07:15,620
See ya soon.
一会儿见

135
00:07:26,350 --> 00:07:28,350
I'm only ready to talk to you
你想重回人文社会的话

136
00:07:28,350 --> 00:07:30,820
if you're ready to rejoin civilization.
我才会跟你说话

137
00:07:30,820 --> 00:07:34,820
How would you like to drive the white oak stake through Rebekah's heart?
你愿意把白桦木锥插进Rebekah的心脏吗?

138
00:07:34,820 --> 00:07:39,880
If it means you're not drinking your way through the Mystic Grill, sure.
如果这意味着你不必继续在Grill那里喝闷酒 当然可以

139
00:07:39,880 --> 00:07:41,650
So...
所以...

140
00:07:41,650 --> 00:07:43,680
First speech under your belt.
上任第一次演讲啊

141
00:07:43,680 --> 00:07:46,180
Now for the fun part.
现在说点有趣的

142
00:07:46,180 --> 00:07:48,820
Welcome to the world of careful cover-ups.
欢迎来到仔细掩饰的世界

143
00:07:48,820 --> 00:07:51,620
We've ruled Carol's death as head trauma from a fall.
我们裁定Carol的死是摔伤头部所致

144
00:07:51,620 --> 00:07:53,520
That's the official autopsy.
是官方的验尸结果

145
00:07:53,520 --> 00:07:55,950
She did not go gently, did she?
她死得很痛苦 是吧?

146
00:07:55,950 --> 00:07:57,520
Any leads?
有线索吗?

147
00:07:57,520 --> 00:07:59,220
We have ideas.
有猜想

148
00:07:59,220 --> 00:08:00,380
Let me guess.
让我猜猜

149
00:08:00,380 --> 00:08:02,180
Sharp teeth and bad table manners?
关于尖牙 不守规矩的怪物?

150
00:08:02,180 --> 00:08:04,280
You sure you want this?
你确定你要接手吗?

151
00:08:04,280 --> 00:08:06,950
I mean, six people were offered this job before you.
之前有六个人出于一定的原因

152
00:08:06,950 --> 00:08:08,680
They all said no for a reason.
推掉了这份工作

153
00:08:08,680 --> 00:08:10,520
I'm saying yes for a reason,
我答应也是有原因

154
00:08:10,520 --> 00:08:13,180
and my reason just walked in.
而且我的原因刚来了

155
00:08:14,620 --> 00:08:17,050
- I'll let you know what we find.  - Thank you, Sheriff.
- 有进展我会通知你  - 谢谢你 警长

156
00:08:17,050 --> 00:08:19,620
Hey, Sheriff. Hey, dad.
嘿 警长 嘿 爸爸

157
00:08:19,620 --> 00:08:22,180
Hey. So...
嘿 那么..

158
00:08:22,180 --> 00:08:24,980
far cry from being a traveling pharmaceutical rep.
与你四处云游的医药代表工作很不同吧

159
00:08:24,980 --> 00:08:28,020
I noticed a few of your friends missing from the assembly.
我注意到你的几个朋友追悼会上不见了

160
00:08:28,020 --> 00:08:30,220
So much for mandatory I guess, huh?
估计是被管太多受不了吧?

161
00:08:30,220 --> 00:08:32,220
Dad, stop it.
爸 别说了

162
00:08:32,220 --> 00:08:35,150
You can't come in here and start making rules.
你不能贸然介入就开始制定规矩

163
00:08:35,150 --> 00:08:37,650
I think this town could use a few more rules.
我认为这个镇需要一些规矩

164
00:08:37,650 --> 00:08:40,250
You're forgetting I can help protect the town.
你忘了我可以帮助保护这个镇

165
00:08:40,250 --> 00:08:44,080
I am well aware of your gifts, Bonnie...
我很清楚你的天赋 Bonnie...

166
00:08:44,080 --> 00:08:46,220
But don't forget I'm your father.
但别忘了我是你父亲

167
00:08:46,220 --> 00:08:49,050
That means that I get to protect you.
这意味着我得保护你

168
00:09:36,780 --> 00:09:38,480
Hello, Stefan.
你好啊 Stefan

169
00:09:39,720 --> 00:09:42,380
I'm here. What do you want?
我来了 你想怎样?

170
00:09:42,380 --> 00:09:45,480
The same thing I wanted when you helped make Klaus stab me.
与你帮助Klaus捅我之时的目的一样

171
00:09:45,480 --> 00:09:47,150
The cure.
治愈之法

172
00:09:50,180 --> 00:09:53,150
I hope you're not waiting for Caroline to show up and stake me...
你该不会是在等Caroline出现 然后戳死我吧

173
00:09:54,060 --> 00:09:56,540
Because I already find her.
因为我早就找到她了

174
00:10:07,950 --> 00:10:09,180
Stefan.
是Stefan

175
00:10:09,180 --> 00:10:11,080
Did I say you could move?
我说过你可以动了吗?

176
00:10:13,120 --> 00:10:15,080
Class is in session.
开始上课

177
00:10:15,080 --> 00:10:17,450
You've all been compelled. You know the rules.
你们都被催眠强制过 知道规矩的

178
00:10:17,450 --> 00:10:20,120
Answer my questions honestly,
如实回答我的问题

179
00:10:20,120 --> 00:10:21,950
no disobedience,
不许违抗

180
00:10:21,950 --> 00:10:23,220
no one leaves.
不许离开

181
00:10:23,220 --> 00:10:25,220
April, my sweet, take notes.
Aprill 亲爱的 记下笔记

182
00:10:25,220 --> 00:10:27,120
This is how you get answers in this town.
在这小镇就要用这方法才能找到答案

183
00:10:27,120 --> 00:10:29,480
Let's start with a little quiz.
先来个小测验

184
00:10:29,480 --> 00:10:33,050
In the year 1114, my brother learned... thanks to yours truly...
在1114年 我哥哥得知... 这都多亏了你

185
00:10:33,050 --> 00:10:35,750
about a brotherhood of vampire hunters with tattoos
一群有刺青的吸血鬼猎人

186
00:10:35,750 --> 00:10:37,720
that grew with each kill.
刺青随着杀戮数增长

187
00:10:37,720 --> 00:10:41,120
And these tattoos reveal what? Elena?
这些刺青会显示什么? Elena来答

188
00:10:41,120 --> 00:10:42,620
A map.
一幅地图

189
00:10:42,620 --> 00:10:45,520
Which led to, Caroline?
它能引领至何处 Caroline说?

190
00:10:45,520 --> 00:10:47,050
A cure for vampirism.
治愈吸血鬼的方法

191
00:10:47,050 --> 00:10:49,080
Perfect. We're all caught up now.
很好 我们都了解情况了

192
00:10:49,080 --> 00:10:52,080
Stefan Salvatore, the last time we saw each other,
Stefan Salvatore 我们最后一次见面时

193
00:10:52,080 --> 00:10:55,080
you had a vampire hunter, but in order to decode the map,
你有个吸血鬼猎人 但为了解开地图

194
00:10:55,080 --> 00:10:57,420
you needed the location of the hunter's sword,
你需要猎人之剑的地址

195
00:10:57,420 --> 00:11:01,820
which you got out of me using some very dirty tricks.
而你对我用了卑鄙的手段 以此获得

196
00:11:01,820 --> 00:11:04,450
Assuming you found the sword, you must have found the cure,
假设你找到了剑 你肯定也找到了治愈方法

197
00:11:04,450 --> 00:11:06,880
and yet you're all still vampires,
但你们都还是吸血鬼

198
00:11:06,880 --> 00:11:08,620
which means something went wrong.
也就是说这中间出岔子了

199
00:11:08,620 --> 00:11:09,920
What are you doing?
你在干嘛?

200
00:11:09,920 --> 00:11:12,980
You asked me to take notes.
你让我记笔记的

201
00:11:12,980 --> 00:11:14,650
I wasn't being literal, darling.
我只是说说而已 亲爱的

202
00:11:14,650 --> 00:11:16,680
But now that you mention it, a flow chart would be nice,
但既然你说到了 流程图很不错

203
00:11:16,680 --> 00:11:19,680
which means index cards and push pins. Go fetch.
这需要索引卡和图钉 去拿吧

204
00:11:21,180 --> 00:11:22,850
You're wasting your time.
你在浪费时间

205
00:11:22,850 --> 00:11:24,780
We don't know anything.
我们什么都不知道

206
00:11:24,780 --> 00:11:26,820
So you just gave up?
所以你们就放弃了?

207
00:11:26,820 --> 00:11:29,520
I thought you'd do anything to save Elena,
我以为你会不顾一切救Elena呢

208
00:11:29,520 --> 00:11:32,150
even if it meant taking the cure yourself
即使要亲自服下解药

209
00:11:32,150 --> 00:11:34,320
so you could grow old and die with her.
以便和她长相厮守

210
00:11:37,650 --> 00:11:40,220
Why do you look so surprised?
你们怎么这么惊讶?

211
00:11:45,380 --> 00:11:47,350
I'm missing something. What is it?
我错过了什么 怎么了?

212
00:11:49,220 --> 00:11:51,420
They broke up, ok?
他们分手了 行了吧?

213
00:11:52,920 --> 00:11:54,250
Now let us go.
现在放我们走吧

214
00:11:54,250 --> 00:11:56,050
Broke up?
分手了?

215
00:11:57,380 --> 00:11:59,180
Wait. I'm confused.
慢着 我有点糊涂了

216
00:11:59,180 --> 00:12:03,050
I thought Elena was your epic love, Stefan.
我以为Elena是你史诗般的爱呢 Stefan

217
00:12:05,050 --> 00:12:07,080
I asked you what happened,
我在问你发生了什么

218
00:12:07,080 --> 00:12:09,080
and you have to tell me.
你必须告诉我

219
00:12:09,080 --> 00:12:11,580
She slept with Damon.
她和Damon上床了

220
00:12:28,720 --> 00:12:30,280
Good.
很好

221
00:12:31,350 --> 00:12:33,020
Now...
现在...

222
00:12:34,480 --> 00:12:37,320
Now do it like your life depends on it 'cause it does.
拼出全力吧 就如同生死相依 也确实如此

223
00:12:37,320 --> 00:12:38,850
Don't act like you care about my life.
别装得好像你很关心我似的

224
00:12:38,850 --> 00:12:40,680
You care about the hunter's mark and curing Elena
你关心的是猎人印记和Elena的解药

225
00:12:40,680 --> 00:12:42,650
So she's not sired to your ass.
这样 她就不再臣服与你了

226
00:12:42,650 --> 00:12:45,020
Both require you to be alive,
但这都需要你活着

227
00:12:45,020 --> 00:12:49,720
which is why I've updated our relationship status to "it's complicated."
所以我认为我们的关系现状是 "错综复杂"

228
00:12:52,020 --> 00:12:55,550
You talked to her at all? Elena?
你跟Elena通话了吗?

229
00:12:55,550 --> 00:12:57,280
Maybe.
可能吧

230
00:12:57,280 --> 00:13:00,250
Why? Run out of voicemails to listen to?
怎么了? 语音信息都听完了?

231
00:13:00,250 --> 00:13:03,350
I'm sorry. Did I interrupt play time?
不好意思 我打扰你们玩乐了吗

232
00:13:03,350 --> 00:13:04,520
What the hell are you doing here?
你在这干嘛?

233
00:13:04,520 --> 00:13:05,680
I'm simply appreciating
我只是单纯地在欣赏

234
00:13:05,680 --> 00:13:07,680
the sights and smells of nature,
大自然的风光

235
00:13:07,680 --> 00:13:09,520
neither of which presently include
但并没有发现

236
00:13:09,520 --> 00:13:10,920
rotting vampire flesh,
腐烂的吸血鬼尸体

237
00:13:10,920 --> 00:13:13,280
so I'm a bit concerned.
这让我有些担心

238
00:13:13,280 --> 00:13:15,320
How many vampires has he killed?
他杀了几个吸血鬼了?

239
00:13:15,320 --> 00:13:18,720
If we throw Jeremy out into the world right now, he's chum.
如果我们现在把Jeremy推出去 他就是个鱼饵

240
00:13:18,720 --> 00:13:21,120
Now, see, that's not a number.
但这并不是数字啊

241
00:13:21,120 --> 00:13:23,150
12... that's a number.
比如12... 这才算

242
00:13:23,150 --> 00:13:24,380
That's how many of my hybrids
这个数字代表我用剑屠杀的

243
00:13:24,380 --> 00:13:26,380
I slaughtered with my sword.
混种数量

244
00:13:26,380 --> 00:13:28,550
3... that's how many days it took
而3... 则是你弟弟作为知情人士

245
00:13:28,550 --> 00:13:30,250
to quell the urge to kill your brother, after
却看着我走进死亡陷阱 花了我

246
00:13:30,250 --> 00:13:33,280
he knowingly watched as I walked into a death trap.
3天时间 才平息掉要杀掉他的冲动

247
00:13:33,280 --> 00:13:34,620
One...
而1...

248
00:13:34,620 --> 00:13:37,620
That's the number of purposes you serve.
你们只有1个目的

249
00:13:37,620 --> 00:13:41,480
You are here to grow Jeremy's mark,
你来这是要让Jeremy的印记增长

250
00:13:41,480 --> 00:13:44,450
So I ask again...
我再问一遍...

251
00:13:44,450 --> 00:13:47,950
how many vampires has he killed since he's been here?
从他到这后 他杀了几个吸血鬼?

252
00:13:47,950 --> 00:13:50,080
Zero.
0个

253
00:13:50,080 --> 00:13:52,680
That's a pity.
真遗憾

254
00:13:53,820 --> 00:13:55,780
I'm going to need that cure
我早晚都要

255
00:13:55,780 --> 00:13:58,120
sooner rather than later,
得到解药

256
00:13:58,120 --> 00:14:01,150
hybrid shortage and all.
因为现在混种不多了

257
00:14:01,150 --> 00:14:03,320
How can I help?
我能帮忙吗?

258
00:14:03,320 --> 00:14:08,480
You know... now that you mention it,
既然你提出来了

259
00:14:08,480 --> 00:14:10,680
Jeremy... watch and learn.
Jeremy... 学着点

260
00:14:15,850 --> 00:14:18,350
That's for Carol Lockwood.
这两枪是为了Carol Lockwood报仇

261
00:14:22,980 --> 00:14:26,680
So, vampire Elena is a trollop who likes bad boys,
吸血鬼Elena是个喜欢坏小子的荡妇

262
00:14:26,680 --> 00:14:28,780
which explains why Stefan reeks of alcohol.
这解释了为什么Stefan一身酒气

263
00:14:28,780 --> 00:14:34,020
But what it doesn't explain is why sweet, loving,
但这不能解释为什么甜美 可爱

264
00:14:34,020 --> 00:14:39,250
innocent Elena could be so heartless towards Stefan.
纯真的Elena 为何对Stefan如此无情

265
00:14:43,050 --> 00:14:46,250
How could she hurt you like that? Answer, please.
她是怎么伤害你的? 请作答

266
00:14:47,280 --> 00:14:48,720
She didn't know it at the time,
她当时并不知道

267
00:14:48,720 --> 00:14:50,580
but she was sired to Damon.
她臣服于Damon

268
00:14:53,250 --> 00:14:56,320
A sire bond. Fascinating.
臣服关系 有意思

269
00:14:56,320 --> 00:14:58,480
And what do you think about that, Elena?
对此你怎么想呢 Elena?

270
00:14:58,480 --> 00:15:01,850
I think you're sad and bored
我认为你无聊并且可悲

271
00:15:01,850 --> 00:15:04,520
and in desperate need of a hobby.
并且你急需一个业余爱好

272
00:15:04,520 --> 00:15:07,850
You're hiding something. 'Fess up.
你隐瞒了什么 坦白吧

273
00:15:07,850 --> 00:15:11,250
I didn't sleep with Damon because of his sire bond.
我跟Damon上床不是因为臣服关系

274
00:15:11,250 --> 00:15:13,780
I slept with Damon because I'm in love with him.
我跟Damon上床是因为我爱他

275
00:15:26,080 --> 00:15:29,180
What does any of this have to do with the stupid cure?
这些跟找解药有什么关系啊?

276
00:15:30,580 --> 00:15:33,080
You're right. We got off the point.
你说的对 我们跑题了

277
00:15:33,080 --> 00:15:36,080
Stefan, how do I find the cure?
Stefan 我怎么才能找到解药呢?

278
00:15:36,080 --> 00:15:39,420
Unless you'd rather talk about Damon and Elena all day.
除非你愿意一直讨论Damon和Elena

279
00:15:39,420 --> 00:15:41,680
There's a professor. He knows where the cure is.
有个教授 他知道解药在哪

280
00:15:41,680 --> 00:15:45,650
Thank you. And, uh, where do I find this professor?
谢谢 那我去哪找这位教授?

281
00:15:45,650 --> 00:15:49,320
Oh, and so now I'm "gifted"? He hates my witch heritage.
现在我成了有"天赋"的人? 他讨厌我女巫的身份

282
00:15:49,320 --> 00:15:51,220
That's why he travels all the time. He can't handle it.
所以他一直旅行 他接受不了

283
00:15:51,220 --> 00:15:53,950
And suddenly he wants to be a protective father?
突然间他想做一个好好爸爸?

284
00:15:53,950 --> 00:15:55,920
No. Not like this.
这可不行

285
00:15:55,920 --> 00:15:58,050
Come on. Distract me.
拜托 分散我的注意力

286
00:15:58,050 --> 00:16:00,020
Isn't there some...
是不是有什么...

287
00:16:00,020 --> 00:16:03,520
magic therapy thing you haven't shown me yet?
魔法疗程之类的你还没有给我展示?

288
00:16:03,520 --> 00:16:05,280
Listen, Bonnie, I hate to tell you this...
听着 Bonnie 我讨厌这么告诉你...

289
00:16:05,280 --> 00:16:06,850
actually, you know what? I take that back.
其实 你知道吗? 我收回刚才那话

290
00:16:06,850 --> 00:16:09,250
I'm proud to tell you this.
我很骄傲地告诉你

291
00:16:09,250 --> 00:16:10,680
You don't need my help anymore.
你再也不需要我的帮助了

292
00:16:10,680 --> 00:16:12,850
In fact...
其实

293
00:16:17,620 --> 00:16:20,680
I was hoping to present this with a cupcake or something.
我本想着把这东西跟蛋糕一块儿给你送上

294
00:16:24,020 --> 00:16:25,680
Happy graduation.
毕业快乐

295
00:16:30,620 --> 00:16:31,780
It's beautiful.
真漂亮

296
00:16:31,780 --> 00:16:34,020
It's human bone.
是人骨

297
00:16:34,020 --> 00:16:36,280
Legend says it was worn
传说它曾戴在

298
00:16:36,280 --> 00:16:38,620
by the 2,000-year-old witch Qetsiyah,
2000岁的女巫Qetsiyah身上

299
00:16:38,620 --> 00:16:40,480
Who drew on it...
你能从这上面...

300
00:16:40,480 --> 00:16:42,120
for strength.
吸取能量

301
00:16:42,120 --> 00:16:46,120
Bonnie, you have come so far so fast.
Bonnie 你学得很快很好

302
00:16:46,120 --> 00:16:48,120
If you trust my opinion,
如果你信我的话

303
00:16:48,120 --> 00:16:50,350
your magic is exactly where it needs to be.
你的魔力会用得其所的

304
00:16:51,350 --> 00:16:53,320
Does this mean I have to go home?
这意味着我得回家了吗?

305
00:16:53,320 --> 00:16:56,150
It means I got a stack of papers I got to grade by tomorrow.
这意味着我有一摞卷子在明天之前要批改

306
00:16:56,150 --> 00:16:57,620
I can take a hint.
我懂得

307
00:17:00,280 --> 00:17:02,220
Thanks, Shane.
谢了 Shane

308
00:17:17,080 --> 00:17:19,020
Oh, my God.
天啊

309
00:17:19,020 --> 00:17:20,480
Kol.
是Kol

310
00:17:22,220 --> 00:17:24,220
Shane?
Shane在哪?

311
00:17:46,920 --> 00:17:48,620
I told you I don't want to talk.
我说了 我现在不想跟你谈

312
00:17:48,620 --> 00:17:50,920
I heard. You're keeping all that rage
我听到了 你把所有的怒气

313
00:17:50,920 --> 00:17:52,920
bottled up inside.
都憋在心里

314
00:17:52,920 --> 00:17:54,680
Caroline's worried sick about you.
Caroline很担心你

315
00:17:54,680 --> 00:17:55,920
Rebekah?
Rebakah吗?

316
00:17:55,920 --> 00:17:57,480
Hello, Tyler.
你好 Tyler

317
00:17:57,480 --> 00:18:00,480
I heard my brother made a real mess of your life.
我听说我哥哥把你的生活都搅乱了

318
00:18:00,480 --> 00:18:04,250
Believe me, I can relate. You have my condolences.
相信我 我明白 向你表示慰问

319
00:18:04,250 --> 00:18:07,950
In fact, why don't you come down to the high school so you can accept them in person?
不如你亲自来学校一趟 当面接受我的慰问吧?

320
00:18:07,950 --> 00:18:09,180
And why would I do that?
我为什么要那么做?

321
00:18:09,180 --> 00:18:11,220
Because I have your girlfriend.
因为你女朋友在我手上

322
00:18:11,220 --> 00:18:14,780
Maybe you have a better shot at saving her than you did your mother.
你失去了你妈妈 但或许你还可以救她

323
00:18:21,950 --> 00:18:24,620
Sister...
妹妹...

324
00:18:24,620 --> 00:18:25,950
Look at this.
看看

325
00:18:25,950 --> 00:18:27,950
You're even worse than Klaus.
你比Klaus还坏

326
00:18:27,950 --> 00:18:29,750
Kol. Finally.
Kol 终于来了

327
00:18:29,750 --> 00:18:31,280
Did you bring me what I asked for?
把我要的带来了吗?

328
00:18:37,720 --> 00:18:39,620
You must be Shane.
你就是Shane

329
00:18:49,120 --> 00:18:51,480
If you're here for payback, go for it.
如果你是来报复的 放马过来吧

330
00:18:51,480 --> 00:18:54,650
But you'll be stuck baby-sitting the little hunter that could.
不过这样你就得给这个小猎人当保姆了

331
00:18:54,650 --> 00:18:56,950
You know...
知道吗...

332
00:18:56,950 --> 00:19:01,080
If you adjust your angle a little bit, you'll find a sharper edge.
你稍微调整一下角度 会削得更尖

333
00:19:02,520 --> 00:19:05,680
I know how to whittle. Thanks.
我知道怎么削木头 多谢了

334
00:19:05,680 --> 00:19:07,650
Now I know why those hybrids hated you.
我现在理解为什么那些混种恨你了

335
00:19:07,650 --> 00:19:08,980
You are annoying.
你真够烦人的

336
00:19:08,980 --> 00:19:11,150
Actually, I'm just perplexed
事实上 我只是困惑于

337
00:19:11,150 --> 00:19:13,820
as to why Jeremy hasn't killed any vampires.
为什么Jeremy还没杀掉一个吸血鬼

338
00:19:13,820 --> 00:19:15,420
Darwinism, Klaus.
他得进化 Klaus

339
00:19:15,420 --> 00:19:17,020
He needs to be able to protect himself
他要先学会保护自己

340
00:19:17,020 --> 00:19:19,650
before we hunt down his first vampire nest.
才能让他去开杀戒

341
00:19:19,650 --> 00:19:21,850
And here was I, thinking you were the fun brother.
我还以为你这哥哥会相对风趣

342
00:19:21,850 --> 00:19:23,820
Well, let's play a little game, shall we?
好吧 我们玩个游戏吧?

343
00:19:23,820 --> 00:19:25,780
Jeremy needs more victims, and there's a whole town of people
Jeremy需要更多的受害者 正好有一个小镇的居民

344
00:19:25,780 --> 00:19:29,920
down the road just waiting to be turned into vampires for the slaughter.
等着变成吸血鬼 就为了被屠杀

345
00:19:29,920 --> 00:19:31,950
You don't think that occurred to me, Klaus?
你以为我没想过吗 Klaus?

346
00:19:31,950 --> 00:19:33,980
The tragedy is, Damon,
悲哀的是 Damon

347
00:19:33,980 --> 00:19:36,850
it did occur to you, yet you chose to ignore it.
你想到了 却选择忽略它

348
00:19:36,850 --> 00:19:39,850
And my guess is you did it to impress Elena.
我猜你是为了讨好Elena

349
00:19:39,850 --> 00:19:43,880
Somehow, to honor her, you'll find a way to spare innocent lives
为了她 你总会找到一个既能赦免无辜的性命

350
00:19:43,880 --> 00:19:46,620
and walk Jeremy down the moral high road.
又能让Jeremy站在道德高地

351
00:19:48,420 --> 00:19:51,880
That's why I've already made the necessary corrections.
所以我做了一些必要的修正

352
00:19:53,720 --> 00:19:55,920
What did you do?
你做了什么?

353
00:20:01,920 --> 00:20:03,820
Don't tell me he ordered another pizza.
他不会又订了披萨吧

354
00:20:03,820 --> 00:20:05,420
No, I'm just an idiot.
没有 是我笨

355
00:20:05,420 --> 00:20:07,780
I ran out of gas and my phone's dead.
我的车没油了 手机也没电了

356
00:20:07,780 --> 00:20:09,620
- Think I could use yours?  - Yeah, come on in.
- 能借用你的吗?  - 当然 进来吧

357
00:20:09,620 --> 00:20:11,280
I'll run upstairs and grab my cell.
我上楼拿手机

358
00:20:15,620 --> 00:20:17,980
What the hell?
怎么搞的

359
00:20:17,980 --> 00:20:19,880
What are you doing here?
你在这里干什么?

360
00:20:19,880 --> 00:20:21,450
Car drama.
车出了故障

361
00:20:21,450 --> 00:20:23,380
Your friend just went to go get his phone.
你朋友上去拿手机了

362
00:20:23,380 --> 00:20:24,780
Well, I'm about to go take a shower,
哦 我刚要去洗澡

363
00:20:24,780 --> 00:20:27,280
but you're more than welcome to wait inside.
不过你可以进来等

364
00:20:34,120 --> 00:20:35,980
Thanks.
谢了

365
00:20:41,820 --> 00:20:43,220
Kol...
你是Kol...

366
00:20:43,220 --> 00:20:45,550
and Rebekah Mikaelson, two members of
和Rebekah Mikaelson 两位

367
00:20:45,550 --> 00:20:48,480
the original vampire family. This is such a trip.
吸血鬼原始家族成员 真是不虚此行

368
00:20:49,520 --> 00:20:51,350
Where's the cure?
治愈之法在哪?

369
00:20:51,350 --> 00:20:54,120
Compulsion won't work.
强制催眠没有用的

370
00:20:54,120 --> 00:20:56,720
It's a little trick I picked up in Tibet.
我在西藏学了个小窍门

371
00:20:56,720 --> 00:21:01,080
Right. Well, we'll just have to do this the old-fashioned way.
原来如此 看来只能用传统的方法了

372
00:21:01,080 --> 00:21:04,120
Beat him until he tells you where to find it.
打到他说为止

373
00:21:08,520 --> 00:21:11,150
Still glued to your seats?
屁股还得粘在椅子上?

374
00:21:11,150 --> 00:21:13,520
Ooh, it's thick with tension in here.
哦 这里的气氛好僵

375
00:21:14,520 --> 00:21:16,550
Let's spice things up a bit.
我们玩点刺激的吧

376
00:21:16,550 --> 00:21:18,950
Elena, truth or dare?
Elena 真心话大冒险?

377
00:21:18,950 --> 00:21:21,080
We're done playing your stupid games, Rebekah.
我们玩够你那愚蠢的游戏了 Rebekah

378
00:21:21,080 --> 00:21:23,180
Truth or dare, Elena?
真心话还是大冒险 Elena?

379
00:21:23,180 --> 00:21:25,220
You're compelled. Answer.
你被强制了 回答我

380
00:21:25,220 --> 00:21:26,820
Dare.
大冒险

381
00:21:27,820 --> 00:21:29,680
I dare you to tell Stefan
我赌你不敢把你和Damon的

382
00:21:29,680 --> 00:21:31,150
the truth about Damon.
真相告诉Stefan

383
00:21:31,150 --> 00:21:32,850
Seriously?
开什么玩笑?

384
00:21:37,450 --> 00:21:39,820
Being with Damon makes me happy.
和Damon在一起让我很开心

385
00:21:39,820 --> 00:21:41,380
Makes you happy?
让你很开心?

386
00:21:41,380 --> 00:21:43,650
Clowns make you happy, Elena.
小丑也能让你开心 Elena

387
00:21:43,650 --> 00:21:45,250
Dig a little deeper.
讲得深入点

388
00:21:45,250 --> 00:21:48,050
When I'm with him...
当我和他在一起...

389
00:21:49,480 --> 00:21:53,520
it feels unpredictable, like...
感觉难以预料 就像...

390
00:21:53,520 --> 00:21:55,750
like I'm free.
就像我自由了

391
00:21:57,720 --> 00:22:00,080
And how do you feel when you're with Stefan?
那和Stefan在一起是什么感觉?

392
00:22:00,080 --> 00:22:01,850
Stop.
别说了

393
00:22:01,850 --> 00:22:03,880
She can't. She's compelled.
不可能 她被强制了

394
00:22:03,880 --> 00:22:07,720
Lately, I feel like I'm a project,
最近 我感觉自己像一个工程

395
00:22:07,720 --> 00:22:12,080
like I'm a problem that needs to be fixed.
像是一件急需解决的麻烦事

396
00:22:13,120 --> 00:22:15,520
I think I make him sad,
我觉得我让他很难过

397
00:22:15,520 --> 00:22:17,620
and I can't be with someone like that
我无法和这样的他在一起

398
00:22:17,620 --> 00:22:20,180
because...
因为...

399
00:22:20,180 --> 00:22:24,450
when he looks at me, all he sees is a broken toy.
他看着我就像是看到个破损的玩偶

400
00:22:31,080 --> 00:22:33,350
Do you still love Stefan?
你还爱Stefan吗?

401
00:22:34,780 --> 00:22:36,550
Yes.
是

402
00:22:38,220 --> 00:22:41,220
Are you still in love with Stefan?
你还爱着Stefan吗?

403
00:22:42,450 --> 00:22:43,920
No.
不

404
00:22:49,880 --> 00:22:52,220
Did that hurt,
伤心吗

405
00:22:52,220 --> 00:22:54,650
having someone you love drive a dagger through your heart?
被你深爱的人 往你胸口插了一把?

406
00:22:54,650 --> 00:22:55,950
Go to hell.
去死吧

407
00:22:55,950 --> 00:22:59,620
Did... that... hurt?
伤... 心... 吗?

408
00:23:04,220 --> 00:23:05,780
Yes.
是

409
00:23:08,980 --> 00:23:13,180
Welcome to the last 900 years of my life.
欢迎体验我过去900年的生命

410
00:23:18,080 --> 00:23:21,580
Ah, good, you're here. It was just getting depressing.
哦 很好 你来了 气氛刚变得凝重了

411
00:23:21,580 --> 00:23:23,080
What the hell is going on?
到底这是在搞什么?

412
00:23:23,080 --> 00:23:25,450
Listen to the rules carefully.
听清楚规矩

413
00:23:25,450 --> 00:23:28,550
Stay in the building. No vamp-running in the hallways.
留在这座楼里 不能在大厅里乱跑

414
00:23:28,550 --> 00:23:29,980
Vamp-running from what?
为什么要乱跑?

415
00:23:34,450 --> 00:23:36,250
- Turn.  - What?
- 变身  - 什么?

416
00:23:36,250 --> 00:23:38,150
You can't. He'll lose control.
不行 他会失控的

417
00:23:38,150 --> 00:23:39,580
That's the whole point.
就是要他失控

418
00:23:39,580 --> 00:23:41,180
I've exhausted all your knowledge.
你们知道的 我都问完了

419
00:23:41,180 --> 00:23:43,480
Now I have the professor to help me find the cure,
现在我有了教授帮我找到治愈之法

420
00:23:43,480 --> 00:23:45,080
you're just competition.
你们就成了我的对手

421
00:23:45,080 --> 00:23:47,980
Whoever finds it first gets to decide what to do with it:
谁先找到它就有权决定用它做什么

422
00:23:47,980 --> 00:23:51,820
use it, share it, destroy it, save it...
使用 分享 毁灭 保存...

423
00:23:51,820 --> 00:23:53,450
I want that to be me.
我要得到决定权

424
00:23:53,450 --> 00:23:55,520
But if I turn, I'll kill them.
如果我变身 会杀死他们的

425
00:23:56,780 --> 00:23:58,680
Yes, you will.
是的 没错

426
00:24:00,930 --> 00:24:02,100
Turn!
变身!

427
00:24:22,020 --> 00:24:24,220
Did you find your phone?
找到手机了吗?

428
00:24:28,280 --> 00:24:29,780
Get off!
滚开!

429
00:24:29,780 --> 00:24:31,250
Get off!
滚开!

430
00:24:52,920 --> 00:24:54,620
Bonnie?
Bonnie怎么来了?

431
00:24:54,620 --> 00:24:55,920
How did you know everyone was here?
你怎么知道大家在这?

432
00:24:55,920 --> 00:24:57,920
Who's everyone? I came to find Shane.
大家是谁? 我来找Shane

433
00:24:57,920 --> 00:25:01,550
Did you do a GPS magic locator spell or something?
你是用了什么魔法定位咒语吗?

434
00:25:01,550 --> 00:25:03,550
Rebekah told me that you're a witch.
Rebekah告诉我你是个女巫

435
00:25:03,550 --> 00:25:05,720
Rebekah? What the hell is going on?
Rebekah? 到底发生了什么?

436
00:25:05,720 --> 00:25:08,350
Rebekah has Stefan, Elena, and Caroline compelled.
Rebekah把Stefan Elena和Caroline强制了

437
00:25:08,350 --> 00:25:11,220
She's getting them to actually tell the truth for a change.
她以此逼他们说出真话

438
00:25:11,220 --> 00:25:13,220
What?
怎么了?

439
00:25:13,220 --> 00:25:14,780
Shane can't be compelled.
Shane不能被强制

440
00:25:14,780 --> 00:25:17,950
She'll have him torture him to find out what he knows.
为了知道答案 她会折磨死他的

441
00:25:17,950 --> 00:25:20,380
- What are you looking for?  - I need salt.
- 你在找什么?  - 我需要盐

442
00:25:20,380 --> 00:25:22,750
I think I just saw some.
我刚才有看到一些

443
00:25:29,150 --> 00:25:30,950
What are you doing?
你在做什么?

444
00:25:30,950 --> 00:25:32,550
If this pendant will connect me to Shane,
如果这个吊坠能把我和Shane连通

445
00:25:32,550 --> 00:25:34,580
then I can do a protection spell.
那我就能施咒保护他

446
00:25:53,680 --> 00:25:55,850
Where is the cure?
治愈方法在哪?

447
00:25:58,980 --> 00:26:00,180
Oh!
哦!

448
00:26:00,180 --> 00:26:02,150
Where is the cure?
治愈方法在哪?

449
00:26:14,450 --> 00:26:17,020
You're human. Why do you want it anyway?
你是人 要治愈方法干嘛?

450
00:26:17,020 --> 00:26:18,250
That's the beauty of this.
这正是妙处所在

451
00:26:18,250 --> 00:26:19,680
You can have it. I just want Silas.
你可以拥有治愈方法 我只想要Silas

452
00:26:19,680 --> 00:26:22,280
No.
不

453
00:26:23,780 --> 00:26:25,950
What do you know about Silas?
关于Silas 你都知道什么?

454
00:26:25,950 --> 00:26:27,920
He's the world's first immortal being,
他是世界上第一个不死之人

455
00:26:27,920 --> 00:26:30,550
who just happens to be imprisoned with the cure,
碰巧和治愈方法囚禁在一起

456
00:26:30,550 --> 00:26:33,020
and I want to free him.
我想解救他

457
00:26:33,020 --> 00:26:34,420
No!
不!

458
00:26:39,250 --> 00:26:40,750
April?
April啊?

459
00:26:42,920 --> 00:26:44,380
What's happening?
你怎么了?

460
00:26:52,750 --> 00:26:54,550
Stop!
停手!

461
00:27:02,780 --> 00:27:04,050
He's of no use dead.
他死了就没用了

462
00:27:04,050 --> 00:27:05,320
Did you not hear what he said?
你没听见他说的吗?

463
00:27:05,320 --> 00:27:07,220
Silas will kill us all, sister.
Silas会把我们全都杀掉的 妹妹

464
00:27:07,220 --> 00:27:10,450
Silas does not exist. He is a fairy tale
Silas根本不存在 他是童话故事里

465
00:27:10,450 --> 00:27:13,020
made up to scare children into eating their vegetables.
编出来吓唬小孩多吃蔬菜的

466
00:27:13,020 --> 00:27:15,280
Silas is very real.
Silas真的存在

467
00:27:17,020 --> 00:27:18,980
I know where he's buried,
我知道他埋在哪里

468
00:27:18,980 --> 00:27:21,220
and soon I'll have the spell that wakes him.
很快我就能拿到唤醒他的咒语了

469
00:27:21,220 --> 00:27:23,050
Wait a second. You're lying.
等一下 你在说谎

470
00:27:23,050 --> 00:27:24,880
You can't get to him without his...
你找不到他 因为你没有他的...

471
00:27:24,880 --> 00:27:26,420
Tombstone?
墓碑?

472
00:27:26,420 --> 00:27:28,950
Dozens to die in a blood sacrifice?
用十二个人完成血祭?

473
00:27:28,950 --> 00:27:30,680
Believe me, I know.
我都知道

474
00:27:30,680 --> 00:27:32,450
I've done it.
而且已经做完了

475
00:27:32,450 --> 00:27:35,680
Those massacres are a pain to engineer.
策划那场大屠杀很痛苦

476
00:27:35,680 --> 00:27:39,120
You're the one who got the council blown up.
是你把创始人理事会的人炸死的

477
00:27:39,120 --> 00:27:41,920
It was a noble sacrifice...
这是一场崇高的献祭...

478
00:27:41,920 --> 00:27:44,750
and temporary.
也是暂时的

479
00:27:44,750 --> 00:27:47,220
Because once I raise Silas,
因为一旦我唤醒Silas

480
00:27:47,220 --> 00:27:49,620
Silas will raise the dead.
Silas就会唤醒那些死去的人

481
00:27:49,620 --> 00:27:53,320
He will bring back every last soul
他会让每一个

482
00:27:53,320 --> 00:27:56,050
who died on his behalf.
因他而死的人复活

483
00:27:56,050 --> 00:27:57,450
No!
不!

484
00:28:03,250 --> 00:28:05,520
April, oh, my god!
April 哦 天啊!

485
00:28:22,650 --> 00:28:24,780
Wait. I can fight it.
等等 我能忍住

486
00:28:42,850 --> 00:28:45,380
Aah! Get out of here!
啊! 快出去!

487
00:28:45,380 --> 00:28:47,650
Go.
快走

488
00:28:49,650 --> 00:28:52,850
That door's not gonna hold him.
那扇门挡不住他

489
00:29:50,180 --> 00:29:51,350
You should be thanking me.
你该感谢我

490
00:29:51,350 --> 00:29:53,550
You killed my only chance at finding the cure.
你杀了唯一能帮我找到治愈方法的人

491
00:29:53,550 --> 00:29:56,080
Silas on the loose would be hell on earth,
Silas恢复自由 全世界都得遭殃

492
00:29:56,080 --> 00:29:58,850
and frankly, sister...
而且坦白地讲 妹妹...

493
00:29:58,850 --> 00:30:01,420
I don't think you could handle it.
我觉得你根本应付不了

494
00:30:01,420 --> 00:30:02,550
How did you get that?
你怎么拿到的?

495
00:30:02,550 --> 00:30:04,650
Way too easily.
太简单了

496
00:30:41,180 --> 00:30:43,150
Bonnie.
是Bonnie

497
00:30:43,150 --> 00:30:45,780
Help! Someone help!
来人啊! 快来人!

498
00:30:47,550 --> 00:30:48,680
Bonnie, what's going on?
Bonnie 怎么了?

499
00:30:48,680 --> 00:30:49,680
She needs help.
她需要帮助

500
00:30:49,680 --> 00:30:51,180
What happened?
发生了什么?

501
00:30:51,180 --> 00:30:52,880
I did a protection spell, but it accidentally linked
我施了个保护咒 但却不小心

502
00:30:52,880 --> 00:30:54,180
Shane to April.
把Shane和April连通了

503
00:30:54,180 --> 00:30:55,620
And you couldn't control it?
你控制不了吗?

504
00:30:55,620 --> 00:30:57,150
I didn't even know I was doing it.
我根本不知道我把他们连通了

505
00:30:57,150 --> 00:30:58,780
Usually I feel pain or I bleed, but this time I just
以前我会感到痛或流血 但这次

506
00:30:58,780 --> 00:31:00,850
felt more power.
我只感觉更加强大

507
00:31:03,680 --> 00:31:05,080
It's ok. It's ok.
没事的 没事的

508
00:31:05,080 --> 00:31:08,750
You're ok. You're ok. You're ok. Ok.
你没事了 没事了 没事了 好了

509
00:31:08,750 --> 00:31:10,950
Bonnie, get her out of the school.
Bonnie 带她离开学校

510
00:31:10,950 --> 00:31:14,180
Just be careful. Tyler is out there, and he turned.
小心点 Tyler在外面 他变身了

511
00:31:14,180 --> 00:31:15,680
What about you?
那你们呢?

512
00:31:15,680 --> 00:31:17,820
No, we can't leave. Rebecca's compelled us.
我们不能走 Rebecca把我们思维强制了

513
00:31:17,820 --> 00:31:20,920
Just go. We'll deal with her later.
你们快走 我们一会儿再对付她

514
00:31:28,280 --> 00:31:29,320
Stefan...
Stefan啊...

515
00:31:29,320 --> 00:31:30,780
No.
别说了

516
00:31:30,780 --> 00:31:33,250
Stefan, we have to talk about this. Please.
Stefan 我们得谈谈 拜托了

517
00:31:33,250 --> 00:31:34,880
Talk about what, huh?
谈什么 嗯?

518
00:31:34,880 --> 00:31:37,980
How many more ways are there for you to rip my heart out?
你还有多少种方式伤我的心?

519
00:31:37,980 --> 00:31:39,480
I'm sorry.
对不起

520
00:31:39,480 --> 00:31:41,250
Sorry that it happened, or sorry that I found out?
对不起 因为你和他上床还是因为我发现真相?

521
00:31:41,250 --> 00:31:43,680
I'm sorry about all of it.
这一切我都深感抱歉

522
00:31:43,680 --> 00:31:45,280
I'm really sorry, Stefan.
真的很对不起 Stefan

523
00:31:45,280 --> 00:31:49,720
I didn't mean to hurt you. I didn't want that.
我不是要故意伤害你 我不想伤害你

524
00:31:52,480 --> 00:31:56,250
Why are my least favorite people always the most durable?
为什么我最讨厌的人 总能活得最久?

525
00:32:02,920 --> 00:32:05,380
Tyler...
Tyler啊...

526
00:32:26,250 --> 00:32:29,350
I'm so sorry.
我真的很抱歉

527
00:32:29,350 --> 00:32:31,920
It wasn't your fault.
那不是你的错

528
00:32:33,920 --> 00:32:37,120
Yes, it was.
是我的错

529
00:32:37,120 --> 00:32:39,680
This whole thing.
整件事情

530
00:32:39,680 --> 00:32:42,020
It's all my fault.
都是我的错

531
00:32:43,450 --> 00:32:46,320
No, Tyler.
不 Tyler

532
00:32:46,320 --> 00:32:48,750
I should have saved her.
我本该救她的

533
00:32:58,880 --> 00:33:00,080
Leave her out of this.
别把她牵扯进来

534
00:33:00,080 --> 00:33:01,720
This is between me and you.
这是咱们两个的事

535
00:33:01,720 --> 00:33:04,650
You're still protecting her?
你还在保护她?

536
00:33:04,650 --> 00:33:07,650
Must I rip your bleeding heart from your chest
非要我把你那颗流血的心挖出来

537
00:33:07,650 --> 00:33:11,220
and show you the scar tissue that is Elena Gilbert?
把Elena Gilbert造成的伤疤展示给你看吗?

538
00:33:14,080 --> 00:33:15,250
There's a solution
倒是有个办法

539
00:33:15,250 --> 00:33:17,050
to all your problems, you know.
能解决你们所有的问题

540
00:33:17,050 --> 00:33:19,120
I could compel him,
我可以把他思维强制

541
00:33:19,120 --> 00:33:23,750
erase every memory he has of you.
抹掉他所有关于你的记忆

542
00:33:23,750 --> 00:33:25,880
Every day you've spent together,
你们一起度过的每一天

543
00:33:25,880 --> 00:33:30,750
every kiss, every lie, every ounce of pain.
每个吻 每个谎言 每分痛苦

544
00:33:30,750 --> 00:33:35,820
I can take away every bit of love he has for you,
我可以抹掉他对你所有的爱

545
00:33:35,820 --> 00:33:37,780
give you both a clean slate.
让你们各自重新开始

546
00:33:37,780 --> 00:33:40,220
Just say the word, and I'll make you
只要你同意 我就可以把你

547
00:33:40,220 --> 00:33:43,820
and all that misery you've caused him disappear.
以及你给他带来的痛苦 统统消失

548
00:33:43,820 --> 00:33:45,280
Do it.
动手吧

549
00:33:47,520 --> 00:33:49,980
Excuse me?
你说什么?

550
00:33:49,980 --> 00:33:52,520
Erase it all. Every memory.
清除我所有的记忆吧

551
00:33:52,520 --> 00:33:53,580
Stefan, no.
Stefan 不要

552
00:33:53,580 --> 00:33:55,850
I said do it.
动手吧

553
00:34:04,020 --> 00:34:08,750
No. That would be far too easy.
不 那就太便宜你了

554
00:34:08,750 --> 00:34:11,580
I refuse to make you forget her
我才不会像Klaus强迫你忘记我那样

555
00:34:11,580 --> 00:34:14,480
the way Klaus made you forget me.
让你轻易忘记她

556
00:34:17,020 --> 00:34:19,720
But at least you know how he really feels.
至少你了解他的感受了

557
00:34:24,150 --> 00:34:29,350
Consider your eternity of pain my revenge, Stefan.
让你永生痛苦是我复仇的一部分 Stefan

558
00:34:29,350 --> 00:34:30,820
I've used you for all you're worth.
你已经没有利用价值

559
00:34:30,820 --> 00:34:33,920
So now you're free to go.
你可以走了

560
00:34:50,180 --> 00:34:52,520
Stefan, wait.
Stefan 等一下

561
00:35:20,780 --> 00:35:21,780
Turns out I miscalculated.
我判断失误了

562
00:35:21,780 --> 00:35:24,950
Kol's gonna be a problem.
Kol是个麻烦人物

563
00:35:24,950 --> 00:35:27,850
I almost killed someone,
我差点杀掉一个无辜的人

564
00:35:28,350 --> 00:35:29,740
and that's what you miscalculated?
这也是你判断失误?

565
00:35:29,740 --> 00:35:31,080
April could've died today.
April今天差点死掉

566
00:35:31,080 --> 00:35:33,480
That's only because you didn't know the extent of your abilities.
这是因为你控制不好自己的能力

567
00:35:33,480 --> 00:35:35,120
My father just became mayor.
我父亲接任了镇长的位置

568
00:35:35,120 --> 00:35:37,380
I can't be out doing black magic.
我不能再使用黑巫术了

569
00:35:37,380 --> 00:35:40,050
That's not what expression is.
这并不是表达式魔法

570
00:35:42,720 --> 00:35:43,880
Then what is it?
那是什么?

571
00:35:43,880 --> 00:35:45,450
It's a way of doing magic.
这是一种巫术施展法

572
00:35:45,450 --> 00:35:46,880
That isn't monitored by nature or the spirits.
它不受自然界和精神界的控制

573
00:35:46,880 --> 00:35:49,050
It isn't good nor bad.
没有好坏之分

574
00:35:49,050 --> 00:35:52,220
But it also has no limits,
但同时它也没有底线

575
00:35:52,220 --> 00:35:54,280
so how you use it is up to you.
一切要取决于你如何使用

576
00:35:54,280 --> 00:35:57,680
That's what I'm here for...
这就是我在这里的原因...

577
00:35:57,680 --> 00:36:00,520
To help you.
帮助你自控

578
00:36:00,520 --> 00:36:04,880
Bonnie, listen to me. You are the key to everything.
Bonnie 听我说 你是一切的关键所在

579
00:36:06,880 --> 00:36:10,080
I'm not going to let anything bad happen to you.
我不会让你受伤害的

580
00:36:27,550 --> 00:36:29,650
Hope your day is going better than mine.
希望你今天过得比我好

581
00:36:29,650 --> 00:36:32,350
Got to say, I'm liking the odds.
可以说 我这里困难重重啊

582
00:36:32,350 --> 00:36:34,580
Stefan knows about us.
Stefan都知道了

583
00:36:35,450 --> 00:36:38,450
Ooh.
哦

584
00:36:38,450 --> 00:36:40,420
How'd he take it?
他怎么样了?

585
00:36:40,420 --> 00:36:42,320
How do you think?
你觉得呢?

586
00:36:43,680 --> 00:36:45,620
I'm thinking, for the first time all week,
我想现在是我这周以来 

587
00:36:45,620 --> 00:36:49,720
I'm happy to be at camp nowhere
首次愿意留在这荒山野岭的时刻了

588
00:36:49,720 --> 00:36:51,120
How's Jeremy?
Jeremy怎么样了?

589
00:36:51,120 --> 00:36:54,150
That depends on how much you trust me.
那就要看你有多信任我

590
00:36:54,150 --> 00:36:56,850
You know that I trust you.
你知道我很信任你

591
00:36:56,850 --> 00:37:01,220
Then I think he's gonna get through this thing just fine.
那我觉得他能顺利度过难关

592
00:37:01,220 --> 00:37:03,580
Thanks for looking out for him.
谢谢你照顾他

593
00:37:03,580 --> 00:37:05,350
Yeah, well, I told them if they were good,
好了 我跟他们说要是好好表现

594
00:37:05,350 --> 00:37:10,120
I'd buy them both ice cream, so I got to go.
就会奖励他们冰激凌 所以我得挂了

595
00:37:10,120 --> 00:37:11,720
Not yet.
等一下

596
00:37:13,350 --> 00:37:16,280
Something happened today.
今天发生了很多事情

597
00:37:16,280 --> 00:37:21,350
I realized something about you, about us.
我对我们的关系有了新的认识

598
00:37:21,350 --> 00:37:23,780
And you can say that it's the sire bond,
你可以说是我对你的臣服导致的

599
00:37:23,780 --> 00:37:26,350
and you know what? Maybe... maybe it is.
或许吧? 可能... 真的是臣服导致的

600
00:37:26,350 --> 00:37:30,550
But I'm telling you it's the most real thing
但这是我这辈子

601
00:37:30,550 --> 00:37:33,420
that I've ever felt in my entire life.
感受最为真实的

602
00:37:36,450 --> 00:37:38,980
I love you, Damon.
我爱你 Damon

603
00:37:45,880 --> 00:37:49,350
I love you.
我是真的爱你

604
00:37:49,350 --> 00:37:52,450
Look.
听我说

605
00:37:52,450 --> 00:37:55,020
I'm going to get this cure for you.
我会为你找到这个治愈之法

606
00:37:58,080 --> 00:38:01,480
And I'm gonna have to do things you don't like.
我还会做你不喜欢的事情

607
00:38:01,480 --> 00:38:02,650
Damon...
Damon啊...

608
00:38:02,650 --> 00:38:04,980
But listen carefully.
现在仔细听我说

609
00:38:06,150 --> 00:38:11,350
Get in your car right now.
你现在立即开车

610
00:38:11,350 --> 00:38:13,020
Come to me.
马上来见我

611
00:38:15,120 --> 00:38:17,020
I'll be there soon.
马上就到

612
00:38:32,380 --> 00:38:33,680
You let yourself in.
你来了

613
00:38:33,680 --> 00:38:35,320
You called me.
你打电话给我的

614
00:38:35,320 --> 00:38:38,620
Should I be checking for hidden daggers?
我要检查你偷藏了匕首吗?

615
00:38:38,620 --> 00:38:39,980
Do you still want to find the cure?
你还想找治愈之法吗?

616
00:38:39,980 --> 00:38:42,020
More than anything.
迫不及待

617
00:38:42,020 --> 00:38:43,780
I want to ram it down Niklaus' throat
我很想撕破Niklaus的喉咙

618
00:38:43,780 --> 00:38:47,550
and look into his eyes as he realizes he's mortal again.
当他意识到自己无法长生不死之时 盯着他

619
00:38:47,550 --> 00:38:50,220
But Shane's dead and you are useless,
不过Shane已经死了 而你也没有利用价值

620
00:38:50,220 --> 00:38:52,950
So I'm right back where I started.
所以我又得重新开始

621
00:38:52,950 --> 00:38:55,720
Shane's not dead.
Shane并没死

622
00:38:55,720 --> 00:38:58,180
But I watched Kol impale him.
我看到Kol杀了他

623
00:38:58,180 --> 00:39:00,680
Well, you probably shouldn't have left him alone.
你们不应该把他尸体留在那里

624
00:39:00,680 --> 00:39:02,520
Bonnie did a little spell.
Bonnie施咒救了他

625
00:39:02,520 --> 00:39:04,350
He's perfectly fine.
他活得好好的

626
00:39:07,480 --> 00:39:09,580
You didn't have to tell me that.
你不需要跟我说这些

627
00:39:09,580 --> 00:39:12,280
Why am I really here?
叫我来到底干什么?

628
00:39:12,280 --> 00:39:14,150
You were right.
你做的对

629
00:39:14,150 --> 00:39:15,750
I'm gonna be here for an eternity,
既然我得永世待在这里

630
00:39:15,750 --> 00:39:18,020
and I will go insane if I don't know
如果Elena对我哥的感情

631
00:39:18,020 --> 00:39:20,520
how Elena truly feels about my brother.
我还懵然不知 我肯定会发疯的

632
00:39:23,750 --> 00:39:26,220
If you really want the cure,
如果想找治愈之法

633
00:39:26,220 --> 00:39:27,620
you should know that Shane has an agenda,
你就要知道Shane的计划

634
00:39:27,620 --> 00:39:29,680
and it's a dark one.
一个黑暗的计划

635
00:39:29,680 --> 00:39:32,580
He said he organized dozens of people to die in sacrifice.
他说他设法杀掉了很多人来完成祭祀

636
00:39:32,580 --> 00:39:35,580
He admitted to the council explosion where 12 people died.
他承认委员会那12人的自杀爆炸事件 是他策划的

637
00:39:35,580 --> 00:39:37,180
And I'm guessing it's not a coincidence
所以我猜我哥哥杀掉那12个混种

638
00:39:37,180 --> 00:39:40,820
that 12 hybrids died at the hand of my brother.
也并非偶然

639
00:39:40,820 --> 00:39:43,880
12...
12个...

640
00:39:43,880 --> 00:39:45,780
Channeling the energy from a mass death is used
实施黑巫术

641
00:39:45,780 --> 00:39:48,950
in witchcraft to perform dark spells.
要通过杀人获取能量

642
00:39:48,950 --> 00:39:51,450
It's called expression.
这就是表达式魔法

643
00:39:51,450 --> 00:39:53,950
Shane admitted all this to you?
Shane跟你承认了?

644
00:39:53,950 --> 00:39:55,820
Proudly.
他还很自豪

645
00:39:55,820 --> 00:39:57,420
Well, then I guess we'll have to figure out how to manage him
那么 我们要想找到治愈之法

646
00:39:57,420 --> 00:40:00,120
while we find the cure for ourselves.
就必须要控制住他

647
00:40:01,150 --> 00:40:03,050
"we"?
"我们"?

648
00:40:03,050 --> 00:40:04,880
There's no "we," Stefan.
没有"我们" Stefan

649
00:40:04,880 --> 00:40:08,620
Listen, I hate my brother, and you hate yours.
听我说 我恨我的哥哥 你也恨你的

650
00:40:08,620 --> 00:40:11,180
But Damon's got Jeremy, and Klaus has the sword,
但是Damon和Jeremy在一起  Klaus找到了剑

651
00:40:11,180 --> 00:40:12,620
and Shane has Bonnie.
Shane有Bonnie助阵

652
00:40:12,620 --> 00:40:15,080
You and I are the only ones left with nothing.
就剩下你我二人一无所有

653
00:40:15,080 --> 00:40:16,750
You said it yourself, right?
你也说过了 不是吗?

654
00:40:16,750 --> 00:40:18,080
Whoever finds the cure first
最先找到治愈之法的人

655
00:40:18,080 --> 00:40:20,620
gets to decide what to do with it.
才握有主动权

656
00:40:20,620 --> 00:40:25,080
What do you say? You want to be partners?
你觉得如何? 想合作吗?

657
00:40:26,720 --> 00:40:29,880
My father had no reason to kill 11 people.
我爸爸不会平白无故杀死11个人

658
00:40:29,880 --> 00:40:32,480
He had no reason to kill himself.
更不会无缘无故自杀

659
00:40:32,480 --> 00:40:34,520
He loved me.
他很爱我

660
00:40:34,520 --> 00:40:38,620
He loved Mystic Falls.
他也很爱Mystic Falls

661
00:40:38,620 --> 00:40:41,520
He was brainwashed into sparking that fire.
他思维被控制 才会点火引爆

662
00:40:41,520 --> 00:40:43,850
Professor Shane organized his death
是Shane教授策划了

663
00:40:43,850 --> 00:40:46,320
and the 11 others who died with him.
他和其他11个人的死亡事件

664
00:40:49,450 --> 00:40:53,150
It's time this entire town started telling the truth.
是时候将真相公之于众了

665
00:41:13,180 --> 00:41:14,320
I was beginning to worry
我还担心

666
00:41:14,320 --> 00:41:16,420
you boys wouldn't find the place.
你们找不到这里呢

667
00:41:16,420 --> 00:41:18,720
What the hell...?
究竟怎么回事...?

668
00:41:18,720 --> 00:41:20,750
Did you kill all these people?
你把这里的人都杀了?

669
00:41:20,750 --> 00:41:23,020
Not exactly.
不完全是

670
00:41:23,020 --> 00:41:26,480
They're in transition.
他们在转化

671
00:41:26,480 --> 00:41:29,320
Killing them is your job.
杀掉他们是你的任务

672
00:41:32,380 --> 00:41:33,680
You said you were going to convince Klaus
你说过会说服Klaus

673
00:41:33,680 --> 00:41:35,680
to do this another way.
寻找其他方法的

674
00:41:39,050 --> 00:41:40,580
I thought about it.
我是有想过

675
00:41:40,580 --> 00:41:45,520
And then I realized his idea was better.
不过我觉得他的方法更好

