Previously on The Mob Doctor...
As long as you're in Chicago,
I own you. That's the deal.
So, I hear you want to take over
Moretti's deal with us.
Yeah, that's right.
Ain't gonna happen.
Constantine: I know
about the double dipping.
Our cut's 25%
al on the machines.
You were asking for 15%.
My brother's
not gonna like this.
Celeste.
Constantine.
You really think uniting
the syndicate is a good thing?
I do.
It's a Pandora's Box.
Let's get
this meeting started.
And if you're not careful,
You'll end up back in jail --
or worse.
Constantine's coming.
You have to leave.
Listen to me. I just got you back.
There's no way I'm running now.
There is no other way.
You have to go -- now.
[ tires squeal ]
Look -- I don't care.
Take a bite.
Go on. Take a bite.
The chocolate tastes cheap.
I-I-I don't want to have cheap
chocolate on my punsch rolls.
Stavos. Come over here
and taste something for me.
Tastes good.
I want the best-tasting
damn punsch rolls in Chicago.
Spend the extra buck
and get the belgian dark.
The bakery's just a front,
you know?
Cash business
to launder our money, right?
Like my old man said,
If you're gonna do something,
do it right.
Speaking of
doing things right,
The Amatos are late with
their gaming-machines cut again.
You call Titus.
You tell him I'm gonna take a
point for every day he's late.
[ door closes ] looks
like you have a visitor.
Celeste.
You're giving Trapani 50%
of our downtown action.
That's right.
You promised me 50%.
Also right.
So, if you're giving away
all the money,
Then what's left
for you?
Hey, can I get you
an espresso or a cupcake?
I don't recommend
the punsch rolls.
I'd like an explanation,
Constantine.
Oh.
[ sighs ]
Hey, fellas,
give me a couple minutes.
The West Side and the North Side
are both gonna get 50%.
I always keep my word.
And the South Side gets nothing?
You get nothing?
Well, you know,
taking over downtown
Means a lot more to me
than money.
[ laughs ] you expect me
to believe that?
Well, it hasn't been done
since Al Capone.
So, this is
about your ego.
You call it
what you want.
To me,
it's about making history.
Hey, what do you say...
We crack this box open,
We put this nice champagne
you gave me on ice.
What?
The bottle of champagne
you sent me this morning.
Tino, I didn't
send that to you.
Then who did?
[ knife clicks ]
What are you doing?
It's rigged
with a pressure plate.
Here we go.
You better
wait outside.
Dr. White: Take-home message --
use the ultrasound
To estimate fluid status
in septic patients
By looking at the IVC collapse
with respiration.
And one last thing --
patient-satisfaction surveys.
Board
takes them seriously.
[ cellphone rings ]
I suggest that you do, too.
Hello?
Dr. Flanigan: Page three of your handouts,
You find a new script
being implemented today.
Dr. Robinson.
[ clicks tongue,
clears throat ]
"hello,
my name is Dr. Blank.
"here's my card.
I am sorry you had to wait
blank minutes to see me."
"can I offer you
an extra pillow or blanket?"
Are we surgeons
or room service?
Any doctor
receiving three failing grades
Within a month will be attending
the bedside-manner seminar.
All right, on my way.
We got a V.I.P.
Five minutes out from the E.R.
Who's on trauma call?
I am.
All right, you're with me.
Dr. Robinson, you, too.
I'm scheduled
for post-op clinic.
Not anymore.
The paramedics radioed ahead.
The patient
requested you by name.
Who's the patient?
We're about to find out.
[ sirens wailing ] cycling
accident. 28-year-old male.
Head injury
with altered mental status.
Open right wrist fracture
A.L.O.C.
GCS 10.
Vitals stable.
Abrasions to anterior chest
and extremities.
Who is he?
Jack Hanson --
U.S. Attorney's son.
Why would he ask for you?
You know him?
Yeah.
He's my brother.
Galvanized-metal pipe.
Rubber blasting caps.
Hand me those pliers.
All right.
Tino,
there could be a short.
Shh. Quiet.
Now all we got to do...
...Is figure out
who's trying to kill me.
It's disarmed.
[ sighs ] thank God.
So,
who wants you dead?
Nowadays?
Pick a number.
One of my girls has a regular
on the bomb squad.
I could ask him
to take a look at the device,
Maybe help us figure out
who sent it.
Well, do you think
you can trust this guy
To keep his mouth shut?
I have a video of him
in a compromising position.
Yeah.
Well, you tell him
to work quick.
Because whoever did this --
they're gonna try again.
Sync and corrected
by www.addic7ed.com
The Mob Doctor
Season 1, Episode 11, "Sibling Rivalry"
Mr. Hanson, squeeze my hand!
Non-responsive.
If Jack Hanson is your brother,
then Mark Hanson --
Is my father.
Only withdraws
to painful stimuli.
Different last name?
It's my mother's maiden name.
I changed it during college.
Can we
talk about this later?
Run an I-stat
to clear his renal function,
Then pan-scan him --
priority one.
Susie is right.
I'll roll him to radiology.
No, he's a family member.
You can observe.
But from here on, hands off.
Dr. Devlin,
how's your V.I.P. Patient?
His vitals are stable.
Good. I need you
for a surgical consult.
Let's go.
Bounce-back
lower-right quadrant pain.
Medicine turfed her
to us.
[ sighs ]
you're joking.
You already know
Ms. Evans?
She's a frequent flyer.
She's here for drugs.
Let me remind you
that you've already received
Two failing grades
on the patient surveys, so --
Dr. Flanigan,
it was a wound recheck
Who got mad that I was busy
with a ruptured appy...
Doctor... And a fecal impaction
who resented the rectal exam.
Doctor.
Her chart
is up and loaded.
Hi, Miss Evans.
I'm Dr. Devlin.
Yeah. I remember you.
Sorry you had to wait
so long.
[ scoffs ]
four damn hours.
[ chuckles ]
could have died.
[ sighs ]
So, you have pain
in your lower abdomen.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Okay, may I?
Yeah. [ sighs ]
Look, I'm gonna -- I'm gonna
need something for the pain.
I'm allergic to ibuprofen,
ketorolac, and morphine.
Mm.
There's this other drug,
"d"-something.
Dilaudid?
Yeah.
You have mild,
diffuse tenderness.
No rebound, no guarding.
Strong femoral pulses.
Yeah, this is really
all good news.
Are -- are you deaf?
[ chuckles ]
I -- I said it hurts.
Are you familiar with
your own hospital's policy?
Excuse me?
Look. [ scoffs ]
You need
to order me a C.T.,
And the you need to get me
something for the pain.
Okay, Miss Evans,
you've actually been here
81 times this year,
each time with a new complaint.
Give you any more C.T.s,
Your ovaries are gonna start
glowing in the dark.
Yeah, but this --
it's different this time.
So, I am gonna follow
hospital policy
And I'm gonna refer you
to a drug-addiction specialist.
[ scoffs ]
I don't --
I don't need that.
[ paper rips ]
please, get some help.
[ sighs ]
Thank you.
[ cellphone rings ]
Hey, Nate.
Grace.
Can you get away?
Um, I'm waiting on some
test results. What's going on?
Please, it's important.
You got to get over here.
Okay, fine.
Uh, I just don't
have much time, though.
I'm texting you
the address.
We got to hurry.
Tell me why I'm here, Nate.
I screwed up, okay?
I-I know what I said before,
but I need your help.
Just follow me, okay?
If you have an emergency,
you call 911.
I can't call anybody
except you!
Why not?
Grace...
Meet Matty Boy.
A horse.
[ sighs ]
Thoroughbred racehorse.
Do I look like a vet?
No, a vet
would call the cops.
Who are you?
Grace, Victor.
Call the cops for what?
It's not our horse.
Matty Boy
won the Arlington Cup.
His sperm
is worth 100 grand.
His sperm?
Why does he
have an erection?
We were
trying to get his sperm.
But he wasn't cooperating.
Our, uh -- [ chuckles ]
our dummy mare wasn't his type.
So, Vic decides to give him
a handful of Viagra,
And now it won't go down.
The horse
has got to race tomorrow.
Yeah, I got to go.
Grace, please.
I have patients who need me,
Nate -- people patients.
The horse belongs to Vic's boss,
Tommy Walls.
Tommy's a captain
with the Hyde Park crew.
Yeah,
I know who he is.
And he's not the kind of guy
that you mess with.
Vic's in charge
of the horse's transport.
It was gonna be
an easy score.
Please! Help me out.
If Tommy finds out what we did,
we're both dead.
Carol.
Oh, Brett.
Hey.
[ sighs ]
How's your brother?
Still unconscious.
We're assessing the extent
of his head trauma.
I was there, you know,
when he crashed.
We were meeting at
the courthouse for a hearing,
His first
since making partner.
Jack's a partner?
Yeah, three weeks now.
It's quick, I know, but your
father can be persuasive.
Yeah, sounds like dad.
Have you
called your family?
The hospital alerted Annabelle.
She's on her way.
And what about
your father?
I -- I don't know.
I'll call him.
Okay.
[ Matty Boy neighs ]
Ro, thank God.
I got Granny Smith
And all the terbutaline
we had in the med room.
I marked the bottles
"expired and destroyed."
[ sighs ] thank you.
You know I love you,
right?
Yeah, I can explain.
Please, don't.
[ chuckles ]
Okay, thanks.
[ Matty Boy grunts ]
What are you doing?
Terbutaline
treats priapism in humans.
A horse is a mammal.
So hopefully, it will work.
Hey, there. Hey.
[ Matty Boy snorts ]
Now what?
You wait and you pray.
[ indistinct conversations ]
What's with the plums?
In prison,
some of the guys
Used to make a little hooch
out of it.
Take a plum,
mix it with some sugar.
Anyway, one day,
the guys got caught,
And the warden banned plums
for an entire year.
I didn't know
you were such a fan.
I'm not.
But the moment I was denied,
that's all I wanted.
Hmm.
Here comes tweedledum.
Titus.
How you doing,
buddy?
Hey, did you know there's a
roman emperor with your name?
Titus Augustus.
Oh, yeah?
Let me
ask you something --
How many machines
you delivered so far?
I don't have an exact count. I do.
117.
It's supposed to be 500.
There's a slight
manufacturing delay.
If we're short, our competition
gets the jump on us.
It'll cost us millions.
I'm handling it.
Yeah, well, I hope
you're not messing around.
I mean, we all know
that you and your brother --
You weren't happy
with the price.
Well,
don't screw around.
Yeah. I don't know.
You're paranoid.
Stavos, talk some sense
into your boss.
Listen,
we're in this together, right?
You need us to help you
with that, uh,
Manufacturing delay,
you say the word.
Yeah, security,
anything you need.
I don't need any help.
I'm telling you guys.
I'm gonna have the machines
for you by the end of the week.
Hey.
How's your brother?
Jack's got
a splenic fracture
With extravasation
and free fluids.
He needs an ex-lap.
He's being prepped
for surgery right now.
Dr. White
asked me to scrub in.
I hadn't seen my brother
since my mom's funeral.
You guys
had a falling out?
No. It's my dad.
We don't really
see eye-to-eye.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[ sighs ]
Fathers can be tough.
Yeah, but, you know, mine
put away two corrupt governors,
So that kind of makes him
a hero, right?
It makes him
good at his job.
My mom used to say
That behind every great man
is an even greater ego.
[ chuckles ]
Hey, I'm gonna head
to the surgery, okay?
You'll be around later?
Yeah.
Okay.
[ monitor beeping ]
How's Brett holding up?
Fine. I think.
Grade the spleen injury,
doctor?
Non-invasive,
subcapsular hematoma
Involving over
50% surface area,
40% devascularization --
grade 4.
Exactly. So, we...
Do a dexon mesh wrap
splenorrhaphy --
Save the spleen.
Good. First step --
mobilization.
[ rapid beeping ]
Hold on.
B.P.'s falling fast.
Can't be from the spleen injury.
There's not enough blood loss.
He's not perfusing.
B.P.'s cratering.
Could have thrown a pulmonary
embolism. Increase the PO2.
Open the saline wide.
[ beeping ]
Damn it. Run of five.
Amiodarone, 150.
All right,
screw the repair.
We got to grab the spleen
and run.
[ indistinct conversation ]
[ monitor beeping ]
Disconjugate,
doll's-eyes movements.
He's moving his legs in response
to stimuli but not his arms.
That's new. He came in
moving extremities times four.
So, he's showing progressive
paralysis following head trauma.
What's the
differential diagnosis?
Spinal C.T. was negative.
Maybe... Central Cord Syndrome?
Sciwora? Need an MRI.
Eh, he's not
stable enough.
What do we know
about the mechanism of injury?
Chest and extremity abrasions.
Wrist fracture.
All right,
which suggests face-plant.
Could there have been extreme
cervical flection or extension?
Carol might know.
She's a senior partner
at Jack's firm.
She was there.
She saw him go down.
I could talk to her.
All right, fine.
Okay.
Take Grace.
[ indistinct conversations ]
Dr. Wilcox.
How's your day?
Well, the gall bladder
is getting a hida scan,
And I am going to the cafeteria
hoping for a blueberry muffin.
At canthait. I need your help
with a surgical consult.
Isn't she
Grace's patient?
Grace discharged her, but
she called 911 from the lobby.
Paramedics brought her back
to the E.R.
Uh-huh.
I'll page Dr. Devlin.
She's on
the Hanson case.
[ sighs ]
this is so not fair.
Yeah.
You can thank Grace later.
I need a C.T. scan.
[ sighs ]
And I'm gonna need something
for the pain.
Uh...
I'm allergic to morphine.
There's this, um...
This other drug.
I think it's "d"-something.
Dilaudid?
Yeah.
That's the one.
It's 10 times more powerful
than morphine.
Well, I got 10 times the pain.
[ sighs ]
I'll order an abdominal/pelvis
C.T. and two of dilaudid.
You're a wonderful
doctor.
Would you like
an extra pillow or blanket?
Dad.
Brett.
It's been too long.
Yeah. Uh, this is Dr. Devlin,
Jack's surgeon.
Well, one of them.
Dr. White, chief of surgery,
is handling his case personally.
Mark Hanson.
This is Carol Goodman.
Jack's wife, Annabelle.
How's Jack?
At the moment,
his blood pressure is unstable.
We're having some trouble
weaning him off the ventilator.
So, there is a possibility
of some brain or spinal injury.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
I thought the C.T. was normal.
Not all neurological injuries
show up on C.T.,
So we need to know
a little more about the crash.
You saw it happen, right?
No. I was there, but no.
I heard it. I came running.
I called the ambulance.
But it happened
outside the courthouse?
Yeah, why? Don't they
have surveillance cameras?
Yeah. Yeah, they do.
I'll call the courthouse.
We'll have those tapes
in 30 minutes.
So...You find out
who's trying to kill me yet?
Well,
it's not that simple.
Our guy put the bomb's markers
through the database.
No names poped up.
The device is identical
to a bomb that was used
To blow up a diner on Belmont
a couple of years back.
Yeah.
Cops make anyone on that?
No.
The place on Belmont --
is it The Royal Diner?
Yeah,
that's what he said.
Why?
It was an insurance scam.
The owner wanted to make the
bombing look racially motivated,
Took the insurance payout,
and split town.
And how do you know so much
about this, my friend?
I may have consulted.
Yeah? Well,
who built the bomb?
Oh, you know him.
Jimmy Needles.
Jimmy Needles?
I'll tell you what --
go have Gio pick him up.
It's time
we had a little homecoming
With our old friend
Jimmy Needles.
[ sighs ]
Dr. White: Ouch.
It's just a glancing blow
to the head.
Yeah.
[ beeping ]
Brett: Yeah, see,
he fractures his arm here,
And then he just...
Rolls.
No major head trauma.
No extreme flection
or extension of his neck.
Can you zoom in?
[ beeping ]
Okay, wait, stop.
Stop right there.
Look, look, look.
Look at his hands.
He just lets go
of the handlebars.
He might have lost consciousness
before the crash.
We've been going about this
the wrong way.
Maybe a neurologic deficit
caused the trauma,
Not the other way around.
So, what's the differential
diagnosis for A.L.O.C.
Besides head trauma?
What about, like, a weird toxin
exposure or brain infection?
Has he been camping
or on any foreign trips?
Oh, we've been so focused
on the trauma, we didn't ask.
Well, he's comatose. Go.
Talk to his family.
[ sighs ]
Maybe encephalitis.
How does dengue fever present?
I don't have a clue.
[ cellphone ringing ]
You know what?
I got to take this.
What?
Grace, the pills made Matty Boy
worse! He's freaking out!
Is he still priapistic?
If that means, "is he still
sporting wood," then yes.
Now he's all aggro.
Look, I am in the middle
of something here, Nate.
Grace,
Vic told me last week
One of Tommy Walls' guys
pissed him off.
Tommy went after him with a blow
torch, burned him to the bone.
What do you think
he's gonna do to me?
All right, look,
I'll get there as soon as I can.
Hey. A guy in ICU
just yanked out his E.T. tube.
All right, I can
get Jack's history on my own,
And then I'll just meet up
with you later.
Thanks.
No, we haven't
been camping.
And we haven't been out
of the country since 2008.
A couple of weeks ago, we went
to a legal conference together.
Anywhere exotic?
Toledo --
the airport hotel.
Could Jack have
caught something on the plane?
Maybe. We're doing
a full infectious workup.
He's gonna be okay.
Right?
Just tell us the truth,
son.
I always do, dad.
Jack is...
Becoming less stable.
If we don't
find out the cause, then...
He could die?
Oh, God.
A-Annabelle, we're doing
everything we can.
I-I'm gonna go
check on Jack.
Easy, buddy.
Easy, easy.
No, no, no.
It's okay. It's okay.
No, I'm, uh...No,
I'm changing the tire right now.
I'm gonna get Matty Boy
to the track on time.
Don't sweat it.
[ sighs ]
[ cellphone beeps ] all right, I
bought us one hour, maybe two tops.
After that,
Tommy's gonna know what's up.
Thank God.
Hey, take your time,
why don't you?
[ Matty Boy neighing,
snorting ]
What's wrong with him?
[ sighs ]
When was the last time
he urinated?
He hasn't.
[ sighs ]
He needs an intracavernosal
injection of phenylephrine.
A what now?
I got to tranquilize him
with ketamine
And drain the blood from
his penis. Whoa, whoa.
This horse
has to race tomorrow,
And the track is gonna test for
performance enhancers, all of that.
Well, ketamine's a downer, not
an upper, so we should be fine.
What about the phenyl...Ephen?
Phenylephrine.
Is it gonna show up
in a urine test?
I don't know
what they test for, Nate.
Then we can't risk it.
Grace.
[ sighs ]
After the horse mounted the,
uh...Dummy mare,
How were you actually
gonna collect the sperm?
[ Matty Boy neighing ]
Well, it's called
an artificial vagina.
[ groans ]
Let me see it.
It's just rubber tubing
filled with water,
But we didn't
get to use it.
[ sighs ]
Okay, get me a bag of ice. Why?
Because I need a noninvasive way
to help the horse.
Do you have
any other questions?
You paged me?
Abdominal C.T.
Check out the clot in the
superior mesenteric artery.
Acute thrombosis.
Who's C.T. is this?
Our frequent flyer.
You're kidding?
She actually
has something wrong this time.
Her bowel's necrosing.
Without surgery, she'll die.
Dr. Devlin missed it.
And I caught it.
That's all that matters.
Jimmy! Huh?
Jimmy Needles.
[ chuckles ]
Long time, no see.
You're not looking
too good there, Jimmy.
I swear...I -- I didn't know
that they'd send you that bomb.
What was that you said?
"they"?
Who's "they," Jimmy?
I never
meet my customers.
[ grunts ]
[ groans ]
I got a booking system.
My customers get a three-digit
code, and they leave me cash.
Says he dropped a package
under a bench in Janura Park.
I'm telling the truth.
All right,
I believe you.
So, what number
is your buyer?
4-4-7.
But I don't know who that is.
I don't want to know.
That's the way it works.
I mean, you know, that makes
sense to me, Jimmy, you know?
Discreet business practice,
looking out for your customers.
Aah!
You listen to me.
You're gonna tell me
what I want to know,
Or I'm gonna crack your head
open like a coconut
And feed you to my dogs!
The Amato brothers.
[ grunts ]
are you lying to me?
4-4-7...
That's the Amato brothers.
They hired me.
I swear.
[ sighs ]
[ crowbar clangs ]
[ breathing heavily ]
Bobby, cut him loose.
Throw him out in the alley
with the rest of the garbage.
You saved Dante's life,
and this is how they repay you?
Hey, the Amatos
were always greedy pigs.
They figured with me gone,
they can get the whole pie.
Want me
to set up a meeting?
No. No more talk.
Grace, the ice
is starting to melt.
Good, then you
can refill it.
What,
is he playing dead?
He's sedated.
Nate: Vic, my hand
is starting to freeze.
Take over.
[ sighs ]
Hey, Doc,
I think it's working.
Damn, is my sister good
or what?
Hey, Vic.
Hang on tight.
Hey, hey!
[ laughs ]
[ chuckling ]
good one, man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You think that's funny?
Dude,
you know who I work for?
I -- I think you should
walk away, Victor.
[ breathing heavily ]
Victor, walk away.
You're lucky
she's your sister, jackoff.
Look...
I know I screwed up, okay?
But can we just, like,
skip the silent treatment
And get to the part
where you yell at me?
You know what?
Right now,
Brett's brother is in the ICU.
And instead of being there,
I am dealing with your crap again.
You have got to
grow up.
I'm part of something
right now.
I-if this had worked --
"if this had worked"?
Come on, Nate.
You know better.
Thanks.
You could have just said no
to the meds, all right?
There are plenty
of other hospitals.
You have
a mesenteric thrombosis.
Like I'm supposed to know
what that means.
It means that without surgery,
you will die.
[ scoffs ]
You're a bad liar, Doc.
Fine.
It's your funeral.
Just read and sign this
"against medical advice" form
While I get a witness.
You need a witness
for what?
That I explained
the consequences
Of denying
the recommended treatment.
See you later.
Wait.
If I agree to the surgery,
can I have some more dilaudid?
[ scoffs ]
[ monitor beeping ]
No response
to painful stimuli at all.
It's progressing.
Well, maybe something will show
during the spinal tap.
Have you seen this?
Is that road rash?
He was wearing a suit.
Boggy to the touch. You think
there's an abscess underneath?
Will you hand me
that wood's lamp over there?
Thinking fungal infection?
If it is, it'll show up
under the black light.
It's not fungus.
It's "Carol."
[ indistinct conversations ]
Brett?
Carol.
Um...I had you paged.
We need to...talk.
What's going on?
Do you know anything
about Jack's tattoo?
Oh, God.
Are -- are you having an affair
with my brother?
Carol, you've...known him
since he was a kid,
And you're his boss.
[ sighs ]
We didn't
mean for it to happen.
Look, the --
the tattoo's infected.
I need to know
where he got it.
Barbados.
It's a tattoo parlor
in Bridgetown
Where they specialize
in U.V. tattoos.
When did he get it?
Nine days ago.
So, you weren't
at a conference in Toledo?
No.
Brett...After
your mother passed,
Jack had no one else
that he could talk to.
How about his wife?
He never
wanted to marry Annabelle.
That was
your father's pick.
All right, you know
that everything that Jack does,
Your father
pulls the strings.
Why do you think
he's so miserable?
I didn't know he was.
Since you left, everything
your father wanted for you --
Now it's on Jack.
Now, you can think what you want
about me, but, please...
[ voice breaking ]
...Don't let him die.
Bones!
[ whistles ]
[ dog food rattles ]
yo, Bones! Come here, boy!
[ Bones growling ]
Bones!
Hey, that better not be
another shoe.
What the hell? Ugh!
[ Dante laughs ]
Man:
Why, you lame brain!
You want a whiskey?
I got to drive home.
So, you crash here.
Why would I
want to crash here
When I got a lake house
to stay in, huh?
You're the one
who's in hiding.
Bastard.
Don't talk about mom
that way.
[ laughs ]
[ gunshot ]
the hell?
Hey.
Fellas, how's it going?
What are you watching?
Oh, the three stooges.
I love the stooges, huh?
It's appropriate.
A couple of clowns sitting
around watching the stooges.
Sit down.
I want you guys to know
I'm disappointed in you.
You --
I saved your life.
And you -- both of you --
I came up with a deal
That's gonna make you
a whole bunch of money.
And this is
what you do to me, huh?
You set me up?
You try to kill me?
You send me a pipe bomb
like some coward?
What are you
talking about?
You're telling --
you're saying we sent the bomb?
That's --
that's insane.
I can prove it wasn't us.
Look on the table here.
It's our contract
for the gaming machines.
I signed them over to you
two weeks ago --
Before you got sent
that bomb.
So what?
So your company owns the rights
to the machines even if you die.
Why would I kill you?
I need you.
So,
what are you saying?
You haven't done any business
with Jimmy Needles lately?
Not to
blow up your place.
And your code's not 4-4-7?
What? What are you
looking at?
That's our number.
I didn't do anything.
He's lying!
He doesn't have to lie.
He's holding a gun.
Hey, come on.
Come on. Come on.
[ breathing deeply ]
What about you?
[ sighs ]
I never liked
the terms of our deal.
But I accepted them.
My brother --
he didn't feel that way.
I never thought
he would try to take you out.
I believe you.
Really, I do.
So,
what's your next move?
[ breathes deeply ]
I'm gonna bury him outside,
and if you and I are square...
[ sighs ]
...Then we're
back in business.
Of course, I'm gonna be
absorbing your brother's shares.
I'm sure
he would understand.
So, we square?
[ sighs ] yeah.
Sorry for your loss.
The infection could be
from a dirty tatoo needle.
M.R.S.A.?
Can't be.
No fever,
normal white count.
There's no evidence
of cellulitis.
Necrotizing fasciitis?
That doesn't explain
the neuro deficits.
What about botulism?
I mean,
the symptoms fit --
Weakness,
then descending paralysis.
Eyes, respiratory, upper,
then lower extremities,
And we have a source.
Yes, very good.
How do we confirm it?
Culture the wound.
Uh, send out
for a botulism assay.
In the meantime, we'll dose him
with heavy antitoxin.
Do it.
[ indistinct conversations ]
Hey. Grace.
You remember that patient you
saw this morning, Tiffany Evans?
Yeah, the addict
who cries wolf. Why?
You missed
a mesenteric artery thrombosis.
You did a C.T.?
Yeah.
And then I performed
a thrombectomy.
She's in recovery.
Wow. Then you
saved her life.
Not that you'll
rub that in or anything.
Yeah,
maybe a little bit.
God, the one time I stand up
to her, fate screws me.
But this time fate
screwed us both.
She flunked you
on the survey?
Post-surgery,
I recommended her
To a pain-management specialist
who took her off dilaudid.
Grace: Hey.
Federal courthouse
is right over there.
Dad used to call it
his tennis court.
[ chuckles ]
Jack and I called him McEnroe
'cause he'd let us skip school
To come watch him mop the floor
with sleazy defense attorneys.
Sounds like
you admired him.
I was young.
Six years ago, my mother
found a lump on her breast.
It was... Cancer.
And my dad asked her
to delay chemo
Until after
his confirmation hearings
So that there wouldn't be
the perception
That he was distracted.
Oh.
So, she delayed... Five weeks,
against doctors' orders,
And it... Spread...
To her lymph nodes.
My dad gave the eulogy
at her funeral.
He said
that she was his soul mate,
That she was
the love of his life,
And then he cried... And made
the cover of Time magazine...
Which is now framed
in his office.
[ clears throat ]
Good save,
Dr. Robinson.
Your brother's responding
to the botulism antitoxin
And antibiotics.
He's already off the vent.
[ sighs ] I must have
bit it hard, huh?
[ sighs ]
compound wrist fracture.
Ortho had to put a pin in it,
so no, uh, strumming it
For at least eight weeks,
okay?
Good thing I'm ambidextrous.
[ chuckles ]
Your, uh, throat's gonna be sore
from being intubated.
So, you had
a wound botulism.
That's why you lost control
and crashed.
Botulism?
From a dirty
tattoo needle.
It's...Still there.
Who knows?
Just Carol...
And your doctors.
So, let's hear it.
Let's hear it.
You're shocked.
You're disappointed.
No. I'm sorry, Jack.
Just... Sorry.
For what?
For living your life?
For getting the hell away
from dad?
I wish
I had half your guts.
So, what now?
You're on a 10-day regimen
of antibiotics.
No, I meant
with the family.
They're gonna
ask questions.
What do you
want me to do?
[ sighs ]
It's possible
that he contracted the botulism
From a dented can of corn,
but he's gonna be okay.
You saved my son's life,
doctor.
If there's ever
anything you need...
Oh, it's --
it's what we do.
Don't be
such a stranger, okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
Catch you later.
Okay.
All right,
I should be going.
Wait. Wait, son.
I know
Jack wasn't in Toledo.
I'm proud of the way you handled
things -- with the family.
Dad,
I didn't lie for you.
I lied because of you.
I thought
you might be thirsty.
I brought you
a gift.
Oh, you've got
a sick sense of humor.
[ chuckles ]
we both do.
Oh, yeah?
Boom.
Very funny.
Oh, it's cold.
So, Stavos told me
you took care of the bomber.
Do I know him?
[ cork pops ]
Yeah. Dante Amato.
And the bastard was even keeping
it secret from his brother.
Hmm.
You know,
it's a funny business.
He and I used to
be good friends.
I think
you should propose a toast.
Oh, yeah?
Why not?
You got so much
to be thankful for.
Well, here's to
what you got on your mind.
[ glasses clink ]
Sorry.
Not now, Gio.
Somebody's here to see you,
boss -- tells me it's urgent.
All right.
Let him in.
He's clean.
I need to talk to you --
in private.
Who the hell
is this guy?
I've never
seen you before.
It's been a long time.
Let me
tell you something, kid.
I never forget a face.
Then look closer.
It's me, dad.
Sync and corrected
by www.addic7ed.com