My name is Elena Gilbert.
I'm a vampire.
♪
You're sired to me, Elena.
Everything you think you fell,
might not even be real.
But there's
hope now.
Tell them what the hunter
told you the tattoo leads to.
He said there was
a cure.
Everyone wants it
for a different reason.
For revenge...
Ohh!
To be human
an in love...
For the truth...
I'm setting you
free, Elena.
And some will
stop at nothing to get it.
Do it!
Carol Lockwood
always said that togetherness,
in times of tragedy,
leads to healing.
That one community is stronger
than a thousand of its members.
But how does a community
stay strong
after losing its leader?
And Carol was so much
more than just a mayor.
She was...
An open-minded friend...
And a concerned mother,
taken from us too soon
by a terrible accident.
Screw this.
Tyler.
Please join me in observing
a minute of silence
in her memory.
You ok?
I'll be right back.
Thank you very much.
In the wake of this tragedy, the
town has selected an interim mayor.
Many of you already know him.
Please welcome Mr. Rudy Hopkins.
Thank you, sheriff.
Carol Lockwood put
this town first,
and that's why I'm here
to talk to you guys.
You folks...
April?
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm fine.
But you're crying.
It's just the whole
mayor thing.
You know,
it's bringing up stuff with my dad.
And I know you're
a vampire.
Wait. What?
Oh, was that
necessary?
No, but it was fun.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/
Hey, you just missed
the mandatory
all-school assembly.
Well, that's because I'm
at a mandatory all-alone
drinking party.
Seriously?
You decided to go
on a ripper
bender now?
My brother slept with Elena.
Kind of puts a little bit
of a damper on things.
First of all,
you are not supposed to know that.
Second of all, Tyler is already
spiraling, and he gets priority.
His mother just died.
What do you expect?
I'm his girlfriend.
I expect him to talk to me.
But instead he's all angry,
and it doesn't help that
everyone keeps referring to his
mother's death as an accident,
which is really just a polite
way of saying that she was drunk.
You think Klaus
killed her?
Well, I don't think
she drowned in a Martini glass.
Just get it together.
I can't do it alone.
The assembly's over.
What the hell's going on?
The school will
be empty soon.
How many times
did you compel me?
Don't...
Just don't lie.
Rebekah says
you lie.
Rebekah's not who you
think she is, April.
What, she's not a thousand-year-old
original vampire?
Listen, we can
figure this out, ok,
but we have
to get out of here.
Sorry.
Not allowed.
Why don't you
take a seat?
The rest of the class
will be here shortly.
First saved message.
Hey, it's me.
Look, I know
why you sent me away.
You think that what I'm feeling for
you is because of the sire bond,
but I hate not being
near you.
Go ahead.
Make a move.
I drove up here to be your wingman,
not kick your ass.
Aah! Ok.
I get it.
You're a badass.
You see that?
Couldn't miss it.
It was in slow motion.
Then teach me
something useful.
We've been here
for days, and so far
all you've done
is bark orders.
Ok.
Take a seat at
the bench, quarterback.
Karate kid wts
a anot at the title.
Jeremy, you're
not ready for this.
Well?
Now, all I have to do is apply
a little pressure under your jaw.
Really? Again?
Ok.
Double pepperoni
3 days in a row.
You guys eat
anything else?
Why?
Are you offering?
A little something
extra, cut off
the pizza pipeline
for a couple days.
No matter how much they beg,
don't come back.
Sorry, guys.
You're gonna
starve us now?
If that's what it takes
to make you a hunter.
Now run around
the lake, twice.
Keep him company.
I don't have
to listen to you.
You do
if you want to eat.
Being
near you, and I miss you, Damon.
I wish you would just
let me come to you.
What?
Guess who.
I'm back, dagger-free,
and I'm holding Elena
hostage at the High School.
Just thought you should know.
Who the hell was
dumb enough
to pull that dagger
out of you?
I'll be asking
the questions today.
See ya soon.
I'm only ready to talk to you
if you're ready
to rejoin civilization.
How would you like to drive the white
oak stake through Rebekah's heart?
If it means you're not drinking your
way through the mystic grill, sure.
So...
First speech
under your belt.
Now for the fun part.
Welcome to the world
of careful cover-ups.
We've ruled Carol's death
as head trauma from a fall.
That's the official
autopsy.
She did not go
gently, did she?
Any leads?
We have ideas.
Let me guess.
Sharp teeth and bad
table manners?
You sure you want this?
I mean, 6 people were
offered this job before you.
They all said no
for a reason.
I'm saying yes
for a reason,
and my reason
just walked in.
I'll let you know what we find.
Thank you, sheriff.
Hey, sheriff.
Hey, dad.
- Hey.
- So...
Far cry from being
a traveling pharmaceutical rep.
I noticed a few of your friends
missing from the assembly.
So much for mandatorat
I guess, huh?
Dad, stop it.
You can't come in here
and start making rules.
I think this town could
use a few more rules.
You're forgetting I can
help protect the town.
I am well aware
of your gifts, Bonnie...
But don't forget
I'm your father.
That means that I get
to protect you.
Hello, Stefan.
I'm here.
What do you want?
The same thing I wanted when
you helped make Klaus stab me.
The cure.
I hope you're not waiting for
Caroline to show up and stake me...
Because I already
found her.
Stefan.
Did I say
you could move?
Class is in session.
You've all been compelled.
You know the rules.
Answer my questions
honestly,
no disobedience,
no one leaves.
April, my sweet,
take notes.
This is how you get
answers in this town.
Let's start with
a little quiz.
In the year 1114, my brother
learned... thanks to yours truly...
About a brotherhood of
vampire hunters with tattoos
that grew with each kill.
And these tattoos
reveal what? Elena?
A map.
Which led to,
Caroline?
A cure for vampirism.
Perfect.
We're all caught up.
Stefan Salvatore, the last time
we saw each other,
you had a vampire hunter,
but in order to decode the map,
you needed the location
of the hunter's sword,
which you got out of me
using some very dirty tricks.
Assuming you found the sword,
you must have found the cure,
and yet you're all
still vampires,
which means something
went wrong.
What are you doing?
You asked me
to take notes.
I wasn't being
literal, darling.
But now that you mention it,
a flow chart would be nice,
which means index cards
and push pins. Go fetch.
You're wasting
your time.
We don't know
anything.
So you just gave up?
I thought you'd do
anything to save Elena,
even if it meant taking
the cure yourself
so you could grow old
and die with her.
Why do you look
so surprised?
I'm missing something.
What is it?
They broke up, ok?
Now let us go.
Broke up?
Wait. I'm confused.
I thought Elena was
your epic love, Stefan.
I asked you what happened,
and you have to tell me.
She slept with Damon.
Good.
Now...
Now do it like your life
depends on it 'cause it does.
Don't act like you care
about my life.
You care about the hunter's
mark and curing Elena
so she's not sired
to your ass.
Both require you
to be alive,
which is why I've updated our relationship
status to "it's complicated."
You talked
to her at all?
Elena?
Maybe.
Why? Run out of
voicemails to listen to?
I'm sorry.
Did I interrupt play time?
What the hell are
you doing here?
I'm simply
appreciating
the sights and
smells of nature,
neither of which
presently include
rotting
vampire flesh,
so I'm a bit
concerned.
How many vampires
has he killed?
If we throw Jeremy out into
the world right now, he's chum.
Now, see,
that's not a number.
12... that's
a number.
That's how many
of my hybrids
I slaughtered
with my sword.
3... that's how many
days it took
to quell the urge to
kill your brother, after
he knowingly watched
as I walked into a death trap.
One...
That's the number of
purposes you serve.
You are here to
grow Jeremy's mark,
so I ask again...
How many vampires has
he killed since he's been here?
Zero.
Hmm. That's a pity.
I'm going to need
that cure
sooner rather
than later,
hybrid shortage
and all.
How can I help?
You know...
Now that you mention it,
Jeremy...
Watch and learn.
That's for Carol Lockwood.
So, vampire Elena is
a trollop who likes bad boys,
which explains why Stefan
reeks of alcohol.
But what it doesn't explain
is why sweet, loving,
innocent Elena could be
so heartless towards Stefan.
How could she hurt you
like that? Answer, please.
She didn't know it
at the time,
but she was sired to Damon.
A sire bond. Fascinating.
And what do you think
about that, Elena?
I think you're sad
and bored
and in desperate need
of a hobby.
You're hiding something.
'Fess up.
I didn't sleep with Damon
because of his sire bond.
I slept with Damon because
I'm in love with him.
What does any of this have
to do with the stupid cure?
You're right.
We got off the point.
Stefan, how do I
find the cure?
Unless you'd rather talk
about Damon and Elena all day.
There's a Professor.
He knows where the cure is.
Thank you. And, uh,
where do I find this Professor?
Oh, and so now I'm "gifted"?
He hates my witch heritage.
That's why he travels all the time.
He can't handle it.
And suddenly he wants to
be a protective father?
No. Not like this.
Come on. Distract me.
Isn't there some...
Magic therapy thing you
haven't shown me yet?
Listen, Bonnie, I hate
to tell you this...
Actually, you know what?
I take that back.
I'm proud
to tell you this.
You don't need
my help anymore.
In fact...
I was hoping to present this
with a cupcake or something.
Happy graduation.
It's beautiful.
It's human bone.
Oh.
Legend says it was worn
by the 2,000-year-old
witch Qetsiyah,
who drew on it...
For strength.
Bonnie, you have come
so far so fast.
If you trust
my opinion,
your magic is exactly
where it needs to be.
Does this mean
I have to go home?
It means I got a stack of papers
I got to grade by tomorrow.
I can take a hint.
Thanks, Shane.
Oh, my God.
Kol.
Shane?
I told you I don't
want to talk.
I heard. You're
keeping all that rage
bottled up inside.
Caroline's worried
sick about you.
Rebekah?
Hello, Tyler.
I heard my brother made
a real mess of your life.
Believe me, I can relate.
You have my condolences.
In fact, why don't you come down to the high
school so you can accept them in person?
And why would I
do that?
Because I have
your girlfriend.
Maybe you have a better shot at
saving her than you did your mother.
Sister...
Look at this.
You're even worse
than Klaus.
Kol. Finally.
Did you bring me
what I asked for?
You must be Shane.
If you're here
for payback, go for it.
But you'll be stuck baby-sitting
the little hunter that could.
You know...
If you adjust your angle a little
bit, you'll find a sharper edge.
I know how
to whittle. Thanks.
Now I know why those
hybrids hated you.
You are annoying.
Actually,
I'm just perplexed
as to why Jeremy hasn't
killed any vampires.
Darwinism, Klaus.
He needs to be able
to protect himself
before we hunt down
his first vampire nest.
And here was I, thinking
you were the fun brother.
Well, let's play
a little game, shall we?
Jeremy needs more victims,
and there's a whole town of people
down the road just waiting to be
turned into vampires for the slaughter.
You don't think that
occurred to me, Klaus?
The tragedy is, Damon,
it did occur to you,
yet you chose to ignore it.
And my guess is you did it
to impress Elena.
Somehow, to honor her, you'll
find a way to spare innocent lives
and walk Jeremy down
the moral high road.
That's why I've already made
the necessary corrections.
What did you do?
Don't tell me he ordered
another pizza.
No, I'm just an idiot.
I ran out of gas
and my phone's dead.
Think I could use yours?
Yeah, come on in.
I'll run upstairs
and grab my cell.
What the hell?
What are you doing here?
Car drama.
Your friend just went
to go get his phone.
Well, I'm about
to go take a shower,
but you're more than
welcome to wait inside.
Thanks.
Kol...
And Rebekah Mikaelson,
two members of
the original vampire family.
This is such a trip.
Where's the cure?
Compulsion won't work.
It's a little trick
I picked up in Tibet.
Right. Well, we'll just have to
do this the old-fashioned way.
Beat him until he tells
you where to find it.
Still glued
to your seats?
Ooh, it's thick
with tension in here.
Let's spice things
up a bit.
Elena, truth or dare?
We're done playing your
stupid games, Rebekah.
Truth or dare,
Elena?
You're compelled.
Answer.
Dare.
I dare you
to tell Stefan
the truth
about Damon.
Seriously?
Being with Damon
makes me happy.
Clowns make you happy,
Elena.
Dig a little deeper.
When I'm with him...
It feels
unpredictable, like...
Like I'm free.
And how do you feel
when you're with Stefan?
Stop.
She can't.
She's compelled.
Lately, I feel
like I'm a project,
like I'm a problem
that needs to be fixed.
I think I make him sad,
and I can't be with
someone like that
because...
When he looks at me, all
he sees is a broken toy.
Do you still love
Stefan?
Yes.
Are you still
in love with Stefan?
No.
Did that hurt,
having someone you love drive
a dagger through your heart?
Go to hell.
Did... that... hurt?
Yes.
Welcome to the last
900 years of my life.
Ah, good, you're here.
It was just getting depressing.
What the hell is going on?
Listen to the rules
carefully.
Stay in the building.
No vamp-running in the hallways.
Vamp-running
from what?
- Turn.
- What?
You can't.
He'll lose control.
That's the whole point.
I've exhausted all
your knowledge.
Now I have the Professor
to help me find the cure,
you're just competition.
Whoever finds it first gets
to decide what to do with it:
Use it, share it,
destroy it, save it...
I want that to be me.
But if I turn,
I'll kill them.
Yes, you will.
Turn.
Did you find
your phone?
Get off!
Bonnie?
Rebekah told me that
you're a witch.
Rebekah? What the hell
is going on?
Rebekah has Stefan, Elena,
and Caroline compelled.
She's getting them to actually
tell the truth for a change.
What?
Shane can't be compelled.
She'll have him torture him
to find out what he knows.
What are you looking for?
I need salt.
I think I just
saw some.
What are you doing?
If this pendant will
connect me to Shane,
then I can do
a protection spell.
Where is the cure?!
Ohh!
Where is the cure?
You're human.
Why do you want it anyway?
That's the beauty
of this.
You can have it.
I just want Silas.
No.
What do you know
about Silas?
He's the world's first
immortal being,
who just happens to be
imprisoned with the cure.
And I want to free him.
No!
April?
What's happening?
Stop!
He's of no use dead.
Did you not hear
what he said?
Silas will kill us
all, sister.
Silas does not exist.
He is a fairy tale
made up to scare children
into eating their vegetables.
Silas is very real.
I know where he's buried,
and soon I'll have
the spell that wakes him.
Wait a second.
You're lying.
You can't get to him
without his...
Tombstone?
Dozens to die in
a blood sacrifice?
Believe me, I know.
I've done it.
Those massacres are
a pain to engineer.
You're the one who got
the council blown up.
It was
a noble sacrifice...
And temporary
because once
I raise Silas...
Silas will raise the dead.
He will bring back
every last soul...
Who died on his behalf.
No!
April, oh, my God!
Wait.
I can fight it.
Aah! Get out of here!
Go.
That door's
not gonna hold him.
You should be
thanking me.
You killed my only chance
at finding the cure.
Silas on the loose would
be hell on earth.
And frankly, sister...
I don't think you
could handle it.
How did you
get that?
Way too easily.
Bonnie.
Help! Someone help!
Bonnie, what's going on?
She needs help.
What happened?
I did a protection spell,
but it accidentally linked
Shane to April.
And you
couldn't control it?
I didn't even know
I was doing it.
Usually I feel pain or I
bleed, but this time I just
felt more power.
It's ok. It's ok.
You're ok. You're ok.
You're ok. Ok.
Bonnie, get her out of
the school.
Just be careful.
Tyler is out there, and he turned.
What about you?
No, we can't leave.
Rebekah's compelled us.
Just go.
We'll deal with her later.
Stefan...
No.
Stefan, we have to
talk about this. Please.
Talk about what,
huh?
How many more ways are there
for you to rip my heart out?
I'm sorry.
Sorry that it happened,
or sorry that I found out?
I'm sorry
about all of it.
I'm really sorry, Stefan.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I didn't want that.
Why are my least favorite
people always the most durable?
Tyler...
I'm so sorry.
It wasn't your fault.
Yes, it was.
This whole thing.
It's all my fault.
No, Tyler.
I should have
saved her.
Leave her out of this.
This is between
me and you.
You're still
protecting her?
Must I rip your bleeding
heart from your chest
and show you the scar tissue
that is Elena Gilbert?
There's
a solution
to all your
problems, you know.
I could compel him...
Erase every memory
he has of you.
Every day you've
spent together,
every kiss, every lie,
every ounce of pain.
I can take away every bit
of love he has for you,
give you both
a clean slate.
Just say the word,
and I'll make you
and all that misery you've
caused him disappear.
Do it.
Excuse me?
Erase it all.
Every memory.
Stefan, no.
I said do it.
No. That would be
far too easy.
I refuse to make
you forget her
the way Klaus made you
forget me.
But at least you know
how he really feels.
Consider your eternity of
pain my revenge, Stefan.
I've used you for
all you're worth.
So now you're free to go.
Stefan, wait.
Turns out I miscalculated.
Kol's gonna be a problem.
I almost killed someone,
and that's what
you miscalculated?
April could've
died today.
That's only because you didn't
know the extent of your abilities.
My father just
became mayor.
I can't be out
doing black magic.
That's not what
expression is.
Then what is it?
It's a way of doing magic
that isn't monitored by
nature or the spirits.
It isn't good nor bad.
But it also has
no limits,
so how you use it is
up to you.
That's what
I'm here for...
To help you.
Bonnie, listen to me.
You are the key to everything.
I'm not going to let
anything bad happen to you.
Hope your day is going
better than mine.
Got to say,
I'm liking the odds.
Stefan knows about us.
Ooh.
How'd he take it?
How do you think?
I'm thinking,
for the first time all week,
I'm happy to be
at camp nowhere.
How's Jeremy?
That depends on
how much you trust me.
You know that I trust you.
Then I think he's gonna get
through this thing just fine.
Thanks for looking
out for him.
Yeah, well,
I told them if they were good,
I'd buy them both ice cream,
so I got to go.
Not yet.
Something happened today.
I realized something
about you, about us.
And you can say
that it's the sire bond,
and you know what?
Maybe... maybe it is,
but I'm telling you
it's the most real thing
I love you, Damon.
I love you.
Look.
I'm going to get
this cure for you.
And I'm gonna have to
do things you don't like.
Damon...
But listen carefully.
Get in your car
right now.
Come to me.
I'll be there soon.
You let yourself in.
You called me.
Should I be checking
for hidden daggers?
Do you still want
to find the cure?
More than anything.
I want to ram it down
Niklaus' throat
and look into his eyes
as he realizes he's mortal again.
But Shane's dead
and you are useless,
so I'm right back
where I started.
Shane's not dead.
But I watched
Kol impale him.
Well, you probably shouldn't
have left him alone.
Bonnie did a little spell.
He's perfectly fine.
You didn't have
to tell me that.
Why am I really
here?
You were right.
I'm gonna be here
for an eternity,
and I will go insane
if I don't know
how Elena truly feels
about my brother.
If you really
want the cure,
you should know that
Shane has an agenda,
and it's a dark one.
He said he organized dozens
of people to die in sacrifice.
He admitted to the council
explosion where 12 people died,
and I'm guessing
it's not a coincidence
that 12 hybrids died at
the hand of my brother.
12...
Channeling the energy
from a mass death is used
in witchcraft to
perform dark spells.
It's called expression.
Shane admitted
all this to you?
Proudly.
Well, then I guess we'll have
to figure out how to manage him
while we find the cure
for ourselves.
"We"?
There's no "we,"
Stefan.
Listen, I hate my brother,
and you hate yours.
But Damon's got Jeremy,
and Klaus has the sword,
and Shane has Bonnie.
You and I are the only ones
left with nothing.
You said it yourself,
right?
Whoever finds
the cure first
gets to decide
what to do with it.
What do you say?
You want to be partners?
My father had no reason
to kill 11 people.
He had no reason
to kill himself.
He loved me.
He loved Mystic Falls.
He was brainwashed into
sparking that fire.
Professor Shane
organized his death
and the 11 others
who died with him.
It's time this entire town
started telling the truth.
I was beginning to worry
you boys wouldn't find
the place.
What the hell...?
Did you kill all
these people?
Not exactly.
They're
in transition.
Killing them is your job.
You said you were
going to convince Klaus
to do this
another way.
I thought about it.
And then I realized
his idea was better.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.addic7ed.com/