×ÖÄ»
A few months ago, I discovered I had a twin sister.
And then she she asked me to take her place,
×ÖÄ»
keep the secret, find our real mother
and try to stay alive.
×ÖÄ»
Put yourself in my shoes.
How long could you keep up the lying game?
×Ö
Not interested.
Ä»
Oh, is that right?
×ÖÄ»
You u ididt , so I slept with him.
It was a mistake, Sutton.
×ÖÄ»
Ted, about the therapy session on Monday,
I'll be there.
×ÖÄ»
I'm so happy for you.
What's going on here?
×ÖÄ»
I was just thanking her for tutoring me.
You know what?
×ÖÄ»
It doesn't matter.
Care to make things interesting?
×ÖÄ»
You want to switch back?
Whoever loses has to stay in the cabin.
×ÖÄ»
That phone I found exonerated him. I can't beat him.
The only mistake I made was taking your bastard ass in.
×ÖÄ»
Hey, hey!
There is nothing left for me here anymore.
×ÖÄ»
What about me?
Tough break, but a deal's a deal.
×ÖÄ»
I left some clean towels for you at the cabin.
I've gotten the feeling that he might blame me for his arrest.
×ÖÄ»
Hey, baby, I'm home.
Good morning, sunshine.
×ÖÄ»
Uh, what are you doing?
Just watching you sleep.
×ÖÄ»
I missed that.
Well, isn't that romantic?
×ÖÄ»
I've been in prison for a while.
I can't believe I'm actually here with you.
×ÖÄ»
Was it worth the wait?
You tell me.
×ÖÄ»
So, your first day as a free man.
What are your plans?
×ÖÄ»
I was thinking maybe we could take that
honeymoon we've been putting off.
×ÖÄ»
Oh, well, that sounds great, but...
where are we gonna go on such short notice?
×ÖÄ»
As it turns out, I got a little spot I know about.
A little bed and breakfast? Hmm.
×ÖÄ»
A five-star resort and spa?
Ah, now, it wouldn't be a surprise
×ÖÄ»
if I told you, would it?
Oh, well, come on, just a little hint.
×ÖÄ»
Please tell me.
Let's just say that this weekend
×ÖÄ»
my bride finally gets everything she deserves.
It's Thayer.
×ÖÄ»
You know what to do.
Hey, it's me again.
Ä»
I tried your cell and you didn't answer,
×Ö
so I'm trying you here.
×ÖÄ»
I just want to know that you're okay.
I hate the way we left things.
×ÖÄ»
Please call me.
Thayer?
×ÖÄ»
Nope, it's me.
I wanted to see how your night at the cabin was.
×ÖÄ»
You're checking on me?
Well, of course, you're my sister.
×ÖÄ»
Plus, I know how lonely it can get there.
Yeah, I can't argue with that.
×ÖÄ»
But it's just for a few days, right?
We're switching back after tennis regionals.
×ÖÄ»
That was the deal.
Anyway, I'm calling
×ÖÄ»
because I wanted to make sure you're not mad at me
×Ö
for what I told you
Ä»
the other day about, you know.
×ÖÄ»
About you sleeping with Ethan?
I told you, it's fine.
×ÖÄ»
Really?
Yes, sleep with whomever you want.
×ÖÄ»
Just promise me you won't do anything
to rock the boat with Ted and Kristin.
×ÖÄ»
If you haven't noticed,
They're getting along better now.
×ÖÄ»
I get it, Emma.
You have my word.
×ÖÄ»
And, in fact, I think you'll find that
×Ö
I am going to be a sweeter, nicer version of myself
Ä»
than you.
×ÖÄ»
Do you have a sec?
You have nothing to worry about. I have to go.
×ÖÄ»
What's up?
I wanted to talk to you about what happened last night.
×ÖÄ»
What happened last night?
When I saw Jordan kissing Mads outside?
×ÖÄ»
Oh, right, yeah, that...
That was rough.
×ÖÄ»
I thought things were going so well between me and Jordan,
and then Mads just totally goes behind my back...
×ÖÄ»
Okay, look, Laurel.
What you need to remember
×ÖÄ»
is that Jordan Lyle is a worldly,
older, dangerously sexy guy
×ÖÄ»
who, let's face it,
is way out of your league.
×ÖÄ»
If I remember correctly, uh, the other day,
you said he'd be lucky to have me.
×ÖÄ»
And clearly you blew it,
so I think you should move on.
×ÖÄ»
I mean, go for some lower hanging fruit like a sophomore.
Or one of those guys in the clubs
×ÖÄ»
in the back of the yearbook.
I-I don't get it.
×ÖÄ»
I know, I know.
Love-- it's very confusing.
×ÖÄ»
I'm hungry for breakfast, though.
I'm thinking tofu scramble?
aaaa
aaa
×ÖÄ»
What are you doing here?
Hi, kiddo. Your father has some news.
×ÖÄ»
What is it?
Well, remember all that pro bono work I was doing
×ÖÄ»
at the burn clinic last summer?
Turns out i was just named
×ÖÄ»
Phoenix Surgical Humanitarian of the Year.
That's awesome.
×ÖÄ»
Is there, like, some kind of ceremony or something?
Yeah, the banquet's tomorrow.
×ÖÄ»
Originally I was gonna go myself,
but then, since they're giving me this award,
×ÖÄ»
I was kind of hoping...
Well, of course, we'll be there.
×ÖÄ»
There's one more thing.
They usually ask the recipient's significant
×ÖÄ»
other to say a few words before the presentation.
So I guess the committee doesn't know about our situation?
×ÖÄ»
Actually, I was going to mention it,
but then I thought things were going
×ÖÄ»
pretty well between us, so...
I know it's a lot to spring on you.
×ÖÄ»
Maybe we can discuss it during family therapy tomorrow.
Maybe.
×ÖÄ»
Great. I'll see you then.
Bye.
×ÖÄ»
Bye, Dad.
Bye, hon.
×ÖÄ»
Bye.
Well, that was awkward.
×ÖÄ»
We are going, right, Mom?
Of course, of course.
×ÖÄ»
But, I mean, for me to be giving a speech is...
Mom, please, it would mean so much to him.
×ÖÄ»
And you guys have been doing better.
Well, yes, in the sense
×ÖÄ»
that we can be in the same room without fighting.
But for me to stand up in front of an audience
×ÖÄ»
and pretend that we're a happy couple...
No, why don't Laurel and I do it?
×ÖÄ»
Really?
I mean, sure, yeah, we can do it.
×ÖÄ»
Sweetie, it's short notice.
Do you have time to prepare a speech?
×ÖÄ»
For a bunch of nerdy doctors? Yeah.
Plus, I already know what I'm going to say.
×ÖÄ»
Mads, I wasn't expecting you.
Uh, because I'm not here to see you.
×ÖÄ»
Hey, is this about last night?
'Cause until Laurel had her little meltdown,
×ÖÄ»
you and I were getting pretty hot and...
I'm not here to discuss that.
×ÖÄ»
Okay, why are you here?
Maddie?
×ÖÄ»
Hi, honey.
Hi.
×ÖÄ»
Oh, I'm so glad to see you.
Me, too.
×ÖÄ»
You good? ALEC: Yes.
Mr. Rybak,
×ÖÄ»
we didn't get a chance to meet last night.
I'm Jordan Lyle.
×ÖÄ»
Jordan. Rebecca's stepson. Yes, sir.
You can call me Alec. All right.
×ÖÄ»
I see you two have already met? Barely.
We've bumped into each other a couple times, yeah.
×ÖÄ»
Hmm, well, glad you're acquainted.
Maddie, since I've moved in here with Rebecca,
×ÖÄ»
I was kind of hoping you might think about doing the same.
Really?
×ÖÄ»
That's an interesting idea, sir.
We'll see.
×ÖÄ»
It's good to see that everybody's getting to know each other.
Honey, did you tell them about our honeymoon plans?
×ÖÄ»
Honeymoon?
Um, yeah...
×ÖÄ»
Sutton?
What are you doing here?
×ÖÄ»
Well, the door was open, so...
So you just walked in?
×ÖÄ»
Well, my godfather is back and
I was just so excited to see him.
×ÖÄ»
Well, you're kind of interrupting a family moment.
So let me show you out.
×ÖÄ»
Okay, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize I was walking
×ÖÄ»
into the Bizarro family reunion back there.
Why are you freaking out?
×ÖÄ»
I'm not freaking out.
You were being careless.
×ÖÄ»
Fine, I screwed up, but I'm just really excited to tell you
×Ö
what happened this morning.
Ä»
What?
×ÖÄ»
My dad's getting this award...
What award?
×ÖÄ»
I don't know. I wasn't really listening.
Maybe for giving homeless people free boob jobs or something?
×ÖÄ»
Anyway,
he asked Kristin to introduce him at the ceremony.
×ÖÄ»
She said no.
Guess who offered to speak instead.
×Ö
Excellent.
Ä»
Mm-hmm, and get this:
×ÖÄ»
we're going to family therapy. Mm-hmm.
And don't worry, I already know what I'm going to say.
×ÖÄ»
Okay, even so, I want you to run it by me first.
Our plan is moving to the next phase,
×ÖÄ»
and I don't want to leave anything to chance.
Call me later.
×ÖÄ»
Okay.
Look, if you want to take a break, we...
×ÖÄ»
No, let's just keep going.
We have a ton of chemistry to do left.
×ÖÄ»
Okay.
Emma, I just want you to know that I,
×ÖÄ»
I appreciate you still tutoring me.
'Cause I know you're probably going through
×ÖÄ»
a lot with Thayer leaving.
Ethan, let's not do this.
×ÖÄ»
What?
I'm-I'm just trying to be a friend here.
×ÖÄ»
You're not my friend.
And I may be helping you study here, but I don't want to discuss
×ÖÄ»
Thayer any more than I want to talk about
what happened with you and Sutton.
×ÖÄ»
Of course.
She told you that we slept together after Jordan's party.
×ÖÄ»
It's not my business.
Then, why are you acting like it is?
×ÖÄ»
Because I used to think you were better than that.
What are they doing here?
×ÖÄ»
Oh, crap.
Alec, I know you wanted to surprise me, but this place?
×ÖÄ»
What are we, hillbillies?
×Ö
Hurry, grab everything. They can't know we were here.
Ä»
All right.
×Ö
Is this yours?
Ä»
Doesn't matter, just take it.
×ÖÄ»
Damn it.
Hang on, uh, here, give me a towel, quick.
×ÖÄ»
Here, take this.
Oh, hurry, hurry, hurry.
×ÖÄ»
Your keys.
Got it. Got it.
×ÖÄ»
What?
I'm sorry.
×ÖÄ»
I'm a little rusty.
Oh. Come here.
×ÖÄ»
I had no idea you were so old-fashioned.
Oh, well, there's more surprises where that came from.
×ÖÄ»
That sounds good.
Look, flat screen.
×ÖÄ»
: Are they on their honeymoon?
I guess.
×ÖÄ»
Oh, my God, what if they start getting naked?
Ted bought this place when they were still in diapers.
×ÖÄ»
Now you couldn't pay 'em to come up here.
Ó²×ÖÄ»
×ÖÄ»
Oh, well, I'm sure i will come to love it.
After all, you brought me up here for some reason.
×ÖÄ»
I'm sure I'll figure out what that is.
Why don't I give you the grand tour?
×ÖÄ»
She saw us.
No, she didn't.
×ÖÄ»
Yes, she did. She looked right at me.
Wait, w-wait, slow down, cowboy.
×ÖÄ»
I'm not done with you in this room.
We have to go.
×ÖÄ»
Let's go. There's a window.
Laurel, come on, I want to apologize
×ÖÄ»
for last night, all right? I...
I don't want it to be weird between us.
×ÖÄ»
Hmm, think it's late for that, don't you?
Well, it doesn't have to be.
×ÖÄ»
When you invited me to the club the other night,
I didn't know that was a date. All right, that's my bad.
×ÖÄ»
Look, you're very pretty, all right?
I'm pretty?
×ÖÄ»
Yeah.
Okay, look, Jordan, any misguided feelings
×ÖÄ»
I might have briefly had for you are definitely over,
so you can save your patronizing compliments.
×ÖÄ»
That's fair enough.
Anything else?
×ÖÄ»
All right, let me tell you what.
Let's go grab some breakfast,
×ÖÄ»
and you can yell at me all you want.
What do you say?
×ÖÄ»
I say,
have fun kissing your stepsister, creep.
×ÖÄ»
Well, I didn't see that one coming.
Yeah, Alec honeymooning at the cabin.
×ÖÄ»
I kind of figured him for a Turks and Caicos kind of guy.
You gonna be okay here?
×ÖÄ»
Yeah.
This is the hotel that Sutton stayed
×ÖÄ»
when her car went into the lake.
You want me to come inside with you?
×ÖÄ»
No. I'm fine. Thanks.
So this means tutoring is out, I guess?
×ÖÄ»
No.
Believe it or not, I don't want to see you go back to juvie.
×ÖÄ»
So...
Just meet me back here later.
×ÖÄ»
We'll finish our session.
Hey.
×ÖÄ»
Emma?
Thanks.
×ÖÄ»
Hi, I need a room, please.
It's you.
×ÖÄ»
I'm sorry?
You owe me money.
×ÖÄ»
I do owe you money
from the last time I was here.
×ÖÄ»
What was the bill again?
You know, this isn't about the bill.
×ÖÄ»
I did you a favor.
When that guy came in asking questions,
×ÖÄ»
you paid me to lie and say you were in that room alone.
Right.
×ÖÄ»
Alone, well, I...
I was with that woman.
×ÖÄ»
That woman. You mean women.
What? Wow.
×ÖÄ»
You really did take a knock on the head that night.
Girly, there were two women with you in that room.
×ÖÄ»
Two women? Yeah, two.
So, where's my 80 bucks?
×ÖÄ»
I got to say, this crappy motel room
isn't exactly the ideal place for studying Faulkner.
×ÖÄ»
Yeah.
Maybe if we talk louder,
×ÖÄ»
the hookers next door will learn something.
Hey, maybe that's them now.
×ÖÄ»
Sutton, what are you doing here?
What does it look like I'm doing here?
×ÖÄ»
Ethan gave me a little hint about your cram session.
So I thought I'd hit the books.
×ÖÄ»
Really?
You're here to study?
×ÖÄ»
Well, yeah, thanks to you,
Sutton Mercer has a hefty GPA to maintain, so...
×ÖÄ»
And studying is all that's going on here, right?
What do you think?
×ÖÄ»
Anyway, you know,
I figured you'd be pretty busy working on your speech.
×ÖÄ»
What speech?
Oh, it's nothing.
×ÖÄ»
Just some stupid awards thing for my dad.
Being here brings back so many memories,
×ÖÄ»
which is surprising,
considering I had a head wound last time I was here.
×ÖÄ»
Yeah, funny you should say that,
because when I was checking in,
×ÖÄ»
the desk clerk said something kind of weird to me.
Well, he's weird.
×ÖÄ»
What did he say?
He said that when you were here,
×ÖÄ»
Annie wasn't the only person with you.
Someone else was here.
×ÖÄ»
Did he now?
Well, he was so busy hitting on me that night
×ÖÄ»
that he couldn't have possibly noticed who I was with.
Who did he think he saw?
×ÖÄ»
He didn't say.
But anyway, you're right.
×ÖÄ»
He...
creeped me out, too.
×ÖÄ»
This is nice.
Cloth napkins,
×ÖÄ»
candlelight.
Le poulet en croute.
×ÖÄ»
It's from Celine,
your favorite spot.
×ÖÄ»
Well, you really did think of everything.
It's a very special wine.
×ÖÄ»
I've been saving it for a very special occasion.
I think tonight might just be that night.
×ÖÄ»
Let's celebrate like tonight
is our last night on Earth.
×ÖÄ»
You know, one of the things we never talked about
is what you did the whole time I was gone.
×ÖÄ»
I mean, that must have been tough for you,
having your new husband locked up.
×ÖÄ»
It was.
They were the hardest days of my life.
×ÖÄ»
I'll bet.
Did you ever wonder if I was ever getting out of there?
×ÖÄ»
Now, why would I?
You're an innocent man.
×ÖÄ»
I have faith in the system.
Although there was this one moment.
×ÖÄ»
Oh, it's nothing.
We were both under a lot of stress.
×ÖÄ»
There was this one time that I went to see you in jail,
and... I...
×ÖÄ»
could have thought that you...
thought that I was somehow...
×ÖÄ»
...behind framing you for Derek's murder.
That's crazy talk.
×ÖÄ»
And we both know you were my rock,
you know, through the whole thing.
×Ö
Of course.
Ä» ×ÖÄ»
Plus, if I thought you were framing me about anything,
×Ö
I don't think we'd be sitting here
Ä»
drinking an $800 bottle of wine.
×ÖÄ»
I'd be outside, burying you in the woods.
Not if I buried you first.
×ÖÄ»
Touché.
Hey, girlie, hold up.
×ÖÄ»
Can I help you?
Actually, I was thinking I could help you.
×ÖÄ»
You know how earlier you couldn't remember
how there were two ladies with you that night you were here?
×ÖÄ»
Yes.
My mind was blank, but yes.
×ÖÄ»
So, to jog your memory,
I, uh, put together a couple sketches of the women you were with.
×ÖÄ»
So what do you think?
I think you're a very talented artist, Carl.
×ÖÄ»
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but wasn't our deal that, if I won our tennis match,
×ÖÄ»
you stay hidden until after regionals?
Actually, the deal was that I stay in the cabin,
×ÖÄ»
which is now full of middle-aged honeymooners.
Here.
×ÖÄ»
What is this?
It's a speech.
×ÖÄ»
I was thinking about Ted's awards banquet,
and I just thought I'd help.
×ÖÄ»
That's really sweet of you, Emma,
but I have it covered. Thank you.
×ÖÄ»
Are you sure?
Because this is huge, Sutton.
×ÖÄ»
I mean, the family is going to be together,
and Ted and Kristin are in such a precarious place.
×ÖÄ»
I said no.
LAUREL: Sutton?
×ÖÄ»
Laurel, wait!
What's going on?
×ÖÄ»
Look who finally decided
to do her hair today.
×ÖÄ»
What are you doing? What do you want?
Okay, I can't believe I'm actually about to say this,
×ÖÄ»
but I wanted to thank you
for the advice you gave me about Jordan.
×ÖÄ»
Seriously?
Yeah. I mean, I don't buy
×ÖÄ»
the whole out-of-my-league thing,
but you were right about him being wrong for me.
×ÖÄ»
Well, you're welcome.
I'll show you to...
×ÖÄ»
Actually, no. Uh, so,
after I told off Jordan,
×ÖÄ»
which was incredibly fun, by the way,
I got to wondering.
×ÖÄ»
What's wrong with us?
Why do the Mercer sisters
×ÖÄ»
keep picking the wrong guys?
Justin, Jordan, Ethan?
×ÖÄ»
Is this you giving me love advice?
I'm just asking.
×ÖÄ»
Why are you wasting your time tutoring Ethan, the guy
who broke your heart, when you have someone like Thayer?
×ÖÄ»
Oh, yeah, Thayer.
Of course, he's just so sweet and kind
×ÖÄ»
and loyal as a puppy dog.
You say that like it's a bad thing.
×ÖÄ»
He cares about you.
And for a while there,
×ÖÄ»
I thought you cared about him, too.
Damn it!
×ÖÄ»
Alec? Alec?!
What happened to the power?
×ÖÄ»
Alec? Are you there?
Alec, where are you?
×ÖÄ»
Alec?
Is this a joke?
×ÖÄ»
That was quite a spill you took.
Get away.
×ÖÄ»
You did that on purpose.
What? I know what you're doing.
×ÖÄ»
This whole honeymoon,
the little looks, the cryptic comments.
×ÖÄ»
You're, you're screwing with my head!
I know those lights
×ÖÄ»
didn't go off by themselves.
Yes, they did. That's exactly what happened, honey.
×ÖÄ»
I went outside to check the breakers,
and the box was locked.
×ÖÄ»
I had to come back in and get the key.
I changed it. You're lying.
×ÖÄ»
Why don't you just cut this whole loving husband act
and tell me why you brought me up here?
×ÖÄ»
Do you really think I framed you?
Sweetheart, we've been through this.
×ÖÄ»
If I still thought that, then where are the divorce papers?
What are we doing up here on our honeymoon?
×ÖÄ»
Why would I move into your house and ask
my daughter to do the exact same thing?
×ÖÄ»
How could I possibly make love to you?
Sweetheart, if I thought you betrayed me
×ÖÄ»
and yet did all those things,
what kind of man would that make me?
×ÖÄ»
Come here.
Why do I get the feeling you're not just running late?
×ÖÄ»
I'm sorry.
I would have called earlier,
×ÖÄ»
but something really important came up.
Sound like you're on the road.
×ÖÄ»
I'm on a bus... to L.A.
Of course you are.
×ÖÄ»
I care about him, Ethan.
And we both know you're better off being tutored
×ÖÄ»
by somebody else anyway.
You're right.
×ÖÄ»
Tell Thayer hey.
I'm... really sorry.
×ÖÄ»
So am I.
Thought Sutton was coming over to help you study.
×ÖÄ»
It's a change of plans.
You pissed her off, didn't you?
×ÖÄ»
Yes, I did. Anything else?
Ethan, the way I see it, you can either sit here
×ÖÄ»
and feel sorry for yourself,
or you can go find Sutton and beg for forgiveness.
×ÖÄ»
Because I'm telling you,
her help is the only thing that is standing between you
×ÖÄ»
and a trip back to juvie right now.
It's a good speech, Dan.
×ÖÄ»
Just a little too late.
Look, nobody wants
×ÖÄ»
these two back together more than I do,
but, I mean, one day, they're fighting in public,
×ÖÄ»
and the next day we're in counseling trying
to work things out.
×ÖÄ»
Meanwhile, everyone's miserable..
Honey, it's a process.
×ÖÄ»
Your mother and I are both working very hard to try...
When does it end? I'm sorry,
×ÖÄ»
I know this is going to sound terrible,
but sometimes I look around me and see how
×ÖÄ»
this is affecting everybody,
and I just think maybe the two of you are better off...
×ÖÄ»
What are you saying, Sutton?
You want Mom and Dad to get a divorce just because
×ÖÄ»
it's too hard for you to watch them work things out?
I'm saying that they need to make a decision
×ÖÄ»
and stick with it.
Do you have any idea how selfish you sound right now?
×ÖÄ»
Oh, really, Laurel? And what if Mom actually wants a divorce?
Okay, I think maybe everyone needs to take a little time-out.
×ÖÄ»
Who asked you?
Laurel! That's okay.
×ÖÄ»
Actually, I think...
I think I understand what Sutton is saying.
×ÖÄ»
And in her own way, she's, she's just trying to look out for me.
Why do you think that?
×ÖÄ»
Well, Sutton's always been strong-willed,
and while it hasn't made it easy being her mom,
×ÖÄ»
I've always just admired that strength.
You know, when she was a baby,
×ÖÄ»
the night Sutton came home to live with us was
the happiest of my life, but I was terrified.
×ÖÄ»
I mean, the adoption-- it happened so quickly.
I felt so unprepared.
×ÖÄ»
What if I did something wrong?
What if you cried, and I couldn't comfort you?
×ÖÄ»
I stayed with you in the nursery all night just holding you.
And you know what?
×ÖÄ»
You didn't cry at all.
You were so calm, just looking around,
×ÖÄ»
taking everything in.
I know this sounds crazy, but it was almost...
×ÖÄ»
it's almost like you were being strong for me.
REBECCA:It's great that you intercepted that drawing of me,
×ÖÄ»
but it is just a reminder that we are running out of time.
I think it's time we step things up.
×ÖÄ»
Well, what does that mean exactly?
Because we're doing everything that we can.
×ÖÄ»
Well, are we?
I mean, I hate to say it, Sutton,
×ÖÄ»
but it sounds like family therapy was kind of a bust.
Okay, look, I know it didn't go as well as I had planned,
×ÖÄ»
but I'm working on this speech for the banquet,
and trust me...
×ÖÄ»
I am covering everything:
the lies, the infidelity, the fights
×ÖÄ»
between Ted and Kristin.
Well, that's good,
×ÖÄ»
um, but I think we need to take things a little bit further.
Well, how much further?
×ÖÄ»
I mean, when you take that stage
with Kristin sitting in the front row,
×ÖÄ»
that's when you tell everybody the truth;
that Dr. Ted Mercer is your biological father.
×ÖÄ»
You're kidding. Not at all.
But are you sure?
×ÖÄ»
I mean, look, I know that that's huge,
But don't you think it's a little much?
×ÖÄ»
Plus, people will know that you're my mother if I say that.
I know...
×ÖÄ»
And no one will be more shocked than I.
After all, who knew that you were the daughter
×ÖÄ»
I was forced to give up 17 years ago?
Well, what about Alec?
×ÖÄ»
What's he gonna say when all of this comes out?
Don't worry about that.
×ÖÄ»
You just work on the speech,
and when the time comes,
×ÖÄ»
I'll take care of Alec Rybak.
What's with the suitcase?
×ÖÄ»
I mean, I know we've been kind of been avoiding each other,
but you're moving out?
×ÖÄ»
You're right, I have been avoiding you,
but that's not why I'm leaving.
×ÖÄ»
Um...
my dad is staying at Rebecca's now
×ÖÄ»
and wants me to move in with him tomorrow.
Rebecca's... where Jordan lives.
×ÖÄ»
Unfortunately.
You know, if you liked him, you could have just told me.
×ÖÄ»
Well, the thing is, I don't.
And now I'm just really sorry that this whole
×ÖÄ»
stupid incident came between us.
Yeah, me, too.
×ÖÄ»
We're friends?
Yeah, friends.
×ÖÄ»
Well, then, as your friend--
and I know you say you're not interested--
×ÖÄ»
but I'm totally over Jordan,
so if you're thinking of kissing him again, go for it.
×ÖÄ»
Thank you, but there are a million reasons why
that's never gonna happen,
×ÖÄ»
including the fact that we are practically related.
And you're sure about that?
×ÖÄ»
Positive.
Hi! Thayer, thank God.
×ÖÄ»
Why didn't you call me back?
Did you get my message about the desk clerk telling me
×ÖÄ»
that there were two women at the motel?
Okay, slow down.
×ÖÄ»
What? I thought you'd be happy to see me.
You asked me to come here, and here I am.
×ÖÄ»
Yeah, I am, but I asked you to come with me... two days ago.
I didn't realize there was an expiration date.
×ÖÄ»
Oh, hey! Who's this?
Uh...
×ÖÄ»
uh...
No one.
×ÖÄ»
Emma...
Emma, could you stop for a second?
×ÖÄ»
That girl you saw is just...
What? Payback? Look, maybe
×ÖÄ»
I should have said yes and come with you out here.
But you need to get past the stupid idea
×ÖÄ»
that I have feelings for Ethan!
Okay, listen, I really don't
×ÖÄ»
want to talk about this right now, okay?
Right now or ever?
×ÖÄ»
Listen, stop.
Can I at least give you a ride to the bus station?
×ÖÄ»
Don't bother.
You don't want to keep your blonde waiting.
Ó²×ÖÄ»
×ÖÄ»
Hey. Hi.
Big day, huh?
×ÖÄ»
Yeah.
It could end up being a lot bigger than people realize.
×ÖÄ»
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
×ÖÄ»
Just nervous for my speech.
Still I'm not quite sure what I'm going to say.
×ÖÄ»
Yeah, well, before she left, Emma seemed
kind of worried about that, too.
×ÖÄ»
Big surprise.
She always expects the worst of me.
×ÖÄ»
Well, maybe this is your chance to prove her wrong.
Oh, hey, sweetheart.
×ÖÄ»
Oh, you look beautiful.
Thank you.
×ÖÄ»
You, too.
You feeling nervous about your speech?
×ÖÄ»
Little more than I thought I would.
It's gonna be fine.
×ÖÄ»
Um...
Hey, Mom, that story you told yesterday
×ÖÄ»
at therapy about my first night at home?
How come you never told me that before?
×ÖÄ»
Well, honey, I'm-I'm sure I did.
Maybe it's just the first time you listened.
×ÖÄ»
Oh, my.
Hey there.
×ÖÄ»
Moving in already?
No, not until tomorrow.
×Ö
I'm just dropping off a few things.
Ä» ×ÖÄ»
Why don't you drop your bags and hang out for a minute?
×ÖÄ»
No, thank you.
Well, why don't you let me help you?
×ÖÄ»
Unpack later.
What the hell was that?
×ÖÄ»
Stop smiling.
'Cause whatever you think is about to happen really isn't.
×ÖÄ»
Oh, is that right?
Yeah.
×ÖÄ»
What's really going on here, Mads?
And don't say dropping the sweaters off and stuff,
×ÖÄ»
'cause you could do that tomorrow.
I promised myself I wouldn't.
×ÖÄ»
Well, then, I guess you lied.
×ÖÄ» ×Ö
The biggest gift my father has given me is
Ä»
the example he's set
×ÖÄ»
by donating his time and talents to others in need.
That's why we're here today,
×ÖÄ»
and it's why I'm proud to call him my dad.
So...
×ÖÄ»
I had written a speech
about my dad...
×ÖÄ»
um, bunch of clichés
about how great of a doctor he is,
×ÖÄ»
how great of a humanitarian, and don't get me wrong,
that's very true.
×ÖÄ»
But today I want to talk about
another truth.
×ÖÄ»
Something you don't know about Ted Mercer.
And that...
×ÖÄ»
is...
that his greatest accomplishment and the smartest thing
×ÖÄ»
he has ever done was to marry my mom Kristin Mercer.
Because she is the one who makes this family work.
×ÖÄ»
And together, she and my dad
×Ö
have built a life that any child
Ä» ×ÖÄ»
would be so lucky to be a part of.
×ÖÄ»
Even an ungrateful daughter
who hasn't always paid attention
×ÖÄ»
enough to notice.
Honey, that was...
×ÖÄ»
Ladies and gentlemen,
Phoenix Surgical Humanitarian of the Year, Dr. Ted Mercer.
×ÖÄ»
Hey, Sutton.
Ethan, not right now, please.
×ÖÄ»
W-What? That was great.
No, it wasn't.
×ÖÄ»
You don't understand. It wasn't great.
Are you kidding me? You were real up there.
×ÖÄ»
Okay, so many times you've talked about how you've changed,
but that was from the heart.
×ÖÄ»
All right, that was the...
that was the Sutton Mercer from the ranch that night.
×ÖÄ»
Well, wonderful.
I gave a sappy speech about my parents
×ÖÄ»
in front of a bunch of doctors.
What is that going to get me?
×ÖÄ»
This.
Home sweet home.
×ÖÄ»
So quiet.
Jordan.
×ÖÄ»
I think I hear him out by the pool.
All right, well, will you say hi for me?
×ÖÄ»
I'm gonna go upstairs and take a bath. Sure.
Bye, baby.
×ÖÄ»
Alec.
Hey.
×ÖÄ»
How was the, uh, how was the honeymoon?
It was memorable.
×ÖÄ»
Good.
You're doing laps at this hour, huh?
×ÖÄ»
Yeah.
You haven't seen Mads, have you?
×ÖÄ»
She was going to stop by here and drop some stuff off.
No, I haven't seen her.
×ÖÄ»
She might have been here earlier
while I was gone, though.
×ÖÄ»
Don't know. Good night.
I thought you said you weren't going to do that anymore.
×ÖÄ»
Well, I thought so, too.
And now we're living under the same roof.
×ÖÄ»
So, things went pretty bad with Thayer, huh?
Yeah.
×ÖÄ»
Should have known it wouldn't work out, though,
when he didn't return any of my phone calls.
×ÖÄ»
Oh, well, when are you coming back?
Soon.
×ÖÄ»
The last bus out last night was canceled,
so I had to sleep here at the station, and it was just...
×ÖÄ»
Shower's free if you want it.
Who are you talking to?
×ÖÄ»
Sutton. Oh, great.
Hey, I didn't realize you'd left already, but I just wanted
×ÖÄ»
to say good luck at regionals
and reiterate how completely genius
×ÖÄ»
that speech was last night.
Thank you.
×ÖÄ»
Love you.
Anyways, um,
×ÖÄ»
I guess I will just check in on you later, okay?
Wait, Mads, no, don't, tell me what...
×ÖÄ»
Sutton, I thought you were on your...
Running late, so do you mind moving?
×ÖÄ»
I can get a yogurt.
Thank you.
×ÖÄ»
BUS ANNOUNCER: Saguaro Bus Lines 237
To Riverside, San Bernardino,and Phoenix, now boarding.
×ÖÄ»
Thank you.
You missed this.
×ÖÄ»
What are you doing here?
Oh, I checked the bus schedule,
×ÖÄ»
figured I still might be able to catch you.
Listen, Emma, that girl you saw at my apartment
×ÖÄ»
is just a friend.
We surf together, but that's it.
×ÖÄ»
Well, why didn't you just tell me that?
Because I can be hardheaded sometimes.
×ÖÄ»
But I also don't want to be one of those guys
×Ö
That lets pride get in the way of what he really wants.
Ä» ×ÖÄ»
and what do you really want?
×ÖÄ»
One question:
those messages you left about Sutton
×ÖÄ»
and the second woman at the motel--
did you come here because you want my help
×ÖÄ»
or because you want me?
Both.
×ÖÄ»
Thayer, when you left, I-I...
Ó²×ÖÄ»
×ÖÄ»
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
What the hell happened at the banquet?
×ÖÄ»
I don't know, I...
You had a golden opportunity and you folded.
×ÖÄ»
Are you going soft on me?
No...
×ÖÄ»
Look, I just realized that my feelings for Kristin
are a little bit more complicated than I had thought.
×ÖÄ»
And I know she's not my mother, but I...
But maybe you prefer her to be.
×ÖÄ»
No.
I was just up on that stage, and-and to humiliate her
×ÖÄ»
in front of everybody--
I'm just not as okay with it as you are.
×ÖÄ»
Well, I'm very sorry to hear that, sweetheart,
because now you've forced me to do something
×ÖÄ»
I was hoping I could avoid.
What is this?
×ÖÄ»
It's a journal, handwritten by Kristin Mercer.
×Ö
Read it and you'll see, when you were a baby,
Ä» ×ÖÄ»
that this "Wonderful mother" That you spoke so glowingly about
×ÖÄ»
wanted to give you away.