Grace: Previously on
The Mob Doctor
As long as you are in
Chicago I own you,
that's the deal.
Downtown should be ours.
We're about to make history here.
Better be on the right side of it.
Downtown is too high-profile.
Like I said, I ain't interested.
What do you want to know?
Did you kill my dad?
I swear to you,
on my life,
on your mother's life,
I did not kill your father.
You know something?
At the end of the day,
me and Constantine...
we're fathers first.
Constantine has kids?
Who the hell is this guy?
It's been a long time.
I never forget a face.
Then look closer.
It's me, Dad.
[ Jet engine roars ]
[ Car alarm chirps ]
[ Beep ]
Constantine:
It's good to see you, Luke.
I heard about your mom's passing
when I was in the joint.
I'm very sorry.
Yeah? I guess your condolence
card was lost in the mail.
Well... we haven't seen
each other in 25 years.
What do you need?
Um, I'm in trouble.
That I figured.
I'm in real estate
down in Miami...
South Beach, mostly.
I figured I should go big
while the rates were low...
You know, take advantage.
Ambitious...
that's a good thing.
[ Sighs ]
I got my hands
on a beachfront property...
Big enough
I could put up 10 units.
And it was all going great
until I got screwed
on the permits,
and then the banks
wouldn't even look at me.
Let me guess... somebody
offered you a private loan.
I was desperate,
and I was supposed to have
three months to pay them back.
That's the oldest trick
in the book.
They wait for you
to spend the money.
And then they call in the loan
at high interest.
It turns out
the money I borrowed
belongs to the Nogales Cartel.
Yeah, well...
you're right, kid.
You're in a lot of trouble.
They broke into my house.
I-I didn't know what to do.
I just ran.
All right,
you let me look into it.
In the meantime,
why don't you stay at my house?
You'll be safer.
All due respect,
I'm not looking for a father.
I'm just looking for help.
I understand.
[ Door chimes ]
Luke.
I'll check back with you
tomorrow.
Well, be careful.
[ Door chimes ]
He's really your kid, huh?
Yeah. He's in the weeds
with the Nogales Cartel.
I want him protected.
Stay with him, Gio.
Don't let him out of your sight.
Tino, the Nogales Cartel...
You know this could be
a problem, right?
He's my blood, Stavos.
What can I do?
Tell Trapani I want a meeting.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
What's with all
the pregnant people?
Guy collapsed
in a Lamaze class upstairs.
We're from the trauma team.
I'm Dr. Wilcox.
This is Dr. Devlin.
I-I'm Bethany.
This... this is Stuart,
my husband.
We were just learning baby CPR,
and he just passed out.
Pressure's 83/40.
Probably vasovagal.
Hang a liter.
Any chronic illnesses?
- No.
- Medications?
No, nothing.
We're... we're having
a natural pregnancy.
Um, yeah, well, both of us.
[ Rapid beeping ]
Looks like a wide-complex
tachycardia, maybe v-tach.
Well, that would explain
the fainting.
Start an amio drip.
Systolic's down to 68.
We need that amio fast!
No, forget it.
He's too unstable.
I think we should
cardiovert him.
Push the etomidate.
All right, listen, Bethany.
We're just gonna give him
a small electrical shock
to reset his heart
to a normal rhythm, okay?
Would you go with the nurse,
wait outside?
We'll come talk to you
as soon as we can.
No. I...
[ Paddles whine ]
Paddles.
Olivia: Clear.
[ Thump ]
[ Flatline ]
Amp of epi.
Come on.
Al: Tino, you brought me
all the way out here.
You don't even bring
those pignoli biscotti.
Yeah, you keep eating crap
like that,
it's gonna take
a dozen pallbearers
to put you in the ground, huh?
How's business?
Can't complain. So?
Word is, you're in bed
with the Nogales Cartel.
I gave them a deal to traffic
junk on the Eisenhower,
if that's what you mean.
Why?
I got a guy close to me.
He's underwater with them.
I'd like you to make
a phone call,
arrange
a sit-down for me.
Who's the guy?
My son.
Ah, the kid you had with
that broad from Hazel Crest.
Yeah. Look, I appreciate you
doing me this favor.
No problem. I'll...
I'll do the best I can.
You tell them
I'll cover everything.
[ Cellphone beeping ] Ah.
Ah.
Is something wrong?
Ah, it's my girl.
She's got some weird flu kicking
her ass the past few weeks.
She can barely get out of bed.
Yeah, well, you know I got
a doctor who makes house calls.
You want me to bring her over?
Really?
I mean, that's how it works,
huh? You help me. I help you.
I shouldn't have rushed
into the cardioversion.
We should have waited for amio
or... or tried adenosine.
And that could have sent him
straight into v-fib
if he wasn't
going there already.
First rule of wide-complex
tachycardia, Grace...
Do no harm.
This is my fault.
What are we gonna say
to his wife?
We made a judgment call,
and we both thought
it was the right one.
How's Stuart?
Will you sit down?
Mrs. Maslan,
I am so sorry.
Your husband died.
Oh, my God.
I want to see him.
[ Sighs, sniffles ]
[ Voice breaking ]
He's still warm.
We tried to restart his heart,
but he didn't respond.
Why couldn't you help him?
We tried everything we could.
Stuart had a severely unstable
heart rhythm.
Sometimes when that happens,
you just can't restore it.
Is there anyone
that we can call?
[ Groans ]
Where am I?
The Mob Doctor 01x12
Resurrection
Original Air Date  January 5, 2013
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com
[ Monitor beeping ]
I hear you folks had quite
an exciting morning.
One minute we were at Lamaze,
and then apparently I died.
[ Coughs ]
Excuse me.
No evidence of infarction.
Other than this cold,
he's been perfectly healthy.
Oh, he is. Or was.
How did this happen?
There are several cases
in the medical literature
of what's called
"Lazarus Syndrome."
People pronounced dead
who come back to life
after attempts at resuscitation
have failed.
It's extremely rare.
In 30 years of practice,
I've never seen a case,
which is why I'd like to borrow
my two doctors for a moment,
- if you don't mind.
- No, of course.
So, what exactly happened
in there?
We have no idea.
What criteria did you use
to call the code?
Over 30 minutes in asystole,
pupils fixed and dilated,
and no cardiac activity
on ultrasound.
Mm, well, that does sound
pretty dead.
His rhythm is still
grossly unstable.
But no evidence of ischemia.
We still can't figure out why
his heart stopped or restarted.
All right, order a stat
coronary C.T. and echo,
and make sure our Lazarus
doesn't return to the cave.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
Answer it.
I got this.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
Listen, Grace,
the guy we're gonna go see...
He's been a friend of mine
a long time.
And he might mention
something to you
that I'd rather you
hear from me.
I have a son.
His name is Luke.
And I saw him today
for the first time in 25 years.
Not exactly close, huh?
I love my son,
and I tried to do right by him
and his mom.
And I guess she just got tired
of the life
and took off for Florida.
She made me promise
to stay away from him.
And I can't tell you how hard
that was...
you know, birthdays, holidays,
not to pick up the phone.
But I kept my word.
You gonna try and reconnect?
No, it's too late.
He just wants me
to dig him out of a jam.
It's never too late
till you're dead.
Look who's the optimist.
Just means if it matters to you,
it might matter to him.
[ Sighs ] Welcome, Tino.
Mr. Trapani,
this is Dr. Devlin.
Hi. I'm Al.
Thanks for coming.
Where's your patient?
Take the doc
up to Chloe's room.
I'll be right there.
I floated the message
to the cartel
that you're willing to pay off
Luke's debt.
And?
It's working its way up
the food chain.
There's something you're not
telling me, Al.
They've already taken
punitive measures.
They've ordered a hit on Luke.
The guy they hired
is boots down in Chicago.
It's Diego Balt.
He never misses, Tino.
Are you saying it's too late?
I'll do the best I can...
I give you my word.
Bobby, call Gio.
Tell him to find Luke,
that we're on our way.
I'm on it.
I'll send a car for Grace.
Well, got no redness.
That's something.
Glands feel normal.
I just hurt all over.
Well, your temperature is fine.
So, um, what's wrong
with her, doc...
Some kind of bad flu
or something?
I'm not really sure yet.
Any chronic medical issues
or surgeries?
Well, I may have had a thing
or two done
to improve my looks
back when I was dancing...
you know, normal stuff.
[ Chuckles ]
So, what kind of surgeries
are we talking about?
Uh, nose, tummy,
the girls, of course.
And, um, your implants...
Are they silicone or saline?
Uh... I don't know.
They were a Christmas present
to me from one of my regulars.
Don't look a gift horse
in the mouth, right?
[ Chuckles ] Why?
Silicone leaks...
They can cause fibromyalgia
or immune disorders.
Do you mind if I check?
Half of Chicago's seen my boobs,
so knock yourself out.
All right.
Okay.
[ Clears throat ]
The right one's smaller
than the left.
- Has it always been that way?
- No.
We're gonna need to remove them
and run some tests.
- The sooner the better.
- Uh, I don't know.
Hey, hey, hey. Look at me.
It's nothing to worry about.
We got to fix
whatever's making you sick.
Okay.
I'll call the hospital
and book an O.R.
[ Beeping ]
[ Rapid beeping ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
You almost here, boss?
He's heading north on Franklin.
He just passed Superior.
No, I got him.
All right.
All right, come up through
the alley between Chicago
and Superior...
I'm gonna grab him, all right?
All right. I got him.
All right.
Luke. Luke!
What are you doing here?
Your father sent me.
I don't need a babysitter.
Hey, buddy, I just do
as I'm told, all right?
[ Tires screech ]
Get in. You scared
the crap out of me.
[ Door closes, engine revs ]
[ Tires screeching ]
You been made, kid. What
are you talking about?
Did you bring your cellphone
from Miami?
Of course I did.
Let me see it.
Hey!
You want to get killed?
Because that's almost
what just happened.
This guy who's after you
is a serious player.
Now I got to get you
someplace safe.
Are you telling me you can't
make this go away?
You want to hate me,
I'll learn to live with that.
But if you're gonna
get through this,
you're gonna do
exactly what I tell you.
Where's Al.
He's just down the hall.
Hi, Chloe.
I'm Dr. Robinson.
I'm gonna be scrubbing in.
Are you sure
we have to do this?
I mean, what if
something goes wrong?
Well, if you have
a silicone leak,
we have to take care of it.
Dr. Devlin's right.
But don't worry...
We're not gonna let anything
happen to you.
Okay.
Let's do it.
I.V. line is in.
Just make sure
that the new girls
are up to Al's standards, okay?
Absolutely.
Dr. White: So, you can see
in this model of a healthy heart
how the electrical current flows
in a regular pattern
down well-defined pathways.
In this model, Stuart's heart,
the contractions
and electrical impulses
are erratic and disorganized.
He hasn't slept in two weeks.
I thought it was
the excitement.
- Insomnia?
- Nightmares.
I-I keep dreaming
that I'm holding our son
and I drop him down a well.
We...
We don't have a well.
I've never even seen a well.
It's... it's pitiful.
Oh, no, not at all.
Becoming a father for the first
time can be pretty terrifying.
So, maybe that's what it is...
He's stressed out over the baby.
I don't think so,
Mrs. Maslan.
It's as if Stuart's
electrical pathways are dying,
and our tests haven't
been able to pinpoint why.
So he could die again?
Until we understand
the etiology,
that's hard to predict.
All right, so it looks like
we're gonna be here
for a little while.
Order an E.P. study
and switch him to Sotalol.
Yes, sir.
You like a challenge,
Dr. Wilcox.
Looks like you've got one.
[ Sighs ]
[ Monitor beeping ]
How is this possible?
I thought Chloe's symptoms
were from a silicone leak.
Well, those are
definitely saline.
Yeah.
Look, good news...
She needed
the implants replaced,
and I think we did
an excellent job.
Look, she probably just
has a virus or something.
She didn't have a fever.
Her symptoms aren't improving.
We're missing something.
Doctors, she's bleeding.
From the incision site?
Her urinary tract
is hemorrhaging.
Okay, get her to the ICU
for monitoring.
Type and cross for four
and get a stat urogram.
Come on. Let's go.
All right.
You got enough food
for a few days.
Now, don't leave the room
until you get the okay from me.
Luke: This is crazy.
Maybe I should have
just called the cops.
No, that's the last thing
you should have done.
Just settle down.
Trapani's working
his connections.
In the meantime,
I got Stavos reaching out
to one of the cartel's
top lawyers in Miami.
Everything's
gonna be fine, kid.
How can you say that?
They already found me once!
Nobody's gonna find you
unless you do something stupid,
and you're not gonna do that.
Buddy, relax.
We'll watch a little something.
We'll eat a little something.
It'll be good.
You want me to put
a couple guys outside?
No. The lower the profile,
the better.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Beep ]
Al, how's your broad?
She's okay.
She had some kind
of complication.
They're doing a scan now.
Well, she's in good hands.
Thanks.
So, uh, I heard back
from our compadres.
So, what's the deal?
Can we buy out of this
with a bag of cash?
Money ain't gonna do it, Tino.
Guy I mentioned before...
The one they sent to Chicago...
Well, soon as he gets hired,
he goes dark.
There's no way
of canceling the job.
I'm sorry, Tino.
I know you want to
protect your kid,
but these guys...
they don't play nice.
All right, thanks, Al.
Message received.
He couldn't do anything,
could he?
Look, it's not over, kid.
I got to get out of here.
Sit down and relax.
You said you could fix this.
And I will.
You're a bully
who scares people for a living.
Look, I screwed up,
and I thought you could help me,
but this is insane.
You're not thinking straight.
Yeah, I am. Now they know I'm
your son, they can find me.
I got a buddy in Alberta
I can stay with.
I'm out of here.
What do you think...
You're gonna be safe in Canada?
They're gonna find you
anywhere you go!
So, what... I'm just
supposed to stick around here
and let you play dad
until then?
I don't think so.
This medal that you're wearing
on your chest...
Tell me about it.
It was my mother's.
She got it
from her grandfather.
No, Luke, she didn't.
That medal belonged
to my grandfather,
and I gave it to your mother,
and she wouldn't have
passed it on to you
unless she thought there was
something right
about the man
who gave it to her.
No. That's a lie.
She knew what you were.
Look, it's not that easy.
I mean, who I am...
it may have been a liability
back then.
But now who I am
is gonna save your life.
Hey.
How's Mr. Maslan?
Not good.
E.P. studies were a bust.
I can't figure this out.
- What about the other tests?
- Inconclusive.
No structural abnormalities
on his echo...
- Normal coronary C.T.
- Electrolytes?
Calcium, potassium,
magnesium, phos...
All normal.
What about trying a different
class of antiarrhythmic?
All maxed out.
Do you realize I'm gonna be
the first resident
to have a patient
die on me twice?
[ Rapid beeping ]
Bethany:
Something's wrong!
Pressure's dropping.
Looks like electrical alternans.
Ultrasound.
Olivia: Damn it.
The CPR must have caused
bleeding into the pericardium.
I need an 18-gauge needle
and a large syringe.
I don't understand.
We need to drain the fluid
from around Stuart's heart.
Are you sure? Everything you've
done has just made him worse.
I'm sorry
for the complications,
but we have to remove the blood
or his heart will stop beating.
Grace: You got it.
Come on, Stuart.
Stay alive.
Gio, long time no see.
Where you been?
Ah, you know, Eddie...
working hard,
trying to keep the lights on.
How's your dad's knee?
Oh, it's good.
It's good, thanks.
You know, he says it, uh,
throbs like hell,
but he's doing these aquatic
classes and that's helping.
Oh.
[ Cellphone rings ]
He's hanging out with a bunch
of old broads...
That's really what's helping.
Oh. Well, I'm sorry, Eddie.
One second.
What's up, Constantine?
No.
No, your... your kid sent me
to get some stuff
'cause they don't have any cable
at the Esquire Motel.
Like skin mags and stuff.
All right, I got it.
I got it.
I'll be back in an hour.
[ Beep ]
What's that about?
Ohh.
You know, it's like,
all of a sudden,
I'm a freaking babysitter.
He's all wound up.
Don't ask.
I'm gonna take this.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll take...
I'll take a Trib, too.
All right.
There you go, Eddie.
Keep the change.
Good to see you.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
I had an emergency with
a Lazarus Syndrome patient.
- Is he okay?
- Barely.
Olivia's really beating herself
up over it.
In other news...
[ Clears throat ]
Check this out.
Chloe's scans came in.
It's a kidney tumor?
It's definitely a tumor,
but it is not on her kidney.
[ Beep ]
It's in her prostate.
What are you talking about?
She was born... a he.
Seminal vesicles,
bilateral ligation
of the vas deferens.
She's a transgender female.
That explains the multiple
cosmetic surgeries.
And why she didn't
want to see a doctor.
But even if she was a man,
I would have missed it.
I mean, she's way too young
for prostate cancer.
Well, not if
she's taking estrogen
as part of
her post-op protocol.
Well, I booked an O.R.
At the rate she's bleeding,
this tumor's got to come out
of her fast.
All right, I'll go talk to her.
Okay.
[ Monitor beeping ]
Hey.
I can't tell under the bandages.
How do they look?
They're gonna be great.
Is, uh, Al around?
He went to get food.
Do you want me to call him?
No. No, that's okay.
Um...
[ Sighs ]
Chloe.
Mm-hmm.
Your C.T. came back,
and it looks like
you have cancer...
In your prostate.
That's not possible.
Unfortunately, it is.
It explains why
you're peeing blood.
I'm a woman.
Yeah, you are.
But at one point, physically,
you were a man.
Your C.T. showed remnants
of your male reproductive tract,
including your prostate...
With a tumor.
I thought I got rid
of that part of me.
And now here it is...
Hurting me all over again.
I guess you can't keep
a secret forever, huh?
I guess not.
Look, we're gonna get you
through this, okay?
It is serious.
But with surgery and chemo,
you're gonna do great.
[ Crying ] No,
you don't understand.
I told you it was a secret.
Al doesn't know.
Sweetie,
your cancer's pretty advanced.
We got to get you into surgery.
How?
I mean, if Al finds out...
He'll kill us both.
Hey.
So, the, uh, surgery went well.
How you feeling?
A little out of it.
[ Door opens ]
Al: Two surgeries,
one on top of the other...
What do you expect?
How'd she do?
Well, we were able to completely
remove the abdominal tumor.
That's great news.
Thank you.
How you doing, honey?
Good.
But, uh, we ran into
an unexpected complication.
When we got in there,
we saw that, uh, the tumor
had invaded Chloe's uterus...
So we had to remove it.
So, you mean...
I can't have kids?
I'm so sorry.
It's okay, honey.
As long as you're healthy,
that's all that matters.
We decide we want to
have kids one day,
we can just adopt, right?
What do you say,
Dr. Devlin?
Definitely.
All right,
I'll leave you two alone.
Thank you...
for everything.
[ Monitor beeping ]
Look at him.
[ Crying ]
He's barely breathing.
Unfortunately, the procedure
seems to have complicated
the arrhythmia.
So you made him worse again.
Bethany, baby, stop.
Stop.
I need you.
He needs you.
I see...
Lights...
Like people talk about.
No.
What kind of light,
Mr. Maslan?
Halos...
Golden halos.
Get the ophthalmoscope.
What is it?
Uh, yellow halos
may be a sign of toxicity.
You said he'd been
having nightmares?
Yeah, the past couple of weeks.
[ Sniffles ]
Fundi are normal.
I know you said you were having
a natural pregnancy,
but did Stuart take anything
herbal for his cold?
Just a cough suppressant
I got him.
I think I have it.
[ Pills rattling ]
Foxglove.
Grab the digibind.
How much has he been taking?
Uh, I don't know...
Whenever he coughs.
Foxglove is an herbal version
of a very potent Western
medicine called "digoxin."
An overdose can lead
to a severe heart arrhythmia,
nightmares, and visual changes.
[ Crying ] I just wanted us
to be healthy for the baby.
The arrhythmia is resolving.
Yes, it is.
Well done, Dr. Wilcox.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Breathes deeply ]
My breathing.
[ Gasps ]
No. No, babe.
It's better.
No, it's not that.
I think my water just broke.
What?
Oh.
Nurse!
Uh, call up to L&D. Tell them
we're gonna need a bed.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Hey, Chloe.
You're looking good.
I don't feel so bad...
You know, considering.
I'll meet you back in the room.
I just want to thank Dr. Devlin
one-on-one.
Two minutes.
Okay.
I need to know the truth
about Chloe's cancer.
Well, like I said, she has...
Don't lie to me, Grace.
I know about her.
I've known about her
for a while,
and I still love her.
Okay, well, then, in that case,
it's none of my business,
but why don't you
just tell her you know?
You're right.
It's none of your business.
I'll tell her when I'm ready
and under my own terms.
Do I make myself clear?
Yeah.
Of course.
If you ever tell Constantine
or anyone else...
Hey, don't threaten me, okay?
If I couldn't keep a secret,
I'd already be dead.
Buddy, I'm gonna go get
some Chinese food.
Do you want anything?
[ Water running ] All right.
[ Water running ]
[ Muffled gunshots ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Gunshot ]
Hey, you heading home?
Yeah. Uh, I thought you left
hours ago.
Oh, I stuck around
for the Maslan delivery.
Baby boy...
7 pounds, 2 ounces.
Mother, child, and Lazarus
are all doing
[Chuckling] very well.
That's great.
And I prescribed a cocktail
for Olivia,
who is very much relieved.
It's been quite a day.
Yeah.
Just when you think
you've seen it all,
here comes the curve ball.
Well, life is full of surprises,
isn't it?
Well...
Good night, Grace.
I'm telling you, Constantine
played it like a chess master...
Had me drop the location
right in front of Eddie Russo.
[ Chuckles ]
Russo... that creep's
always shooting his mouth off.
Exactly.
Within an hour,
I get word from my guy
at Tijuana Grill...
Balt's on the move.
Eddie Russo isn't the only one
with a big mouth.
What do you think...
it's a joke
to kill a member
of the Nogales Cartel?
I left the message
24 hours ago.
Could you tell him
Mr. Alexander and I
need to speak
with him urgently?
That's right.
Mm-hmm. Thank you.
The, uh, Nogales lawyer,
yeah, is calling us back
any minute, the son of a bitch.
I just spoke to Trapani.
The cartel agreed to a truce
until I can have a sit-down
with them.
That's great, boss.
We'll see.
I got my stuff from the car.
I'm gonna take off.
Listen, kid, I'd feel
much better about things
if you came and stayed
at the house with me.
I don't want to
seem ungrateful.
I'm just... not comfortable
with that.
But thank you...
for what you did.
Look, you're not gonna
leave town, are you?
No, I'm gonna check
into a hotel,
stick around a couple days.
Whatever you do,
don't check into the hotel
under your own name.
You pay in cash,
and don't let anybody in
the room till you hear from me.
Yeah. I got it.
I'm glad you're gonna
stick around, Luke.
You know, it gives us a chance
to maybe get to know
each other.
Sure.
Look, I want to meet Grace.
Yeah, my mom told me about her
before she died.
I think it's time we met.
I understand.
Listen to me...
I'm gonna handle this,
but I want you to promise me
you're gonna keep
your head down.
Be very careful.
Okay. I will.
Give me the keys
to the car, Bobby.
Boss, you want me to drive?
No, not this time.
It's something
I got to do alone.
Tino, what are you doing?
I'm going to the Devlins'.
It's something I should have
taken care of a long time ago.
[ Train rumbling ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Beep ]
Yes. Yes, Mr. Buchman,
good to hear from you.
I, uh, called regarding
a business misunderstanding
with your clients from Nogales.
Yes, uh, I know Al Trapani
has already reached out,
but we would like to go
on record direc...
You're certain about that?
I need to call you back, sir.
Thank you.
[ Beeping ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
Answer, answer.
[ Beep ]
Tino, the Nogales lawyer
called back.
We have a problem.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Trapani lied about the cartel.
There is no truce.
Trapani never even passed on
your offer to pay Luke's debt.
If they find out
you killed their man
without trying to negotiate,
this is going to get ugly fast.
Tino, call me
as soon as you can.
[ Sighs ]
Oh. Hey.
I thought I heard
someone come in.
- How you doing?
- Good.
I already ate, but I can
heat you up some leftovers.
Yeah, that sounds nice.
Thank you.
I'm just gonna take a shower
real quick.
Okay. You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay. Love you.
I love you, too.
Is Ray watching out there,
or is he just sitting there,
picking through pastries?
He's watching.
He's eating the pastries, too.
Look at this. This broad
lies in the interview...
Says those are real.
You paid money for this thing?
You can go online and see
these broads naked for nothing.
Bobby, there's something to be
said about old-school.
Hey, did one of you two move
Constantine's phone book?
Uh, yeah, it's with the orders.
[ Door chimes ]
Did I not tell him
to keep it closed?
You did.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Gun cocks ]
Where's Constantine?
Go to hell.
Where is he?
I don't know.
[ Gunshot ] Ohh!
Where is he?
[ Straining ]
[ Screaming ]
Where... is... he?
[ Tires screech ]
[ Doorbell rings ]
Constantine.
[ Chuckles ]
What's the occasion?
We got to tell Grace, Dannie.
Tell Grace what?
We've got to tell
her everything
before she finds out
on her own.
[ Tires screech ]
[ Dog barking in distance ]
Mom?
[ Sobbing ] Mom?
Mom.
Help!
[ Echoing ] Somebody, help!
Help!!
[ Siren wails in distance ]
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for addic7ed.com