Merry crap-mas, everyone.
This sucks.
(sighs)
Okay, guys.
I know christmas didn't
go exactly how we planned.
We don't have any presents
under the tree.
- We don't have a tree.
- But santa...
Santa called. He's not gonna
be able to make it this year.
But here's the thing...
we have each other.
We got through another year together,
and that's what really matters.
- Yay, none of us died.
- (angrily) Merry christmas.
So this is what we're
gonna do, okay?
We're gonna go downstairs,
and we are gonna make the best of this.
All right? Let's go.
Come on.
♪ We wish you
a merry christmas ♪
God bless us, every one!
Aah!
Ow!
(squealing)
S01E09
Merry Crap-Mas
Sync by ninh
www.addic7ed.com
Did you get Max's Ipad?
I think we forgot the Ipad.
We didn't forget it.
It's right there.
It's the blue wrapping paper.
Are you sure that's the Ipad?
Honey, you tend to remember
something you bought your 8-year-old
that you're gonna be paying for
for the next three years.
Okay, I got Amber's snowboard,
and our list is officially complete.
(groans)
The rest is up to Santa.
Ho! (grunts)
(grunts)
(knocks on door)
Hello!
Hey, guys!
What's with the apron?
You cooking something?
No. I just like what it does
for my silhouette.
He loves the apron.
So, guys, we need
a small favor.
We need a place to hide
our christmas gifts.
We got some nosy kids,
and...
Christmas! I've been
so excited for this one!
Oh, you people.
So, we're not excited
about this one, either?
- Here we go.
- You mean the orgy of commercialism
I've been hearing about
since March? No.
I just don't see how two
relatively sane human beings
can participate in such
an insane holiday.
Oh, it's not insane, Larry.
It's fun for us,
and for the kids, and Abby's 6,
and she still gets caught up
in the magic of it all.
Ah, there it is. Abby.
It's always about "Abby."
Don't put my daughter
in quotations, Larry.
What's so special about that little girl?
Nothing, as far as I can see.
Yet you two have concocted
yet another excuse
to lavish both her and the more
worthwhile Weaver children
with disposable
commercial crap.
- Larry, you've got it all wrong.
- Okay, christmas is about family
and smiles and the joy
of being together.
The gifts are just
one tiny part of it.
Oh, yes. And there's that
fat, slovenly burglar
you call Santa Claus. Honestly.
Put on an apron
for god's sake, fatso.
He's struggling
with Santa Claus.
Of course you can keep
your presents here.
- All right, get around back.
- Ready, babe?
- 1... 2...
- Watch the top.
- Wheel your barrow your full of crap...
- I'm okay.
- (Marty) The door. The door.
- Oh! Oh!
(shouting indistinctly)
Man down. Man down.
All right.
Yeah, we got it.
(shouting indistinctly) Just
watch the floors. They're bamboo.
I got it. Yes.
Okay.
(man) ♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of holly ♪
♪ fa la-la-la-la,
la la-la-la ♪
(sighs)
What's wrong?
(clicks tongue)
Do you think Larry's right,
and we're too caught up in the presents?
No, babe. Larry's just
being Larry, okay?
Our kids understand
the meaning of christmas.
They don't even need
presents.
Hey, mom, make sure my snowboard has
step-in bindings and not those lame straps.
(singsongy) We'll see
what Santa brings.
Yeah, uh, don't even worry
about wrapping it.
It's just gonna slow me down.
Also, Jeremy called,
and it turns out
we're going on the ski trip
the day before christmas
instead of the day after,
so I'm gonna need my presents early.
Hold up, Amber.
- This family celebrates christmas together.
- Yeah.
Yeah. I'll text you
from the mountain.
What...
Well, I'll be here.
And I want some new games
for the Xbox.
Wait. I thought you wanted
an Ipad.
I'll multitask. Oh,
and I also want a new bike.
A new bike.
What about you, huh?
You have any changes
you'd like to make?
Nah. Santa knows what I want.
He'll take care of me.
Oh, and, uh,
here's my new list.
I've highlighted the changes.
Be sure to look at page 3.
Page 3.
You should probably fax it.
It's getting pretty late.
Okay, I'll get on that.
Thank you.
God! What the hell?
Is this the constitution?
Who makes amendments
to a christmas list?
You know what? You're right.
It's become all about this stuff.
Our kids are completely out of control.
I hated all three of them
just now, Marty.
In that moment, I hated
all three of our children.
You know what?
Maybe we should try something
different this year.
Forget the presents.
Let's take a nice
vacation somewhere
and hang with the family
for christmas.
Somewhere nice.
Maybe somewhere tropical.
Yeah, but we can't afford
tropical.
We just spent a buttload
of money on all their presents.
No! We return the presents
and we use the money for the trip!
- Can we do that?
- We're the parents.
We named those
greedy little monsters.
- We can do whatever we want!
- Oh, my god!
We could have christmas tans.
(squeals)
I'm gonna be brown
for the super bowl!
(Larry Bird) Look at this
bloated pile of consumerism.
And most of it for that
little girl.
What's her deal?
Is she really that cute?
She is pretty cute,
husband.
Dad, she's pretty much
the cutest kid ever.
And her teeth keep on
falling out of her face.
What's gonna fall off
next, her nose?
Oh, father! I love it
when you make fun of children.
The whole thing is ridiculous.
I mean,
what could possibly be
this shape,
and yet be so exciting
to receive?
No, really. It's not
a rhetorical question.
- What do you think it is?
- It looks like a giant board,
perhaps for some sort
of, um, winter sport.
Don't be a dolt, Reggie.
(Abby) What's the surprise?
(Debbie) Well, your dad
and I were talking,
And we decided to do christmas
a little different this year.
Presents early?
No.
Can we do jewish christmas
and get presents for eight days?
What? No. We decided
that instead of presents this year...
We're going
on a family trip!
(laughing)
We're not joking.
(laughing stops)
They're not joking!
You're not joking?
What kind of sick game
are you playing?
We're just children!
(men harmonizing)
♪ Merry christmas
Perhaps it's a galapagos
turtle with a flattened shell.
A giant stick of gum?
Okay, one more time, why are we so quick
to dismiss snowboard?
(paper rips)
(gasps)
Oh, my. (scoffs)
(ripping)
Oh, that felt
really, really good.
Oh.
(gasps)
(exhales)
It's beautiful.
- What is it, husband?
- It's a... it's... it's...
- It's a thing.
- (Jackie Joyner-Kersee) Oh.
- And it's glorious.
- Okay, was that as fun as it looked?
Even better.
- (gasps) I want one!
- Me, too!
- Yes! Presents for everyone!
- Oh!
(andy williams) ♪ it's most
wonderful time ♪
♪ of the year
♪ There'll be much mistletoeing
and hearts will be glowing ♪
♪ when loved ones are near
I got a bike! Cool!
♪ wonderful time
(glass shatters)
Christmas is
the best thing ever!
Yeah!
So no presents
for christmas this year?
Great. You've ruined the one day a year
I actually find this family tolerable.
So just to be clear,
I've been good all year,
and I'm getting lumped in
with her?
Well, I guess a trip
for the family sounds fun.
Oh, zip it, kiss-ass.
You already told me I could
go on a trip with Jeremy.
Okay. I think we've all lost sight
of what christmas is really about.
It is not about presents.
It's about being together,
and we are gonna go away
as a family, all of us.
Does this mean we have to return
the presents we got for you?
You got us presents?
Of course not, but do you
see how that feels?
Mommy, I'm confused.
I saw Santa at the mall,
and he said I was
very good this year,
and I would be getting
everything I asked for.
Well, don't worry
about that, sweetie,
because daddy was texting back and forth
with Santa this morning, and guess what?
- He approved our trip!
- You know what? That's interesting,
Because I was skype-ing with Santa
after you finished texting with him,
and he said that I could go on
a ski trip with my friends.
What?
I know Santa, too.
All right.
You know what, smart-mouth?
Let me be really clear.
You are not going
on your ski trip.
So lame.
Come on, guys. Let's go to our rooms
before they take those away, too.
Can you remind me again why want to be
alone on island with these children?
("deck the halls" playing)
(Larry Bird) That "christmas carol"
is a wonderful story.
I love the ghost.
Agreed. Although I didn't
like tiny Tim.
Little, weird,
and totally unrelatable.
I admit it.
I was wrong about christmas.
It's a lovely holiday.
The things, the trees,
the snow.
Mmm.
The things.
Christmas is magical,
father! Magical!
Dick, Dick, fix your joints.
You're going to get
a bellyache.
I still can't get past
that Santa fellow, though.
526 million children
celebrate christmas.
That means
he has to deliver presents
to 22 million children
an hour.
I mean, really!
I mean, we're saying he gets around
the whole world in one night...
at that weight.
I mean, he can't fit
into a sleigh,
Let alone fly in one.
(grunts)
I'm sorry.
I know this is off topic,
but is anyone gonna admit
that I got this right?
No.
Tell you what.
Let's watch "The Muppets:
A christmas carol" again.
The Muppets I like.
(beeps)
I could really get down
with the muppets.
Kermit.
(imitating Kermit the frog)
Jackie Joyner-Kersee,
please press "play."
(laughing)
- That was very good!
- (normal voice) Did you see that?
- Yes.
- I know, it's awfully good.
Very good.
Oh, I got it, Marty.
Look at this...
"available time-share
in hawaii.
"three bedrooms, updated kitchen,
short walk to the beach, bidet"!
(gasps) The tushie-squirting thing?
Holy crap, they have
the tushie-squirting thing!
(gasps) Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Can we afford this?
It's in our price range.
Marty, this is ours!
We can do this!
We're going to hawaii!
- Yeah!
- Oh, let's go get the gifts and return them
- so we can pay for this thing.
- My tushie feels wet already.
Merry christmas
to me.
(rock version of "Jingle bells"
playing)
(man) ♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♪
(zabvronians speaking indistinctly)
♪ jingle all the way
♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride
♪ in a one-horse open sleigh
♪ hey!
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells,
jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride
in a one-horse open sleigh ♪
(grunts)
I have never been so wrong
about anything in my life.
I love christmas!
Larry, what the hell
is the matter with you?
For the first time on this
stupid planet, nothing.
I'm totally joyous.
I have sugarplums in my head!
Why? What's the matter
with you?
You were supposed to hold on
to our gifts
for a few days,
not give them away!
- Or destroy 'em!
- Merry christmas!
I can't believe
this is happening.
To be honest, I think you're
being completely illogical
and a bit of a nasty elf.
You said christmas
is about giving.
I won't let you ruin christmas
for me. I just won't!
I'm sorry. We're ruining
your christmas?!
You gave our gifts away!
(scoffs)
Why are the aliens
playing with our presents?
Are they throwing
my Ipad?
Jackie, this is
a major screw-up.
Oh, no, not again.
It's just that you have so many holidays
for us to screw up.
Can't we just get to the part
where everything ends up being all right
and we learn
from one another?
- Can't we do that?
- Jackie, we save up all year for this.
And now we can't return those gifts
and use the money to go to hawaii!
I'm so sorry.
My husband didn't mean...
Stop apologizing
for him, Jackie.
You can't keep apologizing for him
every time he makes a mistake
and expect everything
to be better.
Worst christmas ever!
Whole year of being good
right down the crapper!
I'm afraid you've been
naughty, Mr. Bird.
And Santa knows
when you've been naughty,
and he knows
when you've been nice.
♪
Does he know
where the gym is?
Because he's going to lose
a foot to diabetes.
♪ Oh, what fun is to ride
♪ in a one-horse open sleigh
Ohh!
Hello, my little
overlooked friend.
Husband, I think we've
made a terrible mistake.
You bet your sweet bippy
we did. We missed one. Ohh!
- The new Ipad!
- Husband.
Oh, it's fine.
It's just stuff
They would have got bored with
within a day or two.
But not this. Steve jobs really
got it right with this one.
Larry Bird! The Weavers
have been so good to us,
and we keep on
disappointing them.
We have to make this right.
Either you do it, or I will.
Wait, Jackie.
What do you want from me?
Do you want me to send them
some flowers? Is that it?
(door closes)
Siri, did I really
ruin their christmas?
Siri?
I don't even know
how it happened.
Just seeing all that
wrapping paper and boxes...
(sighs)
I know you can't ever
forgive us,
but we are truly, truly
sorry for what we did.
Jackie, what do you want me
to say?
I know you didn't mean
to hurt us.
You guys got carried away.
I get it.
You celebrated
your first christmas.
The first ones are always
the best ones.
Even Amber.
She had the sweetest look of excitement
on her face her first few christmases.
I hang on to that memory when
she says hurtful things to me.
Ooh.
I imagine you must think
of that several times a day.
Yeah. Yeah.
(Kermit the frog)
♪ Have yourself
♪ a merry little christmas
♪ Let your heart be light
(clicks)
♪ From now on
♪ our troubles will be
out of sight ♪
♪ have yourself...
What do you want?
We need to talk.
(scoffs)
With the kids
all getting older,
we were afraid that this was gonna be
the last christmas where we'd have
one of those magical
mornings together.
Marty and I just got
carried away.
Ohh.
So we really screwed your pooch
on this one.
Oh, Jackie. Not only
did you screw my pooch,
but you didn't call her
the next day, either.
Mmm.
(slurps)
♪ happy golden days
of yore ♪
♪ faithful friends...
It's... Very good.
Thank you.
Um... (sighs)
I've been watching you.
(scoffs)
And I can tell you're sad.
So I came over to tell you
not to be sad,
'cause Santa's going to make
everything all better.
Ohh...
Santa's going to make
everything all better.
(scoffs)
When I was 4,
I got the flu,
So I coun't visit Santa.
So my mom told me
to write a letter
so she could mail it
to him before christmas.
The whole time, I was really worried
that he had forgotten about me.
- But guess what?
- What?
He wrote me back.
(scoffs)
Oh, please.
(sighs)
What did he write?
He reminded me to be good
even when no one was watching,
and to never forget
what christmas is all about.
What's that?
Family, silly.
(gasps)
Santa... told you that?
So no more sad faces, Mr. Bird,
'cause Santa's going to make
everything all better.
He always comes through.
♪ our troubles will be
miles away ♪
Thank you for the tea.
Let's do it again sometime.
♪ and have yourself
(door closes)
♪ a merry little christmas
Oh, dear.
I've been very, very naughty.
Oh, goodness.
What are you up to now?
You were right, wife.
The Weavers have been
good to us,
so I'm going
to make this right.
I'm going to be like Santa Claus
and save their christmas.
All I need is a helper elf.
I've already made the costume.
Oh, husband,
love of my life,
I would be your elf
any day.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're too tall.
Oh.
Oh, I do not like
where this is going.
("Christmas in hollis"
by Run-D.M.C. playing)
♪ It's christmastime
in hollis, queens ♪
♪ Mom's cookin' chicken
and collard greens ♪
♪ Rice and stuffing,
macaroni and cheese ♪
♪ and santa put gifts
under christmas trees ♪
♪
I have a limitless amount cash
and desire to buy a car.
♪ Merry christmas
and happy new year ♪
(cheering, whistles blowing)
Ooh!
Jackpot.
♪
Excuse me. Do you have
any plans this christmas?
Oh, my family's all dead.
Perfect.
Boo-yah!
Kept it.
Move rapid, son.
Capture the christmas swine!
Get the pretty one!
♪ Macaroni and cheese
(oinking)
♪ and Santa put gifts
under christmas trees ♪
♪ in the fireplace
is the yule log ♪
♪ beneath the mistletoe
as we drink eggnog ♪
- Merry crap-mas, everyone.
- This sucks.
(sighs) Okay, guys.
I know christmas didn't
go exactly how we planned.
- We don't have any presents under the tree.
- We don't have a tree.
So this is what we're
gonna do, okay?
We're gonna go downstairs,
and we are gonna make
the best of this.
All right? Let's go.
(claps hands)
Come on.
(pig squealing)
♪ We wish you a merry christmas ♪
♪ we wish you a merry christmas ♪
(drumming)
♪ We wish you
a merry christmas ♪
God bless us, every one!
Aah! (squealing)
♪ We wish you
a merry christmas ♪
Merry christmas, Weavers!
What the heck is going on?
Well, we know you wanted the
perfect christmas... (humming)
and we know you wanted
to go to hawaii,
so we decided
to give you both.
Believe it or not,
it was Larry Bird's idea.
Where is Larry?
(Larry Bird) Ho, ho, ho!
(bellowing laugh)
I understand your children
had a bit of a mishap
with their presents
this year.
It was short notice, but I was able
to get the key items on their lists.
Now gather 'round the tree,
let's light up the menorah,
and we'll kwanzaa
till the break of dawn.
(bellowing laugh)
(Max laughs)
(Larry Bird) Check it out.
Your dad and I know how badly you wanted
to go snowboarding with your friends...
- Snowboarding!
- Wh...
(Debbie) So here's the deal.
If you can be packed
and ready to go in a couple hours,
I will personally
drive you there myself.
Are you kidding me?
And miss this insanity?
There's absolutely no way.
Ohh!
There's the christmas face I've been
hanging on to for all these years.
You owe me a snowboard.
And there's the one
I've learned to accept.
Now, I hear you wanted
the new ipad.
Gee, thanks.
The wi-fi's a bit spotty.
(lowered voice)
I know who you are.
I knew you were an alien,
but I didn't know
you were also Santa Claus.
(lowered voice)
Oh, I'm not real...
Oh.
Don't tell anyone.
It'll be our little secret.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
♪ We wish you a merry christmas ♪
(bellowing laugh)
♪ and a happy new year
♪ We wish you
a merry christmas ♪
♪ We wish you a merry christmas ♪
(bleating)
♪ and a happy new year
Siri, who won the knicks game?
Give me
a 5-day weather forecast.
Buy me the new
Mumford & Sons album. Ugh.
That's it.
I'm gonna get a kindle.
I'm done with you!
(scoffs)
(inhales deeply)
Mm.
I'm sorry.
It's been a rough week.
Come along.
Let's go for a walk.
Siri, does this suit
make my ass look big?
www.addic7ed.com