1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:26,000


2
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:26,000


3
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:26,000


4
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:10,000
{\pos(90,248)}

5
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:10,000
{\pos(100,254)}人人影視
YYeTs.com

6
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:10,000
{\pos(105,265)}原創翻譯 雙語字幕

8
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:10,000
{\pos(237,265)}僅供學習 禁止用於任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com

9
00:00:10,000 --> 00:00:15,000
翻譯：冰藍

11
00:00:15,000 --> 00:00:20,000
校對：冰藍天然呆    時間軸：小雨     貝貝

12
00:00:20,000 --> 00:00:25,000
後期/特效：WiLL    總監：冰藍     WiLL

14
00:00:53,610 --> 00:00:57,580
我是德拉戈  老子的包裹呢
This is Drago. Where is my fucking package?

15
00:00:57,770 --> 00:00:59,480
老子才不管什麼狗屁規矩
I don't give a fuck about his fucking rules!

16
00:00:59,480 --> 00:01:02,750
我的規矩是  付了錢就要交貨
My rule is: I'll make the delivery that I fucking paid for!

17
00:01:10,820 --> 00:01:13,510
告訴你  我決定跳過中介  凱根  
You know what? I'm cutting out the middle man, Kagan.

18
00:01:13,510 --> 00:01:17,020
沒錯  就是你  告訴我聯繫人的電話
Yes, I mean you. Give me the contact number.

19
00:01:34,410 --> 00:01:37,570
再讓我問一次  我就割斷你的喉嚨
Make me ask you again, and I'll cut your throat out.

20
00:01:56,190 --> 00:01:56,960
您好
Yes?

21
00:01:56,960 --> 00:01:59,460
-司機在哪  -您說什麼
- Where is the driver? - I'm sorry?

22
00:01:59,460 --> 00:02:02,460
中介凱根太不靠譜
That piece of shit Kagan set up this deal that's gone bad.

23
00:02:02,460 --> 00:02:05,270
-我要你辦好這事  -我們只和凱根做交易
- I want you to make it good. - We only deal with Kagan.

24
00:02:05,270 --> 00:02:07,340
凱根和這次交易沒關係了
Kagan's no longer part of this deal.

25
00:02:07,610 --> 00:02:10,620
我是客戶  貨在哪
I'm the client. Where is the package?

26
00:02:10,650 --> 00:02:13,250
抱歉  先生  可能有所延誤
I'm sorry, sir. The delivery might be behind schedule.

27
00:02:12,040 --> 00:02:13,290
{\an8}來電

28
00:02:13,250 --> 00:02:14,790
現在就該送到了
The delivery was due now!

29
00:02:13,290 --> 00:02:14,880
{\an8}無法顯示對方號碼

30
00:02:15,540 --> 00:02:18,570
抱歉  先生  我正在盡力查看運送情況
Excuse me, sir, but I'm doing my best to locate your package now.

31
00:02:18,780 --> 00:02:21,660
再加點油  找到我的貨
Well, do better than your best. Find it.

32
00:02:22,040 --> 00:02:22,790
{\an8}無法顯示對方號碼

33
00:02:22,390 --> 00:02:23,920
別追蹤我的號碼了
Don't bother tracing the call.

34
00:02:23,920 --> 00:02:26,430
我是德拉戈·蘇也克  去問問吧
My name is Drago Sojic, ask around.

35
00:02:22,790 --> 00:02:23,720
{\an8}查找//弗蘭克

36
00:02:23,720 --> 00:02:25,300
{\an8}無法獲取位置

37
00:02:26,640 --> 00:02:30,360
聽到我的大名  你的司機就該乖乖把貨送來
My reputation should encourage your driver to finish this deal.

38
00:02:30,970 --> 00:02:32,260
他是快遞員
Transporter. 

39
00:02:32,260 --> 00:02:34,360
而且我正在確定他的位置  蘇也克先生
And I'm locating him, Mr. Sujic.

40
00:02:34,460 --> 00:02:37,530
為了他的安全  希望你比我更早找到他
For his sake, I hope you locate him before I do.

41
00:02:40,430 --> 00:02:42,010
{\an8}撥打弗蘭克電話 開始查詢來電號碼 無法追蹤位置

42
00:02:42,030 --> 00:02:43,070
{\an8}撥打弗蘭克電話

43
00:02:42,650 --> 00:02:44,140
拜託  弗蘭克  接電話
Come on, Frank, pick up.

44
00:03:09,010 --> 00:03:10,490
非常人販 電視劇版
第一季 第四集

45
00:04:28,050 --> 00:04:32,460
三小時前

46
00:04:43,850 --> 00:04:46,050
抱歉  不是好消息
I'm sorry, but the news is not good.

47
00:04:47,080 --> 00:04:50,530
理查德的第三次心臟移植手術排斥了
Richard's heart has rejected the third ventricle implant.

48
00:04:50,960 --> 00:04:54,130
-心肌病加重了  -這是什麼意思
- And cardiomyopathy is worsening. - What does that mean?

49
00:04:55,130 --> 00:04:57,120
現在您兒子唯一活下去的指望
At this point, the only chance your son has 

50
00:04:57,120 --> 00:04:59,490
就是第四次心臟移植手術
for survival is a full transplant.

51
00:04:59,890 --> 00:05:00,840
天啊
Oh, my god.

52
00:05:01,010 --> 00:05:04,340
阿爾貝尼茲先生  我得說這並不容易
I should tell you there are many hurdles, Monsieur Albeniz.

53
00:05:04,340 --> 00:05:07,250
匹配的心臟目前還沒有
A compatible heart is not automatically available.

54
00:05:07,290 --> 00:05:08,780
如果有了就是我們優先對吧
We are very high on the waiting list.

55
00:05:08,780 --> 00:05:11,270
當然  明早把理查德
Of course. Bring Richard back to the hospital

56
00:05:11,280 --> 00:05:13,170
送來醫院進行觀察
tomorrow morning for observation.

57
00:05:13,170 --> 00:05:15,470
如果有了匹配的心臟
When and if a suitable heart becomes available,

58
00:05:15,470 --> 00:05:18,680
我們就能馬上動手術
we will be ready to go into surgery immediately.

59
00:05:19,840 --> 00:05:20,790
您覺得心臟...
Do you think a heart--

60
00:05:20,790 --> 00:05:22,220
我無法保證
I can't promise anything.

61
00:05:30,660 --> 00:05:31,930
要帶書嗎
Do you want books?

62
00:05:31,940 --> 00:05:33,600
要  我要看完《動物莊園》
Yes. I'll finish Animal Farm.

63
00:05:33,850 --> 00:05:35,830
高中就要求看《動物莊園》了嗎
They make you read Animal Farm at school?

64
00:05:35,830 --> 00:05:38,010
這是額外任務  我已經看完了其他書
It's extra. I finished the other ones already.

65
00:05:39,280 --> 00:05:42,060
如果我要上巴黎政治大學  就得刻苦
I have to be ready for exams if I'm going to Sciences Po.

66
00:05:47,820 --> 00:05:51,640
爸爸  你必須堅持下去  媽媽現在很痛苦
Dad, we have to keep going--for Mama. She's having a tough time.

67
00:05:52,960 --> 00:05:54,580
她好害怕  理查德
She's so afraid, Richard,

68
00:05:55,620 --> 00:05:56,500
害怕失去你
to lose you.

69
00:05:57,630 --> 00:05:59,200
你們不會失去我  爸爸
No one's losing anyone, Papa.

70
00:06:05,690 --> 00:06:07,860
去吧  媽媽會嚇壞的
Allez. Maman va flipper.

71
00:06:22,570 --> 00:06:24,750
你想過招個人來幫忙嗎 
Do you ever think of hiring someone to help you with that?

72
00:06:24,750 --> 00:06:26,360
你可能受傷
You know, someone could get hurt.

73
00:06:26,850 --> 00:06:28,390
不用  弗蘭克  我一直使用這些工具
Look, Frank, when you've used this equipment

74
00:06:28,390 --> 00:06:31,210
太得心應手了
for as long as I have, it is an instinct.

75
00:06:33,780 --> 00:06:34,760
怎麼
Why?

76
00:06:36,470 --> 00:06:37,570
我讓你緊張了嗎
Do I make you nervous?

77
00:06:38,050 --> 00:06:39,800
我只是不想看你摧毀一輛車
I'd just hate to see you damage the car.

78
00:06:40,110 --> 00:06:42,460
你負責駕駛  我負責修車
You take care of the driving, I take care of the cars.

79
00:06:43,290 --> 00:06:44,060
好吧
Ok.

80
00:06:56,920 --> 00:06:58,340
也許你沒取掉所有螺絲
Maybe you didn't get all the nuts.

81
00:06:58,840 --> 00:07:01,040
我當然全取掉了  你為什麼要這樣
Of course I got all the nuts. Why do you do this?

82
00:07:01,250 --> 00:07:02,450
安全第一哦  迪爾特
Safety first, Dieter.

83
00:07:02,450 --> 00:07:04,610
你還和我談安全
Oh, look who's talking to me about safety.

84
00:07:13,770 --> 00:07:14,630
你還好嗎
Everything all right?

85
00:07:14,920 --> 00:07:16,900
挺好的
Uh, yeah, yeah, everything's all right.

86
00:07:19,980 --> 00:07:22,350
你能把手推車拿給我嗎
Um... can you pass me this, um, dolly?

87
00:07:23,990 --> 00:07:24,860
-那個嗎  -對
- That one? - Yeah.

88
00:07:26,300 --> 00:07:29,020
-這裡的手推車嗎  -對
- That one there? - Oui, oui. Uh, yeah.

89
00:07:35,330 --> 00:07:36,170
謝了  
Thanks.

90
00:07:37,330 --> 00:07:38,140
天啊
Oh, my god.

91
00:07:39,920 --> 00:07:42,340
-你確定沒事吧  -沒事
- Are you sure everything's all right? - Yeah, yeah. Fine, fine.

92
00:07:43,170 --> 00:07:44,710
我只是要檢查集合管
I'll just check the manifold.

93
00:07:51,560 --> 00:07:53,200
能推我一把嗎
Uh, could you give me a little push?

94
00:07:59,850 --> 00:08:00,920
再推一下
Just a little bit more...

95
00:08:01,510 --> 00:08:02,650
推到車下
under the car, please.

96
00:08:04,030 --> 00:08:05,490
太好了
Yeah, that's great.

97
00:08:05,680 --> 00:08:08,800
-我得走了  -保重  回見
- I gotta go. - Sure, sure. See you later.

98
00:08:09,090 --> 00:08:10,280
起來時別指望我
Don't get up on my account.

99
00:08:10,350 --> 00:08:13,400
好  我只是檢查一下聯動裝置
Yeah. Like I said, I'll just check the linkage.

100
00:08:13,430 --> 00:08:15,530
-不是集合管嗎  -對  集合管
- Not the manifold? - Yes, the manifold.

101
00:08:17,700 --> 00:08:21,010
待會兒我想
I was thinking maybe... maybe later today

102
00:08:21,010 --> 00:08:23,130
做個按摩  舒筋活骨
I could get a massage, ease the aches and pains, yeah?

103
00:08:23,130 --> 00:08:25,640
聽起來是個好主意
Oh, that sounds like a very good idea for you.

104
00:08:26,380 --> 00:08:29,450
-我得走了  謝謝你的咖啡  -不客氣
- I gotta push off. Thanks for the coffee. - Welcome. 

105
00:08:29,450 --> 00:08:32,490
-慢慢檢查聯動裝置吧  -好
- Good luck with the, uh, linkage. - Yeah.

106
00:08:35,420 --> 00:08:36,460
去死吧
Fuck you.

107
00:08:43,170 --> 00:08:47,700
如果我是銀行  你就會破產蹲大牢
If I was a bank, you'd be bankrupt and in jail.

108
00:08:48,420 --> 00:08:52,860
不過我只是個人  也沒人權
But since I am just an individual person and I have no rights,

109
00:08:53,070 --> 00:08:55,560
你就可以免此一劫了
you are allowed to walk free,

110
00:08:56,270 --> 00:08:59,970
所以我就得自己打理生意
so I have to take care of my business however I can,

111
00:09:00,260 --> 00:09:02,080
在這件事中  就是說...
which, in your case, means--

112
00:09:05,690 --> 00:09:06,610
去外面等著
Wait outside.

113
00:09:18,060 --> 00:09:18,820
真抱歉
I'm sorry.

114
00:09:20,050 --> 00:09:20,930
我試過了
I tried.

115
00:09:21,870 --> 00:09:23,880
我試過了一切  但是仍然不能康復
I tried everything, but I-I just didn't get better.

116
00:09:24,410 --> 00:09:26,070
不不不  別怪自己
No, no, no, don't blame yourself.

117
00:09:26,080 --> 00:09:29,360
只是...  你只是病了  沒關係
It's... You're just sick. It's OK.

118
00:09:30,490 --> 00:09:33,790
你還可以接受別的療法  看別的醫生
There are other treatments, other doctors. You'll see.

119
00:09:34,280 --> 00:09:36,050
這次我只想回家
I just wanted to come home all this time.

120
00:09:37,220 --> 00:09:38,070
我知道
I know.

121
00:09:39,700 --> 00:09:41,590
安娜帶你回家  我一會兒就回去
Anna will take you home. I'll be there shortly. 

122
00:09:41,590 --> 00:09:44,750
-還有些事要辦  -你不生氣嗎
- I just have some business to finish. - You're not angry?

123
00:09:44,750 --> 00:09:47,950
生氣  我怎麼會生氣
Angry? How could I be angry?

124
00:09:51,360 --> 00:09:52,840
讓我靜一下
I just need a minute.

125
00:09:55,040 --> 00:09:58,570
菲利普  我的兒子  我的乖兒子
Oh, Filip, my boy. My precious boy.

126
00:10:00,330 --> 00:10:03,400
我不會讓你死的  我向你保證
I will not let you die. I promise you that.

127
00:10:05,250 --> 00:10:06,980
我會盡一切努力  好嗎
I'll do anything. OK?

128
00:10:26,330 --> 00:10:29,870
總之  引用弗裡德裡希·馮·席勒的話
So, in conclusion, to quote Friedrich Schiller,

129
00:10:26,350 --> 00:10:30,190
{\an8}德國18世紀著名詩人  哲學家  歷史學家和劇作家

130
00:10:30,840 --> 00:10:32,540
父子不僅是血肉至親
"It is not flesh and blood,

131
00:10:33,620 --> 00:10:37,270
更是靈魂相依
but heart that makes us fathers and sons".

132
00:10:47,520 --> 00:10:48,920
索菲  
Sophie?

133
00:10:48,930 --> 00:10:50,810
-親愛的  有了  -怎麼了
- Sweetie, they have one. - What?

134
00:10:50,810 --> 00:10:52,030
-什麼  -他們有心臟了
- What? - They have a heart.

135
00:10:52,710 --> 00:10:55,350
不可能  天啊
C'est pas vrai. Oh, my god.

136
00:10:56,750 --> 00:11:00,680
-難以置信  -馬上過來
- Encroyable. - Yes, come down immediately.

137
00:11:00,680 --> 00:11:02,520
謝天謝地  我就過來
Oh, thank God. I'm on my way.

138
00:11:05,640 --> 00:11:07,080
我以前喜歡打拳擊  
I used to love to box,

139
00:11:07,120 --> 00:11:09,780
但我不再辦健身會員卡了
but I don't bother with a gym membership anymore.

140
00:11:09,780 --> 00:11:12,130
現在我就在家打
I make do with what I have.

141
00:11:16,480 --> 00:11:19,850
省錢  而且健身效果很好
It saves me money, and it's such a good workout.

142
00:11:19,850 --> 00:11:22,040
我會付款  我手裡有你的錢
I'll pay! I've got your money!

143
00:11:22,050 --> 00:11:24,420
現在我無所謂了
At this point, I don't care.

144
00:11:31,830 --> 00:11:32,580
怎麼了
It's happened?

145
00:11:33,000 --> 00:11:35,360
有名捐贈者  心臟就要到了
There is a donor. The heart is on its way.

146
00:11:35,670 --> 00:11:37,390
我派司機過去  一小時內趕到
I'll have a driver there within the hour.

147
00:11:37,910 --> 00:11:41,370
偷心臟對我來說很困難
Listen, it's going to be difficult for me to get the heart out. 

148
00:11:41,370 --> 00:11:43,150
有人一直守著心臟
There is constant supervision.

149
00:11:43,420 --> 00:11:46,260
如果你失手了  那你就等死吧
It's going to be a lot harder for you if you fail.

150
00:12:13,730 --> 00:12:14,760
快來了
Almost time.

151
00:13:20,780 --> 00:13:23,250
{\an8}急診室

152
00:13:28,390 --> 00:13:29,470
你是司機嗎
Are you the transporter?

153
00:13:29,920 --> 00:13:31,870
盡快把這個帶給客戶   
You've got to get this to the client as fast as possible. 

154
00:13:31,870 --> 00:13:33,110
時間緊迫
There's no time to lose.

155
00:13:46,740 --> 00:13:47,610
怎麼回事
What is going on?

156
00:13:49,630 --> 00:13:50,500
心臟呢
Where's the heart?

157
00:14:04,480 --> 00:14:07,570
-怎麼會這樣  -我們尚且不知
- How could this happen?! - We don't know yet.

158
00:14:07,860 --> 00:14:09,110
我們已經確認心臟
We've confirmed that the heart

159
00:14:09,110 --> 00:14:11,080
在捐贈醫院的救護車上
was placed in the ambulance at the donor hospital.

160
00:14:11,080 --> 00:14:13,030
肯定是在路上被偷了
It must have gone missing somewhere en route.

161
00:14:13,030 --> 00:14:15,690
難道沒人一直守著嗎
Isn't someone supposed to be with it the entire way?

162
00:14:15,690 --> 00:14:18,240
有  醫護人員一路監督
Yes. Our technicians were there to supervise delivery.

163
00:14:18,240 --> 00:14:19,820
我們在查明真相
We're trying to figure out what happened.

164
00:14:19,820 --> 00:14:22,510
我向你保證我們在盡全力尋找心臟
I can assure you everything is being done to locate the heart. 

165
00:14:22,510 --> 00:14:23,760
警察正在趕來
The police are on their way.

166
00:14:24,460 --> 00:14:26,790
過多久心臟會停跳
How long before the heart is not usable?

167
00:14:27,910 --> 00:14:31,240
最多四小時
The heart can remain viable for only four hours at the most.

168
00:14:35,080 --> 00:14:36,880
你們最好在那時之前找到它
You'd better find it before then.

169
00:15:03,550 --> 00:15:04,390
打擾一下
Excuse me.

170
00:15:06,530 --> 00:15:09,440
-你是孩子的父親嗎  -是
Uh, are you the father of the young boy? - Yes.

171
00:15:09,510 --> 00:15:11,080
我是塔科尼警探  
I'm Inspector Tarconi.

172
00:15:11,800 --> 00:15:13,910
負責調查此案
I will be in charge of the investigation.

173
00:15:14,050 --> 00:15:15,150
有線索了嗎
Do you have any leads?

174
00:15:16,100 --> 00:15:17,570
確實有
As a matter of fact, we do. 

175
00:15:17,570 --> 00:15:19,450
負責運送心臟的
One of the technicians involved 

176
00:15:19,450 --> 00:15:22,040
一名醫護人員失蹤了
in the transfer of the heart has gone missing.

177
00:15:22,040 --> 00:15:26,670
我們在出入市的大路上設立了檢查點
We have set up checkpoints on all major roads into and out of the city.

178
00:15:27,000 --> 00:15:29,560
警探  醫護人員找到了
Inspector. They found the technician. 

179
00:15:29,560 --> 00:15:31,340
-他在這裡  - 失陪了
- He's here. - Excuse me.

180
00:15:36,290 --> 00:15:39,310
他按時取了心臟  但是沒送過來
He collected the heart as scheduled, but it was never delivered. 

181
00:15:39,400 --> 00:15:42,150
顯然  他在去機場的路上被攔下了
Apparently, he was picked up on his way to the airport.

182
00:15:42,150 --> 00:15:44,150
他說自己要去度假
He claims he was going on vacation,

183
00:15:44,150 --> 00:15:46,800
但是醫院沒有他請假的記錄
but the hospital has no record of him asking for time off.

184
00:15:50,180 --> 00:15:51,790
還剩多少時間
How much time do we have?

185
00:15:52,560 --> 00:15:54,540
三個小時多一點
Just over three hours.

186
00:15:55,440 --> 00:15:57,740
我進來時看到記者了
I passed some reporters on my way in.

187
00:15:57,740 --> 00:15:59,850
是啊  壞事傳千里
Yes, the story got out quite fast.

188
00:16:00,640 --> 00:16:02,180
我要請你幫個忙
I need you to do me a favour.

189
00:16:23,020 --> 00:16:25,840
-我是塔科尼警探  -好吧
- I'm Inspector Tarconi. - Good for you.

190
00:16:28,030 --> 00:16:30,180
你在這家醫院工作對吧
You work for this hospital, yes?

191
00:16:30,490 --> 00:16:33,490
醫護人員  還是移植小組的一員
A medical technician with access to the transplant team?

192
00:16:33,490 --> 00:16:36,100
我已經告訴他們  我和這事沒關係
Look, I already told them I had nothing to do with this.

193
00:16:39,660 --> 00:16:40,850
這是怎麼回事
What the fuck is this?

194
00:16:42,260 --> 00:16:43,390
記者
Reporters.

195
00:16:43,660 --> 00:16:45,730
他們一聽說這種事就趨之若鶩
When they get a whiff of something like this,

196
00:16:45,730 --> 00:16:48,120
簡直無法攔住他們
it's almost impossible to keep them away.

197
00:16:48,160 --> 00:16:49,370
我去和他們談談
I will talk to them.

198
00:17:08,720 --> 00:17:10,090
深表歉意
Sorry about that.

199
00:17:12,020 --> 00:17:15,910
我們說到哪裡來了
Now... um, where were we?

200
00:17:16,060 --> 00:17:17,370
你和他們說了什麼
What did you say to them?

201
00:17:17,370 --> 00:17:19,190
我說你認罪了
I just told them you confessed 

202
00:17:19,190 --> 00:17:24,030
還要供出所有涉案人員的名字
and that you were giving us the names of everyone involved in the plot.

203
00:17:24,080 --> 00:17:26,970
你他媽瘋了吧  我從沒這麼說過
Are you fucking insane? I didn't say anything like that.

204
00:17:26,980 --> 00:17:28,570
當然沒有
Of course not.

205
00:17:28,740 --> 00:17:31,110
但如果你真是無辜的
But if you're innocent, as you claim,

206
00:17:31,110 --> 00:17:33,430
真正的罪犯就馬上會知道
the people responsible will know immediately 

207
00:17:33,430 --> 00:17:35,660
這不過是我的計策
that it was just a trick on my part.

208
00:17:36,520 --> 00:17:39,560
當然  我會保護
Of course, I am in a position to offer protection

209
00:17:39,620 --> 00:17:42,930
願意合作的人
for anyone willing to cooperate.

210
00:17:50,050 --> 00:17:51,450
他知道心臟在哪嗎
Does he know where the heart is?

211
00:17:51,560 --> 00:17:55,150
不知道  但他告訴我們有人也許能幫忙
No. But he led us to a man who may be able to help.

212
00:17:55,920 --> 00:17:58,980
-誰  -我以前和他打過交道
- Who? - Someone I have dealt with before.

213
00:18:15,040 --> 00:18:16,370
警探
Yes, Inspector?

214
00:18:16,570 --> 00:18:18,160
情況緊急  弗蘭克
It's urgent Frank.

215
00:18:18,160 --> 00:18:19,850
現在我不方便說話
I'm afraid I can't really speak now.

216
00:18:19,940 --> 00:18:21,680
也許你看了新聞
Perhaps you have heard on the news.

217
00:18:22,120 --> 00:18:24,640
用於移植的心臟被偷了
A heart was stolen. It was needed for a transplant.

218
00:18:24,640 --> 00:18:27,220
-不  我沒聽說過  -我們抓到了一名男子
- No, I've not heard. -I just arrested a man 

219
00:18:27,220 --> 00:18:30,370
他說把心臟交給了快遞員
who confessed to giving the heart to a driver for transport.

220
00:18:30,460 --> 00:18:34,110
他描述了快遞員和車的樣子
He gave a description of the man and his car.

221
00:18:34,110 --> 00:18:35,640
弗蘭克  和你相符
Frank, it matched you.

222
00:18:35,640 --> 00:18:37,130
我有消息就告訴你
I'll let you know if I hear anything.

223
00:18:37,130 --> 00:18:37,840
弗蘭克  要知道
Frank, you should know that 

224
00:18:37,840 --> 00:18:40,550
一名14歲男孩急需心臟  他病得很重
the heart is for a 14-year-old boy, very sick.

225
00:18:40,830 --> 00:18:44,330
如果手術不在三小時內進行  
He will die if this surgery is not carried out

226
00:18:44,330 --> 00:18:45,920
他就會死
just under three hours now.

227
00:18:46,450 --> 00:18:49,290
-弗蘭克  -我得掛了  警探
- Frank? - Got to go, Inspector.

228
00:18:49,290 --> 00:18:51,030
掛斷

229
00:18:55,380 --> 00:18:57,240
-貨在哪裡  -後備箱裡
- Where's the package? - Trunk.

230
00:18:57,640 --> 00:18:58,530
打開後備箱
Open it.

231
00:19:10,180 --> 00:19:11,480
搞什麼
What the fuck?

232
00:19:15,960 --> 00:19:18,900
快打開  沒空和你耗著
Hey. Let's go. We don't have time for this.

233
00:19:22,620 --> 00:19:25,270
要報酬嗎  打開後備箱
You want the payment? Open the trunk.

234
00:19:33,800 --> 00:19:35,510
攔住他  攔住他

235
00:19:42,310 --> 00:19:44,000
把老子的電話拿來
Give me my fucking phone!

236
00:19:49,020 --> 00:19:51,540
我不喜歡你突然造訪
You know I don't like it when you come by without calling. 

237
00:19:51,830 --> 00:19:53,640
我正好在這附近
I was in the neighbourhood.

238
00:19:54,260 --> 00:19:57,990
-凱根  你想怎麼樣  -什麼
- Kagan, what do you want. - What?

239
00:19:58,210 --> 00:19:59,920
如果你不告訴我你來幹嘛
If you don't tell me what you're doing here,

240
00:19:59,920 --> 00:20:01,820
我就把你從窗戶扔出去
I'm throwing you out those windows.

241
00:20:03,100 --> 00:20:06,180
我們得談談你男人的事
We need to talk about your man.

242
00:20:20,410 --> 00:20:21,610
說重點
Get to your point. 

243
00:20:22,340 --> 00:20:23,400
我在想
I've been thinking.

244
00:20:23,400 --> 00:20:24,830
這可是頭一回
That's a first. 

245
00:20:25,020 --> 00:20:27,890
最近  這些任務
Lately, when it comes to these jobs,

246
00:20:27,890 --> 00:20:31,280
變得有些複雜
things have been getting a little complicated.

247
00:20:31,600 --> 00:20:32,520
你得承認  
I mean, you gotta admit,

248
00:20:32,520 --> 00:20:34,640
有太多人死了
the body count has been getting a little high.

249
00:20:34,640 --> 00:20:37,860
兩次都是自衛  而且那些人都是匪徒
Self-defence both times, and they were both scumbags.

250
00:20:37,860 --> 00:20:39,520
有一個還是你介紹來的
One of them was referred by you. 

251
00:20:39,520 --> 00:20:41,730
我只是說  
All I'm saying is that 

252
00:20:41,730 --> 00:20:45,830
你男人開始小有名氣了
your boy is starting to get a bit of a reputation.

253
00:20:45,830 --> 00:20:47,070
什麼名氣
For what?

254
00:20:48,550 --> 00:20:53,080
這樣說吧  他很引人注目
Oh, let's just call it a flair for the dramatic.

255
00:20:53,380 --> 00:20:56,040
這傢伙很會惹麻煩  卡拉
The guy is a bull in a china shop, Carla,

256
00:20:56,190 --> 00:20:57,760
樹敵不少
and he's making enemies.

257
00:21:00,840 --> 00:21:03,800
找到快遞員  拿回心臟
Find the transporter, get me the heart, 

258
00:21:03,800 --> 00:21:05,870
再殺了那混蛋
then kill that asshole.

259
00:21:06,650 --> 00:21:07,620
快去
Go!

260
00:22:16,750 --> 00:22:21,130
我是德拉戈  老子的包裹呢
This is Drago. Where is my fucking package?

261
00:22:21,310 --> 00:22:24,020
告訴你  我決定跳過中介  凱根
You know what? I'm cutting out the middle man, Kagan.

262
00:22:24,020 --> 00:22:25,700
沒錯  就是你
Yes, I mean you.

263
00:22:35,080 --> 00:22:36,270
又怎麼了
Now what? 

264
00:22:36,360 --> 00:22:38,220
我剛剛都還和你談過
What were we just talking about?

265
00:22:38,220 --> 00:22:40,690
-你什麼意思  -你男人又闖禍了
- What do you mean? - Your man is at it again.

266
00:22:40,690 --> 00:22:42,010
阿吉  怎麼回事
Aggy, what's going on? 

267
00:22:42,010 --> 00:22:43,430
別說我沒警告過你
Don't say I didn't warn you.

268
00:22:53,020 --> 00:22:53,970
給你

269
00:23:03,340 --> 00:23:05,080
如果心臟超過三小時才到
If this heart takes any more than three hours to get here,

270
00:23:05,080 --> 00:23:06,400
就失效了
it's not going to be viable. 

271
00:23:06,400 --> 00:23:07,840
血壓下降
Blood pressure's dropping.

272
00:23:15,190 --> 00:23:16,020
他的心臟正在衰竭
His heart's failing. 

273
00:23:16,020 --> 00:23:18,580
我們必須送他進手術室  去開門
We have to get him in the OR right away. Get the door.

274
00:23:18,680 --> 00:23:20,490
走吧  快點
Let's go, let's go, quick.

275
00:23:22,640 --> 00:23:23,870
快  快

276
00:23:27,270 --> 00:23:28,070
走
Let's go. 

277
00:23:29,310 --> 00:23:30,820
怎麼回事
What's happening?

278
00:23:30,930 --> 00:23:33,570
他現在充血性心力衰竭  要進手術室
He's in congestive heart failure. They're taking him to the OR.

279
00:23:33,570 --> 00:23:35,410
要立刻接上人工心肺機
They need to put him on a cardiopulmonary 

280
00:23:35,410 --> 00:23:36,740
給他保命
bypass machine immediately.

281
00:23:36,740 --> 00:23:39,130
但是心臟還沒找到
But the new heart has not been recovered yet!

282
00:23:39,130 --> 00:23:41,520
抱歉  我們別無選擇
I'm sorry. We have no other choice.

283
00:23:46,690 --> 00:23:49,710
{\an8}酒吧  餐館

284
00:23:57,500 --> 00:23:58,800
{\an8}內有器官  心臟

285
00:24:19,060 --> 00:24:19,890
您好
Hello?

286
00:24:19,810 --> 00:24:21,860
{\an8}進行全球跟蹤

287
00:24:19,890 --> 00:24:22,540
-你找到他了嗎  -找到了
- Have you found him yet? - Yes.

288
00:24:22,900 --> 00:24:25,900
-他在回來的路上嗎  -還沒有
- Is he on his way back here? - Not yet.

289
00:24:26,270 --> 00:24:28,120
我告訴過你  我保證
I told you. I promise no harm 

290
00:24:28,120 --> 00:24:29,910
如果他送回包裹  我就不傷害他
will come to him if he brings me the package,

291
00:24:29,910 --> 00:24:31,780
但他現在就得送過來
but he needs to bring it to me now.

292
00:24:32,450 --> 00:24:35,290
-我理解  -那你為什麼還不阻止他
- I understand. - Then why haven't you stopped him?

293
00:24:34,690 --> 00:24:37,010
{\an8}來源是誰
跟蹤來源
查找來源

294
00:24:35,460 --> 00:24:37,150
他不聽我的
He doesn't take orders from me.

295
00:24:37,150 --> 00:24:38,600
讓我和他談談
Let me speak to him.

296
00:24:38,600 --> 00:24:39,920
這可不是個好主意
I don't think that's a good idea.

297
00:24:39,920 --> 00:24:42,180
我才不管你怎麼想
I don't give a shit what you think!

298
00:24:42,340 --> 00:24:44,120
給我接通他的電話
Put me through to him right now.

299
00:24:44,420 --> 00:24:45,850
我盡力吧
Let me see what I can do.

300
00:24:48,980 --> 00:24:51,420
{\an8}來電  卡拉·瓦萊麗
接聽  忽略

301
00:24:51,700 --> 00:24:52,520
卡拉
Carla?

302
00:24:52,520 --> 00:24:54,540
弗蘭克  我接到了憤怒客戶的來電
Frank, I just got an angry call from the client. 

303
00:24:54,540 --> 00:24:56,310
你沒有送去包裹
You didn't deliver the package.

304
00:24:56,310 --> 00:24:57,480
你知道那是什麼東西嗎
You know what it is?

305
00:24:58,160 --> 00:25:01,180
弗蘭克  我還以為這沒關係
Frank, I thought that wasn't suppose to matter.

306
00:25:01,180 --> 00:25:02,510
是心臟
It's a human heart, 

307
00:25:02,510 --> 00:25:05,460
要移植給一名垂死男孩  後來被偷了
stolen before it could be transplanted into a dying boy.

308
00:25:06,220 --> 00:25:08,570
客戶是德拉戈·蘇也克
The client is Drago Sujic.

309
00:25:08,570 --> 00:25:11,720
你知道他是法國南部最有名的犯罪頭子
And you know he's one of the biggest crime bosses in Southern France.

310
00:25:11,720 --> 00:25:14,920
和政界  警察都有勾結
Extremely well connected-- politicians, cops...

311
00:25:14,920 --> 00:25:17,290
我才不管  他為什麼要心臟
I don't give a shit. Why does he need a heart?

312
00:25:17,340 --> 00:25:18,430
我不知道
I don't know.

313
00:25:18,680 --> 00:25:20,120
去查啊
Well find out!

314
00:25:24,870 --> 00:25:25,840
{\an8}德拉戈·蘇也克

315
00:25:31,440 --> 00:25:32,480
{\an8}德拉戈·蘇也克

316
00:25:32,910 --> 00:25:34,260
{\an8}申請接受捐贈

317
00:25:42,430 --> 00:25:44,950
-喂  -德拉戈有個16歲的兒子
Yes? - Drago has a son, 16 years old.

318
00:25:44,950 --> 00:25:46,370
患有先天性心臟病
Born with a heart defect.

319
00:25:46,370 --> 00:25:47,830
他的心臟衰竭好幾年了
His heart has declined for years, 

320
00:25:47,830 --> 00:25:49,820
現在急需移植
now he's in desperate need of a transplant.

321
00:25:49,820 --> 00:25:51,930
德拉戈插隊了
So Drago cuts to the front of the line.

322
00:25:51,930 --> 00:25:54,140
他在家裡準備了一間現代化手術室
He built a state-of-the-art operating room in his mansion

323
00:25:54,140 --> 00:25:56,850
雇了一隊醫生
and hired an entire team of surgeons.

324
00:25:56,850 --> 00:25:58,870
他為此花費數百萬  弗蘭克
He's spent millions on this, Frank.

325
00:25:58,890 --> 00:26:00,740
你指望我同情他嗎
You expect me to feel something for the man?

326
00:26:00,740 --> 00:26:03,270
你之前問我原因  我只是在回答
You asked me why he needed a heart; I'm telling you.

327
00:26:03,270 --> 00:26:05,140
這活兒是凱根推薦的對吧
Kagan referred this job, didn't he?

328
00:26:05,180 --> 00:26:07,180
我來處理凱根的事  弗蘭克
Let me deal with Kagan, Frank.

329
00:26:07,350 --> 00:26:09,880
德拉戈在另一條線上  他想和你談談
Drago is on the other line. He wants to talk to you. 

330
00:26:10,560 --> 00:26:11,510
好吧
Fine.

331
00:26:11,870 --> 00:26:14,630
蘇也克先生  快遞員的電話接通了
Mr. Sujic, you're on with the transporter.

332
00:26:14,790 --> 00:26:15,690
你在哪
Where are you? 

333
00:26:16,240 --> 00:26:18,100
恐怕計劃有變
I'm afraid there's been a change of plans.

334
00:26:18,100 --> 00:26:21,050
別人說你從不改變交易
I was told you make it a point of never changing the deal.

335
00:26:21,910 --> 00:26:23,140
我們把定金還給你
We'll return your down payment. 

336
00:26:23,140 --> 00:26:25,030
去他媽的定金啊
Fuck the down payment!

337
00:26:25,270 --> 00:26:27,390
你必須在兩小時內送來包裹
You have less than two hours to bring me the package,

338
00:26:27,390 --> 00:26:30,720
不然老子一定會找到你  把你碎屍萬段
or I will track you down and I will fucking kill you!

339
00:26:36,740 --> 00:26:37,730
怎麼了
What is it?

340
00:26:39,280 --> 00:26:41,330
醫生想知道該不該把他弄醒
The surgeon wants to know if we should wake him up.

341
00:26:41,330 --> 00:26:42,280
幹什麼
What for?

342
00:26:43,130 --> 00:26:44,860
他們只能讓他昏迷這麼久
They can only keep him under for so long.

343
00:26:44,860 --> 00:26:46,820
手術照常進行
The surgeon goes ahead as planned,

344
00:26:47,050 --> 00:26:49,350
你要告訴組織裡所有人
because you are going to put out a description of the driver 

345
00:26:49,350 --> 00:26:51,460
司機的外貌和車型
and the make of the car to the whole organization. 

346
00:26:51,460 --> 00:26:53,410
街上要設立眼線
I want eyes on the street.

347
00:26:53,410 --> 00:26:55,160
我要所有皮條客  
I want every pimp, every hooker, every dealer

348
00:26:55,160 --> 00:26:56,790
妓女和毒販
that has ever been put on the payroll 

349
00:26:56,790 --> 00:26:58,710
都去找這個人
to be out there looking for this guy.

350
00:26:58,970 --> 00:27:02,240
一旦找到他  就通知我
And as soon as he's found, I want to know about it.

351
00:27:25,520 --> 00:27:26,930
開什麼玩笑啊
You've got to be kidding me.

352
00:28:38,390 --> 00:28:41,100
你要瑞典式按摩還是深層組織按摩
Swedish or deep tissue?

353
00:28:41,400 --> 00:28:43,260
能讓我的背放鬆就行
Whatever brings relief for my back. 

354
00:28:43,260 --> 00:28:45,220
我坐不下  站不直
I cannot sit or stand.

355
00:28:45,220 --> 00:28:46,760
放鬆吧
Just relax.

356
00:28:46,760 --> 00:28:49,660
我會讓你康復的
I am going to fix everything.

357
00:28:51,850 --> 00:28:53,140
等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.

358
00:28:54,230 --> 00:28:57,670
再給你點小費  最後要讓我
Here is a little something extra for the...

359
00:28:57,750 --> 00:28:58,780
爽一把
finishing. 

360
00:28:59,600 --> 00:29:00,410
爽一把
The finishing?

361
00:29:00,410 --> 00:29:03,210
就是最後...
The ending. Um, you know?

362
00:29:03,780 --> 00:29:05,370
讓我開心開心
To make it happy.

363
00:29:06,170 --> 00:29:07,770
抱歉
Oh, sorry. 

364
00:29:08,380 --> 00:29:11,290
-喂  -迪爾特  我需要一輛車
- Oui, hello? - Dieter, I need a car.

365
00:29:11,760 --> 00:29:13,090
-什麼時候  -現在
- When? - Now.

366
00:29:15,330 --> 00:29:17,900
-那是什麼聲音  -我在按摩
- What the hell was that? - I get a massage.

367
00:29:18,160 --> 00:29:20,700
今早我弄傷了背  我的背...
I hurt my back this morning. My back, I cannot... aah!

368
00:29:20,700 --> 00:29:23,540
我沒時間閒聊  情況緊急  我要一輛車
Listen, I don't have time to talk. It's urgent. I need a car.

369
00:29:23,540 --> 00:29:27,210
-放開我  -放鬆就好
- Ah! Let go of me! - Just relax. 

370
00:29:27,210 --> 00:29:29,080
你要扭斷我脖子  我怎麼放鬆
How can I relax when you break my neck?

371
00:29:29,080 --> 00:29:29,990
-迪爾特  -在
- Dieter? -Yes?

372
00:29:31,090 --> 00:29:34,070
-我要車  -你開的那輛呢
- The car. - Where is the one you drive in?

373
00:29:34,690 --> 00:29:36,290
出了點意外
I had a little accident.

374
00:29:36,680 --> 00:29:39,080
-車子陷在水泥裡了  -夠了
- The car ended up in a pool of wet cement. - Ah! Enough, enough.

375
00:29:39,080 --> 00:29:41,730
夠了  別讓我遭罪
Enough. Oh. Stop this savagery.

376
00:29:42,110 --> 00:29:45,360
還你  自己去爽吧
Here. Go finish yourself!

377
00:29:46,220 --> 00:29:46,750
迪爾特
Dieter! 

378
00:29:47,290 --> 00:29:49,400
弗蘭克  對不起  聽著
Frank, I'm sorry. Yes, listen,

379
00:29:49,400 --> 00:29:52,480
我幾乎動彈不得  更別提開車了
my back, I can barely move, and let alone drive.

380
00:29:52,480 --> 00:29:54,040
算了  你好好享受按摩吧
All right, forget it. Enjoy your massage.

381
00:29:54,040 --> 00:29:55,880
等等  你剛才是不是說水泥
Wait, did you say cement?

382
00:30:20,410 --> 00:30:23,110
雷內·杜加  街上盯梢的一個毒販
René Dugas, one of our dealers on the street. 

383
00:30:23,750 --> 00:30:24,720
雷內
René.

384
00:30:24,800 --> 00:30:26,900
蘇也克先生  我看到了您要找的人
Mr. Sujic, I just spotted your man.

385
00:30:26,900 --> 00:30:29,830
跟著他  別讓他離開你視線  盡量抓住他
Follow him, don't let him out of your sight, catch him if you can.

386
00:30:29,970 --> 00:30:31,900
跟緊點  他車技很棒
And stay sharp. He's an expert driver.

387
00:30:31,900 --> 00:30:33,710
不不  他在走路
No, no, he's on foot.

388
00:30:35,250 --> 00:30:37,110
他帶著包裹嗎
OK, does he have the package with him?

389
00:30:37,110 --> 00:30:38,730
他背了一個包  是指這個嗎
He's carrying a bag, if that's what you mean.

390
00:30:38,730 --> 00:30:41,010
抓住他  必要時可以幹掉他  我無所謂
Get him, kill him if you need to, I don't really care.

391
00:30:41,010 --> 00:30:44,600
但是一定要保護好包  明白嗎
But make sure you do not damage the package, do you understand me?

392
00:30:45,330 --> 00:30:46,320
是  先生
Yes, sir.

393
00:31:02,600 --> 00:31:04,180
快  快  抓住他
Go, go, go! Get him!

394
00:32:05,620 --> 00:32:07,430
停下  警察

395
00:32:30,420 --> 00:32:33,040
-喂  -弗蘭克  你在哪
- Yeah. - Frank, where are you?

396
00:32:33,040 --> 00:32:34,670
我一直在給你打電話  
I've been trying to call you.

397
00:32:34,800 --> 00:32:38,320
沒多少時間了  男孩的心臟衰竭了
There is not much time, the boy's heart has failed.

398
00:32:38,320 --> 00:32:40,550
此時他正躺在手術台上
He is on the operating table as I speak,

399
00:32:40,550 --> 00:32:42,850
我們接了台機器給他保命
hooked up to a machine that is keeping him alive.

400
00:32:42,850 --> 00:32:45,050
-我正努力呢  -你什麼意思
- I'm working on it. - What do you mean?

401
00:32:45,050 --> 00:32:46,770
你在幹什麼
What are you doing? 

402
00:32:46,770 --> 00:32:49,870
-心臟到底在不在你手裡  -我再打給你
- Do you have the heart or not?! - I'll get back to you. 

403
00:32:50,220 --> 00:32:52,240
天啊  該死
Aw, shit!

404
00:33:09,210 --> 00:33:10,290
先生
Monsieur!

405
00:33:11,610 --> 00:33:14,230
-有什麼能幫您的  先生  -不好意思  警官
Je peux vous aider, Monsieur? - Sorry, officer, uh...

406
00:33:15,260 --> 00:33:16,810
我只是在欣賞這輛車
just admiring your vehicle. 

407
00:33:17,450 --> 00:33:18,580
包裡是什麼
What's in the bag?

408
00:33:19,070 --> 00:33:20,610
其實我確實需要您的幫助
Actually, I do need your help.

409
00:33:21,200 --> 00:33:23,530
請保證把包裡的東西
It's critical that the contents of this bag 

410
00:33:23,920 --> 00:33:25,970
盡快送去醫院  這至關重要
get to a hospital as soon as possible. 

411
00:33:27,100 --> 00:33:29,120
放心  把包給我吧
I see. Leave it with me.

412
00:33:29,700 --> 00:33:30,660
謝謝
Thank you.

413
00:33:32,940 --> 00:33:34,520
你能幫我頂一會兒崗嗎
Can you hold the fort for a few minutes?

414
00:33:34,520 --> 00:33:37,300
剛才有人給了我這個  我要送去醫院
Someone just handed me this. I'll take it in.

415
00:33:37,300 --> 00:33:39,190
看起來是被偷的心臟
It looks like the missing heart.

416
00:33:46,080 --> 00:33:47,190
總部...
Dispatch--

417
00:34:00,520 --> 00:34:03,180
弗蘭克  別再玩遊戲了
Frank, we cannot be playing this game.

418
00:34:03,180 --> 00:34:04,940
心臟在警察手裡  警探
The police have the heart, Inspector.

419
00:34:04,940 --> 00:34:07,500
什麼  這是什麼時候的事
What? When did this happen?

420
00:34:07,540 --> 00:34:09,610
我剛給了警察  他們一定上報了
I just handed it over. They must have called it in.

421
00:34:09,610 --> 00:34:11,150
不可能
That's not possible.

422
00:34:11,150 --> 00:34:14,650
我的無線電裝置和總部連接
My radio has an open channel with Central Dispatch.

423
00:34:14,650 --> 00:34:16,470
如果有電話我會知道
I would have heard such a call.

424
00:34:16,870 --> 00:34:19,610
警察沒有上報給總部
These cops didn't call the central station.

425
00:34:24,600 --> 00:34:26,210
警探  我回頭找你
Inspector, I'll get back to you. 

426
00:34:26,430 --> 00:34:28,230
弗蘭克  你在幹什麼
Frank, what are you doing?!

427
00:34:59,460 --> 00:35:02,330
警探  恕我直言  我現在不方便說話
Inspector, with all due respect, I really can't talk now.

428
00:35:02,330 --> 00:35:04,250
我剛和總部聯繫了
I've just confirmed with dispatch.

429
00:35:04,250 --> 00:35:06,110
沒有警員打過電話
No officers called in.

430
00:35:06,700 --> 00:35:09,250
但是有一支分隊沒有回覆
But there is one unit not responding.

431
00:35:09,450 --> 00:35:12,420
他們被收買了  我知道他們要去哪  
Dirty cops. I know where they're going.

432
00:35:12,420 --> 00:35:13,310
我要搶先趕到
I'm going to get there first.

433
00:35:13,310 --> 00:35:15,100
-怎麼辦到  -我可是飆車達人
- How? - It's what I do.

434
00:35:15,100 --> 00:35:16,560
不到一小時  
We have less than one hour 

435
00:35:16,560 --> 00:35:19,050
捐贈的心臟就會停跳
before the donated heart becomes useless.

436
00:35:19,050 --> 00:35:20,720
我知道時間緊迫  警探
I'm aware of the time, Inspector.

437
00:35:20,720 --> 00:35:22,420
所以我得掛了
That's why I need to hang up now.

438
00:35:38,630 --> 00:35:40,780
-喂  -我拿到包裹了  正在趕來
- Yes? - I've got the package. I'm on my way.

439
00:35:40,780 --> 00:35:43,990
好  你到了我給你報酬
All right. I'll have the money for you when you get here.

440
00:35:55,640 --> 00:35:57,960
你說的是開警車過來
You said that you were coming in a police car.

441
00:36:02,220 --> 00:36:03,600
搞什麼
What the fuck?

442
00:36:07,260 --> 00:36:08,390
倒霉
Shit.

443
00:36:19,780 --> 00:36:22,030
心臟在哪  時間寶貴
Where's the heart? We don't have much time.

444
00:36:22,270 --> 00:36:23,230
這裡
Here.

445
00:36:53,540 --> 00:36:55,110
你個沒用的東西
Hey, you piece of shit.

446
00:36:56,680 --> 00:36:57,690
我的胸...
My chest.

447
00:36:57,690 --> 00:36:59,890
-好痛  -快上車
- Get in the car. - I'm fucking hurt.

448
00:37:02,950 --> 00:37:04,280
你要我開車嗎
You want me to drive?

449
00:37:04,440 --> 00:37:06,310
不然你想被爆頭嗎
You want me to shoot you in the fucking head?

450
00:37:35,170 --> 00:37:35,960
喂
Hello?

451
00:37:35,960 --> 00:37:38,590
在醫院的緊急入口等我
Go to the Emergency Room entrance at the side of the hospital.

452
00:37:38,590 --> 00:37:41,100
-你拿到心臟了嗎  -快去
- Do you have the heart? - Just go now.

453
00:37:45,750 --> 00:37:46,340
{\an8}聖塞巴斯蒂安醫院

454
00:37:59,030 --> 00:38:02,570
王八蛋  把包放下
Hey. Asshole. Put down the heart.

455
00:38:32,990 --> 00:38:35,570
住手  放下槍
Stop! Drop your gun!

456
00:38:52,490 --> 00:38:54,430
去吧  把心臟拿去
Go. Take the heart.

457
00:38:56,250 --> 00:38:57,300
找個醫生來
Get a doctor.

458
00:38:59,680 --> 00:39:01,770
求你了  我兒子
Please. My son.

459
00:39:10,980 --> 00:39:12,080
他要喪命了
He's fading.

460
00:39:13,550 --> 00:39:16,990
菲利普  拜託  我兒子
Filip. Please. My son.

461
00:39:17,420 --> 00:39:19,340
他要喪命了  快送他進去
He's fading. Get him inside now.

462
00:39:19,340 --> 00:39:20,810
不  他的脈搏跳動有力  
No, his pulse is still strong.

463
00:39:20,810 --> 00:39:22,240
如果心臟被擊中  脈搏才會衰弱
If the heart was hit, his pulse would be fading.

464
00:39:22,240 --> 00:39:23,290
如果不給他動手術
If we do not get him to surgery, 

465
00:39:23,290 --> 00:39:24,680
半小時內他就會死
he will die within a half an hour.

466
00:39:24,680 --> 00:39:26,000
那他的心臟呢
What about his heart?

467
00:39:27,730 --> 00:39:28,720
我同意  心臟沒被擊中
I agree, the heart was not hit,

468
00:39:28,720 --> 00:39:31,630
但他失血過多  性命難保
but he's losing too much blood. He cannot survive.

469
00:39:32,090 --> 00:39:33,990
你和你兒子心臟匹配嗎
Do you know if you're a match with your son?

470
00:39:35,850 --> 00:39:37,910
-送他上救護車  -他活不下來
- Put him in the ambulance. - He cannot survive.

471
00:39:37,910 --> 00:39:39,970
快送他上救護車
Put him in the ambulance! 

472
00:39:40,500 --> 00:39:41,760
快聽他的
Do as he says.

473
00:39:42,610 --> 00:39:44,100
快  快
Venez. Venez! Vite!

474
00:39:44,100 --> 00:39:45,990
快  上救護車
Vite! A l'ambulance!

475
00:39:52,210 --> 00:39:53,690
你需要人手幫忙照看他
You will need help to keep him alive.

476
00:39:53,690 --> 00:39:55,430
車上有我和他  速度就已經夠慢了
This crate's going to be slow enough with just me and him.

477
00:39:55,430 --> 00:39:57,440
如果再有人上車  就無法按時趕到
Any extra weight, we're not going to make it.

478
00:39:57,500 --> 00:39:59,650
他家有一隊醫生等著
He has surgeons at his home, waiting.

479
00:40:00,020 --> 00:40:02,250
-等心臟  -他只有這個機會
- The heart. - He has one chance.

480
00:40:02,250 --> 00:40:04,590
就帶一名醫護人員照顧他
Take one EMT for while you are driving.

481
00:40:05,250 --> 00:40:06,940
她  你
Her. You.

482
00:40:08,610 --> 00:40:10,540
你上車  不用別人了
You get in. No one else.

483
00:40:10,540 --> 00:40:12,310
快點  快點
Allez, allez, vite, vite!

484
00:40:12,960 --> 00:40:16,000
上車吧  快  快
A l'ambulance. Allez, allez! Vite!

485
00:40:52,860 --> 00:40:54,830
到哪了
Where... where are we?

486
00:40:55,900 --> 00:40:56,930
到家了
Home.

487
00:41:05,690 --> 00:41:07,060
我們把你送進去
We're going to get you inside.

488
00:41:08,730 --> 00:41:09,750
謝謝你
Thank you.

489
00:41:14,960 --> 00:41:15,970
他死了
He's dying.

490
00:41:17,510 --> 00:41:20,350
-他的心臟還能用  把他送進去  -好
- His heart's still good. Get him inside. - Ok.

491
00:41:37,710 --> 00:41:39,040
他看起來情況不錯
He looks good there.

492
00:41:44,450 --> 00:41:45,400
準備好了嗎
Ready?

493
00:41:59,900 --> 00:42:01,570
移植手術完成
We finished the transplant.

494
00:42:01,630 --> 00:42:04,630
到目前為止  一切都好
So far... everything looks good.

495
00:42:04,760 --> 00:42:06,580
心臟還能用嗎
The heart, it was all right?

496
00:42:06,640 --> 00:42:09,270
雖然耽擱了  但沒多大影響
Despite the delay, it showed no signs of damage.

497
00:42:09,360 --> 00:42:11,690
一安上就開始跳動了
It started beating almost immediately.

498
00:42:11,690 --> 00:42:14,600
-太神奇了  -謝天謝地
Quite remarkable, actually. - Thank God.

499
00:42:19,560 --> 00:42:21,140
謝謝你  警探
Thank you, Inspector.

500
00:42:21,550 --> 00:42:23,400
您是我兒子的救命恩人
Our son owes you his life.

501
00:42:31,880 --> 00:42:34,650
天啊  卡拉  你瘋了嗎
Jesus Christ, Carla. This is some kinky shit.

502
00:42:34,650 --> 00:42:37,110
我在想要不要殺了你
I'm trying to decide whether or not to kill you.

503
00:42:37,240 --> 00:42:38,560
什麼  為什麼
What? Why?

504
00:42:38,560 --> 00:42:41,880
你接的每份活都搞得一團糟
And lately every job you sent our way has turned to shit!

505
00:42:42,700 --> 00:42:45,940
那不是我的錯  我是說...
Hey, that is not my fault, OK? I mean...

506
00:42:46,570 --> 00:42:48,090
我不在意是不是耍了你
I don't care about screwing you!

507
00:42:49,030 --> 00:42:51,390
只要報酬豐厚  你什麼都肯幹
You'd do anything for a big payday.

508
00:42:51,520 --> 00:42:54,800
你也知道這行競爭激烈
Well, you know, it is a competitive business.

509
00:42:54,800 --> 00:42:57,310
對  但我決定與誰合作
Yes, but I can decide who to do business with.

510
00:42:57,310 --> 00:42:59,640
合作結束  阿吉  你走吧
We're done, Aggy. You can show yourself out.

511
00:42:59,640 --> 00:43:00,880
你被炒了
You're fired.

512
00:43:09,000 --> 00:43:11,830
{\an8}德希米耶醫院

513
00:43:18,600 --> 00:43:19,660
孩子怎麼樣
How's the boy?

514
00:43:20,370 --> 00:43:21,550
他會沒事的
He will be fine.

515
00:43:22,060 --> 00:43:24,610
醫生相信他會完全康復
The doctors are confident of a full recovery.

516
00:43:24,990 --> 00:43:26,100
真是個好消息
That's good to hear.

517
00:43:26,400 --> 00:43:27,870
弗蘭克
Frank... 

518
00:43:28,450 --> 00:43:32,150
你得說說樓下發生的事
we have to talk about what happened downstairs-- 

519
00:43:32,150 --> 00:43:33,250
我開槍打死的人
the man I shot.

520
00:43:33,250 --> 00:43:35,190
他叫德拉戈·蘇也克
His name is Drago Sujic.

521
00:43:35,920 --> 00:43:38,580
難怪我覺得眼熟
Ah, I thought I recognized him.

522
00:43:39,140 --> 00:43:40,680
他是幕後黑手嗎
He was responsible for all this?

523
00:43:40,680 --> 00:43:42,200
他想救他兒子
He was trying to save his son.

524
00:43:43,340 --> 00:43:44,580
最後救成了
And in the end, that's exactly what happened.

525
00:43:44,580 --> 00:43:47,050
我把他送回家  把他的心給了他兒子
I took him home, and they gave his son his heart.

526
00:43:47,070 --> 00:43:50,420
他最終還是做了件好事
Then some good came of it after all.

527
00:43:51,250 --> 00:43:53,530
不過  這還是偷
Still, such a theft... 

528
00:43:54,270 --> 00:43:58,300
真想知道某人是怎麼捲入這場犯罪的
It's troubling how someone could be involved in such a terrible crime.

529
00:43:58,300 --> 00:44:01,490
可能他不知道一切
It's possible some of the people involved didn't know all of the details.

530
00:44:01,490 --> 00:44:04,540
我覺得他以後應該多加小心
I think these people should be more careful in the future.

531
00:44:14,480 --> 00:44:16,180
我們不和凱根合作了
No more jobs from Kagan.

532
00:44:16,540 --> 00:44:18,700
別擔心  你不會再聽到他的名字  
Don't worry, you'll never hear his name again, 

533
00:44:18,700 --> 00:44:20,250
更不會看到他
let alone see him.

534
00:44:23,390 --> 00:44:25,200
順便說一句  今天幹的很出色
Nice job today, by the way.

535
00:44:25,560 --> 00:44:27,180
解決方案很巧妙
An elegant solution.

536
00:44:27,990 --> 00:44:29,570
這就是我們的特點  
That's what we're all about.

537
00:44:29,830 --> 00:44:30,890
晚安  卡拉
Night, Carla.

538
00:44:31,060 --> 00:44:32,440
晚安  弗蘭克
Good night, Frank.

539
00:44:45,200 --> 00:44:48,250
-德拉戈死了  -你該開心啊
- Drago didn't make it. - You should be pleased.

540
00:44:48,250 --> 00:44:51,410
如果我能活捉那些混蛋  我會更開心
if I could get some of these bastards alive.

541
00:44:51,490 --> 00:44:53,620
弗蘭克·馬丁呢
What about Frank Martin?

542
00:44:53,620 --> 00:44:56,440
他是聯繫人  我會盯緊他
He's the connection. I'll stay with him.

543
00:44:56,440 --> 00:44:58,480
別在司機身上浪費精力 
Don't waste your energy on this driver.

544
00:44:58,480 --> 00:45:00,470
他沒有利用價值
He's not an asset.

545
00:45:00,640 --> 00:45:03,440
他不只是司機  而是快遞員
He's not just a driver; he's a transporter.

546
00:45:30,190 --> 00:45:32,670
-要玩麼  -免了
- You want? - No.

547
00:45:36,270 --> 00:45:37,740
你知道什麼很難嗎
You know what's difficult?

548
00:45:38,230 --> 00:45:39,680
學匈牙利語
Learning Hungarian. 

549
00:45:40,250 --> 00:45:42,850
不  比學匈牙利語還難
No, no, no. Harder than learning Hungarian.

550
00:45:46,270 --> 00:45:47,620
你要我繼續猜嗎
Do you want to keep me guessing?

551
00:45:47,770 --> 00:45:50,370
從車身上清除乾掉的泥巴
Removing dry cement from an automobile.

552
00:45:50,680 --> 00:45:55,250
過程漫長且累人
You see, Frank, this is a very long, very tiring process.

553
00:45:55,820 --> 00:45:58,470
-想知道詳情嗎  -不想
You want to know what's involved? - Not really.

554
00:45:58,540 --> 00:46:02,190
取一份鹽酸  四份清水
You take one part of muriatic acid and four parts of water,

555
00:46:02,420 --> 00:46:07,940
然後用牙刷蘸取  刷掉乾掉的混凝土
and then you use a toothbrush to scrub it away at the hardened concrete.

556
00:46:19,600 --> 00:46:21,450
來摸摸
Here, feel that.

557
00:46:23,110 --> 00:46:25,580
-迪爾特  我才不想摸你的背  -快摸
- I don't want to feel your back, Dieter. - Just feel.

558
00:46:27,240 --> 00:46:29,850
摸到了嗎
Oh! Yeah. Do you feel that?

559
00:46:30,420 --> 00:46:32,840
我不是醫生  迪爾特
I'm n-- I'm not a doctor, Dieter. 

560
00:46:32,840 --> 00:46:34,880
你要去看醫生就去看吧
If you need to see a doctor, you should see one.

561
00:46:43,810 --> 00:46:45,520
我要按摩
What I need is a massage.

562
00:46:45,940 --> 00:46:46,980
你不是按過了嗎
I thought you got a massage. 

563
00:46:46,980 --> 00:46:48,730
和我期望的不一樣
It was not what I was expecting.

564
00:46:48,730 --> 00:46:50,260
你期望的...
What were you... 

565
00:46:51,190 --> 00:46:52,390
我最好還是不要知道  對吧
I don't want to know, do I?

566
00:46:55,150 --> 00:46:56,490
結局不妙
It didn't end well.

567
00:46:57,010 --> 00:46:58,430
知道這點就行了
That's all you need to know.

