1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:26,000
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:26,000
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:26,000
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:10,000
{\pos(90,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:10,000
{\pos(100,254)}人人影视
YYeTs.com

6
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:10,000
{\pos(105,265)}原创翻译 双语字幕

8
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:10,000
{\pos(237,265)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

9
00:00:10,000 --> 00:00:15,000
翻译：冰蓝

11
00:00:15,000 --> 00:00:20,000
校对：冰蓝天然呆    时间轴：小雨     贝贝

12
00:00:20,000 --> 00:00:25,000
后期/特效：WiLL    总监：冰蓝     WiLL

14
00:00:53,610 --> 00:00:57,580
我是德拉戈  老子的包裹呢
This is Drago. Where is my fucking package?

15
00:00:57,770 --> 00:00:59,480
老子才不管什么狗屁规矩
I don't give a fuck about his fucking rules!

16
00:00:59,480 --> 00:01:02,750
我的规矩是  付了钱就要交货
My rule is: I'll make the delivery that I fucking paid for!

17
00:01:10,820 --> 00:01:13,510
告诉你  我决定跳过中介  凯根  
You know what? I'm cutting out the middle man, Kagan.

18
00:01:13,510 --> 00:01:17,020
没错  就是你  告诉我联系人的电话
Yes, I mean you. Give me the contact number.

19
00:01:34,410 --> 00:01:37,570
再让我问一次  我就割断你的喉咙
Make me ask you again, and I'll cut your throat out.

20
00:01:56,190 --> 00:01:56,960
您好
Yes?

21
00:01:56,960 --> 00:01:59,460
-司机在哪  -您说什么
- Where is the driver? - I'm sorry?

22
00:01:59,460 --> 00:02:02,460
中介凯根太不靠谱
That piece of shit Kagan set up this deal that's gone bad.

23
00:02:02,460 --> 00:02:05,270
-我要你办好这事  -我们只和凯根做交易
- I want you to make it good. - We only deal with Kagan.

24
00:02:05,270 --> 00:02:07,340
凯根和这次交易没关系了
Kagan's no longer part of this deal.

25
00:02:07,610 --> 00:02:10,620
我是客户  货在哪
I'm the client. Where is the package?

26
00:02:10,650 --> 00:02:13,250
抱歉  先生  可能有所延误
I'm sorry, sir. The delivery might be behind schedule.

27
00:02:12,040 --> 00:02:13,290
{\an8}来电

28
00:02:13,250 --> 00:02:14,790
现在就该送到了
The delivery was due now!

29
00:02:13,290 --> 00:02:14,880
{\an8}无法显示对方号码

30
00:02:15,540 --> 00:02:18,570
抱歉  先生  我正在尽力查看运送情况
Excuse me, sir, but I'm doing my best to locate your package now.

31
00:02:18,780 --> 00:02:21,660
再加点油  找到我的货
Well, do better than your best. Find it.

32
00:02:22,040 --> 00:02:22,790
{\an8}无法显示对方号码

33
00:02:22,390 --> 00:02:23,920
别追踪我的号码了
Don't bother tracing the call.

34
00:02:23,920 --> 00:02:26,430
我是德拉戈·苏也克  去问问吧
My name is Drago Sojic, ask around.

35
00:02:22,790 --> 00:02:23,720
{\an8}查找//弗兰克

36
00:02:23,720 --> 00:02:25,300
{\an8}无法获取位置

37
00:02:26,640 --> 00:02:30,360
听到我的大名  你的司机就该乖乖把货送来
My reputation should encourage your driver to finish this deal.

38
00:02:30,970 --> 00:02:32,260
他是快递员
Transporter. 

39
00:02:32,260 --> 00:02:34,360
而且我正在确定他的位置  苏也克先生
And I'm locating him, Mr. Sujic.

40
00:02:34,460 --> 00:02:37,530
为了他的安全  希望你比我更早找到他
For his sake, I hope you locate him before I do.

41
00:02:40,430 --> 00:02:42,010
{\an8}拨打弗兰克电话 开始查询来电号码 无法追踪位置

42
00:02:42,030 --> 00:02:43,070
{\an8}拨打弗兰克电话

43
00:02:42,650 --> 00:02:44,140
拜托  弗兰克  接电话
Come on, Frank, pick up.

44
00:03:09,010 --> 00:03:10,490
非常人贩 电视剧版
第一季 第四集

45
00:04:28,050 --> 00:04:32,460
三小时前

46
00:04:43,850 --> 00:04:46,050
抱歉  不是好消息
I'm sorry, but the news is not good.

47
00:04:47,080 --> 00:04:50,530
理查德的第三次心脏移植手术排斥了
Richard's heart has rejected the third ventricle implant.

48
00:04:50,960 --> 00:04:54,130
-心肌病加重了  -这是什么意思
- And cardiomyopathy is worsening. - What does that mean?

49
00:04:55,130 --> 00:04:57,120
现在您儿子唯一活下去的指望
At this point, the only chance your son has 

50
00:04:57,120 --> 00:04:59,490
就是第四次心脏移植手术
for survival is a full transplant.

51
00:04:59,890 --> 00:05:00,840
天啊
Oh, my god.

52
00:05:01,010 --> 00:05:04,340
阿尔贝尼兹先生  我得说这并不容易
I should tell you there are many hurdles, Monsieur Albeniz.

53
00:05:04,340 --> 00:05:07,250
匹配的心脏目前还没有
A compatible heart is not automatically available.

54
00:05:07,290 --> 00:05:08,780
如果有了就是我们优先对吧
We are very high on the waiting list.

55
00:05:08,780 --> 00:05:11,270
当然  明早把理查德
Of course. Bring Richard back to the hospital

56
00:05:11,280 --> 00:05:13,170
送来医院进行观察
tomorrow morning for observation.

57
00:05:13,170 --> 00:05:15,470
如果有了匹配的心脏
When and if a suitable heart becomes available,

58
00:05:15,470 --> 00:05:18,680
我们就能马上动手术
we will be ready to go into surgery immediately.

59
00:05:19,840 --> 00:05:20,790
您觉得心脏...
Do you think a heart--

60
00:05:20,790 --> 00:05:22,220
我无法保证
I can't promise anything.

61
00:05:30,660 --> 00:05:31,930
要带书吗
Do you want books?

62
00:05:31,940 --> 00:05:33,600
要  我要看完《动物庄园》
Yes. I'll finish Animal Farm.

63
00:05:33,850 --> 00:05:35,830
高中就要求看《动物庄园》了吗
They make you read Animal Farm at school?

64
00:05:35,830 --> 00:05:38,010
这是额外任务  我已经看完了其他书
It's extra. I finished the other ones already.

65
00:05:39,280 --> 00:05:42,060
如果我要上巴黎政治大学  就得刻苦
I have to be ready for exams if I'm going to Sciences Po.

66
00:05:47,820 --> 00:05:51,640
爸爸  你必须坚持下去  妈妈现在很痛苦
Dad, we have to keep going--for Mama. She's having a tough time.

67
00:05:52,960 --> 00:05:54,580
她好害怕  理查德
She's so afraid, Richard,

68
00:05:55,620 --> 00:05:56,500
害怕失去你
to lose you.

69
00:05:57,630 --> 00:05:59,200
你们不会失去我  爸爸
No one's losing anyone, Papa.

70
00:06:05,690 --> 00:06:07,860
去吧  妈妈会吓坏的
Allez. Maman va flipper.

71
00:06:22,570 --> 00:06:24,750
你想过招个人来帮忙吗 
Do you ever think of hiring someone to help you with that?

72
00:06:24,750 --> 00:06:26,360
你可能受伤
You know, someone could get hurt.

73
00:06:26,850 --> 00:06:28,390
不用  弗兰克  我一直使用这些工具
Look, Frank, when you've used this equipment

74
00:06:28,390 --> 00:06:31,210
太得心应手了
for as long as I have, it is an instinct.

75
00:06:33,780 --> 00:06:34,760
怎么
Why?

76
00:06:36,470 --> 00:06:37,570
我让你紧张了吗
Do I make you nervous?

77
00:06:38,050 --> 00:06:39,800
我只是不想看你摧毁一辆车
I'd just hate to see you damage the car.

78
00:06:40,110 --> 00:06:42,460
你负责驾驶  我负责修车
You take care of the driving, I take care of the cars.

79
00:06:43,290 --> 00:06:44,060
好吧
Ok.

80
00:06:56,920 --> 00:06:58,340
也许你没取掉所有螺母
Maybe you didn't get all the nuts.

81
00:06:58,840 --> 00:07:01,040
我当然全取掉了  你为什么要这样
Of course I got all the nuts. Why do you do this?

82
00:07:01,250 --> 00:07:02,450
安全第一哦  迪尔特
Safety first, Dieter.

83
00:07:02,450 --> 00:07:04,610
你还和我谈安全
Oh, look who's talking to me about safety.

84
00:07:13,770 --> 00:07:14,630
你还好吗
Everything all right?

85
00:07:14,920 --> 00:07:16,900
挺好的
Uh, yeah, yeah, everything's all right.

86
00:07:19,980 --> 00:07:22,350
你能把手推车拿给我吗
Um... can you pass me this, um, dolly?

87
00:07:23,990 --> 00:07:24,860
-那个吗  -对
- That one? - Yeah.

88
00:07:26,300 --> 00:07:29,020
-这里的手推车吗  -对
- That one there? - Oui, oui. Uh, yeah.

89
00:07:35,330 --> 00:07:36,170
谢了  
Thanks.

90
00:07:37,330 --> 00:07:38,140
天啊
Oh, my god.

91
00:07:39,920 --> 00:07:42,340
-你确定没事吧  -没事
- Are you sure everything's all right? - Yeah, yeah. Fine, fine.

92
00:07:43,170 --> 00:07:44,710
我只是要检查集合管
I'll just check the manifold.

93
00:07:51,560 --> 00:07:53,200
能推我一把吗
Uh, could you give me a little push?

94
00:07:59,850 --> 00:08:00,920
再推一下
Just a little bit more...

95
00:08:01,510 --> 00:08:02,650
推到车下
under the car, please.

96
00:08:04,030 --> 00:08:05,490
太好了
Yeah, that's great.

97
00:08:05,680 --> 00:08:08,800
-我得走了  -保重  回见
- I gotta go. - Sure, sure. See you later.

98
00:08:09,090 --> 00:08:10,280
起来时别指望我
Don't get up on my account.

99
00:08:10,350 --> 00:08:13,400
好  我只是检查一下联动装置
Yeah. Like I said, I'll just check the linkage.

100
00:08:13,430 --> 00:08:15,530
-不是集合管吗  -对  集合管
- Not the manifold? - Yes, the manifold.

101
00:08:17,700 --> 00:08:21,010
待会儿我想
I was thinking maybe... maybe later today

102
00:08:21,010 --> 00:08:23,130
做个按摩  舒筋活骨
I could get a massage, ease the aches and pains, yeah?

103
00:08:23,130 --> 00:08:25,640
听起来是个好主意
Oh, that sounds like a very good idea for you.

104
00:08:26,380 --> 00:08:29,450
-我得走了  谢谢你的咖啡  -不客气
- I gotta push off. Thanks for the coffee. - Welcome. 

105
00:08:29,450 --> 00:08:32,490
-慢慢检查联动装置吧  -好
- Good luck with the, uh, linkage. - Yeah.

106
00:08:35,420 --> 00:08:36,460
去死吧
Fuck you.

107
00:08:43,170 --> 00:08:47,700
如果我是银行  你就会破产蹲大牢
If I was a bank, you'd be bankrupt and in jail.

108
00:08:48,420 --> 00:08:52,860
不过我只是个人  也没人权
But since I am just an individual person and I have no rights,

109
00:08:53,070 --> 00:08:55,560
你就可以免此一劫了
you are allowed to walk free,

110
00:08:56,270 --> 00:08:59,970
所以我就得自己打理生意
so I have to take care of my business however I can,

111
00:09:00,260 --> 00:09:02,080
在这件事中  就是说...
which, in your case, means--

112
00:09:05,690 --> 00:09:06,610
去外面等着
Wait outside.

113
00:09:18,060 --> 00:09:18,820
真抱歉
I'm sorry.

114
00:09:20,050 --> 00:09:20,930
我试过了
I tried.

115
00:09:21,870 --> 00:09:23,880
我试过了一切  但是仍然不能康复
I tried everything, but I-I just didn't get better.

116
00:09:24,410 --> 00:09:26,070
不不不  别怪自己
No, no, no, don't blame yourself.

117
00:09:26,080 --> 00:09:29,360
只是...  你只是病了  没关系
It's... You're just sick. It's OK.

118
00:09:30,490 --> 00:09:33,790
你还可以接受别的疗法  看别的医生
There are other treatments, other doctors. You'll see.

119
00:09:34,280 --> 00:09:36,050
这次我只想回家
I just wanted to come home all this time.

120
00:09:37,220 --> 00:09:38,070
我知道
I know.

121
00:09:39,700 --> 00:09:41,590
安娜带你回家  我一会儿就回去
Anna will take you home. I'll be there shortly. 

122
00:09:41,590 --> 00:09:44,750
-还有些事要办  -你不生气吗
- I just have some business to finish. - You're not angry?

123
00:09:44,750 --> 00:09:47,950
生气  我怎么会生气
Angry? How could I be angry?

124
00:09:51,360 --> 00:09:52,840
让我静一下
I just need a minute.

125
00:09:55,040 --> 00:09:58,570
菲利普  我的儿子  我的乖儿子
Oh, Filip, my boy. My precious boy.

126
00:10:00,330 --> 00:10:03,400
我不会让你死的  我向你保证
I will not let you die. I promise you that.

127
00:10:05,250 --> 00:10:06,980
我会尽一切努力  好吗
I'll do anything. OK?

128
00:10:26,330 --> 00:10:29,870
总之  引用弗里德里希·冯·席勒的话
So, in conclusion, to quote Friedrich Schiller,

129
00:10:26,350 --> 00:10:30,190
{\an8}德国18世纪著名诗人  哲学家  历史学家和剧作家

130
00:10:30,840 --> 00:10:32,540
父子不仅是血肉至亲
"It is not flesh and blood,

131
00:10:33,620 --> 00:10:37,270
更是灵魂相依
but heart that makes us fathers and sons".

132
00:10:47,520 --> 00:10:48,920
索菲  
Sophie?

133
00:10:48,930 --> 00:10:50,810
-亲爱的  有了  -怎么了
- Sweetie, they have one. - What?

134
00:10:50,810 --> 00:10:52,030
-什么  -他们有心脏了
- What? - They have a heart.

135
00:10:52,710 --> 00:10:55,350
不可能  天啊
C'est pas vrai. Oh, my god.

136
00:10:56,750 --> 00:11:00,680
-难以置信  -马上过来
- Encroyable. - Yes, come down immediately.

137
00:11:00,680 --> 00:11:02,520
谢天谢地  我就过来
Oh, thank God. I'm on my way.

138
00:11:05,640 --> 00:11:07,080
我以前喜欢打拳击  
I used to love to box,

139
00:11:07,120 --> 00:11:09,780
但我不再办健身会员卡了
but I don't bother with a gym membership anymore.

140
00:11:09,780 --> 00:11:12,130
现在我就在家打
I make do with what I have.

141
00:11:16,480 --> 00:11:19,850
省钱  而且健身效果很好
It saves me money, and it's such a good workout.

142
00:11:19,850 --> 00:11:22,040
我会付款  我手里有你的钱
I'll pay! I've got your money!

143
00:11:22,050 --> 00:11:24,420
现在我无所谓了
At this point, I don't care.

144
00:11:31,830 --> 00:11:32,580
怎么了
It's happened?

145
00:11:33,000 --> 00:11:35,360
有名捐赠者  心脏就要到了
There is a donor. The heart is on its way.

146
00:11:35,670 --> 00:11:37,390
我派司机过去  一小时内赶到
I'll have a driver there within the hour.

147
00:11:37,910 --> 00:11:41,370
偷心脏对我来说很困难
Listen, it's going to be difficult for me to get the heart out. 

148
00:11:41,370 --> 00:11:43,150
有人一直守着心脏
There is constant supervision.

149
00:11:43,420 --> 00:11:46,260
如果你失手了  那你就等死吧
It's going to be a lot harder for you if you fail.

150
00:12:13,730 --> 00:12:14,760
快来了
Almost time.

151
00:13:20,780 --> 00:13:23,250
{\an8}急诊室

152
00:13:28,390 --> 00:13:29,470
你是司机吗
Are you the transporter?

153
00:13:29,920 --> 00:13:31,870
尽快把这个带给客户   
You've got to get this to the client as fast as possible. 

154
00:13:31,870 --> 00:13:33,110
时间紧迫
There's no time to lose.

155
00:13:46,740 --> 00:13:47,610
怎么回事
What is going on?

156
00:13:49,630 --> 00:13:50,500
心脏呢
Where's the heart?

157
00:14:04,480 --> 00:14:07,570
-怎么会这样  -我们尚且不知
- How could this happen?! - We don't know yet.

158
00:14:07,860 --> 00:14:09,110
我们已经确认心脏
We've confirmed that the heart

159
00:14:09,110 --> 00:14:11,080
在捐赠医院的救护车上
was placed in the ambulance at the donor hospital.

160
00:14:11,080 --> 00:14:13,030
肯定是在路上被偷了
It must have gone missing somewhere en route.

161
00:14:13,030 --> 00:14:15,690
难道没人一直守着吗
Isn't someone supposed to be with it the entire way?

162
00:14:15,690 --> 00:14:18,240
有  医护人员一路监督
Yes. Our technicians were there to supervise delivery.

163
00:14:18,240 --> 00:14:19,820
我们在查明真相
We're trying to figure out what happened.

164
00:14:19,820 --> 00:14:22,510
我向你保证我们在尽全力寻找心脏
I can assure you everything is being done to locate the heart. 

165
00:14:22,510 --> 00:14:23,760
警察正在赶来
The police are on their way.

166
00:14:24,460 --> 00:14:26,790
过多久心脏会停跳
How long before the heart is not usable?

167
00:14:27,910 --> 00:14:31,240
最多四小时
The heart can remain viable for only four hours at the most.

168
00:14:35,080 --> 00:14:36,880
你们最好在那时之前找到他
You'd better find it before then.

169
00:15:03,550 --> 00:15:04,390
打扰一下
Excuse me.

170
00:15:06,530 --> 00:15:09,440
-你是孩子的父亲吗  -是
Uh, are you the father of the young boy? - Yes.

171
00:15:09,510 --> 00:15:11,080
我是塔科尼警探  
I'm Inspector Tarconi.

172
00:15:11,800 --> 00:15:13,910
负责调查此案
I will be in charge of the investigation.

173
00:15:14,050 --> 00:15:15,150
有线索了吗
Do you have any leads?

174
00:15:16,100 --> 00:15:17,570
确实有
As a matter of fact, we do. 

175
00:15:17,570 --> 00:15:19,450
负责运送心脏的
One of the technicians involved 

176
00:15:19,450 --> 00:15:22,040
一名医护人员失踪了
in the transfer of the heart has gone missing.

177
00:15:22,040 --> 00:15:26,670
我们在出入市的大路上设立了检查点
We have set up checkpoints on all major roads into and out of the city.

178
00:15:27,000 --> 00:15:29,560
警探  医护人员找到了
Inspector. They found the technician. 

179
00:15:29,560 --> 00:15:31,340
-他在这里  - 失陪了
- He's here. - Excuse me.

180
00:15:36,290 --> 00:15:39,310
他按时取了心脏  但是没送过来
He collected the heart as scheduled, but it was never delivered. 

181
00:15:39,400 --> 00:15:42,150
显然  他在去机场的路上被拦下了
Apparently, he was picked up on his way to the airport.

182
00:15:42,150 --> 00:15:44,150
他说自己要去度假
He claims he was going on vacation,

183
00:15:44,150 --> 00:15:46,800
但是医院没有他请假的记录
but the hospital has no record of him asking for time off.

184
00:15:50,180 --> 00:15:51,790
还剩多少时间
How much time do we have?

185
00:15:52,560 --> 00:15:54,540
三个小时多一点
Just over three hours.

186
00:15:55,440 --> 00:15:57,740
我进来时看到记者了
I passed some reporters on my way in.

187
00:15:57,740 --> 00:15:59,850
是啊  坏事传千里
Yes, the story got out quite fast.

188
00:16:00,640 --> 00:16:02,180
我要请你帮个忙
I need you to do me a favour.

189
00:16:23,020 --> 00:16:25,840
-我是塔科尼警探  -好吧
- I'm Inspector Tarconi. - Good for you.

190
00:16:28,030 --> 00:16:30,180
你在这家医院工作对吧
You work for this hospital, yes?

191
00:16:30,490 --> 00:16:33,490
医护人员  还是移植小组的一员
A medical technician with access to the transplant team?

192
00:16:33,490 --> 00:16:36,100
我已经告诉他们  我和这事没关系
Look, I already told them I had nothing to do with this.

193
00:16:39,660 --> 00:16:40,850
这是怎么回事
What the fuck is this?

194
00:16:42,260 --> 00:16:43,390
记者
Reporters.

195
00:16:43,660 --> 00:16:45,730
他们一听说这种事就趋之若鹜
When they get a whiff of something like this,

196
00:16:45,730 --> 00:16:48,120
简直无法拦住他们
it's almost impossible to keep them away.

197
00:16:48,160 --> 00:16:49,370
我去和他们谈谈
I will talk to them.

198
00:17:08,720 --> 00:17:10,090
深表歉意
Sorry about that.

199
00:17:12,020 --> 00:17:15,910
我们说到哪里来了
Now... um, where were we?

200
00:17:16,060 --> 00:17:17,370
你和他们说了什么
What did you say to them?

201
00:17:17,370 --> 00:17:19,190
我说你认罪了
I just told them you confessed 

202
00:17:19,190 --> 00:17:24,030
还要供出所有涉案人员的名字
and that you were giving us the names of everyone involved in the plot.

203
00:17:24,080 --> 00:17:26,970
你他妈疯了吧  我从没这么说过
Are you fucking insane? I didn't say anything like that.

204
00:17:26,980 --> 00:17:28,570
当然没有
Of course not.

205
00:17:28,740 --> 00:17:31,110
但如果你真是无辜的
But if you're innocent, as you claim,

206
00:17:31,110 --> 00:17:33,430
真正的罪犯就马上会知道
the people responsible will know immediately 

207
00:17:33,430 --> 00:17:35,660
这不过是我的计策
that it was just a trick on my part.

208
00:17:36,520 --> 00:17:39,560
当然  我会保护
Of course, I am in a position to offer protection

209
00:17:39,620 --> 00:17:42,930
愿意合作的人
for anyone willing to cooperate.

210
00:17:50,050 --> 00:17:51,450
他知道心脏在哪吗
Does he know where the heart is?

211
00:17:51,560 --> 00:17:55,150
不知道  但他告诉我们有人也许能帮忙
No. But he led us to a man who may be able to help.

212
00:17:55,920 --> 00:17:58,980
-谁  -我以前和他打过交道
- Who? - Someone I have dealt with before.

213
00:18:15,040 --> 00:18:16,370
警探
Yes, Inspector?

214
00:18:16,570 --> 00:18:18,160
情况紧急  弗兰克
It's urgent Frank.

215
00:18:18,160 --> 00:18:19,850
现在我不方便说话
I'm afraid I can't really speak now.

216
00:18:19,940 --> 00:18:21,680
也许你看了新闻
Perhaps you have heard on the news.

217
00:18:22,120 --> 00:18:24,640
用于移植的心脏被偷了
A heart was stolen. It was needed for a transplant.

218
00:18:24,640 --> 00:18:27,220
-不  我没听说过  -我们抓到了一名男子
- No, I've not heard. -I just arrested a man 

219
00:18:27,220 --> 00:18:30,370
他说把心脏交给了快递员
who confessed to giving the heart to a driver for transport.

220
00:18:30,460 --> 00:18:34,110
他描述了快递员和车的样子
He gave a description of the man and his car.

221
00:18:34,110 --> 00:18:35,640
弗兰克  和你相符
Frank, it matched you.

222
00:18:35,640 --> 00:18:37,130
我有消息就告诉你
I'll let you know if I hear anything.

223
00:18:37,130 --> 00:18:37,840
弗兰克  要知道
Frank, you should know that 

224
00:18:37,840 --> 00:18:40,550
一名14岁男孩急需心脏  他病得很重
the heart is for a 14-year-old boy, very sick.

225
00:18:40,830 --> 00:18:44,330
如果手术不在三小时内进行  
He will die if this surgery is not carried out

226
00:18:44,330 --> 00:18:45,920
他就会死
just under three hours now.

227
00:18:46,450 --> 00:18:49,290
-弗兰克  -我得挂了  警探
- Frank? - Got to go, Inspector.

228
00:18:49,290 --> 00:18:51,030
挂断

229
00:18:55,380 --> 00:18:57,240
-货在哪里  -后备箱里
- Where's the package? - Trunk.

230
00:18:57,640 --> 00:18:58,530
打开后备箱
Open it.

231
00:19:10,180 --> 00:19:11,480
搞什么
What the fuck?

232
00:19:15,960 --> 00:19:18,900
快打开  没空和你耗着
Hey. Let's go. We don't have time for this.

233
00:19:22,620 --> 00:19:25,270
要报酬吗  打开后备箱
You want the payment? Open the trunk.

234
00:19:33,800 --> 00:19:35,510
拦住他  拦住他

235
00:19:42,310 --> 00:19:44,000
把老子的电话拿来
Give me my fucking phone!

236
00:19:49,020 --> 00:19:51,540
我不喜欢你突然造访
You know I don't like it when you come by without calling. 

237
00:19:51,830 --> 00:19:53,640
我正好在这附近
I was in the neighbourhood.

238
00:19:54,260 --> 00:19:57,990
-凯根  你想怎么样  -什么
- Kagan, what do you want. - What?

239
00:19:58,210 --> 00:19:59,920
如果你不告诉我你来干嘛
If you don't tell me what you're doing here,

240
00:19:59,920 --> 00:20:01,820
我就把你从窗户扔出去
I'm throwing you out those windows.

241
00:20:03,100 --> 00:20:06,180
我们得谈谈你男人的事
We need to talk about your man.

242
00:20:20,410 --> 00:20:21,610
说重点
Get to your point. 

243
00:20:22,340 --> 00:20:23,400
我在想
I've been thinking.

244
00:20:23,400 --> 00:20:24,830
这可是头一回
That's a first. 

245
00:20:25,020 --> 00:20:27,890
最近  这些任务
Lately, when it comes to these jobs,

246
00:20:27,890 --> 00:20:31,280
变得有些复杂
things have been getting a little complicated.

247
00:20:31,600 --> 00:20:32,520
你得承认  
I mean, you gotta admit,

248
00:20:32,520 --> 00:20:34,640
有太多人死了
the body count has been getting a little high.

249
00:20:34,640 --> 00:20:37,860
两次都是自卫  而且那些人都是匪徒
Self-defence both times, and they were both scumbags.

250
00:20:37,860 --> 00:20:39,520
有一个还是你介绍来的
One of them was referred by you. 

251
00:20:39,520 --> 00:20:41,730
我只是说  
All I'm saying is that 

252
00:20:41,730 --> 00:20:45,830
你男人开始小有名气了
your boy is starting to get a bit of a reputation.

253
00:20:45,830 --> 00:20:47,070
什么名气
For what?

254
00:20:48,550 --> 00:20:53,080
这样说吧  他很引人注目
Oh, let's just call it a flair for the dramatic.

255
00:20:53,380 --> 00:20:56,040
这家伙很会惹麻烦  卡拉
The guy is a bull in a china shop, Carla,

256
00:20:56,190 --> 00:20:57,760
树敌不少
and he's making enemies.

257
00:21:00,840 --> 00:21:03,800
找到快递员  拿回心脏
Find the transporter, get me the heart, 

258
00:21:03,800 --> 00:21:05,870
再杀了那混蛋
then kill that asshole.

259
00:21:06,650 --> 00:21:07,620
快去
Go!

260
00:22:16,750 --> 00:22:21,130
我是德拉戈  老子的包裹呢
This is Drago. Where is my fucking package?

261
00:22:21,310 --> 00:22:24,020
告诉你  我决定跳过中介  凯根
You know what? I'm cutting out the middle man, Kagan.

262
00:22:24,020 --> 00:22:25,700
没错  就是你
Yes, I mean you.

263
00:22:35,080 --> 00:22:36,270
又怎么了
Now what? 

264
00:22:36,360 --> 00:22:38,220
我刚刚都还和你谈过
What were we just talking about?

265
00:22:38,220 --> 00:22:40,690
-你什么意思  -你男人又闯祸了
- What do you mean? - Your man is at it again.

266
00:22:40,690 --> 00:22:42,010
阿吉  怎么回事
Aggy, what's going on? 

267
00:22:42,010 --> 00:22:43,430
别说我没警告过你
Don't say I didn't warn you.

268
00:22:53,020 --> 00:22:53,970
给你

269
00:23:03,340 --> 00:23:05,080
如果心脏超过三小时才到
If this heart takes any more than three hours to get here,

270
00:23:05,080 --> 00:23:06,400
就失效了
it's not going to be viable. 

271
00:23:06,400 --> 00:23:07,840
血压下降
Blood pressure's dropping.

272
00:23:15,190 --> 00:23:16,020
他的心脏正在衰竭
His heart's failing. 

273
00:23:16,020 --> 00:23:18,580
我们必须送他进手术室  去开门
We have to get him in the OR right away. Get the door.

274
00:23:18,680 --> 00:23:20,490
走吧  快点
Let's go, let's go, quick.

275
00:23:22,640 --> 00:23:23,870
快  快

276
00:23:27,270 --> 00:23:28,070
走
Let's go. 

277
00:23:29,310 --> 00:23:30,820
怎么回事
What's happening?

278
00:23:30,930 --> 00:23:33,570
他现在充血性心力衰竭  要进手术室
He's in congestive heart failure. They're taking him to the OR.

279
00:23:33,570 --> 00:23:35,410
要立刻接上人工心肺机
They need to put him on a cardiopulmonary 

280
00:23:35,410 --> 00:23:36,740
给他保命
bypass machine immediately.

281
00:23:36,740 --> 00:23:39,130
但是心脏还没找到
But the new heart has not been recovered yet!

282
00:23:39,130 --> 00:23:41,520
抱歉  我们别无选择
I'm sorry. We have no other choice.

283
00:23:46,690 --> 00:23:49,710
{\an8}酒吧  餐馆

284
00:23:57,500 --> 00:23:58,800
{\an8}内有器官  心脏

285
00:24:19,060 --> 00:24:19,890
您好
Hello?

286
00:24:19,810 --> 00:24:21,860
{\an8}进行全球跟踪

287
00:24:19,890 --> 00:24:22,540
-你找到他了吗  -找到了
- Have you found him yet? - Yes.

288
00:24:22,900 --> 00:24:25,900
-他在回来的路上吗  -还没有
- Is he on his way back here? - Not yet.

289
00:24:26,270 --> 00:24:28,120
我告诉过你  我保证
I told you. I promise no harm 

290
00:24:28,120 --> 00:24:29,910
如果他送回包裹  我就不伤害他
will come to him if he brings me the package,

291
00:24:29,910 --> 00:24:31,780
但他现在就得送过来
but he needs to bring it to me now.

292
00:24:32,450 --> 00:24:35,290
-我理解  -那你为什么还不阻止他
- I understand. - Then why haven't you stopped him?

293
00:24:34,690 --> 00:24:37,010
{\an8}来源是谁
跟踪来源
查找来源

294
00:24:35,460 --> 00:24:37,150
他不听我的
He doesn't take orders from me.

295
00:24:37,150 --> 00:24:38,600
让我和他谈谈
Let me speak to him.

296
00:24:38,600 --> 00:24:39,920
这可不是个好主意
I don't think that's a good idea.

297
00:24:39,920 --> 00:24:42,180
我才不管你怎么想
I don't give a shit what you think!

298
00:24:42,340 --> 00:24:44,120
给我接通他的电话
Put me through to him right now.

299
00:24:44,420 --> 00:24:45,850
我尽力吧
Let me see what I can do.

300
00:24:48,980 --> 00:24:51,420
{\an8}来电  卡拉·瓦莱丽
接听  忽略

301
00:24:51,700 --> 00:24:52,520
卡拉
Carla?

302
00:24:52,520 --> 00:24:54,540
弗兰克  我接到了愤怒客户的来电
Frank, I just got an angry call from the client. 

303
00:24:54,540 --> 00:24:56,310
你没有送去包裹
You didn't deliver the package.

304
00:24:56,310 --> 00:24:57,480
你知道那是什么东西吗
You know what it is?

305
00:24:58,160 --> 00:25:01,180
弗兰克  我还以为这没关系
Frank, I thought that wasn't suppose to matter.

306
00:25:01,180 --> 00:25:02,510
是心脏
It's a human heart, 

307
00:25:02,510 --> 00:25:05,460
要移植给一名垂死男孩  后来被偷了
stolen before it could be transplanted into a dying boy.

308
00:25:06,220 --> 00:25:08,570
客户是德拉戈·苏也克
The client is Drago Sujic.

309
00:25:08,570 --> 00:25:11,720
你知道他是法国南部最有名的嫌疑犯
And you know he's one of the biggest crime bosses in Southern France.

310
00:25:11,720 --> 00:25:14,920
和政界  警察都有勾结
Extremely well connected-- politicians, cops...

311
00:25:14,920 --> 00:25:17,290
我才不管  他为什么要心脏
I don't give a shit. Why does he need a heart?

312
00:25:17,340 --> 00:25:18,430
我不知道
I don't know.

313
00:25:18,680 --> 00:25:20,120
去查啊
Well find out!

314
00:25:24,870 --> 00:25:25,840
{\an8}德拉戈·苏也克

315
00:25:31,440 --> 00:25:32,480
{\an8}德拉戈·苏也克

316
00:25:32,910 --> 00:25:34,260
{\an8}申请接受捐赠

317
00:25:42,430 --> 00:25:44,950
-喂  -德拉戈有个16岁的儿子
Yes? - Drago has a son, 16 years old.

318
00:25:44,950 --> 00:25:46,370
患有先天性心脏病
Born with a heart defect.

319
00:25:46,370 --> 00:25:47,830
他的心脏衰竭好几年了
His heart has declined for years, 

320
00:25:47,830 --> 00:25:49,820
现在急需移植
now he's in desperate need of a transplant.

321
00:25:49,820 --> 00:25:51,930
德拉戈插队了
So Drago cuts to the front of the line.

322
00:25:51,930 --> 00:25:54,140
他在家里准备了一间现代化手术室
He built a state-of-the-art operating room in his mansion

323
00:25:54,140 --> 00:25:56,850
雇了一队医生
and hired an entire team of surgeons.

324
00:25:56,850 --> 00:25:58,870
他为此花费数百万  弗兰克
He's spent millions on this, Frank.

325
00:25:58,890 --> 00:26:00,740
你指望我同情他吗
You expect me to feel something for the man?

326
00:26:00,740 --> 00:26:03,270
你之前问我原因  我只是在回答
You asked me why he needed a heart; I'm telling you.

327
00:26:03,270 --> 00:26:05,140
这活儿是凯根推荐的对吧
Kagan referred this job, didn't he?

328
00:26:05,180 --> 00:26:07,180
我来处理凯根的事  弗兰克
Let me deal with Kagan, Frank.

329
00:26:07,350 --> 00:26:09,880
德拉戈在另一条线上  他想和你谈谈
Drago is on the other line. He wants to talk to you. 

330
00:26:10,560 --> 00:26:11,510
好吧
Fine.

331
00:26:11,870 --> 00:26:14,630
苏也克先生  快递员的电话接通了
Mr. Sujic, you're on with the transporter.

332
00:26:14,790 --> 00:26:15,690
你在哪
Where are you? 

333
00:26:16,240 --> 00:26:18,100
恐怕计划有变
I'm afraid there's been a change of plans.

334
00:26:18,100 --> 00:26:21,050
别人说你从不改变交易
I was told you make it a point of never changing the deal.

335
00:26:21,910 --> 00:26:23,140
我们把定金还给你
We'll return your down payment. 

336
00:26:23,140 --> 00:26:25,030
还你妹啊
Fuck the down payment!

337
00:26:25,270 --> 00:26:27,390
你必须在两小时内送来包裹
You have less than two hours to bring me the package,

338
00:26:27,390 --> 00:26:30,720
不然老子一定会找到你  把你碎尸万段
or I will track you down and I will fucking kill you!

339
00:26:36,740 --> 00:26:37,730
怎么了
What is it?

340
00:26:39,280 --> 00:26:41,330
医生想知道该不该把他弄醒
The surgeon wants to know if we should wake him up.

341
00:26:41,330 --> 00:26:42,280
干什么
What for?

342
00:26:43,130 --> 00:26:44,860
他们只能让他昏迷这么久
They can only keep him under for so long.

343
00:26:44,860 --> 00:26:46,820
手术照常进行
The surgeon goes ahead as planned,

344
00:26:47,050 --> 00:26:49,350
你要告诉组织里所有人
because you are going to put out a description of the driver 

345
00:26:49,350 --> 00:26:51,460
司机的外貌和车型
and the make of the car to the whole organization. 

346
00:26:51,460 --> 00:26:53,410
街上要设立眼线
I want eyes on the street.

347
00:26:53,410 --> 00:26:55,160
我要所有皮条客  
I want every pimp, every hooker, every dealer

348
00:26:55,160 --> 00:26:56,790
妓女和毒贩
that has ever been put on the payroll 

349
00:26:56,790 --> 00:26:58,710
都去找这个人
to be out there looking for this guy.

350
00:26:58,970 --> 00:27:02,240
一旦找到他  就通知我
And as soon as he's found, I want to know about it.

351
00:27:25,520 --> 00:27:26,930
坑爹啊
You've got to be kidding me.

352
00:28:38,390 --> 00:28:41,100
你要瑞典式按摩还是深层组织按摩
Swedish or deep tissue?

353
00:28:41,400 --> 00:28:43,260
能让我的背放松就行
Whatever brings relief for my back. 

354
00:28:43,260 --> 00:28:45,220
我坐不下  站不直
I cannot sit or stand.

355
00:28:45,220 --> 00:28:46,760
放松吧
Just relax.

356
00:28:46,760 --> 00:28:49,660
我会让你康复的
I am going to fix everything.

357
00:28:51,850 --> 00:28:53,140
等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.

358
00:28:54,230 --> 00:28:57,670
再给你点小费  最后要让我
Here is a little something extra for the...

359
00:28:57,750 --> 00:28:58,780
爽一把
finishing. 

360
00:28:59,600 --> 00:29:00,410
爽一把
The finishing?

361
00:29:00,410 --> 00:29:03,210
就是最后...
The ending. Um, you know?

362
00:29:03,780 --> 00:29:05,370
让我开心开心
To make it happy.

363
00:29:06,170 --> 00:29:07,770
抱歉
Oh, sorry. 

364
00:29:08,380 --> 00:29:11,290
-喂  -迪尔特  我需要一辆车
- Oui, hello? - Dieter, I need a car.

365
00:29:11,760 --> 00:29:13,090
-什么时候  -现在
- When? - Now.

366
00:29:15,330 --> 00:29:17,900
-那是什么声音  -我在按摩
- What the hell was that? - I get a massage.

367
00:29:18,160 --> 00:29:20,700
今早我弄伤了背  我的背...
I hurt my back this morning. My back, I cannot... aah!

368
00:29:20,700 --> 00:29:23,540
我没时间闲聊  情况紧急  我要一辆车
Listen, I don't have time to talk. It's urgent. I need a car.

369
00:29:23,540 --> 00:29:27,210
-放开我  -放松就好
- Ah! Let go of me! - Just relax. 

370
00:29:27,210 --> 00:29:29,080
你要扭断我脖子  我怎么放松
How can I relax when you break my neck?

371
00:29:29,080 --> 00:29:29,990
-迪尔特  -在
- Dieter? -Yes?

372
00:29:31,090 --> 00:29:34,070
-我要车  -你开的那辆呢
- The car. - Where is the one you drive in?

373
00:29:34,690 --> 00:29:36,290
出了点意外
I had a little accident.

374
00:29:36,680 --> 00:29:39,080
-车子陷在泥浆里了  -够了
- The car ended up in a pool of wet cement. - Ah! Enough, enough.

375
00:29:39,080 --> 00:29:41,730
够了  别让我遭罪
Enough. Oh. Stop this savagery.

376
00:29:42,110 --> 00:29:45,360
还你  自己去爽吧
Here. Go finish yourself!

377
00:29:46,220 --> 00:29:46,750
迪尔特
Dieter! 

378
00:29:47,290 --> 00:29:49,400
弗兰克  对不起  听着
Frank, I'm sorry. Yes, listen,

379
00:29:49,400 --> 00:29:52,480
我几乎动弹不得  更别提开车了
my back, I can barely move, and let alone drive.

380
00:29:52,480 --> 00:29:54,040
算了  你好好享受按摩吧
All right, forget it. Enjoy your massage.

381
00:29:54,040 --> 00:29:55,880
等等  你刚才是不是说泥浆
Wait, did you say cement?

382
00:30:20,410 --> 00:30:23,110
雷内·杜加  街上盯梢的一个毒贩
René Dugas, one of our dealers on the street. 

383
00:30:23,750 --> 00:30:24,720
雷内
René.

384
00:30:24,800 --> 00:30:26,900
苏也克先生  我看到了您要找的人
Mr. Sujic, I just spotted your man.

385
00:30:26,900 --> 00:30:29,830
跟着他  别让他离开你视线  尽量抓住他
Follow him, don't let him out of your sight, catch him if you can.

386
00:30:29,970 --> 00:30:31,900
跟紧点  他车技很棒
And stay sharp. He's an expert driver.

387
00:30:31,900 --> 00:30:33,710
不不  他在走路
No, no, he's on foot.

388
00:30:35,250 --> 00:30:37,110
他带着包裹吗
OK, does he have the package with him?

389
00:30:37,110 --> 00:30:38,730
他背了一个包  是指这个吗
He's carrying a bag, if that's what you mean.

390
00:30:38,730 --> 00:30:41,010
抓住他  必要时可以干掉他  我无所谓
Get him, kill him if you need to, I don't really care.

391
00:30:41,010 --> 00:30:44,600
但是一定要保护好包  明白吗
But make sure you do not damage the package, do you understand me?

392
00:30:45,330 --> 00:30:46,320
是  先生
Yes, sir.

393
00:31:02,600 --> 00:31:04,180
快  快  抓住他
Go, go, go! Get him!

394
00:32:05,620 --> 00:32:07,430
停下  警察

395
00:32:30,420 --> 00:32:33,040
-喂  -弗兰克  你在哪
- Yeah. - Frank, where are you?

396
00:32:33,040 --> 00:32:34,670
我一直在给你打电话  
I've been trying to call you.

397
00:32:34,800 --> 00:32:38,320
没多少时间了  男孩的心脏衰竭了
There is not much time, the boy's heart has failed.

398
00:32:38,320 --> 00:32:40,550
此时他正躺在手术台上
He is on the operating table as I speak,

399
00:32:40,550 --> 00:32:42,850
我们接了台机器给他保命
hooked up to a machine that is keeping him alive.

400
00:32:42,850 --> 00:32:45,050
-我正努力呢  -你什么意思
- I'm working on it. - What do you mean?

401
00:32:45,050 --> 00:32:46,770
你在干什么
What are you doing? 

402
00:32:46,770 --> 00:32:49,870
-心脏到底在不在你手里  -我再打给你
- Do you have the heart or not?! - I'll get back to you. 

403
00:32:50,220 --> 00:32:52,240
天啊  该死
Aw, shit!

404
00:33:09,210 --> 00:33:10,290
先生
Monsieur!

405
00:33:11,610 --> 00:33:14,230
-有什么能帮您的  先生  -不好意思  警官
Je peux vous aider, Monsieur? - Sorry, officer, uh...

406
00:33:15,260 --> 00:33:16,810
我只是在欣赏这辆车
just admiring your vehicle. 

407
00:33:17,450 --> 00:33:18,580
包里是什么
What's in the bag?

408
00:33:19,070 --> 00:33:20,610
其实我确实需要您的帮助
Actually, I do need your help.

409
00:33:21,200 --> 00:33:23,530
请保证把包里的东西
It's critical that the contents of this bag 

410
00:33:23,920 --> 00:33:25,970
尽快送去医院  这至关重要
get to a hospital as soon as possible. 

411
00:33:27,100 --> 00:33:29,120
放心  把包给我吧
I see. Leave it with me.

412
00:33:29,700 --> 00:33:30,660
谢谢
Thank you.

413
00:33:32,940 --> 00:33:34,520
你能帮我顶一会儿岗吗
Can you hold the fort for a few minutes?

414
00:33:34,520 --> 00:33:37,300
刚才有人给了我这个  我要送去医院
Someone just handed me this. I'll take it in.

415
00:33:37,300 --> 00:33:39,190
看起来是被偷的心脏
It looks like the missing heart.

416
00:33:46,080 --> 00:33:47,190
总部...
Dispatch--

417
00:34:00,520 --> 00:34:03,180
弗兰克  别再玩游戏了
Frank, we cannot be playing this game.

418
00:34:03,180 --> 00:34:04,940
心脏在警察手里  警探
The police have the heart, Inspector.

419
00:34:04,940 --> 00:34:07,500
什么  这是什么时候的事
What? When did this happen?

420
00:34:07,540 --> 00:34:09,610
我刚给了警察  他们一定上报了
I just handed it over. They must have called it in.

421
00:34:09,610 --> 00:34:11,150
不可能
That's not possible.

422
00:34:11,150 --> 00:34:14,650
我的无线电装置和总部连接
My radio has an open channel with Central Dispatch.

423
00:34:14,650 --> 00:34:16,470
如果有电话我会知道
I would have heard such a call.

424
00:34:16,870 --> 00:34:19,610
警察没有上报给总部
These cops didn't call the central station.

425
00:34:24,600 --> 00:34:26,210
警探  我回头找你
Inspector, I'll get back to you. 

426
00:34:26,430 --> 00:34:28,230
弗兰克  你在干什么
Frank, what are you doing?!

427
00:34:59,460 --> 00:35:02,330
警探  恕我直言  我现在不方便说话
Inspector, with all due respect, I really can't talk now.

428
00:35:02,330 --> 00:35:04,250
我刚和总部联系了
I've just confirmed with dispatch.

429
00:35:04,250 --> 00:35:06,110
没有警员打过电话
No officers called in.

430
00:35:06,700 --> 00:35:09,250
但是有一支分队没有回复
But there is one unit not responding.

431
00:35:09,450 --> 00:35:12,420
他们被收买了  我知道他们要去哪  
Dirty cops. I know where they're going.

432
00:35:12,420 --> 00:35:13,310
我要抢先赶到
I'm going to get there first.

433
00:35:13,310 --> 00:35:15,100
-怎么办到  -我可是飙车达人
- How? - It's what I do.

434
00:35:15,100 --> 00:35:16,560
不到一小时  
We have less than one hour 

435
00:35:16,560 --> 00:35:19,050
捐赠的心脏就会停跳
before the donated heart becomes useless.

436
00:35:19,050 --> 00:35:20,720
我知道时间紧迫  警探
I'm aware of the time, Inspector.

437
00:35:20,720 --> 00:35:22,420
所以我得挂了
That's why I need to hang up now.

438
00:35:38,630 --> 00:35:40,780
-喂  -我拿到包裹了  正在赶来
- Yes? - I've got the package. I'm on my way.

439
00:35:40,780 --> 00:35:43,990
好  你到了我给你报酬
All right. I'll have the money for you when you get here.

440
00:35:55,640 --> 00:35:57,960
你说的是开警车过来
You said that you were coming in a police car.

441
00:36:02,220 --> 00:36:03,600
搞什么
What the fuck?

442
00:36:07,260 --> 00:36:08,390
倒霉
Shit.

443
00:36:19,780 --> 00:36:22,030
心脏在哪  时间宝贵
Where's the heart? We don't have much time.

444
00:36:22,270 --> 00:36:23,230
这里
Here.

445
00:36:53,540 --> 00:36:55,110
你个没用的东西
Hey, you piece of shit.

446
00:36:56,680 --> 00:36:57,690
我的胸...
My chest.

447
00:36:57,690 --> 00:36:59,890
-好痛  -快上车
- Get in the car. - I'm fucking hurt.

448
00:37:02,950 --> 00:37:04,280
你要我开车吗
You want me to drive?

449
00:37:04,440 --> 00:37:06,310
不然你想被爆头吗
You want me to shoot you in the fucking head?

450
00:37:35,170 --> 00:37:35,960
喂
Hello?

451
00:37:35,960 --> 00:37:38,590
在医院的紧急入口等我
Go to the Emergency Room entrance at the side of the hospital.

452
00:37:38,590 --> 00:37:41,100
-你拿到心脏了吗  -快去
- Do you have the heart? - Just go now.

453
00:37:45,750 --> 00:37:46,340
{\an8}圣塞巴斯蒂安医院

454
00:37:59,030 --> 00:38:02,570
王八蛋  把包放下
Hey. Asshole. Put down the heart.

455
00:38:32,990 --> 00:38:35,570
住手  放下枪
Stop! Drop your gun!

456
00:38:52,490 --> 00:38:54,430
去吧  把心脏拿去
Go. Take the heart.

457
00:38:56,250 --> 00:38:57,300
找个医生来
Get a doctor.

458
00:38:59,680 --> 00:39:01,770
求你了  我儿子
Please. My son.

459
00:39:10,980 --> 00:39:12,080
他要丧命了
He's fading.

460
00:39:13,550 --> 00:39:16,990
菲利普  拜托  我儿子
Filip. Please. My son.

461
00:39:17,420 --> 00:39:19,340
他要丧命了  快送他进去
He's fading. Get him inside now.

462
00:39:19,340 --> 00:39:20,810
不  他的脉搏跳动有力  
No, his pulse is still strong.

463
00:39:20,810 --> 00:39:22,240
如果心脏被击中  脉搏才会衰弱
If the heart was hit, his pulse would be fading.

464
00:39:22,240 --> 00:39:23,290
如果不给他动手术
If we do not get him to surgery, 

465
00:39:23,290 --> 00:39:24,680
半小时内他就会死
he will die within a half an hour.

466
00:39:24,680 --> 00:39:26,000
那他的心脏呢
What about his heart?

467
00:39:27,730 --> 00:39:28,720
我同意  心脏没被击中
I agree, the heart was not hit,

468
00:39:28,720 --> 00:39:31,630
但他失血过多  性命难保
but he's losing too much blood. He cannot survive.

469
00:39:32,090 --> 00:39:33,990
你和你儿子心脏匹配吗
Do you know if you're a match with your son?

470
00:39:35,850 --> 00:39:37,910
-送他上救护车  -他活不下来
- Put him in the ambulance. - He cannot survive.

471
00:39:37,910 --> 00:39:39,970
快送他上救护车
Put him in the ambulance! 

472
00:39:40,500 --> 00:39:41,760
快听他的
Do as he says.

473
00:39:42,610 --> 00:39:44,100
快  快
Venez. Venez! Vite!

474
00:39:44,100 --> 00:39:45,990
快  上救护车
Vite! A l'ambulance!

475
00:39:52,210 --> 00:39:53,690
你需要人手帮忙照看他
You will need help to keep him alive.

476
00:39:53,690 --> 00:39:55,430
车上有我和他  速度就已经够慢了
This crate's going to be slow enough with just me and him.

477
00:39:55,430 --> 00:39:57,440
如果再有人上车  就无法按时赶到
Any extra weight, we're not going to make it.

478
00:39:57,500 --> 00:39:59,650
他家有一队医生等着
He has surgeons at his home, waiting.

479
00:40:00,020 --> 00:40:02,250
-等心脏  -他只有这个机会
- The heart. - He has one chance.

480
00:40:02,250 --> 00:40:04,590
就带一名医护人员照顾他
Take one EMT for while you are driving.

481
00:40:05,250 --> 00:40:06,940
她  你
Her. You.

482
00:40:08,610 --> 00:40:10,540
你上车  不用别人了
You get in. No one else.

483
00:40:10,540 --> 00:40:12,310
快点  快点
Allez, allez, vite, vite!

484
00:40:12,960 --> 00:40:16,000
上车吧  快  快
A l'ambulance. Allez, allez! Vite!

485
00:40:52,860 --> 00:40:54,830
到哪了
Where... where are we?

486
00:40:55,900 --> 00:40:56,930
到家了
Home.

487
00:41:05,690 --> 00:41:07,060
我们把你送进去
We're going to get you inside.

488
00:41:08,730 --> 00:41:09,750
谢谢你
Thank you.

489
00:41:14,960 --> 00:41:15,970
他死了
He's dying.

490
00:41:17,510 --> 00:41:20,350
-他的心脏还能用  把他送进去  -好
- His heart's still good. Get him inside. - Ok.

491
00:41:37,710 --> 00:41:39,040
他看起来情况不错
He looks good there.

492
00:41:44,450 --> 00:41:45,400
准备好了吗
Ready?

493
00:41:59,900 --> 00:42:01,570
移植手术完成
We finished the transplant.

494
00:42:01,630 --> 00:42:04,630
到目前为止  一切都好
So far... everything looks good.

495
00:42:04,760 --> 00:42:06,580
心脏还能用吗
The heart, it was all right?

496
00:42:06,640 --> 00:42:09,270
虽然耽搁了  但没多大影响
Despite the delay, it showed no signs of damage.

497
00:42:09,360 --> 00:42:11,690
一安上就开始跳动了
It started beating almost immediately.

498
00:42:11,690 --> 00:42:14,600
-太神奇了  -谢天谢地
Quite remarkable, actually. - Thank God.

499
00:42:19,560 --> 00:42:21,140
谢谢你  警探
Thank you, Inspector.

500
00:42:21,550 --> 00:42:23,400
您是我儿子的救命恩人
Our son owes you his life.

501
00:42:31,880 --> 00:42:34,650
天啊  卡拉  你疯了吗
Jesus Christ, Carla. This is some kinky shit.

502
00:42:34,650 --> 00:42:37,110
我在想要不要杀了你
I'm trying to decide whether or not to kill you.

503
00:42:37,240 --> 00:42:38,560
什么  为什么
What? Why?

504
00:42:38,560 --> 00:42:41,880
你接的每份活都搞得一团糟
And lately every job you sent our way has turned to shit!

505
00:42:42,700 --> 00:42:45,940
那不是我的错  我是说...
Hey, that is not my fault, OK? I mean...

506
00:42:46,570 --> 00:42:48,090
我不在意是不是耍了你
I don't care about screwing you!

507
00:42:49,030 --> 00:42:51,390
只要报酬丰厚  你什么都肯干
You'd do anything for a big payday.

508
00:42:51,520 --> 00:42:54,800
你也知道这行竞争激烈
Well, you know, it is a competitive business.

509
00:42:54,800 --> 00:42:57,310
对  但我决定与谁合作
Yes, but I can decide who to do business with.

510
00:42:57,310 --> 00:42:59,640
合作结束  阿吉  你走吧
We're done, Aggy. You can show yourself out.

511
00:42:59,640 --> 00:43:00,880
你被炒了
You're fired.

512
00:43:09,000 --> 00:43:11,830
{\an8}德希米耶医院

513
00:43:18,600 --> 00:43:19,660
孩子怎么样
How's the boy?

514
00:43:20,370 --> 00:43:21,550
他会没事的
He will be fine.

515
00:43:22,060 --> 00:43:24,610
医生相信他会完全康复
The doctors are confident of a full recovery.

516
00:43:24,990 --> 00:43:26,100
真是个好消息
That's good to hear.

517
00:43:26,400 --> 00:43:27,870
弗兰克
Frank... 

518
00:43:28,450 --> 00:43:32,150
你得说说楼下发生的事
we have to talk about what happened downstairs-- 

519
00:43:32,150 --> 00:43:33,250
我开枪打死的人
the man I shot.

520
00:43:33,250 --> 00:43:35,190
他叫德拉戈·苏也克
His name is Drago Sujic.

521
00:43:35,920 --> 00:43:38,580
难怪我觉得眼熟
Ah, I thought I recognized him.

522
00:43:39,140 --> 00:43:40,680
他是幕后黑手吗
He was responsible for all this?

523
00:43:40,680 --> 00:43:42,200
他想救他儿子
He was trying to save his son.

524
00:43:43,340 --> 00:43:44,580
最后救成了
And in the end, that's exactly what happened.

525
00:43:44,580 --> 00:43:47,050
我把他送回家  把他的心给了他儿子
I took him home, and they gave his son his heart.

526
00:43:47,070 --> 00:43:50,420
他最终还是做了件好事
Then some good came of it after all.

527
00:43:51,250 --> 00:43:53,530
不过  这还是偷
Still, such a theft... 

528
00:43:54,270 --> 00:43:58,300
真想知道某人是怎么卷入这场犯罪的
It's troubling how someone could be involved in such a terrible crime.

529
00:43:58,300 --> 00:44:01,490
可能他不知道一切
It's possible some of the people involved didn't know all of the details.

530
00:44:01,490 --> 00:44:04,540
我觉得他以后应该多加小心
I think these people should be more careful in the future.

531
00:44:14,480 --> 00:44:16,180
我们不和凯根合作了
No more jobs from Kagan.

532
00:44:16,540 --> 00:44:18,700
别担心  你不会再听到他的名字  
Don't worry, you'll never hear his name again, 

533
00:44:18,700 --> 00:44:20,250
更不会看到他
let alone see him.

534
00:44:23,390 --> 00:44:25,200
顺便说一句  今天干的很出色
Nice job today, by the way.

535
00:44:25,560 --> 00:44:27,180
解决方案很巧妙
An elegant solution.

536
00:44:27,990 --> 00:44:29,570
这就是我们的特点  
That's what we're all about.

537
00:44:29,830 --> 00:44:30,890
晚安  卡拉
Night, Carla.

538
00:44:31,060 --> 00:44:32,440
晚安  弗兰克
Good night, Frank.

539
00:44:45,200 --> 00:44:48,250
-德拉戈死了  -你该开心啊
- Drago didn't make it. - You should be pleased.

540
00:44:48,250 --> 00:44:51,410
如果我能活捉那些混蛋  我会更开心
if I could get some of these bastards alive.

541
00:44:51,490 --> 00:44:53,620
弗兰克·马丁呢
What about Frank Martin?

542
00:44:53,620 --> 00:44:56,440
他是联系人  我会盯紧他
He's the connection. I'll stay with him.

543
00:44:56,440 --> 00:44:58,480
别在司机身上浪费精力 
Don't waste your energy on this driver.

544
00:44:58,480 --> 00:45:00,470
他没有利用价值
He's not an asset.

545
00:45:00,640 --> 00:45:03,440
他不只是司机  而是快递员
He's not just a driver; he's a transporter.

546
00:45:30,190 --> 00:45:32,670
-要玩么  -免了
- You want? - No.

547
00:45:36,270 --> 00:45:37,740
你知道什么很难吗
You know what's difficult?

548
00:45:38,230 --> 00:45:39,680
学匈牙利语
Learning Hungarian. 

549
00:45:40,250 --> 00:45:42,850
不  比学匈牙利语还难
No, no, no. Harder than learning Hungarian.

550
00:45:46,270 --> 00:45:47,620
你要我继续猜吗
Do you want to keep me guessing?

551
00:45:47,770 --> 00:45:50,370
从车身上清除干掉的泥巴
Removing dry cement from an automobile.

552
00:45:50,680 --> 00:45:55,250
过程漫长且累人
You see, Frank, this is a very long, very tiring process.

553
00:45:55,820 --> 00:45:58,470
-想知道详情吗  -不想
You want to know what's involved? - Not really.

554
00:45:58,540 --> 00:46:02,190
取一份盐酸  四份清水
You take one part of muriatic acid and four parts of water,

555
00:46:02,420 --> 00:46:07,940
然后用牙刷蘸取  刷掉干掉的泥巴
and then you use a toothbrush to scrub it away at the hardened concrete.

556
00:46:19,600 --> 00:46:21,450
来摸摸
Here, feel that.

557
00:46:23,110 --> 00:46:25,580
-迪尔特  我才不想摸你的背  -快摸
- I don't want to feel your back, Dieter. - Just feel.

558
00:46:27,240 --> 00:46:29,850
摸到了吗
Oh! Yeah. Do you feel that?

559
00:46:30,420 --> 00:46:32,840
我不是医生  迪尔特
I'm n-- I'm not a doctor, Dieter. 

560
00:46:32,840 --> 00:46:34,880
你要去看医生就去看吧
If you need to see a doctor, you should see one.

561
00:46:43,810 --> 00:46:45,520
我要按摩
What I need is a massage.

562
00:46:45,940 --> 00:46:46,980
你不是按过了吗
I thought you got a massage. 

563
00:46:46,980 --> 00:46:48,730
和我期望的不一样
It was not what I was expecting.

564
00:46:48,730 --> 00:46:50,260
你期望的...
What were you... 

565
00:46:51,190 --> 00:46:52,390
我最好还是不要知道  对吧
I don't want to know, do I?

566
00:46:55,150 --> 00:46:56,490
结局不妙
It didn't end well.

567
00:46:57,010 --> 00:46:58,430
知道这点就行了
That's all you need to know.

