Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
'It's a comic?'
No, it's a graphic novel.
It's called Utopia Experiments.
You had this. Where is it?
It's just one of those conspiracy
theories.
- What about Utopia, then?
- Tell him, Becky.
Utopia Part Two, there must be
something in it that they want.
I also live with my mum.
Jesus Christ! You're going
to make me cry now, Ian.
I'm mission?
You should persuade him to take it.
What about the vaccine? Russian flu.
I think we could reconsider.
He signed.
He's fucking resigning, Michael.
My mate's going to ask you
a question.
Where is Jessica Hyde?
My name is Jessica Hyde.
Come with me now or you'll all die.
Who are you and what's going on?
Ian, don't point that gun at me.
How... how do you know my name?
Jessica Hyde?
Wilson? They did this.
We all have to go now.
We're not going anywhere until
you tell us who you are,
how you know my name
and what the fuck is going on.
Ian, you won't be able to shoot me.
Yeah? Don't imagine I won't, "Jess".
No, really, you won't
be able to shoot me.
You've got the safety catch on.
They don't generally have
safety catches, except on telly.
Every second we stay here is a
second they are getting closer
and they'll kill us all.
Please, come with me.
What about my dad? He's going home.
I've arranged for someone to pick
up your dad from where he works.
You don't know where he works.
Davingdon's on Vesta Road.
They're picking him up now.
I promise.
I'm not sure about this.
You two ready?
Yeah, we're ready.
There's CCTV at both ends of your
street. We'll go through the back.
Stay there.
What if someone's in?
Social uprest
if prices continue to rise.
The Shadow Home Secretary has
suggested the Government's apparent
lack of planning
could lead to outbreak of...
Is this your car?
You're so cute.
Are you going to tell us what's
going on? Who's after us?
In the 1970s, the Soviets set up
a germ warfare programme called
Biopreparat. It was huge.
They were weaponising anthrax,
Ebola, smallpox, on a massive scale.
The West panicked and created an
organisation to combat the threat.
It was known as The Network.
It was based in no country,
reported to no-one
and was utterly deniable.
It did things democratic
governments couldn't.
They were insane,
totally out of control.
What's that got to do with us?
Basically, that's who's after you.
You're fucking joking, right?
Right.
Do you know where that is yet?
No.
I'll come later, anyway.
Gimmme the gun.
We need clothes and money.
Your accounts are useless now.
You're going to rob them?
Let me make this very clear. Your
lives as you knew them are over.
What the next 48 hours are about
is abandoning everything you knew
or thought you could rely on
and adjusting to the new reality.
If you can adjust you will live.
If you can't you will die.
Now we need to change
the way you look.
We need to get very far away
and we need drugs for Wilson.
Give me the gun.
Ian, hang on,
can we talk about this?
I mean, it's an armed robbery.
It's adjust or die, Ian.
I don't know what to think of her.
You could've fooled me.
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
What, you just going
to watch, are you?
Here. Diamorphine.
What, heroin?
It's a painkiller. Do for now.
You look good.
Should wear that colour more often.
You look shit. But in a good way.
We need to get out of the city.
We'll transfer to a van to
keep Wilson out of sight,
then burn this out.
Do you have the manuscript, Ian?
Utopia Part Two.
You need to tell me if you have it.
We don't.
Bejan never turned up.
I haven't got Wilson's father.
I need to do things
to keep us alive.
Some of those things you
wouldn't normally approve of.
This is insane.
Yesterday I was arrested for a
sex crime, today I'm on the run
from ex-government nutters
who want to pull out my eyes.
I'm a fucking IT consultant.
Geoff?
Hmmm?
Have you seen this?
Oh yes.
Those bastards have got real
a bee in their bonnet about
the bloody vaccine.
But they've named me.
Well, you did buy it, Michael.
In any case, there's nothing we can
do about it. We're tied into the
contract.
Well... we're not, actually.
I've found a cancellation clause.
It can be enacted
if the department's total spend with
the supplier is over 240 million.
It's to ensure diversity of supply.
Yeah, but this is only 83 million,
Michael, I mean...
No, but it's total spend. We get
two other vaccines from Corvadt.
Plus a wide range of antibiotics,
cytotoxics, hypoglycaemics...
I mean, this puts us
well over 240 mil.
Have the contracts sent to me
immediately. No-one to see them.
Look, whatever Corvadt
are paying you,
we are not going to
get away with it.
We can stop all this.
We can stop it all now.
It's horrendous trying
to conceive, isn't it?
The medical nature of it all,
the IVF, all that science.
A man needs warmth.
So I understand you fucking
a prostitute, I do.
What I don't understand
is you getting her pregnant.
Do you think
your wife will understand?
Get the contract
straight over to me now.
It's for the best.
Ian and I are going up ahead to...
Great. Have fun.
Where are we going?
I hack airline companies,
look for people going on holiday,
stay at their houses.
They never know.
This is connected to
a trip wire in the drive.
Have everything by the back door,
always be ready to leave
within 60 seconds.
What if you're in the bath?
No baths, no showers.
It's time to stop worrying
about looking pretty, Becky.
Are you trying to wind me up?
There'd be no value
to that that I can see.
You got a thing for
tough women, is it?
Don't worry, Ian. I get it.
Imagine her big,
strong arms around you.What?
You let us walk into this.
I mean, how much did you know?
Because we had no idea.
Look at Wilson's face.
And that is not my fault!
Tell that to his dad.
Because she doesn't have him,
by the way.
Tell us the truth. All of it,
not bits, not pieces, all.
Or I leave.
Would you at least like
to sit down first, Becky?
No, Jessica. I fucking wouldn't.
The Network was created by two men.
A geneticist called Philip Carvel,
and someone called Mr Rabbit...
Mr Rabbit?
It's a codename, no-one knows
the real identity.
When the cold war began to wind down,
the various governments involved
decided to back away.
Only thing was, Mr Rabbit and
Carvel had no intention of stopping.
At some point, Carvel wanted out.
So they tortured him
to keep him working
and held his daughter hostage.
Eventually, his mind snapped
and he went mad.
He was going be got rid of
but somehow he was smuggled out,
given a new name and hidden
in a psychiatric hospital.
The hospital was Shenley.
And the new name was Mark Dane.
What, you...
you mean Carvel wrote Utopia?
A therapist got him drawing.
What he drew was...
incredible.
So all the things
in Utopia are real?
What, like BSE, they created that?
It's hard to say
what's real and what's not.
But, yeah. BSE was theirs.
How do you know all this?
I'm Philip Carvel's daughter.
I was smuggled out
with him when I was four.
I've been on the run ever since.
Did you pricks give me heroin?
We had to, for the pain. Oh.
Hope it wasn't Afghan.
Taliban have been altering it
for years to make us infertile.
Everyone knows that.
We need to find Utopia.
We start with where it came from.
What? What about the others?
It's fine. I left a note.
"Back soon, don't have a bath."
Look, Wilson needs someone to...
That is not the reason!
Don't you see what she's doing?
She's trying to divide us!
- Becky, that makes no sense.
- Then why take you and not me?
Because you're not strong enough.
I can't risk taking you.
I know stuff.
I know more than he does.
What about Corvadt?
They're involved,
they gave people disease.
What about Corvadt?
They're involved, so what?
They're a bit player.
You're not ready, Becky.
- Look, you just need time to...
- Right, go on then.
Fuck off!
What's that?
It's nothing.
It's work.
Don't worry.
'I very scared.'
I know, I mean...
They find out I pregnant,
they angry.
You just have to get me some time.
Michael, I think I watched.
Watched? By who?
Don't know. I scared.
They come now.
Michael, you help, yes?
You good man, yes...?
Michael Dugdale?
My name's William Kaye,
I'm a journalist,
I want to talk
about the flu vaccine.
- No, no, I'm sorry...
- Listen to me! Your life is in danger.
This isn't about a fucking story!
If I just wanted a story,
I'd report the fact that you've got
a Russian prostitute pregnant.
There's my card.
Things are going to get mad.
You'll need me when they do.
Bejan got Utopia
from the comic shop.
They got it from
a dealer in Scotland...
who is now dead.
And he got it from this guy,
Jack Tate.
And who's Jack Tate?
The man who published Utopia.
Mrs Tate?
Yes.
We need to speak to your husband.
Right.
My... husband's dead.
Do you want to come in?
This was his study.
Can you tell us where he died?
The A22 under the Hailsham Bridge.
He walked out in front of a lorry.
I'm sorry. Do you miss him?
Of course I miss him.
Actually, I have something
you might be interested in.
Yes, it's a... thing, I can't
describe it, papers and drawings.
That sounds like exactly
the sort of thing we're looking for.
We have to get out of here, now.
What? Why?
You might want these papers...
What the fuck have you done?!
She's with them.
What? What are you talking about?
Police turn up asking to see your
dead husband and you don't ask why?
Ah, shit.
Glock 22.
She's CIA.
It means she knows
next to fucking nothing.
That's how they work.
They have people high up
who get their drones
to do their work for them.
You're going to answer my questions.
And if I think
you've told me even one lie...
I'll put this wire
in the water...
plug this in,
flip the switch.
Understand?
Why are you here?
We got a tip-off.
The man who lived here
has been wanted on terrorism
charges for over 25 years.
We were too late,
he'd killed already himself,
so... so we took his wife in.
Has the wife given
you any information?
I don't know.
What did she say when you got here?
On the day he died he was talking
crazy, he wasn't making sense,
he said he'd been
visited by a tramp...
"A tramp"?
"A tramp" or "THE tramp"?
I don't know, "the" maybe, or...?
Look, hang on...
I asked you a question.
Was it "a tramp",
or "the tramp"?
"The". It was "the",
definitely "the".
She said "the".
- A select committee?
- Yes.
With powers to look into all
aspects of the acquisition process.
This is not going away, Geoff.
They're announcing it tomorrow.
Do nothing. Keep quiet.
The morning will bring something new.
It always does.
Geoff, we can't do nothing!
Well, it's sort of an order,
actually.
Worry less.
Look, I know it's scary now.
But tomorrow you'll be a hero,
I promise.
You didn't call in.
We were worried.
You're not agency. Who are you?
No.
I'm not agency.
I'm a specialist.
What did you tell them?
What did I tell them?
They were going to fucking fry me,
what do you think I told them?
I told them everything I knew.
Was it her?
Yeah.
Yeah, it was her.
She was with
a young black male, 25, 28.
Was a young man there?
Messed-up face, missing an eye?
Er...
no.
No, just them.
Look, are you going to untie me?
Wow. That looks great.
It's like, um, pirate chic.
How's your sight?
Er... I can see shapes and colours.
Thanks for looking after me, Becky.
Where's my dad?
She lied.
She had to get us out, Wilson.
I mean, he's probably fine.
I need to find out.
We can't.
They'll be monitoring our families,
we'll put them in danger...
Look online, I'll show you how to
disguise the search.
I swear they won't know it
came from here.
Wilson, we can't.
I need to know.
Please.
His name's Milton.
Milton? Milton Wilson?
What is it
with your family and names?
Right, you're sure they can't trace
this?
Positive. He's a cricket nut,
he logs in every day.
You'll see whether or not
he's logged in.
Is he there?
Hang on, I'm not in yet.
Er... Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, he's there, he's fine.
Grant has the manuscript.
I heard them talking about it,
they mentioned him.
I weren't going to fucking tell her.
Who are you, then?
I'm Alice.
What are you doing?
You're not from this school.
Just fuck off before you get hurt!
I'm not scared of you!
What's that?
Comic.
Well? Are you going to show me or
are you going to be a twat all day?
Are you going to tell me your name,
then, twat?
Grant.
Pleased to meet you, Grant.
Alice.
Shit!
Don't go.
Same time tomorrow, twat.
Are you sure this'll work?
Fanaticomix?
Grant's addicted to it.
It's nerd heaven.
And you have to read the personals
or you miss the good stuff.
I don't, but other people do.
But what if they're monitoring it?
Say to meet at the Embassy.
Dane based the Embassy
on the Taunton building
on the Kame Hill Estate.
Only a real twat would know that.
And me.
Never deny your inner twat, Wilson.
It's part of your charm.
Oh.
20...
and then six plus something
equals 20...
Don't forget to brush.
I won't.
Good night, Mummy.
Sleep tight, darling.
Love you.
♪ Der
♪ Der der
♪ Der der. ♪
What are you doing?
Can I sleep on your floor?
I won't do nothing, I promise.
Have you got that comic?
This is so beautiful.
Yeah. And that's part two.
No-one's ever seen that,
just you and me.
You're quite surprising, you know.
You strike me more as a
Spider-Man type.
Oh, we should sleep.
If my mum sees a light,
she'll come in.
Twat.
Thanks for letting me read Utopia.
Just to look after, like.
Keep it under your bed.
I-I-I'll come back...
for that.
Did they come back last night?
Nope. Wankers.
What we going to do?
I know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to have a fucking bath.
'We're getting more information
'on our breaking news story -
'the outbreak of flu
in the Shetland Islands.
'We can confirm
two more people have now died
'bringing the death toll to 11.
'That's 11 now dead
on the Shetland Island of Fetlar
'from the suspected
outbreak of Russian flu.'
Shit!
18 dead, 33 infected.
There's only 86 on the island.
Geoff's ordered a quarantine.
No-one gets in or out.
Right.
If it's a new strain, it's got
infection rates already of 58%.
Michael, thank god
you got the vaccine.
You're a fucking hero.
You tell them my name?
Did you tell them my fucking name?
No, no, I didn't say anything.
I think they're on to me.
I think I'm being followed.
I saw two men.
Jesus Christ!
Have you seen the news?
It's happening. I told you.
What do I do?
I mean, people are dying!
We need a sample of the vaccine.
You can request one
direct from Corvadt.
It's within your remit as advisor.
There's a man in Sheffield.
A scientist called Donaldson.
Get it to him.
What about you?
Do exactly as I fucking say!
The Tramp used to be a scientist
with the Network. He got out.
Now he monitors their activities.
He has to keep under the radar
to stay alive.
I reckon that's his office.
A public phone?
Here we go.
Him? But...
He really is a tramp?
Yeah, he's called 'The Tramp', Ian.
Hello, Danny.
Oh, shit! Oh!
Fucking hell!
You nearly broke my nose. You
nearly broke my fucking nose!
Jessica, how lovely.
How did you know Utopia
had a part two?
He's on our side, isn't he?
There's no sides.
Just people who help you
and people who don't.
Now, now, Jess, you know
a gentleman never reveals his...
Don't make me ask you again, Danny.
Jack told me years ago.
I went to see him now
because I wanted part two.
I knew Jack from
the old days, you see.
Why?
What's in it?
He never told me,
and when your father died
it didn't matter any more
but now they have something.
Your father was working on a project
called Janus before he died.
They've replicated his research.
They have it.
They're going to test it.
And what does Janus do?
I swear I don't know.
The last thing
your father was working on
were viral delivery vectors
that attack the human genome.
And Tate? What did he say?
He said that this is the end.
He said we are all finished.
And he took his own life.
We need to work together, Jess,
you and I...
What I still don't get is
what you were going to do with it.
I mean, what use would it be to a
decrepit old sack of filth like you?
What do you think your last breath
will feel like, Danny?
There's a woman. MI5.
They already have MI5.
Not this one. She's like us.
Works in secret, trusts no-one.
She can help.
Now, Jess, if you get me
the manuscript I can get it to her.
What's her name?
Please don't make me
tell you that, Jessica.
Milner. Her name's Milner.
She's a good woman, Jessica.
Ian, we need a vehicle.
You've seen me enough times.
It's time for you to do it.
Why didn't he give it to you?
Bit odd?
I'm on your side, Jessica,
you know that.
I'm one of the...
If we found him, they would.
He gave up Milner's name like that.
You saw what they did to Wilson.
So you just killed him?
- I pulled up the ladder.
- What?
You fucking killed him!
You took his life!
You just kill people if they're
not convenient, is that it?
Why are you being so odd?
What the fuck are you doing?
They... They just came in.
So you tied them up?
Children? You tied up children?
We're making it
look like a burglary!
You did the right thing.
We meet here tomorrow, 10pm.
Keep Wilson out of sight.
Stay on country roads, avoid CCTV.
You did exactly the right thing.
So, I-I-I want
a sample of the vaccine.
I-I-I'm sure you understand,
with the events of last night.
So, this is an R680 request...
Excellent, yes. You want a sample.
Yes, it's all filled. It's all
in order. The paperwork is...
What do you want it for?
You are contractually obliged
to supply a sample within 48 hours.
Yes, of course. Something wrong?
No, no, nothing's wrong.
I just need... I want a sample.
I can do that.
'Freelance journalist,
William Kaye has been murdered
'in a car park in Wapping
in East London,
'in what is being described by police
as a gangland-style execution.
'Mr Kaye was shot three times
in the chest and once in the head.
'Police have a suspect in custody,
'a Russian National
named as Anya Lutchenko.'
Anya?!
'Police have described her
as a sex worker. The detective...'
How's your wife, Dugdale?
Still trying to conceive, are you?
Still trying for a little baby?
Forget the vaccine, Mr Dugdale.
You're not a spy.
Becky, they'll be in
the Taunton Building.
It's a huge water tower
and, Becky, be careful.
Grant's a city trader.
He's bound to be a cock.
Are you Becky?
Grant?
I thought you were a city trader?
Fuck me.
Don't worry. It's just Wilson.
He's been hurt.
You better get in the back with him.
Wilson Wilson?
You look a mess, man.
Bloody hell, you sound about ten.
Close. He's 11.
What? Really?
You said you owned a Porsche and that
your girlfriend was a supermodel.
Yeah, I've got ambitions.
Stay here and be nice, both of you.
She got a boyfriend?
I'm just going to get some water
for us from the shop, OK?
It's me. The manuscript exists.
The boy.
The boy knows where it is.
Where is Jessica Hyde?
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.