Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
'It's a comic?'
这是漫画?
No, it's a graphic novel.
不，是图像小说
It's called Utopia Experiments.
《乌托邦实验》
You had this. Where is it?
你拿走了 到底在哪?
It's just one of those conspiracy
theories.
不过是个阴谋论罢了
- What about Utopia, then?
- Tell him, Becky.
- 那么"乌托邦"是什么?
- Becky 告诉他
Utopia Part Two, there must be
something in it that they want.
《乌托邦》第二部 一定有什么他们想要的东西
I also live with my mum.
我还和我妈住在一起
Jesus Christ! You're going
to make me cry now, Ian.
天哪 我都快感动地哭了 Ian
I'm mission?
我的任务?
You should persuade him to take it.
你必须税负他签字
What about the vaccine? Russian flu.
I think we could reconsider.
俄罗斯流感的疫苗怎么办?我觉得我们应该再考虑一下
He signed.
他辞职了
He's fucking resigning, Michael.
他TMD辞职了 Michael
My mate's going to ask you
a question.
我的同伴要问你一个问题
Where is Jessica Hyde?
Jessica Hyde 在哪?
My name is Jessica Hyde.
我是Jessica Hyde
Come with me now or you'll all die.
跟我走 不然你们都死定了
Who are you and what's going on?
你是谁?到底怎么回事?
Ian, don't point that gun at me.
Ian 别拿枪指着我
How... how do you know my name?
我...你怎么知道我的名字?
Jessica Hyde?
Wilson? They did this.
Wilson? 他们干的
We all have to go now.
我们现在都得走
We're not going anywhere until
you tell us who you are,
我们才不走 除非告诉我们你是谁
how you know my name
and what the fuck is going on.
你怎么知道我的名字 还有到底怎么回事
Ian, you won't be able to shoot me.
Ian 你打不死我的
Yeah? Don't imagine I won't, "Jess".
是吗? 别以为我不敢 "Jess"
No, really, you won't
be able to shoot me.
真的 你打不死我
You've got the safety catch on.
保险开着呢
They don't generally have
safety catches, except on telly.
电视上的才有保险
Every second we stay here is a
second they are getting closer
这儿越待越危险
and they'll kill us all.
Please, come with me.
他们找来会杀了我们 快 跟我走吧
What about my dad? He's going home.
我老爸怎么办? 他要下班回家了
I've arranged for someone to pick
up your dad from where he works.
我已经派人接他去了
You don't know where he works.
你不知道他在哪工作
Davingdon's on Vesta Road.
Vesta路 Davindon公司
They're picking him up now.
I promise.
他们已经去接了 我保证
I'm not sure about this.
我不晓得怎么办
You two ready?
你们准备好了吗?
Yeah, we're ready.
准备好了
There's CCTV at both ends of your
street. We'll go through the back.
路口有摄像头 我们从后门走
Stay there.
等等
What if someone's in?
屋里有人怎么办?
Social uprest
if prices continue to rise.
物价继续上涨将会引起严重社会不安
The Shadow Home Secretary has
suggested the Government's apparent
影子内政大臣指责政府缺乏计划
lack of planning
could lead to outbreak of...
未来情形会进一步恶化...
Is this your car?
这是你的车?
You're so cute.
你好天真
Are you going to tell us what's
going on? Who's after us?
告诉我们怎么回事 谁在追杀我们?
In the 1970s, the Soviets set up
a germ warfare programme called
上世纪七十年代 前苏联启动了一个细菌武器项目
Biopreparat. It was huge.
叫做"Biopreparat" 规模很大
They were weaponising anthrax,
Ebola, smallpox, on a massive scale.
他们将炭疽菌,伊波拉病毒和天花病毒制成大杀器
The West panicked and created an
organisation to combat the threat.
西方大为震惊 于是成立了一个机构来对抗威胁
It was known as The Network.
叫做"Network"
It was based in no country,
reported to no-one
它没有总部 不对任何人负责
and was utterly deniable.
没人知道它的存在
It did things democratic
governments couldn't.
却做着民主政府不敢做的事
They were insane,
totally out of control.
他们很疯狂 没人管得住
What's that got to do with us?
那跟我们有什么关系?
Basically, that's who's after you.
有 正是追杀你们的人
You're fucking joking, right?
你特么开玩笑吧?
Right.
嗯
Do you know where that is yet?
知道在哪了没?
No.
不
I'll come later, anyway.
反正我要过来
Gimmme the gun.
枪给我
We need clothes and money.
Your accounts are useless now.
我们需要衣服和钱 你们的账户都冻结了
You're going to rob them?
你要去打劫?
Let me make this very clear. Your
lives as you knew them are over.
听好了 你们原来的生活结束了
What the next 48 hours are about
is abandoning everything you knew
接下来的两天也要放弃过去的一切
or thought you could rely on
and adjusting to the new reality.
抛开所有 适应新生活
If you can adjust you will live.
If you can't you will die.
适者生存 败者毁灭
Now we need to change
the way you look.
现在我们要伪装起来
We need to get very far away
and we need drugs for Wilson.
跑得远远的 还要个Wilson找药
Give me the gun.
枪给我
Ian, hang on,
can we talk about this?
Ian 等等 你真要给她?
I mean, it's an armed robbery.
这可是抢劫啊
It's adjust or die, Ian.
生存 还是毁灭? Ian
I don't know what to think of her.
我不知道该不该相信她
You could've fooled me.
你也可能是骗子
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
我靠 逗我玩呢吧?
What, you just going
to watch, are you?
干嘛 看我脱干净?
Here. Diamorphine.
拿着 二乙酰吗啡
What, heroin?
什么 海洛因?
It's a painkiller. Do for now.
可以止痛 赶快
You look good.
你看着不错
Should wear that colour more often.
应该多穿这个颜色的
You look shit. But in a good way.
你的好难看 不过正好
We need to get out of the city.
我们要出城
We'll transfer to a van to
keep Wilson out of sight,
搞辆货车 把Wilson藏起来
then burn this out.
然后烧了这些东西
Do you have the manuscript, Ian?
手稿在不在你手上 Ian?
Utopia Part Two.
《乌托邦》第二部分
You need to tell me if you have it.
有的话 告诉我
We don't.
没有
Bejan never turned up.
Bejan就没现身
I haven't got Wilson's father.
我也没接到Wilson的父亲
I need to do things
to keep us alive.
我必须保证我们的安全
Some of those things you
wouldn't normally approve of.
就算有些事你们接受不了
This is insane.
可这也太扯了
Yesterday I was arrested for a
sex crime, today I'm on the run
昨天因为性侵入狱
from ex-government nutters
who want to pull out my eyes.
今天又在逃避前政府疯子的追杀
I'm a fucking IT consultant.
我特么只是个IT顾问啊
Geoff?
Hmmm?
- Geoff?      - 嗯?
Have you seen this?
你见过这个么?
Oh yes.
见过
Those bastards have got real a bee
in their bonnet about the bloody vaccine.
这些二货快被疫苗的事逼疯了
But they've named me.
但他们也提到我了
Well, you did buy it, Michael.
确实是你买的 Michael
In any case, there's nothing we can
do about it. We're tied into the
contract.
怎么说都没用了 合同可不能推翻
Well... we're not, actually.
事实上 可以推翻
I've found a cancellation clause.
其中有一条
It can be enacted
if the department's total spend with
假如政府的全部花销
the supplier is over 240 million.
超过2.4亿英镑的话 就可解除合同
It's to ensure diversity of supply.
这是为了确保供货渠道多元化
Yeah, but this is only 83 million,
Michael, I mean...
是吗 可这才8千3百万 Michael 我说...
No, but it's total spend. We get
two other vaccines from Corvadt.
不 全部花销 还有两种疫苗也是Corvadt提供的
Plus a wide range of antibiotics,
cytotoxics, hypoglycaemics...
再加上大量的抗生素,细胞干扰素和降血糖药
I mean, this puts us
well over 240 mil.
加起来远远超过2.4亿
Have the contracts sent to me
immediately. No-one to see them.
立即把合同发给我 不许其他人看到
Look, whatever Corvadt
are paying you,
听着 不管Corvadt公司给了你多少钱
we are not going to
get away with it.
我们还来得及反悔
We can stop all this.
一切还可以挽回
We can stop it all now.
现在就可以挽回
It's horrendous trying
to conceive, isn't it?
怀孕是不是很难?
The medical nature of it all,
the IVF, all that science.
求医啊 试管受精啊 各种方法
A man needs warmth.
男人需要释放
So I understand you fucking
a prostitute, I do.
所以我理解你为什么招妓
What I don't understand
is you getting her pregnant.
但我不能理解 你怎么让妓女怀孕的
Do you think
your wife will understand?
你觉得 你老婆能理解吗?
Get the contract
straight over to me now.
立即把合同拿给我
It's for the best.
都是为了你好
Ian and I are going up ahead to...
我和Ian要去...
Great. Have fun.
好极了 祝玩好
Where are we going?
我们去哪?
I hack airline companies,
look for people going on holiday,
我侵入航空公司系统 找一些度假的人
stay at their houses.
They never know.
住他们的房子 他们绝不会知道
This is connected to
a trip wire in the drive.
这条绳子通到外面路上
Have everything by the back door,
always be ready to leave
把东西都放在后门
within 60 seconds.
随时准备在一分钟内闪人
What if you're in the bath?
如果在洗澡怎么办?
No baths, no showers.
不能洗澡 冲凉都不行
It's time to stop worrying
about looking pretty, Becky.
没时间打扮了 Becky
Are you trying to wind me up?
你是想气死我吗?
There'd be no value
to that that I can see.
气死你对我有什么好处
You got a thing for
tough women, is it?
你是不是和那个剽悍小妞有一腿?
Don't worry, Ian. I get it.
没问题 Ian 我懂的
Imagine her big,
strong arms around you.What?
- 想躺在她健壮的臂弯里吧     - 什么?
You let us walk into this.
是你把我们搞成这样的好吧
I mean, how much did you know?
你说你知道多少?
Because we had no idea.
Look at Wilson's face.
And that is not my fault!
Tell that to his dad.
Because she doesn't have him,
by the way.
Tell us the truth. All of it,
not bits, not pieces, all.
Or I leave.
Would you at least like
to sit down first, Becky?
No, Jessica. I fucking wouldn't.
The Network was created by two men.
A geneticist called Philip Carvel,
and someone called Mr Rabbit...
Mr Rabbit?
It's a codename, no-one knows
the real identity.
When the cold war began to wind down,
the various governments involved
decided to back away.
Only thing was, Mr Rabbit and
Carvel had no intention of stopping.
At some point, Carvel wanted out.
So they tortured him
to keep him working
and held his daughter hostage.
Eventually, his mind snapped
and he went mad.
He was going be got rid of
but somehow he was smuggled out,
given a new name and hidden
in a psychiatric hospital.
The hospital was Shenley.
And the new name was Mark Dane.
What, you...
you mean Carvel wrote Utopia?
A therapist got him drawing.
What he drew was...
incredible.
So all the things
in Utopia are real?
What, like BSE, they created that?
It's hard to say
what's real and what's not.
But, yeah. BSE was theirs.
How do you know all this?
I'm Philip Carvel's daughter.
I was smuggled out
with him when I was four.
I've been on the run ever since.
Did you pricks give me heroin?
We had to, for the pain. Oh.
Hope it wasn't Afghan.
Taliban have been altering it
for years to make us infertile.
Everyone knows that.
We need to find Utopia.
We start with where it came from.
What? What about the others?
It's fine. I left a note.
"Back soon, don't have a bath."
Look, Wilson needs someone to...
That is not the reason!
Don't you see what she's doing?
She's trying to divide us!
- Becky, that makes no sense.
- Then why take you and not me?
Because you're not strong enough.
I can't risk taking you.
I know stuff.
I know more than he does.
What about Corvadt?
They're involved,
they gave people disease.
What about Corvadt?
They're involved, so what?
They're a bit player.
You're not ready, Becky.
- Look, you just need time to...
- Right, go on then.
Fuck off!
What's that?
It's nothing.
It's work.
Don't worry.
'I very scared.'
I know, I mean...
They find out I pregnant,
they angry.
You just have to get me some time.
Michael, I think I watched.
Watched? By who?
Don't know. I scared.
They come now.
Michael, you help, yes?
You good man, yes...?
Michael Dugdale?
My name's William Kaye,
I'm a journalist,
I want to talk
about the flu vaccine.
- No, no, I'm sorry...
- Listen to me! Your life is in danger.
This isn't about a fucking story!
If I just wanted a story,
I'd report the fact that you've got
a Russian prostitute pregnant.
There's my card.
Things are going to get mad.
You'll need me when they do.
Bejan got Utopia
from the comic shop.
They got it from
a dealer in Scotland...
who is now dead.
And he got it from this guy,
Jack Tate.
And who's Jack Tate?
The man who published Utopia.
Mrs Tate?
Yes.
We need to speak to your husband.
Right.
My... husband's dead.
Do you want to come in?
This was his study.
Can you tell us where he died?
The A22 under the Hailsham Bridge.
He walked out in front of a lorry.
I'm sorry. Do you miss him?
Of course I miss him.
Actually, I have something
you might be interested in.
Yes, it's a... thing, I can't
describe it, papers and drawings.
That sounds like exactly
the sort of thing we're looking for.
We have to get out of here, now.
What? Why?
You might want these papers...
What the fuck have you done?!
She's with them.
What? What are you talking about?
Police turn up asking to see your
dead husband and you don't ask why?
Ah, shit.
Glock 22.
She's CIA.
It means she knows
next to fucking nothing.
That's how they work.
They have people high up
who get their drones
to do their work for them.
You're going to answer my questions.
And if I think
you've told me even one lie...
I'll put this wire
in the water...
plug this in,
flip the switch.
Understand?
Why are you here?
We got a tip-off.
The man who lived here
has been wanted on terrorism
charges for over 25 years.
We were too late,
he'd killed already himself,
so... so we took his wife in.
Has the wife given
you any information?
I don't know.
What did she say when you got here?
On the day he died he was talking
crazy, he wasn't making sense,
he said he'd been
visited by a tramp...
"A tramp"?
"A tramp" or "THE tramp"?
I don't know, "the" maybe, or...?
Look, hang on...
I asked you a question.
Was it "a tramp",
or "the tramp"?
"The". It was "the",
definitely "the".
She said "the".
- A select committee?
- Yes.
With powers to look into all
aspects of the acquisition process.
This is not going away, Geoff.
They're announcing it tomorrow.
Do nothing. Keep quiet.
The morning will bring something new.
It always does.
Geoff, we can't do nothing!
Well, it's sort of an order,
actually.
Worry less.
Look, I know it's scary now.
But tomorrow you'll be a hero,
I promise.
You didn't call in.
We were worried.
You're not agency. Who are you?
No.
I'm not agency.
I'm a specialist.
What did you tell them?
What did I tell them?
They were going to fucking fry me,
what do you think I told them?
I told them everything I knew.
Was it her?
Yeah.
Yeah, it was her.
She was with
a young black male, 25, 28.
Was a young man there?
Messed-up face, missing an eye?
Er...
no.
No, just them.
Look, are you going to untie me?
Wow. That looks great.
It's like, um, pirate chic.
How's your sight?
Er... I can see shapes and colours.
Thanks for looking after me, Becky.
Where's my dad?
She lied.
She had to get us out, Wilson.
I mean, he's probably fine.
I need to find out.
We can't.
They'll be monitoring our families,
we'll put them in danger...
Look online, I'll show you how to
disguise the search.
I swear they won't know it
came from here.
Wilson, we can't.
I need to know.
Please.
His name's Milton.
Milton? Milton Wilson?
What is it
with your family and names?
Right, you're sure they can't trace
this?
Positive. He's a cricket nut,
he logs in every day.
You'll see whether or not
he's logged in.
Is he there?
Hang on, I'm not in yet.
Er... Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, he's there, he's fine.
Grant has the manuscript.
I heard them talking about it,
they mentioned him.
I weren't going to fucking tell her.
Who are you, then?
I'm Alice.
What are you doing?
You're not from this school.
Just fuck off before you get hurt!
I'm not scared of you!
What's that?
Comic.
Well? Are you going to show me or
are you going to be a twat all day?
Are you going to tell me your name,
then, twat?
Grant.
Pleased to meet you, Grant.
Alice.
Shit!
Don't go.
Same time tomorrow, twat.
Are you sure this'll work?
Fanaticomix?
Grant's addicted to it.
It's nerd heaven.
And you have to read the personals
or you miss the good stuff.
I don't, but other people do.
But what if they're monitoring it?
Say to meet at the Embassy.
Dane based the Embassy
on the Taunton building
on the Kame Hill Estate.
Only a real twat would know that.
And me.
Never deny your inner twat, Wilson.
It's part of your charm.
Oh.
20...
and then six plus something
equals 20...
Don't forget to brush.
I won't.
Good night, Mummy.
Sleep tight, darling.
Love you.
♪ Der
♪ Der der
♪ Der der. ♪
What are you doing?
Can I sleep on your floor?
I won't do nothing, I promise.
Have you got that comic?
This is so beautiful.
Yeah. And that's part two.
No-one's ever seen that,
just you and me.
You're quite surprising, you know.
You strike me more as a
Spider-Man type.
Oh, we should sleep.
If my mum sees a light,
she'll come in.
Twat.
Thanks for letting me read Utopia.
Just to look after, like.
Keep it under your bed.
I-I-I'll come back...
for that.
Did they come back last night?
Nope. Wankers.
What we going to do?
I know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to have a fucking bath.
'We're getting more information
'on our breaking news story -
'the outbreak of flu
in the Shetland Islands.
'We can confirm
two more people have now died
'bringing the death toll to 11.
'That's 11 now dead
on the Shetland Island of Fetlar
'from the suspected
outbreak of Russian flu.'
Shit!
18 dead, 33 infected.
There's only 86 on the island.
Geoff's ordered a quarantine.
No-one gets in or out.
Right.
If it's a new strain, it's got
infection rates already of 58%.
Michael, thank god
you got the vaccine.
You're a fucking hero.
You tell them my name?
Did you tell them my fucking name?
No, no, I didn't say anything.
I think they're on to me.
I think I'm being followed.
I saw two men.
Jesus Christ!
Have you seen the news?
It's happening. I told you.
What do I do?
I mean, people are dying!
We need a sample of the vaccine.
You can request one
direct from Corvadt.
It's within your remit as advisor.
There's a man in Sheffield.
A scientist called Donaldson.
Get it to him.
What about you?
Do exactly as I fucking say!
The Tramp used to be a scientist
with the Network. He got out.
Now he monitors their activities.
He has to keep under the radar
to stay alive.
I reckon that's his office.
A public phone?
Here we go.
Him? But...
He really is a tramp?
Yeah, he's called 'The Tramp', Ian.
Hello, Danny.
Oh, shit! Oh!
Fucking hell!
You nearly broke my nose. You
nearly broke my fucking nose!
Jessica, how lovely.
How did you know Utopia
had a part two?
He's on our side, isn't he?
There's no sides.
Just people who help you
and people who don't.
Now, now, Jess, you know
a gentleman never reveals his...
Don't make me ask you again, Danny.
Jack told me years ago.
I went to see him now
because I wanted part two.
I knew Jack from
the old days, you see.
Why?
What's in it?
He never told me,
and when your father died
it didn't matter any more
but now they have something.
Your father was working on a project
called Janus before he died.
They've replicated his research.
They have it.
They're going to test it.
And what does Janus do?
I swear I don't know.
The last thing
your father was working on
were viral delivery vectors
that attack the human genome.
And Tate? What did he say?
He said that this is the end.
He said we are all finished.
And he took his own life.
We need to work together, Jess,
you and I...
What I still don't get is
what you were going to do with it.
I mean, what use would it be to a
decrepit old sack of filth like you?
What do you think your last breath
will feel like, Danny?
There's a woman. MI5.
They already have MI5.
Not this one. She's like us.
Works in secret, trusts no-one.
She can help.
Now, Jess, if you get me
the manuscript I can get it to her.
What's her name?
Please don't make me
tell you that, Jessica.
Milner. Her name's Milner.
She's a good woman, Jessica.
Ian, we need a vehicle.
You've seen me enough times.
It's time for you to do it.
Why didn't he give it to you?
Bit odd?
I'm on your side, Jessica,
you know that.
I'm one of the...
If we found him, they would.
He gave up Milner's name like that.
You saw what they did to Wilson.
So you just killed him?
- I pulled up the ladder.
- What?
You fucking killed him!
You took his life!
You just kill people if they're
not convenient, is that it?
Why are you being so odd?
What the fuck are you doing?
They... They just came in.
So you tied them up?
Children? You tied up children?
We're making it
look like a burglary!
You did the right thing.
We meet here tomorrow, 10pm.
Keep Wilson out of sight.
Stay on country roads, avoid CCTV.
You did exactly the right thing.
So, I-I-I want
a sample of the vaccine.
I-I-I'm sure you understand,
with the events of last night.
So, this is an R680 request...
Excellent, yes. You want a sample.
Yes, it's all filled. It's all
in order. The paperwork is...
What do you want it for?
You are contractually obliged
to supply a sample within 48 hours.
Yes, of course. Something wrong?
No, no, nothing's wrong.
I just need... I want a sample.
I can do that.
'Freelance journalist,
William Kaye has been murdered
'in a car park in Wapping
in East London,
'in what is being described by police
as a gangland-style execution.
'Mr Kaye was shot three times
in the chest and once in the head.
'Police have a suspect in custody,
'a Russian National
named as Anya Lutchenko.'
Anya?!
'Police have described her
as a sex worker. The detective...'
How's your wife, Dugdale?
Still trying to conceive, are you?
Still trying for a little baby?
Forget the vaccine, Mr Dugdale.
You're not a spy.
Becky, they'll be in
the Taunton Building.
It's a huge water tower
and, Becky, be careful.
Grant's a city trader.
He's bound to be a cock.
Are you Becky?
Grant?
I thought you were a city trader?
Fuck me.
Don't worry. It's just Wilson.
He's been hurt.
You better get in the back with him.
Wilson Wilson?
You look a mess, man.
Bloody hell, you sound about ten.
Close. He's 11.
What? Really?
You said you owned a Porsche and that
your girlfriend was a supermodel.
Yeah, I've got ambitions.
Stay here and be nice, both of you.
She got a boyfriend?
I'm just going to get some water
for us from the shop, OK?
It's me. The manuscript exists.
The boy.
The boy knows where it is.
Where is Jessica Hyde?
Jessica Hyde在哪？
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.